[Music]
as the enemy of the past it threatens
the fastest weapon you wouldn't make it
past a second and that's the question
play it brash and reckless to choose a
car solution you saw was prudent in any
sepulcher poker doodle become the putrid
it's that well said I pursue in no
mountain too steep for dungeon to teeth
to send expendable marks up to the top
of the peak of beneath they see you be
they come like sharks to it while I swim
in that line even like Carl Barks
through it so send your National Parks
drew it I'll send him home in a natural
box with the close tie but most of the
parks included save your breath for a
cleric confessor that there's a lesson
than life is attending professor but if
you're seeking my official advice sign
on the dotted line English of the twice
[Applause]
[Music]
shadow council may our Labor's please
you please allow me the honor of
introducing your servants to my right
Dragonborn narcissist dinar Blitzen
[Applause]
all right you got it
let's see how this goes can you see
anything I are what are we doing we
playing game yeah
we're gonna do we're gonna do our
goddamnedest to the right of my right
repping the natural world walnut on
grass
[Applause]
[Music]
oh you're gonna be rolling for me a lot
yeah I know to the to my left not your
grandma's grandma except in those rare
cases where she is your grandma's
grandma
Rosie be stinger
[Applause]
[Laughter]
100% on friends distributing brothers
originals this is a grandma that knows
how to grandma
Rosie be stinger looking like I'm Millie
looking like a Millie to the left of my
left emerging let's know from a mist
shroud cthe wrist drow
[Applause]
[Laughter]
all right let me see if it's possible to
sit in a chair hi early my rat
yes you got chosen I don't listen I got
my own problems man I don't need your
shit oh sweet boy all right are we ready
to get down with the c-team holiday
special all right here we are the night
of a thousand hours
tell me again father Gordon tell me
about my parents are you certain child
have you not heard it enough
never she is resolute she pulls the
blanket up beneath her chin she will not
be moved very well then very well he
takes a seat on the rough stool near the
bed and begins to speak the drawn and
courtier is an inn known of as far away
as water deep there are those who say
the towns sprang up around the inn but
this story is usually told late in the
night after many rounds have been
ordered and another is on its way the
sign swings on links of new change
shining in the torchlight fresh paint
draws your eye to the sign of the drawn
and courtier below it a smaller sign
hangs it bares an eight situated over an
eye the weather is apocalyptic
and it's getting late so it's good to be
off the road you shake the rain off your
traveling cloaks and step inside to a
roar of welcome and clanked mugs
when last are you good you gotta repeat
all this yeah okay have we started I
can't hear a thing in there
so when last we saw our heroes they had
recently quite recently returned from
the adventure in the wandering crypt
basically omen drones white whale killed
it 100% success on the part of the sea
team but you returned with a new friend
a a woman who had more or less passed
into myth in the drawn family auspicious
drawn and it has been two weeks since
you have returned and she is slowly but
surely regaining her strength helping
her mother prophetess drawn around the
drowning courtier and the sea team is
basically in the off season roads are
muck it's 100% bullshit from Hell to
breakfast this is a this is a chance for
the team to rest and recuperate how
would you like to spend some of your
time at home in the warm confines of the
drawing corner drinkin mystery potions
just just bring the bring the trophy
downstairs and just like it's like it's
like when a place has that like mystery
cask yeah and you're just drawing
potions for random strangers and I can
imagine you've got all these colorful
potions and you drink the yellow one
you're like oh no that's no good
oh yeah even those no like a flight yeah
it's now offering potion flights let's
just let's just dive in yeah yeah we're
gonna let's play Dungeons and Dragons
[Music]
why not
so I'd like to say downstairs in those
seats by the fire with the ledger out
just making a note of all of the things
that we probably did in the last two
weeks I got us a lot of gold right yeah
and I have mine so much gold not to do
paperwork for us okay
rosie has been I think that walnut and
Rosie didn't end things great last time
and Rosie has been feeling really
anxious about it because walnuts been
weird like walnuts been openly weird so
Rosie knows she said some stuff she
should regret and she's been working on
some apology gifts
[Music]
she's been cross-stitching listening
she's been cross stitching so she's
she's got some cross stitch apologies
that she's been working on that she
wants to deliver to you is this a genre
yeah well it is now after that last
episode so she's she's stitched three
apology cross stitches denars says
you're not a baby
oh you are yeah but I can't like both
you near dinar cannon he is a horse he
can only see how the side yeah Rosie in
the last episode called dinar an idiot
baby so she you're not a baby
[Laughter]
nice I'll take it
walnut she called she doesn't remember
any of this but she called her a horny
elf with daddy issues
she'd and Rosie doesn't know why walnut
is mad but she has cross stitched a
whole thing like it's a paragraph it's
just like my dearest walnut it is with
deepest sorrow that I and it just keeps
going and going and going she's bored
she's like I'm making all the guesses
about what I could have said but it
obviously took a long time because it's
all cross stitch and then the one for
Chris whom she called an esoteric
lunatic it just says Happy Holidays this
is the perfect gift has everything so
auspicious drawn after a low these two
weeks as I said is has begun to regain
her strength she's filling out on the
unseasonable produced cornerstones there
is there is more or less an endless
stream of cornerstones now that people
are coming from cities around the
drawing Cordier to experience this
keulen Airy delight but there's also the
fact that there's there's an attenuation
that's occurring where prophetess has
not been able to feed her child for
decades and you get the sense that she
is making up for lost time and it's just
an endless parade of childhood favorites
it's an absolute it's an absolute
delight occasionally there are
remainders that can be taken advantage
of but auspicious is basically taken on
a sort of like lieutenant role in the
drone and courtier there's always a
broom at the ready there's a lot of
sweeping even when sweeping is not
necessarily required she's in that phase
where she is sweeping clean floors she's
gonna find new floors beneath
when when folks come in there's a big
smile and she greets them and then
people look over at profit and profit
nods gently that's quick yeah that's
great there's more okay oh oh there's
more advice well there's the end what
are Chris and Denard
excuse me cut through San Dena review it
just you look more like yourself now so
yeah cuz you dead Nate yeah you're more
Chris that you've ever been yeah what
are you guys up to
um I I'm enjoying how busy it is because
that lets me sort of crouch and dark
corners that are clean now this is a
novelty
just some quality time with Locati is
he's been through a lot too he's been
spending time I had the staff yeah it
felt like any time you anytime you're
not walking used to be becomes a
friendly noodle again he sort of zips
himself back up in his traditional size
but he anticipates any time he feels you
sort of like tightening and flexing to
get up
he's a cool my god and he he activates
his rod form Kevin yeah so there's that
knee and him both exactly so yeah
there's people here exactly so
auspicious is sweeping in the corner
over near you how do you interact with
this she clearly needs this corner oh I
see so has she been has she been
speaking he been oh she's more she's
more like yes she is she is definitely
warming up I just would I is she and
treating upon my corner maybe I am
visually I'm there and she's sweeping in
it and I approach at night you think
there's a couple sweeps and then like
she's raised the broom toward the corner
and then there's a couple more tent you
know sort of tenuous sweep around the
edge we both have our eye on
unlike the last hors d'oeuvre dark
corners huh that's a favorite of mine
too a lot of time spent 100% I get it
she she she grins at you and sort of
like brooms the hem of your cloak and
your boots so kind oh oh that's not
necessary
I guess I'm going to get it very dirty
again she smiles and then her her eyes
closed for a second and the smile melts
away and then she takes up the broom and
supports herself with it and sort of
almost leans into the leaves into the
edge of the wall there in the corner
for support and then when she looks down
at you there's no trace of the mirth and
she looks directly into your eyes and
says she's hurt she's hurt she's hurt
who you need to help her who is hurt she
collapses into the corner where you are
physically I catch her she is just like
a sack just like a sack of potatoes you
can just transfer her down into the
corner with no loss of momentum at all
okay yeah
profile is this where you have to do it
now on the right in the eye
please yeah hurry your daughter yeah
exactly
so profit profit this first smile melts
as well she looks over into the corner
and rushes into it it is at that moment
that the front door of the drowning
courtier swings wide
and because this is the drawn-in
courtier it's customary for mugs to be
raised the patrons cheer as an elven
woman enters people quickly return to
their drinks their meals in the town
gossip the thrives in places like this
but you can't take your eyes off the
newcomer still framed by the door she
seems to be scanning the room looking
for someone but her eyes never rest in
any one place she clutches the bundle at
her chest even tighter a couple of
shuffling steps later she collapses on
the nearest table yours the back of her
tunic is black with rain and blood mugs
clatter to the floorboards I have a very
unique idea about what constitutes a
Christmas adventure mugs clatter to the
floorboards their contents pooling and
running through the cracks she looks
into the bundle or appears to but
there's no light in her eyes inside this
nest of rags a baby peeks out without
understanding her tiny face is encircled
by blonde curls she is the spitting
image of the elf who carried her she's
on my table I've taken it back for a
moment and then I am I rushed to this I
put my hands on itself it's like it's
like mom powers activate
oh yeah instantly I'm like what
sweetheart what's going on what are you
alright she's gone she's dead she's dead
heard there's this cloak is it once once
you go over an approach and you place
your hand on it you see that there are
no fewer than six distinct rents in the
back of this cloak stab wounds that's
your guess okay and this but the baby's
alive the baby is quite alive yes okay
that's what makes it a Christmas episode
maybe in a manger we got into got
another a couple hours Oh anything's
possible okay so if she's she's dead and
she's a she like on the baby
no no the baby is sort of like after her
okay she is like she had the business of
mind aside and she is looking at it but
there is nothing in her eyes that
indicates that she's able to comprehend
this prophetess and auspicious are in a
corner I was rushed to her okay so I
look over because I was gonna go for
prophetess to help me yet I I I'm going
for the baby I'm walnut walnut please
help
oh my god it's time it wasn't me um
Walmart runs over and starts like grabs
the though elf the dead elf yeah I've
got the baby whore and well that's super
strong lifts itself like nothing and
it's gonna just go into the the back and
get this out of the way yeah where'd she
go she would take it right into the
kitchen
this is good eatin that's the house yeah
it's um it's the kind of thing where i'm
like i look at dinar to who I assume is
down here I don't know I'm framing the
thingy game I can't hear a fucking thing
you're doing oh really
I've been dropping gold this whole time
that's a shame no we actually might need
acts on your human heavy re make my face
off can you wear like a hair
configuration Ryan you might want it put
the you won't put the helmet on like on
the on like the little hat yeah I can't
touch my head I need that gold can we
hear me now I need that gold flavor yes
so there we go you got to wear your
dragon head sort of broke off you know
like ya got save that um so uh we have
customers right no indeed okay we the
drinking has more or less all right come
to a pause all right but dude but in the
drowning courtier there is a recognition
that provinces new guests are adept at
problem solving the issue that you have
presently is that more customers are
coming in well in fact you can see them
moving in front of the like the warm
glow that the DNC casts out into the
street you can see shapes that don't you
can see shapes that are hunched and
predatory and what's odd is that the
shape that you see as they pass the
window is not the shape that you see
entering the door the shapes that enter
the door look like a patron okay like a
sort of person that you might interact
with in a positive way and not like the
sort of gangly elongated shapes that you
saw pass and they enter and their
clothing is not slick with the rain as
they enter the room they look freshly
dressed I stand up and I say welcome
like menacingly at the ready but I mean
if they are real guests and yeah yeah I
don't want to drive mom's body I'm good
for business absolutely murder Monday I
mean I've observed a lot already but I
want to see if there's something else
okay
reception as opposed to the 13 anything
anything I noticed no okay okay big
especially even aside from the things
that you've already identified right
there are four of them that come in in a
similar raiment okay it's a combination
of red and black leather straps and they
are armed not over much for the road but
they they are absolutely they have steel
at the ready okay it's not drawn but
they had come in and they immediately
just as she did
immediately scan the room and as soon as
they identify the bundle their hands are
going for the the knives well oh no you
don't oh no no you don't want to do that
not in this house the the woman who
leads them steps forward and says
grandmother grandmother there's no need
to spill blood here no I agree you don't
know this child you've clearly never met
me hey who are you and why what are you
doing what what just happened there's a
woman who came in here she she just died
and now you're coming in with swords and
I'm holding the baby and I can tell you
this is not gonna end well for you she
looks at the at that the Elven woman in
the cloak and she says she is ours and
then she points at the child and says
she is ours no one belongs to you you
were wrong and we can prove it
please roll initiative Hey
I storm down the stairs I was gonna
write down a bunch of shit then I was
like no Alyssa brought all my awesome
shit this is yes
Alyssa a plus now so what do you got
sixteen sixteen is real real good for a
dinar how are you on that twenty-one god
damn damn girl
I got damn turkey what do you got
thirteen yeah love it how about you kiss
first Robin huh but before initiative
starts I think anybody can come in here
and say that she brought that child in
here that's ours to eat
[Laughter]
Rosi rolls initiative against you yeah
yeah no now that that elicits a grin the
mouth is not the right shape it is too
long and the teeth that are planted
within it are not the right shape what's
going on with your mouth
cool mouth walnut dong grass you can see
these increasingly as that as the
daggers come out they the limbs extend
you would suspect three to four inches
okay
they are sort of loose and languid in a
way their language okay their language
is with their language after their long
and they're using daggers cool I would
like all of them to do a strength saving
throw what are we doing here walnut die
cast entangle on the group oh I don't
like where this is going and I don't
like when I don't like anything about
this yeah this sucks oh this is great so
string I'm only slightly mad at you
Rosie but they're threatening you and
that's all bets are off unacceptable
yeah I must protect well strength is a
pretty good one for them to go after so
that's pretty solid you did say they
were lying they say there's four of them
three of them save but one of them is
one of them is trapped okay you can you
can you can recall profit front perhaps
a week and a half ago clipping away the
rest of the hop vines from the trellis
out front and instantly fresh green
shoots come in straight under the door
and then reach halfway up one of these
targets tank
grass so that one just so for everyone
to know anyone restrained by these
plants hops gonna make a heck of a beer
later need to make a strength to check
against my spell save DC for their whole
action
what's Rudy see
a thing that I will find thank you when
it's its turn an integer 14 here 14
right and then entangle just for the
folks at home tell me what that does
grasping weeds and vines sprout from the
ground in a 20 foot square starting from
a point within range whoops for the
duration of these plants turn the ground
area into difficult terrain so I guess
even if they save it's still difficult
terrain yeah so they can pull around but
it's very difficult for them to maneuver
in here so for a very brief period that
drownin courtier has been reclaimed by
the wood absolutely looks nice
alright so you have done that grasping
vines and plants are reaching in Denard
Blitzen you know there's four of these
a-holes
there's four in one's tangled occupied
oh yeah one of them's got a grip and
they're totally tugging there
weirdly long limbs trying to maneuver
through this space what are they wearing
are they armored up yeah it's this
leather armor but they are armored yes
okay uh I was upstairs saying before I
took a sleeping no I was in our office
framing the crocheted thing that said
I'm not a baby like a diploma like a
point to it like I'm not a baby comes
out yeah if it ever comes to bring
someone wardroom
I got it in writing ish so I come out
and I catch the tail end of all this
dead body baby people make any case to
murder baby typical Wednesday and I was
like whomp whomp back to bed no I go
they haven't made a compelling case to
murder that baby so I will command
because I feeling like metagaming this a
little bit probably be harder to hit the
leader so I'll hit of the of the three
remaining I'll go after two of the
flunkies with command and I'll say
disrobe
nice yeah then I gotta take a turn
taking all their clothes off and
dropping their weapons that's a safe you
want to murder that baby Megan naked
[Laughter]
Christmas so what do we what do they
save against for that Kamandi Oh 14 my
LD say 14 no just this place just got a
lot hotter nah weapons first make me
forget my troubles it's gone it got
really heavy in here nope let's lighten
the mood so their their faces are still
Stern and angry and they have a sort of
like an evil sort of like like they kill
for sport like cats like their their
body language is just is unpleasant but
they've managed to retain the facial
expression that would communicate this
while stripping off all of their armor
so but they're still very defiant yeah
but they have a lot less clothes on now
so that was a but that was able to get a
hold of two of them they were they both
fucked that up
they have to do that for the full turn -
so no no no yeah yeah exactly but they
but they mean it like they're there
they've managed to discover a way to
remove their clothes that still seems
dangerous somehow if they remove their
clothes with lethal precision yeah oh
yeah you think so
so the other the other two have
immediately begun and they are not they
are not approaching the party or the
environment in a tactical way they have
a very specific intention so you work
you are holding this child yeah
absolutely you are the only thing they
care about okay in this world apparently
Wow
now what's your AC 16
okay you are struck by a dagger and you
are struck by another dagger so they
descend upon you in a way that almost
looks as though there's a single
intellect like these these are creatures
that that hunt with regularity and they
give each other space so they can be
very very close to you and not get in
each other's way they just sort of bend
and flow around each other and then
knives are coming out of this this these
waving limbs just out of this cloud it's
like it's like the cartoon version of a
fight where it's just a cloud and then
occasionally limbs are emerging right
it's like that except it's nice yeah
that's 18 okay so ten and eight okay so
lethal precision but here's the deal
they are not trying to stab you at all
well they did a real bad job then no
they are literally trying to kill the
child and when that dagger goes into
this nest of rags you feel it oh wait so
there there's that they're actually
stabbing the baby I'm not even able to
protect it no no they go right for the
child but when that dagger intersects
with this nest of rags you feel the pain
okay oh okay and I take the damage you
take the damage exactly right okay
there's something about this swaddle
that is not Babies R Us there's a unique
quality to it okay rosy bee stinger okay
so I I'm holding this child you are I'm
not going to be able to use my hands at
all which sucks for me use one hand one
hand I don't think I need it so good
four foot but my I I believe my own arm
strikes are a bonus section that I can
only take after I take a staff attack
correct
that's Sherman that I learned the hard
way so what I'm going to do then would
be I think what I'm gonna do is command
I'm going to use my commands to command
that the one attacking me that's closest
to disrobe it's a good gear yeah yeah
yes yeah my cc's 13 oh no no no they did
not do well so so immediately this was
the same dark malevolence plates armor
plates are being pulled off yeah like
right in front of you like to close nice
too close and the body beneath it has
none of the characteristics you would
expect I narrow my eyes and I it's not
it's not a nice face I make but I go
mommy like well because of like the
damage potential yeah Chris trout
emerging is though from a mr. trout
so how do you how do you perceive and
interact with this novel news scenario
just just take a break and enjoy it
ancient menacingly eat my crust of bread
what's the scene infirm who is who's
attacking so Rosie has two friends in
front of her there are two more sort of
in the open area they're in the entrance
that are still dutifully removing their
armor plates okay are the ones near
Rosie also removing one is one of them
the other one is not okay I'm going to
i'ma throw hex oh I'm gonna bring hexie
back yeah
right yeah so let me let me toss that on
to the one getting naked in there Rosie
yeah bonus and then I'm going to split
up my eldritch blast on the on the -
poor kid on the ones on Rosie yeah
absolutely
let's see it alright let's see what we
got here is that that huh so let's do
the nude man first Oh fine B oh it's a
uh last
oh come on math sixteen oh yeah that's
great okay great
that's no problem and remember so there
we go
[Applause]
yeah recall that one of them is train
ood so here let's let's go ahead and get
some
let's get damaged for the first one this
is the part that's gonna not impress
anybody first one is gonna get is gonna
enjoy a seven uh-huh and then the other
guy who's not naked is gonna have a five
for himself you don't get any pluses on
that I don't think so I don't think so I
would if I'd taken that application oh
yeah there's the hex against the one guy
thank you and that is a oh and don't
forget don't forget don't forget the
crit too I mean you need Pope you dice
on the crit oh yeah it was it - okay
there's the other die it's good to have
it it's here
and let's see hex hex hex oh that's
right well yeah I'm trying to see if it
increases at this level but it's just
the duration that increases so it's
still a gentle one but it's just I could
hold it on him for three weeks exactly
should I care to write um in the corner
once profit has established that
auspicious is okay you can hear her sort
of whimpering do you think that she
might have had some foreknowledge of
this event that she is contending with
it may be that she is experiencing what
is happening five minutes from now it
doesn't appear to be good
prophetess drawn is not having any of
this at all she comes over purposefully
just in ass in a direct line from the
wall and just overhand punches one of
the ones that are like halfway getting
the breeches down
hmm my fucking heart extremely Jesus
yeah that's pretty good profit I'm so
here for profit getting it on the
columns yes no no this is all that
bullshit
she just crashes right down for 12 and
then when there when the person they're
halfway down she comes down for another
100 and connects hard yeah this person
is this person is now flat on the ground
and she's and then she gets she just
kicks him over the rest of the way with
her foot and then makes her way behind
the bar Rosie's like raised this baby
with me we can rule the universe
Walnut Don grass things are still pretty
crazy here at the drunk courtier yeah
you do talk to me about at the top of
the turn what's the layout right now we
still got two bad boys by Rosie yeah
exactly two bad boys by Rosie
at two increasingly nude figures closer
to the actual entrance of the door okay
great they're still pulling off their
stuffs their three nudes I got - we got
three news
yeah we should have three oh yeah yeah
there's one nude in front of Rosie as
well okay yeah okay Oh gotcha okay cool
so I see all these people in front of
Rosie I don't know what they're stabbing
but they're stabbing into her and that
stinks you say no I say no so you're
gonna make it absolutely clear for
obviously for the crowd and of course Oh
your position on baby stabbing no huh
you're saying no on the data I mean yeah
no yeah what is entangled it's Christmas
yeah you know it's Christmas and you're
right I think yes
so it wasn't angry or nude no I'm gonna
cast uh so I'm gonna grab this is my
flavored version of flame blade Oh what
I'm gonna flame blade them which is
where I grab for mother can you do it
please really gonna brand for mother
yeah and I say no to you sir I got flame
blade and it erupts in green flame which
you can't see but it does and I lash out
at the person in front of me
bye Rosie one of those boys yeah one of
them is definitely worse off than the
other if I hit it I'd do some good
damage so let's see let's see what
happens it's gonna be a lot easier since
half of them there's a fully
three-quarters of them are basically
don't have pants on yeah it's true ah it
just says you can use your action to
make it om a light spell attack yeah yes
so it's a little that's a good one I
like it
whoo 24 that's gonna work yeah great now
what happens I gotta borrow some thanks
for this uh it's 3d six big money okay
so that's a ten
another one that's a 515 good God nice
Yong Yong you sure this foe in half and
immediately the entangling roots sense
this nutrition that they want to send
directly to their roots and immediately
that's the carpet of crawling reaching
vines yeah it starts to dig and bore
into these chunks dinar blitz int well
after seeing all that it took fucking
Christmas special yeah Christmas
I feel festive yes I go right leg or the
groin holly berries on yeah I think it's
beginning to look a lot like Christmas
[Applause]
and we go yeah how would you gardener
Blitzen uh ones on the ground ones all
fucked oh yeah you know profit put one
on the ground that's an easy picking
yeah I'll go after I'll finish him off
oh go get him up yeah let's see it do
you have a oh my help I have all the
power
I'm just a baby
not an idiot baby no not anymore
alright I'm not gonna I'm not gonna take
great got straight I don't think I need
to he's naked on the ground I don't know
blaster or I'm you could hump it into
myself so I'm gonna just toothbrush
right down on top of them 19 oh that's
quite good
yes yum yum - d6 + 3 is a I get to roll
a 1 I get 3 roll a 1 on damage it's a 4
and a 2 I get 3 roll to everything until
I get what I like well it's the Rothfuss
rule yep sure uh 9/10 Oh 12 except is it
you know you know like some I have an
insensitive he's dead so I got he's no
he's not dead all right well he's gonna
be uh then almost divine smite a little
little pop on top for a 3d 8 7 good lord
oh sorry 7 and in a 2222 more Ted they
liquefy him No
so you you give him a you slash him as
he's trying to as he's trying to reach
his way up trying to crawl back up out
of this mesh of plants and then the
initial slash elicits a sort of cruel
smile but then a second later in this
shockwave of divine power
just flattens him to the ground I'm not
digging this no the first the first one
was fine you don't know if it's like a
Power Exchange thing like you don't know
what's going on with him is he well I
he's will get litter ated now all right
well I have to keep going no no you're
fine you're fine after the other one
exactly so next to the one that prophet
had beat down there is another one who
is though disrobe is perfectly capable
of combat well so they have to keep him
dressing until their turn it hasn't been
their turn yet well there goes Anil
distracted can't I get him like I'm
buckling his pants like they already
lost that turn from before they did you
go before them I thought I had to spend
the whole full turn did they do anything
cool all right no no no it's just me I'm
gonna give you I'm gonna give you what
you earned trying to office this no no
but you're doing your best you're doing
your lab my best Godzilla so much to
learn from it could be his protege yeah
so here's but here's what occurs is that
this other target that is in front of
you from this group of two hmm does not
pay you attention at all their intention
is to get to this baby now so they he
actually turns his back to you and goes
to Rosie so I can attack them you do
that do okay is that it your own attack
yeah you just get a free attack yeah
Joey auto hits oh you get a free 1007
plus 8 15 yes that's quite good
give me the damage from its jack jacked
be three reroll two - I have to take the
second one
so that's five and then I'll smite him -
okay I don't think I get to re-roll the
damage on the smites okay someone can't
correct me if I do Wow
so so you you slash straight across the
back there's no armor plate and almost
immediately you can see like you make a
slash and then the slash itself like a
second later fills up across the back so
this entity stumbles as a result of the
hit and the smite but then continues to
doggedly pursue Rosie be stinger - to
1000 no jeez oh that's a natural 20 all
right here we go
Oh shadow councils there ladies please
we could play baby keep away if you take
the damage and you realize that just use
a baby the shield hit him all you want
it's gonna I'm gonna take it yeah I
think that ends up being the same deal
for me oh yes it's just a fundamental
picture that's an additional 16 points
or is EB 505 huge just yeah deep deep
cuts yep okay Rosie B let's see there's
actually there's actually another one
that was already over by you
ah and they are going to well you're
also gonna hit you know by mile he goes
last she out all that's five points Mary
it's been great everybody the gift was
death so Rosie how do you want to
fall I will offer you this boon right on
it even even though I know that it's
it's a useless gesture I fall curled
around this bundle in the hopes that
they'll just keep stabbing me instead
because I'm dead already
I have another long beautiful life
that's fine right so you become a shield
for this child and the moment before
your eyes flutter close you can see its
jaw unhinge and sort of hang and droop
and swing from left to right with some
kind of evil delight thrist drow lucky
that especially i don't see that yeah
what's that I don't see that right I die
how you can see that oh I see the jaw
yes okay no 100% job big thing about
parenting I'm gonna I'm gonna do it
worked already and I'll just blast the
two of these two targets remain and
obviously there's just one in front of
Rosie and then okay they're both in
front of Rosie right now they both sort
of coalesced in front of her okay is one
of them still the hexed one mm-hmm
yeah let's just do Eldridge class and I
try the hex one first get it get make
some mods well thank you there you go
grandma say thank you grandma
Mike uh yeah let's do that
I'm just I'm trying to think of like
what charisma do after seeing the jaw
oh no no feel free to listen because my
listen might play Dungeons &amp; Dragons man
like figure out how you want to do it
you don't gotta rush through this you
tell me how you feel about this I know
that this baby is important would I be
able to release ligado
tell him get that get that
Thursday maggot to safety I don't never
the name for a baby right now
pupae out of here and have him like coil
one coil around the baby and then snake
away those like snakey muscles yeah that
is ball in yeah love it yeah what you do
so you basically like sticks to snakes
like you'll take your rod and then just
cast it out yeah just communicate your
intention to lagari yeah I could like
take him upstairs take the child
upstairs no exactly so what happens is
you throw out Lou got Eve and that the
rod immediately is sort of like
elastically sort of like snaps into his
shorter length and he hits the floor and
you can see that the dagger point that
is in the end of the staff is now held
like that like a rattlesnakes rattle
yeah and he sort of burrows underneath
Rosie and then coils around the child
and then moves like a spring the child
sort of like held in the middle of this
coil while it travels across the room
over toward these the warm stove and
near the stairs he constrict but he also
protect no no he don't he does yeah he
does protect that's actually that's
that's rather that's a recognized
phenomenon and you can see you can see
thee you can see the creature
sort of like turn to watch this happen
you can see the jaw so like a pendulums
I see that I see that from maga T's eyes
yes he's exiting and IO cuz currently
I'm functionally blind right right yeah
yeah yeah you've you've contended yeah
you have you've basically committed
yourself to this action of rescue walnut
on grass there are two foes that remain
either and one and one very deeply
sleepy grandma so here's the thing is
that as long as I don't let go of the
blade
it does not disappear haha
you're gonna keep working yeah yeah I
think I'm gonna keep working yeah you
know what I could heal you but it's dead
I'm gonna you're gonna hurt the bad guys
I gotta do it baby
I got I got something I got something
you'll like okay great I'm cool
so once again I'm gonna try and hit one
of the one of the goo boys and Oh No Oh
Han it's just a ten total just a ten
like that's the whole number yes that's
very four five six seven eight to ten
then you stop there base 10 what are we
talking about that's it so you you rate
you raise this flaming for mother and
use you swipe down along the flank of
this creature and it draws its arm into
its torso pushes it back out on the
front and pushes it out along the side
and for mother speaks in your mind
she says the elven word for changeling
okay yes and I know what this means
absolutely okay good I also know what
the changelings are yeah change links
and the EPA have a because it's because
it's such a protected sacred culture
okay changelings are always trying to
gain entree into it okay oh so I don't
like this no no no this is there's a lot
of there's a lot of stories about
changelings let's put it that way so I
don't want to disengage but I'm gonna
I'm gonna move to body block like they
if they want to get to Licata you have
to go through me I love it
okay that's in credit dinar bulletin I
will move towards rosy exactly so try to
heal so these these creatures are their
eyes are tracking like now that Rose is
on the floor you know here to care at
all so I can they're only about this
bizarre amethyst screw that is trance
there's a baby around in a completely
new way so so they had their backs to me
they were going after Rosie like Audi
took him out of the way
are they close enough that I can just Oh
Absalon my way over to Rosie indeed they
would have to pass you to get the baby
all right
no I might as well just hit him on my
way over yeah cuz I shove in the back
sorry I will do that I will do those
things I said all right I'm good
20 not a natural time I like it five
five that's 13 and god damn well you put
a little sauce on there give him a
little top them off there I will burn
locate object I don't think I need that
so that's a little too so you can add a
little sauce on there yep
so 3d8 bread get that heat seven big
money want one but what's the total okay
17 more on top of that first number I
said all right so you you connect you
connect directly with this creatures
chest and then a pulse of divine power
accompanied by a draconic roar you know
knocks them Eluga over knocks him over
the bar and back into the kitchen
prophetess drawn suits on real inner
stones so a prophetess drawn reaches
down toward Rosie and sort of grabs like
by the Cinch of your cloak in your robes
and with one hand picks you up on the
ground says a word of power and then
sets you on your feet you have 20 hit
points oh well
I like it that's hospitality no I say
okay yeah I was gonna do that but all
right look you've put away your helis
yeah fades out as she does that she
reaches behind the bar and pulls out a
mall like drags it up over the top of it
you can see it sort of like scratch the
top of the bar as she brings it over and
then she says she says Rosie get this
child out of here
absolutely I love you a little bit
she says that line goes around the block
[Music]
damn she says you need to take this
child to father Gordon take the road
that leads west out of town the Cal Dell
Road and in the forest you will pass the
way rest in father Gordon holds sway
there and he'll know what to do he has
been a friend for many many years okay
so I I I'd not to profit and I say thank
you for saving my ass yeah then I have
them all up onto the shoulder yeah okay
I'm gonna go are we are all the enemies
dead
so you murdered everybody there's one
more okay where that is still there is
still hungry for babe okay and it's sort
of it's sort of like almost kneels down
and then lopes how far away very very
near near enough to hit kneels down like
with the dagger in one hand and then
lopes like in a three-legged gate Oh
over toward this bizarre screw okay no
Rosie's gonna unleash she she looks at
this this thing and she goes we don't we
don't do that in the drowning quarter
and we'll do just the full array cuz you
know I don't think she knows how how
much their health they've got left
so oh but you're lucky I'm a lucky
halfling thank God
all right that's still not that great
that's as 12 but they're naked
wait did 12 is okay yeah and so that's
gonna be a are you doing you're studying
strike or anything like that um no I'm
just gonna obliterate my mature okay I'm
so I'm gonna do but I am gonna do as
many strikes as it takes up to four okay
so that's gonna be a I'll do another
attack that's not great that's a nine is
that a hit okay another nine I'll do eat
my shorts dweeb remember that unkind
[Applause]
their Labour's please now don't forget
to double those dice okay okay so I'll
stop there I won't spend a key for four
Fleury so I will do my staff hits for
nine points and my punch hits for eight
last seven nineteen God okay these D
eights are being very kind today yeah so
does the staff comes down just you it
was a sickening crack against the skull
and then as it's trying to roll away you
drop a precision strike just right in
the middle of the spine and it collapses
knocking over chairs and scooching a
table with an audible screech profit
not sir head toward the door okay I'm
gonna go to legaly n' and kneel down and
and tell him that the what is his name
for me the knife bringer that he called
me something what was the name which is
because I gave legate the knife and I
did so the god he thinks fondly of me
anyway he does yeah I kneel down and I
tell I tell the Ngati I've you know I've
got it I've got it from here
you can you can let her go and I hold
out my arms right it's it raises up a
little bit and gives you just like a
gentle nip on the edge of your cloak
oh my petit I yeah yeah sure thing toys
the kids all you like so
[Laughter]
so you're you're reaching down to get
the child from lagari but Locati
whines and curls like an Archimedes
screw and sort of like via via this sort
of action sort of like the baby is sort
of like produced by the center of the
spring like directly into your hands he
poops it out basic okay he emits baby
okay great great thanks bud you could
work on being a little less disturbing
good don't worry bout it I like just as
you are come on back exactly so after
he's done everybody's done curling
around he's sort of like in a coiled
spring like jumps up toward you and then
becomes a staff yeah wrap all right now
you can hear just outside the drawn and
cordial you can hear inhuman powell's
and cries of alarm from the populace you
can also hear heavy bronze hooves coming
down hard inside the carriage house ha
ha oh my girl she hungers for freedom we
gotta go gotta get alright um so I goes
that's you and we're gonna sneak out yes
so I go to you and I put my hand at your
back and I leaned in and I whisper and I
go I go this child is dangerous what do
you mean I mean here give me some
history okay I don't know how much I
like a good history I don't know how
much please so lean doll with your spell
when you knocked out that really oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah where is mine just main
old character sheet Amy it's here I know
you got it I never doubted you for a
second oh well that's an 18 let's go
that's gonna do it plus some yeah yeah
tell me I need the plus
your notebook on the right oh is it
sorry folks no here this is yes it's
okay to show people real Dungeons and
Dragons on occasion the bonus is zero
okay
there are many many stories okay in the
Enclave about changelings yes that
attempt to cajole their way in and
corrupt the faith there is one story
okay
the story is called the Royal changeling
so there is a there are changelings that
are not a part of the greater changeling
community for lack of a better term
royal changelings are not evil alignment
and they are universally hated by
changelings okay they are basically
outcasts in changeling society and their
prized because their blood is
functionally speaking a potion oh wow
like I would add like add like mystic
like the story is about the stories
about the Royal changeling are about
them giving their lives to heal
lycanthropy like they show up it's like
the deus ex machina of enclave stories
but there's no way to know if it's the
bad kind or that kind no you would have
to you would have to get to know them
better okay well so I say I say to Rosie
I say this child is dangerous it could
be dangerous to us or it could be
dangerous for those who who will hunt us
to no end to get it well Rosie looks
down this baby who I believe is adorable
no no absolutely okay looking looking up
at you from the like not conscious of
the events that have just transpired
just looking up looking up with a
slightly upturned
Green okay Rosie touches the baby and
she's listening she's she's she's very
attentive but she she looks at walnut
and she says this baby might be
dangerous but I think that the ones who
chase us will find that we are more
dangerous well I guess maybe exactly so
as you as you burst out prophet nods to
you and the front of the carriage house
the door is busted off of its hinge
corriander smashes directly through the
door again holds the cart out and you
can hear the stretch up along the roofs
you can see shapes in human shapes sort
of like boiling and twisting in a
silhouette against the moonlit sky and
you can hear the stretch of bowstrings
who is holding the baby Rosie you're
gonna want to consider reconsider this
yeah I could I can free one hand for the
good tank it yeah you take seven points
I can deflect missile yeah but it
requires a roll it do and I'm gonna look
for it
feel free to talk amongst just like
Tasha Tasha 20 yeah yeah nice okay well
what do you ten Wendy ten ten flush your
level so see you don't have to roll this
and you don't have to roll the twenty
yeah oh there it is she's right thank
you and twenty ten plus six plus my
dexterity modifier okay so that's a 6-4
and my Dex mod is three yes that's 13 as
long as as long as over it so this this
this arrow is flying directly toward
this bundle okay and it's just like you
just catch it and then the baby sort of
freeze its arm from the bundle and it's
like giggles a little bit as it reaches
out toward the arrow
uh-huh okay
oh no not yet yeah all right I could
talk about that later
absolutely so tell me how we're getting
into this situation until we're moving
out
um can I throw the arrow back absolutely
all right
I'll spend a key point and I'm gonna
chuck that thing as a monk weapon
directly back from whence it came and
that is going to be a an eight plus six
probably a fourteen mm-hmm so you grab
it it reaches out it's a no honey no no
no it's not a toy
and then just without even looking at
the target uh-huh
just and you hear it you hear a shriek
and then you can hear it sort of clatter
along the rain-soaked roof and then you
hear a thud back in the alley I'll teach
you that one later
[Applause]
all right this is great I can't
I'm so thirsty you guys gotta go to the
bit I can't
I know all right yes oh sorry right I
mean like so coriander is coriander is
like pawing the cobble okay
can I give one of you the baby you sit
inside oh yeah you take the child
I can oh no I can take the damage for
tennis eggy you're fine
yeah yeah I'm like you and then I am in
in one single vault up okay yep hand the
baby up on the Front's walnut I'm
actually I read our classic
configuration super important that I
know where you are I want to sit in the
front but I want the window open so I
have eyesight I'm inside on the oh you
don't trust me no I'll sit next to Rose
the outside okay
okay up up on the up on the bench
classic shotgun position yeah okay for
you guys yeah I'm gonna stance eyes in
the back okay back in town boys in the
back all right exactly
coriander like a like a coiled spring is
just ready for action she pulls south
along that side road in red larch moves
out
skids the cart out around the long road
you can see you can see well ver
wistfully looking on as the cart that he
put so much work into he raises a glass
as the cart goes by he put the work in
yeah yeah
yeah I test and then you had you haven't
you don't have much experience heading
out this road but there has been a West
leading road the entire time called the
caldera Road you pull a hard left and
just gunned yourself straight out you
can see behind the cart you can see a
number of these figures loping toward
the party you would not believe how
difficult it is to scoot your chair
forward if you're covered in rats if I
didn't I'd that's it it's a new type of
challenge this is hard mode for sitting
if you ever wanted to know so but you
can see I mean there's there's got to be
20 of them chasing the cart okay and
then but coriander is slowly but
steadily pulling away and they are just
being lost in this rain okay and mist
so we're outrunning them oh yes okay
usually korok coriander is the coriander
knows her business do we see this forest
oh yeah it doesn't take long okay you
know maybe a half-hour you know 45
minutes travel are we confident we're
being pursued should we use not very
little I think we at random no jabs okay
no there are little owls and we can get
no I think well you're you're you're
welcome to you're welcome to use your
ear mobs I mean you have it I don't
think we probably haven't changed it out
of the 100 I would allow you to make I
would allow you to make some checks to
quick swap okay one of those objects
want all radio on yeah right get those
tunes go on tunes yeah yeah right it's
it's like the Elven version of phil
collins yes Susu you know so we let me
yeah let me go ahead and swap us out the
for the owl the cat silent running
oh yeah nice what kind of a check with
that exam yeah it's Arkana so just
Arkana okay here we go
well it's gonna be 12 just needs 10 I
mean you've done it before
okay um it's just you just screw it off
good unscrewed in so it's it is eerie to
be traveling with this massive cart
through this for this rain soaked path
trees whipping in the wind and it is
just dead silent there's no sound of the
carriage wheel there's no sound even
corianders heavy gate and you know you
can see these are giant splashes from
puddles going up and it's just like a
ghost floating through through this mist
so you were inside right now yeah I need
perception checks from Walnut Don grass
and Rosie be stinger you know I got it
Oh keep me another 20 oh that's amazing
I mean it is this is impossible to see
okay what what you have detected is
hidden with such cleverness with such
lethal cleverness that it I mean its
purpose is clearly to seize and snare
carts as they travel through this wood
you can see strung along at the height
of the cart driver look oh you can see a
fine fine silver thread oof so I need
dexterity checks from y'all all right
acrobatics is perfectly acceptable here
if you have another way you want me to
calculate you not getting shredded by
this I'm down oh look two lucky sevens
I got a 13 I got a 10 okay I ordered my
sandwich cut yeah Simpsons joke it's fun
someone will get
someone out there is loving it you grab
a 1 a 1 1 damage a 1 damage okay and
walnut you grab a 6 so these so these
are it there's it's it isn't merely a
thread there is there I'm enchanted in
some way like their their their
sharpness is beyond this silver thread
catches just the top part of the bun and
Rosie's hair collapses down and cascades
over her shoulder in the rain
Wow I got in the moonlight it's exactly
rosie actually this this is disorienting
because it's she's not ready now no you
know she's not ready prepare yeah and so
and so she she's she put the hand on her
for a second and then she looks and it's
it's you and she's like it's okay yeah
enjoy it yeah well that grabs the rain
[Laughter]
no no this no so I need perception
checks now from the occupants we don't
abs well what's my oh okay 16 perfect
what do you got
7s sucks I'm a dumb baby so you you look
over and you can see dinar sort of like
like a football carry like the baby
against his full silhouette is a very
very small little you know lozenge of
humanity and then you just cast a glance
out the right side of the cart
and you can see on all fours you can see
a for all intents and purposes Wolf's
individual eloping on all fours clearly
a biped in its normal configuration you
have no need to roll a check to
determine this is almost some kind of
God
werewolf and you can just do the tongue
is just out like a dog that's been
running a while
yeah just foamies flecks of spittle
around the jowl and you can see it sort
of it's running alongside matching speed
with the cart and then you can feel it
jump up and then hang on to the side of
the cart itself and it is like fumbling
on the side trying to find the door I
communicate to the group I'm like as
fast as I can communicate it in words
it's like wolf side that isn't like I
thought you fast rearrange itself no
that's not a good band name either stop
it all so bad it is a good name and we
have a werewolf on the other part now I
tell you dinar blitz in uh you can sort
of hear a rattle on the side of the on
the on the door side thanks to no more
babies that was a good joke - wolf snake
dog man person individual lawyer so on
NBC this is this fall so you you can you
can see like the inside of the latch you
can see it just like flipping down in an
attempt to do like be open from outside
okay what are we gonna do uh so that's
the bed where will that Trevor right
that's however coming to help right now
you stabbed him through the door no
bellhop cap alright that's a key and I
roll to see if I see that's the
indicator of a good boy okay so he's a
bad boy like it's okay if your friend
the bellhop kept me afloat I see you've
learned bad lessons about werewolves
yeah so if he's up against the door I
want to kick the door open
I wanna baby here was one Bigfoot man
one big-ass foot kick the door open
alright that's my that's my thing let's
see it
oh well I'm not worried about it isn't
about that
what I actually need more is damage
because the door is right in front of
him right like I leave this pack roll
I missed a hit though hit Chris Todd
toss me a 6 I just want to get a sense
of what we're talking about here then
with you safe 17 okay you're Plus okay
okay so you walk over and you just like
full-on
like leonidas style yeah
Barton kick straight into the door but
you can hear the latch of the door snap
yeah and obviously value card decrease
yeah but you can see this door swing out
and you hear this you hear like a like a
canine Yelp of pain and you see this
sort of like fur orb fling off of the
side and then bounce and roll behind the
cart don't let you hit the door on your
way out
yeah got him you're getting there yeah
[Music]
yeah so could risk this you this the the
werewolf on your side of the cart his
tongue is just all over the window it's
just it's not a good look for him and
then it's Lavery does this foam and
slick spittle mixing with the rain and
flowing down and then you see it
crawling up on the top I need a
perception role from you about walnut oh
no and Rosie got it 15:26 right you you
hear that you hear the Scrabble back on
the left side of the cart and then you
see you see his you see it's Joel's pull
themselves up over the side and then
sort of flattened out along the top of
it you get a free action Oh free action
hold yeah I do nothing I just him in
this whole deal you guys hey y'all I go
hey I succeeded preemptively I know a
vampire um I have a thing I can do but
it has never worked on the history of
our show
let's go ahead with all these people
here yeah it'll work it's gonna work
you gotta blast out please make a melee
spell attack so that is my regular plus
we'll use a bow what are you I'm gonna
do cast thorn whip and I'm gonna do a
vine like whip covered in thorns lashes
out at your command towards a creature
flying like whip it goes loops beckon
and hits Chris now yeah ready I yeah
it's a 9 now a night it's pretty good
I'm not a real exotic I'm just rolling
to intimidate him and I'm saying back
nice that's crease nice nice yeah it it
clings in it it roars and it didn't
adjust itself to the side as this
crackling is cracking whip reaches out
past it and snaps I need initiative from
Rosie
and the nut and if you guys want to get
in you can come in next time I got a 15
okay well you guys got nothing six
that's less yeah wow you are good all
right rosy bee stinger yeah rain rains
in hand so this this werewolf is on top
of the cart behind us is that about
absolutely yeah coming up on your side
on the left did you take the rain so for
real or was that it was that a bit okay
I wanna drive that thing uh at this
point the rains are largely ornamental
anyway coriander knows her business is
mostly just like a comfort thing for
Rosie to be well it's probably a comfort
thing for coriander as well yeah I mean
there's there's a relationship there we
try to we try to pretend she's a normal
horse but right y'all know the truth
okay so I'm gonna just drop them and
fuck him up and vault right over and and
start start with the pain hopefully
hopefully we'll see what's up and the
long hair is like blowing oh yeah and in
the in the as the cart continues to go
may I offer something no yeah absolutely
like just a second you grab on to the
for the lip of the roof and then you
just flip oh yeah yeah and put your feet
into it
yeah it's eye-sockets oh that's good
that's pretty smooth alright alright
we'll see if my if my melee is hit
that's right there's a flavor yeah okay
so this is gonna be yeah oh that's a 23
that's a 22 I'll do one melee attack
with my with those eye-sockets no that's
an 18 god damn ball good yeah so
let's see some damage alright um the
first one is a seven the second one is a
five and the eye sockets is another
seven okay solid yeah nineteen fourteen
nineteen yes there's our kicks in here
punches so uh the first one as I when I
volts whenever it's the staff it's got a
it's got to come left right and then the
feet plow right into the eyeballs right
so you so it's it's like a punching bag
basically yeah
it just left right it's just it's
spindle flex and flying in each
direction and when you when you bring
the foot up it appears it appears to it
doesn't have any fear of this foot but
when the foot connects there is an
audible Yelp at six you got the ability
to your your your feet and hands are
magic weapons yes they are and that's
just that is deeply deeply required to
manage this wolf shit nice okay okay
done
what happens to him as a result of my
magical foot he takes a bunch of damage
okay nice now he's super pissed okay so
he climbs up over the edge so you
flipped back over his hands are here
with one pull a lot of upper body a lot
of upper body on this werewolf not
skipping pulls himself up and then
plants his feet and then stands up his
full height towering over you on the
very top of this cart I give his belly a
little rub yeah oh hey he's a one boy
he's mine now this robe you choose him
no no so he is snapping like snapping
and you just move with ease just like
micro movements on your part you're
avoiding massive bites like a huge sweep
of the claw and it's just like one foot
slight move a slight turn of the head
just effortless avoidance walnut don't
grass I am so sick of trying to cast
magic so I'm just gonna go for it here
so I look I see what's going on up there
and I'm like this is not gonna get too
crowded at all and I transform into your
book nut Wolfie wolf how will there's a
wolf fight it's a wolf on sunday sunday
sunday why does the whole card but you
only need the edge hold card that's
right
please continue oh sorry are you done
Sara Lee oh
shake the dice somewhere I do a lot of
what I'm gonna do a bite I get an
advantage because of pact tactics cuz I
am right next to you that's right hey
beautiful young yeah 121 boy ah and then
I get to do some damage it's 2d six plus
three
piercing seven plus three nice where'd
you hide him what do I bite him target
the haunch yeah right in the heart it's
gotta be right Scott of the meal yeah I
get them right in that meaty meaty oh
yeah yeah um whereas you shift into your
wolf form you you are able to do it with
an ease that you haven't experienced in
months it is instantaneous instinctual
flawless all the memories of like every
other time that you've you've converted
yourself into this perfect predatory
form it's all flowed back to you now
there's it's not corrupt in any way
there's no hesitation it is an instant
reaction but in the moment you wind up
right yeah you you you you're you
preparing to have to push through yeah
to have to put down two poles but I
don't
there's no pull it's instantaneous nice
very nice you know that's a pretty solid
amount of damage
Rosie be stinger how's he looking okay
alright so yeah just keep doing what I
do bet it's gonna say like so don't we
individually roll initiative and then
we'll come in at the end of this yeah
exactly go ahead you're the initiative
now yeah cause right now you can hear it
you can hear stomps are in there and
there's there's a moment where deserted
you can hear a couple of footfalls and
then you just sort of hear like wait
more like yeah here the roof clean
that's - it's too late to be the bear
right is the wolf today so what he got
thirteen six okay put them before me
right what's that you can play Dennard
before me
we both had sex okay okay uh right be a
stinger there's full moon oh yes yeah
how many silver bullets we have in their
inventory
okay okay here mommy a little bit
couldn't make it out oh he didn't do a
DC uh strike saving throw shitty he
needs to or be knocked prone oh yeah
he's on the fuse flat he is prone enjoy
no I have a minute oh yeah yes deeply as
a result that hunch he's never been he's
never been bitten in that hunch
[Laughter]
so is he prone on the roof take the
fight to the back of coriander to wolves
Dragonborn that's a 15 or that's a
better one that's 25 that is a 22 and
that is a 15 but I'm gonna take a higher
one that's a 16 do they all hit yeah
okay great great
so she's going to pick up her her staff
the the werewolf got bit by the good
wolf nut and it went down and there's
it's it's bleeding from this honking
yeah exactly and Rosie desperately she's
just jamming the end of the staff of the
master
right in that open wound over again it's
real nasty turn that butter okay that's
a wolf butter
oh no premium be fresh for anybody yeah
no Rosie bee stingers haunch butter yeah
that's a 23 what my dairy section it
howls and the last one is a melee attack
which is just the fist going as far into
that wound
yeah at the final at the final punch
like each time it's been trying to like
it's being struck and am actually the
motion of the cart there's a lot of
challenge for this thing to sort of
Scrabble and keep on that last hit like
if it has a couple weak attempts to
maintain itself up on the thing there's
a couple quick scrabbles you can hear it
scraping and scratching on the roof and
then it just slides off the top it hits
the ground in a puddle and then you can
just sort of see it disappearing in the
background oh no don't go yeah now is I
would like to get some history checks as
we start moving deeper into the wood
from everybody uh-huh okay I'm good
history hmm I lied I'm not good at
history well eight today eleven eleven
also a fifteen ten fifteen ten eleven
eleven you know that the way rest chapel
that you you have heard of it
is this the way rest anyway where's
chapel we were strapped oh okay all
right it goes it goes by many names the
Chapel of the way rest a woodland temple
to helm a God of protection okay the way
rest is a friend to merchants and weary
travelers as they make their way through
the would you think or rather hope it
isn't far from here
and you are glad
to see torchlights just off this rainy
path up and opt to the left okay and in
the in the surrounding wood you can hear
a chorus of howls and you and you know
that these are celebrations and it's
like there's some part of you that
senses that pack and that that family
but you know that the feast they're
celebrating is you and your friends yes
hmm
so you at a moment you exist in these
two coordinates extremely conflicted
right now and I go I go walnut Suns
getting real low so you are able to you
were able to slow the cart corriander
does not want to corriander just wants
to keep going until she reaches the end
of the fucking map
okay you're able to pull the cart off
into these into this torch lid area a
couple hundred feet off to the left so
you can sort of see these torches and
lights twinkling in the back and there's
a couple torches near the road itself
that are lit with green flame and you're
able to pull the cart straight down this
side path the church itself is lit
within by a combination of torches red
candles and glowing orbs of unknown
manufacturer light pours out of the
windows bringing to mind the lantern or
a lighthouse built in the wrong place so
as you enter you see no one inside right
now you see basically a simple chapel
with a couple beds against the wall like
this is this is clearly a place of rest
for travelers but it is they
very it's almost like it's almost like
battlefield decor like the way that it's
set up inside is almost like a it's like
a combination Chapel and barracks okay
you can tell that at any moment these
pews can be converted into small beds
but like I say there's right now that
any if there's someone named father
Gordon you cannot see him here every few
feet the walls to the left and right are
adorned with stained glass depicting aid
to Wanderers it is a place of such
perfect comfort you can hardly let
yourself believe it for a wilderness
chapel it is well-appointed
hill mites collect a tithe which some
call the dust of the road on goods that
travel through this wood the pews are
stained dark and are polished the
fragrant wax a decorative shield stands
on a casual podium with three arrows of
pure silver in a row on the front a
massive wall of stained glass stands
behind the wooden podium depicting a
brilliant sun shining over a golden cup
the howls outside rise to a sharp
crescendo rising in a blood-curdling
hunting song whose notes are clear and
pure no work of mere beasts even even
there even the Christmas specials the
Halloween special I got all these rats
you guys can read all right here we go
so you can see that chorus voice for
voice is diminished every few seconds
that chorus seems to lose a howl ooh
these howls are slowly but surely
turning into individual yelps of pain
that are receding into the distance
these terrifying chords are held for
what seems to be an eternity and at the
moment you think the sound will drive
you mad at melts into stillness there's
a long terrible moment of silence before
the stained glass at the end of the
chamber shatters inward it's majestic
Sun replaced by the brilliant eye of the
full moon unfolding itself from the
ground pieces of jagged glass are
dropping to the floor as its wounds mend
themselves this is an ancient where bare
a grizzled old creature and his body is
full of daggers swords and spirits that
the skin is closed around holding them
in place his ragged fur is gray and in
the light sparkles with a ghostly glow
his huge black eyes scour across the
room and he finds the child with a
terrifying speed with a roar echoed by
the wind outside he leaps so I need
initiative from everybody I've had zero
chance to like catch our breath I know I
know I've been begging to summon Clark
boy I know this is just like all the
combat from the show all put into it all
all mushed into one episode or so we got
1915 okay also 15 okay also for for okay
the reality that he actually goes after
you guys good so this this thing like I
said this thing unfolds and its height
is massive it is different though the
werewolves are not small by any means
but this is just like a side of beef
holding a gigantic battle ax in one hand
mouth just a froth with hunger and it is
zeroed in directly on the bundle okay so
it's looking at dinar then oh well it is
not looking at dinar it doesn't care
about dinar well I care about dinner oh
don't tell him I said that
okay but I go first you do okay so um
I'm gonna go ahead and and try to use
some stunning strikes on this thing in
the off chance that that'll work I
assume it's Constitution is unbelievable
but you do roll like shit so hey listen
she's not wrong uh okay so this is gonna
be two staff of the Masters that's 20
yep and that's a 19 that's also good
okay what these thing are you're a beast
that's pieces inner beast finger so do
I'm gonna try to stunning strike with
both of those so due to context I bet my
spell save is 13 he's looking like a
million shit okay one more just like
there's these wax I mean it's like
hitting a tree yeah it's like you can
remember training in the monastery
against against a wooden sort of dummy
yeah and it's just like that like you
don't know if it is feeling these at all
okay I remember that the werewolf send
it I had had a better response to my
magical fingers and toes so I'm gonna do
flurry of blows to on arm strikes that's
gonna be a and 18 whoa Rosie getting
crazy and that is a 10 there I love it
so those are both also gonna be stunning
strikes I am using a lot of key points
today folks and he save he's good yeah
just Connors like damn it
okay so here comes damage here it comes
that's not grade five
ten ten and six twenty thirty one mmm 31
31 quits downs third one that's worth it
up oh yeah
now it's okay now
Rosie be sneer that is great each of the
each of these are connecting and you
know you can feel the staff of the
master and the key energy flowing
through your strikes you know that these
are functionally required to make this
happen you feel like that is the only
edge you have against this creature
walnut on grass okay well first things
first
I'm gonna race ya what first things
first I'm the realest person I'm the
realest first thing is I'm gonna have
post right
extremely close Oh deeply profoundly
close in a big room is okay well I'm
gonna do this small room all right uh it
was a nine so no little baby
um so that is intimidating see now back
off
oh but I packed tactics nice yeah yeah
yeah thank you no I forgot oh wait
you're still
oh yeah 23 so that's a bite
fantastic so make sure he does it he's
gonna pass up at the DC 13 strength
saving throw only be pulled down no he's
fine
yeah I figured and then just real quick
that's a 5 that's a 5 to 10 13 damage
goddamn kid and then I'm gonna back up
as much as I can wait I just get it just
get out of the way you don't want to
move away from this thing oh you're
right you're right I don't no no no you
you you committed you did I would this
has this axis as big as you are you're
right okay
I don't think that was I was really
gracious no I just that was my Christmas
present and I accept it Chris trout okay
so this has been an opportunity for you
to experience an entire menagerie of
we're creatures there has to be some
delight
but just just about a pure interest yes
like what other things used to be a
person shape and now they could be a
bear not the time exciting eventually
well I mean it's exciting and then it's
gets monotonous do multiple animal
shapes so a wolf big deal bear big deal
okay yeah now we're done yeah we're
sharp it's like all right yeah let's see
what's my best use damage or promote uh
advantage to everybody subsequently who
comes after me
we got dinar do not pretend he's it
taste and then what clues has enunciated
on the back as bad guy bad guy okay here
we go let it I'm gonna confer I'm gonna
cast fairy fire rather than Mike oh that
kicks ass yeah yeah so he's gonna he's
gonna turn into a little hot bear he's
gonna blow faintly oh he's gonna but
first he's got to uh oh it's a Dex
that's not his thing yeah all right no
that's suck shit that's a to enjoy it
yeah it's gonna go so it's but somehow
it's like yes it does make him easier to
detect in battle but it is not improving
things like you between the moon outside
the window the house outside and now
he's sort of further enunciated in his
size and gait
yeah with this eldritch light like you
feel like that like a red fell shading
around exactly like you do there is an
advantage in combat but everything else
about it is bad I see but I wanted have
it that going yeah that's cool yeah
that's better
now we're getting somewhere yeah Genaro
it's in all right I wanted some things
Paladini and not Paladini who is the
farthest from the bear not me is
everyone up in this bears grill no one
everyone said a child I would be keeping
away yeah I got a march into a bears
mouth all right so you're the farthest
away probably all right so I want to
disengage as well I want to get away
from the bear I don't be near the mayor
okay I'm holding the kid wait he's gonna
swing on you if you leave he's that he's
that he's that big I mean think about it
think about it like this this is like a
small chapel
all right off the edge of the road I
want to throw the baby to Chris
wonderful gently no not over hand that's
crazy
underhand to to the most responsible
person in the party with the paternal
instincts that we get child care
requires I got so many limbs to catch
that and he's got yeah this baby's gonna
land in a nest of tendrils and it's
gonna be great athletics oh I'm swimming
in them yeah exactly
oh my god can't see is the one who
should catch the baby that's so blind
that I can't catch a baby in the dark
athletics
Oh baby
that baby gets rocked to sleep midair
dinar blitzen's the throw is good that's
a 25 let's see how the catch is oh I got
a I got a question do you I have so does
verifier apply in within this cube to
the baby whose decks I assume is low I
can have a new bandit on the baby
alright that's not everything know is
that I wouldn't have no cuz this is so
weird like I don't have a problem with
this at all but you definitely don't
want to have advantage on the baby and
won't give you a well I realize that
thing to do let's read the card it's a
20 foot cube yes in tacular special
because what I've been able to catch the
baby in the light but not dinar cuz I
don't want listen Garrett again I am so
so here for you figuring out some
awesome way to catch this baby my guy
yeah I'm ready to go to throw is amazing
okay that's gonna help you but you got
to figure out a good way to do this yeah
it's located right in the hands know for
the first thing to mind is that I don't
personally want to catch the baby with
my hands Bugatti seems to have that
under control so I can I love this
uh none staff and and coil up to form a
much larger shape then it's got a little
bounce to it
basket yeah yeah and that's what else
exactly are you this but ligarius rolls
are mine so this is maybe this is bad
for you okay see you got it I'll tell
you if you catch them you can eat them
yeah brilliant plan it all went perfect
so the it's like coming like it's a
surprise yeah this baby's coming for you
well you're just like who like you just
you let go of legate sort of like huh in
midair well I didn't yell first sure
impossible baby as the baby the baby is
is flying toward you you leave it up and
then you see Lagasse sort of soften and
bend and this sees the baby then it goes
and then wraps and coils almost like the
path of an electron oh yes just wraps
and coils all around and then the baby
is caught in it and then it just sails
through the air and it goes and bounces
against the back corner nice far away
okay now I can back up spinner you don't
care about me right no okay he's not
interested in you I want to get as far
away from the baby as possible with the
bear between us and then when I'm far
enough away I want to compel dual to the
bear so he's gonna be like yo yogi I got
your picnic basket right here
I just thought of that I did not like it
that you've seen this adventure before
that was just off the dome that was off
the dome all right it's been everyone
its turn singing of a funny line all
right so you have tossed a baby I've
tossed a baby and I've run away and then
I've talked about shit I think we know
you have a plan but to anybody else it
would look like the coward a child down
third act of my turn
it all comes the light exactly so he
needs a wisdom saving throw on a failed
save he's drawn to me compelled by
divine demand further me duration
disadvantage on attack roles against
anyone other than me and he's got to
keep making wisdom throws any time he
wants to get away from me what's the
safe wisdom save me throw against my you
you may be surprised to learn that we're
bears 14 like wisdoms not like yeah yeah
I mean like it's not like you know up
here it's down here the water is MCATs
grass
yeah exactly what's his myers-briggs
yeah let's see he is compelled to deal
with you if anyone touches him he will
not be okay this is me the bear you guys
are good
enjoy bye you can tell like there is a
hunger that is not about flesh in his
eyes toward this child it is only just
the thinnest thread of magic so he's
like looking over in the corner and then
like the magic is like yanking him back
into combat with you and then he just
looks over and sees it like takes a
sidestep and then pulls back so he's
sort of like he is at war with himself
about this and you you think that you
know why I do you think that you know
why okay you know that if this is indeed
a royal changeling okay that lycanthropy
as a curse Oh yep it would be a very
very simple matter okay to cure mmm
gotcha gotcha gotcha
ah so then that would make this one of
the good ones
it's possible okay it is a Christmas
story Oh obviously all right here's how
everybody else know everybody else is
chilling out so he is going to bring his
shit down on you
whatever what's your AC 18 I'm in her
I'll live forever no problem no problem
how many plates do you have 50 fucking
smartass 52 yeah let's start coming down
all right we're talking about that's 10
points off the top yeah the axe just
comes straight down on your pauldron
like it glances off but the weight of it
is just like a battering ram that's
trying to drive you into the wooden
floor but you can see the floorboard
underneath his left leg splinters but
that's not he has so many attacks like
he has so he's a weird bear um so now
now that he has come down on the
shoulder he is going to try to bite you
which you suspect would be bad and bite
proof but heroes a 1 that's how I bite
back
yeah I counter buddy when I go bite
explain um command like or no sorry dual
right you commit how he hit him if you
hit him here I'll break this fell so
basically this is me calling him out and
he has to obey spell ends if you attack
and yeah if I attack anyone else if I
cast a spell that targets a hostile
creature other than him or or if a
creature friendly to me damages the
target or cast a harmful spell on him
or if I get more than 30 feet away okay
so this is like mano a mano so we have
to like buff you buff me or buff you me
take the baby away then we'll break the
spell okay
all right here rosy bcs okay so the
Gottis got the baby true okay
just sort of like in a like a kind of
snake orb yeah sure like it bounced hit
the wall and now it's sort of rolling
away from the wall a little bit kind of
in a little circle okay and then
ligarius poked his head inside and
appears to be having a detailed
conversation with the child all right
I don't have any kinds of buffs or
healing no healing nothing I'm useless
for that and I all my key points so I'm
not gonna be able to stun him so I'm
gonna go for that baby and that baby
yeah I'm gonna try to get that baby and
now that he is focused on you is there
anywhere inside of this Chapel that
looks like a passage a door there is
where what is it there is there's there
is there are two simple wooden doors
okay I think next to each other or where
we have but one is in the back by the
put the child itself yeah and one is
sort of in the far wall that would be to
the right of this conflict
okay then Rosie will dash over and give
a thumbs up to Locati get that baby
oh so you want to take the baby itself
you don't wanna bring Locati with no I I
kind of feel like my friend needs them
to see gotcha okay so you reach down in
and then ligado just sort of folds out
like a nest okay you can grab the baby
okay grab the baby again and I booked it
through that door that's right next to
the baby quick question yeah while
ligado was conversing with the baby yeah
what did I perceive did I see anymore
that weird jaw action from duh yeah
because I'm still seeing through him
from the baby itself no I'm seeing yeah
I'm seeing through lagari but I'm seeing
what he sees oh absolutely yeah the baby
looks normal or no no what you see is
that the baby is looking out like
reaching out and ligado is giving the
baby little nips on the fingers like
gentle like a puppy yeah and then the
baby smiles and then you see rings of
red eyes grow on her face and then you
see her skin turn to a purple Sheen and
so during the fight you just hear me go
there is the coolest little bit of red
lip inside though no I keep catching
it's under I know I know I love it so
much
it's bringing me so much joy walnut de
Grasse here well that dank grass so you
push you you you you take the baby
shoulder your way through yeah and you
and inside there it is much warmer in
this area than it is out in the front
and back in here you can see a forage
that is in active operation okay and you
see a man with precisely zero shirt okay
a mythically proportioned chest okay
with only a dusting of white hair there
is a leather almost like a leather skirt
pleated studded with armor around the
base and you can see the man associated
with it
the the mustache is like mustache of the
year here it's going out and then it's
going up yeah oh yeah going on both
sides oh boy it's like this mustache
goes all the way up all the way you know
what I mean
and that man that robe he's looking in
there he's in there he's most of the way
there a stiff breeze he's he's looking
in the Forge and he's scooting something
around in it and he looks over and he
says I'll be on a second oh wait no
Rosie takes this all in and in her head
she goes another time
and and she goes father Gordon the same
there's a situation typically okay uh
have you been hearing the commotion out
in there I've got it I'm doing something
I'm gonna go back out there you think
this is the first time dire bear weapons
in skin it's the bear it's the bear
mm-hmm he starts to scoot it and scoot
it around in there he pulls out what
looks to be a tiny crucible full of a
silver liquid and he's like okay that's
gonna have to do anything
excuse me excuse me grabs it with a pair
of tongs and then moves out turns around
and then backs his way through the door
and goes out into the front room okay
Rosie's gonna stay in this Forge area
with this little baby and and she's
watching from the door just in case it's
also like talking to the baby and that
just just on pure instinct like fumes of
instinct she's like oh you're you're so
it's so exciting isn't it bounce bounce
down and then the eyes the jeweled eyes
sort of return back like in a reverse
spiral and then you see a few gray curls
walnut dan grass that's no good Jerry
you know like before we get what she is
is it maybe you could do Dan grass it's
grass I thought you were saying dank
grass
oh no I've said it lose it at least
three different ways yeah okay well um
okay so unless we want to do an
elaborate feign death where we make the
baby look dead I got plans unless we
thank you for another episode I'm going
to go ahead and enhance this guy's
ability here and a werebear yeah no I'm
gonna touch it in our opener oh I turned
sorry excuse me I'm a wolf mmm I turned
back into myself yeah uh shedding my
wolf form and I touched dinner on the
pauldron and I give him and this is kind
of a kick in the face cuz it's called
bears endurance
uh-oh yeah that's kind of a kick in the
nuts if you had to do a con check you
would get advantage on it but the
important thing is that it gives you
temporary hit points o con check for
real
boo this might come in handy give me a
name oh it's like I know something about
this guy I don't yeah oh so sorry 5hp
well it wasn't the best but maybe the
context I'll help you out
Smith hey now Christopher Stroud
emerging as though from a mr. trout oh
yeah so Locati has sneaked back over to
you and then jumped up into the air dang
it do we feel comfortable about where's
the baby where's the baby situation I
got it I got it it's good it's creepy I
don't know it but it's fine he's it yeah
it's life okay that's all I care about
when it comes to things like that it's a
1 or a 0 it's a good talk yeah you need
that you need to convey to me that help
is coming
because otherwise I'll hold action cuz I
don't wanna break the thing sure yeah we
didn't know yeah yeah yeah I guess I
will know I was like father father
Gordon is here
and look behind you cuz he's coming in
the room right now they're like if
anyone touches this bear he's gonna stop
oh do it so can I see father Gordy
emerging he didn't back out with the
tongs around this crucible he has turned
around now he is walking toward dinar
Blitzen walk toward the bear well you're
walking toward the encounter yes ok ok
ok so I'm assuming he's coming to help
so I I go oh shit and then I'm gonna
break that your duel and I'm gonna do
dissonant whispers on him oh you know
hiss on him yeah what you gonna say to
this weird bear bad things I
communicated the Bears are dumb I
whisper it but I but I also enter his
mind as well and I say you
bear you weren't even you were a person
that you're a bear how long you've been
at it
Oh ancient huh since ancient times sucks
you look like shit
you're very flammable why don't you just
give it up yeah
what she's Barry so you're attacking his
self-esteem yeah there's a save on that
right bits of wisdom save yeah that's
him vs. 15 he sucks shit okay you're
gonna love the taste of 5d6
oh my god faced and we have a couple of
these and then also will flee the space
tell us there's two but he's compelled
to duel hurt broken oh yeah break I was
gonna look through that baby again so 10
10 plus 16 oh and then one more Hey so
that's 24 him watts to him nice ah
that's a needle whispered I got in under
there I got in exactly so he so he wants
to leave he had he has to use that
action to flee yeah okay or his movement
to flee rather yes exactly the first
thing he's going to do is throw his
battle-axe at you oh that's not gonna be
good
that's thing I'd be good at all oh it's
super super bad oh wow
oh my soft boy yeah deeply soft Oh
creamy Oh a lot more dice that's 16
points
so this sou you're saying all this mean
stuff and this axe just flies in this
perfect linear progression it catches
you in the chest and puts you against
the wall exactly he he is now going to
bite Denard Blitzen before he tries to
get out
he bites you all right can you get bit
you know I need
there's something unique about creatures
like this when they bite you do you know
what it is oh what's that oh you need to
play more D&amp;D I do well that first of
all it is 18 points of damage and now I
need you to do a con save dc1400 Ben it
thank you thank you work walnut can't
save with advantage that's come on name
panic con oh wait a minute oh wait is it
um oh sorry never mind Constitution I
did 10 okay Oh No we'll talk about this
in season 2
quite me in half here is born where bear
now so he he attempts to flee to move
out but you can but his neck is craned
toward the door and so he sustains
damage against himself to resist the
spell Oh Danny wants that kid he has to
have it and then he's moving directly
toward the door would you like to
respond with an attack well if I get an
attack of opportunity I'm on yeah well I
don't like being bit
you also have advantage because he's
blowing dirty mouth yeah let's see it I
am so many advantages ma'am
hey twenty cumulative twenty you have
hit a lot of different things with your
sword but you have never felt something
like this luxurious
yes sir yeah exactly it's like the touch
the feel right your sword
basically you know it goes about you
know halfway in like it starts out the
way that you expect this to go mm-hmm
and then your sword is actually stuck
just like the other weapons you see in
his flesh okay
your sword is physically stuck within it
and you can see the wound closed
completely around and father Gordon is
like if you'd given me a minute to
handle this well can I roll damage and
so might it last it out so he takes the
he takes the crucible and he pours hot
silver all the way down the edge of the
blade okay and it runs down and cools
and hardens all along the cutting edge
rosy be stinger the cutting edge of can
I get this gonna get a reception role no
9 nope it's horrible great what do you
do
um I am still hold this baby it was a
nine
I'd had the attack of opportunity our
wait was that my turn the attack of
opportunity when you turned into oh like
real turn I don't know
yeah did you skipped it because we
weren't cut wrists distant whispers well
dude our butts and I'm just moving your
weight yeah here so yeah feel free to
attack yeah I am sore down yeah yeah go
it can i smite can I like explode the
wound and try to pop it out I love it
let's do the attack role because this
mites all tied to them so the weapon my
sword got stuck in him yeah okay attack
rollers are good okay do it I'm saying
if it's already in there wear that like
I'm on attacking yeah I'll try just blow
it up to one no you have it but you have
you have advantage thank God it's a 20
18 18 plus a so the the silver the
silver edge just slides out of this
flesh like a good butter and you were
able to finish your initial strike let's
see some damage I want to do they can't
lose that swords important you'll find
out season two bye thank you and a six
and so 14 okay nice that's very very
good you're gonna add some sauce I mean
I don't like this bear might as well run
now smells awesome we gonna throw on top
a level 2 smite 8 8 G's 420 God very
nice very nice all right the good boy
so you you finished you finish your
initial strike it slices through the
rest of the bear and then that that the
rest of the smite hurls the bear through
the back door where Rosie is standing
right oh wait the bear is no the whole
bear is still there okay all right I
thought I was leaving the buildings as
he pointed with the snoot toward me he's
snoot word all right okay so he then are
just punched the bear into the door and
now I'm staring it down
smite exactly so the door is open right
like this you have a baby yeah here is a
bear okay the bear the baby giggles at
the site of the large funny bear it's
not funny
Rosie is momentarily taken aback between
these two things obviously this baby's
got a got the priority and I don't think
the bear can fit through the door so her
she's she leaps backward as far back
into this room as she can get and and
she contemplates for a moment she's like
what can I do what they do I'm here so
you're looking around the room yeah I'm
looking at what do I say junior
perception gender okay five five nothing
nothing there's nothing here you can he
does make weapons back here okay what
what kind of weapons do I see all kinds
you can you think that he might have to
manage issues like this from time to
time okay are they silver you see a
number you see a number of silver
weapons yes okay small daggers darts Oh
wonderful wonderful I tipped arrows I
could do some I could do some darts my
darts are not silver so but I can throw
some darts so with the baby in one hand
I'd like to go over and just grab as
many as my little half finger don't
carry yeah and then put them in my teeth
yeah start taking them out one by one
and the nice how many can I throw up
returns see him look I'm gonna give you
two - okay
boom that's a nynuk advantage
ahaha that's not Nate and then that's a
ten and a twenty three twenty three is
gonna be good okay and it's not too much
it's only one D four plus three
but that's a seven that's good does it
look good there's a little bit of extra
sauce on these father Gordon knows it'll
work okay okay
walnut on grass yeah I mean
his back is to you yeah in framed in the
doorway bear boy he eats weapons it's
like Winnie the Pooh stuck in the rabbit
that yeah well you think I did just get
a text from Patrick Rothfuss oh yeah
where is he is he here is he over there
what Streep is doing he says Grievous
has just been arrested for trespassing
with the intent to urinate caring it's a
multi-level story it's very
Shakespearean he also wants you to know
that Rosie's maternal instinct would
probably give her advantage in a
situation like this
that's that pat rough no both no in fact
I said what I think is actually true is
that her level of concern has distracted
her god damn it Jerry ha ha ha granting
disadvantaged walnut done crap there's
nowhere this brand mother just Hearst
her scene ility it's just rising yeah
sure um throwing the worthless that's
the stress gramma AF alright yeah what
do you got I'm ready I'm ready I'm ready
please play I look at the bear yeah and
I say hold it hey bear
and I want to cast hold person that's a
great one humanoid because he does not
have a ton of wisdom so please make him
do a wisdom saving throw but wait you
know that's it so uh he is paralyzed for
the duration how long is the duration up
to one minute but that's a couple rounds
that's a lot of time nice cuz wrist
robbed this this this bear is growling
and panting but is apparently frozen in
time and space in the threshold of this
doorway like bears anymore they used to
respect them I have a feeling about it
either way
I'm gonna send I'm gonna send to these
eldritch blasts gonna blast him in the
eldritch way yeah let's see it don't get
the advantage that's true now do you had
are you hex as a bonus action let me
just help you out here
well I that's it's awesome but I think
I've burned my my spells for the day
before I can rest can't trip right I
think that's how it's listed yeah yeah
it's still active oh that's true I could
I move it but to a new target okay yeah
let's hexam wish I'd known that before
thank you I'm here with an audience is
pretty sweet yeah okay hexed and now
let's do - eldritch blast oh oh he got
blasted eldritch Li I'll roll it anyway
oh it didn't want to be rear old and
here's the other one very good and not
elders blast to d-10 d-10 hey I wrote
ice oh yeah no users it's gonna be a 9
amazing
plus the necrotic exactly this bear duo
does each hit get the necrotic yeah yeah
excellent warlock is kind of cool it's
good so nice so this so even though
frozen in place in the doorway when
these violet darts
strike it in the back not the bat I'm
good I'm going right the bullseye desert
acquisitions incorporated nights you can
see it shudders sort of like in the with
pleasure know in the doorway and it
stumbles in to the back room
in a dazed way and you can see it it
collapses off to the left and it's great
poss off everything that's on this table
and it collapses through the table you
look down and see what you think is a
drawing of a young woman drawn what
before he can finish the story she is
asleep he tried to gloss over the worst
parts to soften them but he knows she is
no fool father Gordon stands from his
stool leaning over the simple bed making
sure the blanket is tucked properly as
he does show as he does so she begins to
change gently she begins to suckle her
thumb whose golden scales glint in the
candle light her skin is the color of a
chestnut now and her blue ears peek out
from her silver hair her life will be
hard he knows very hard she must learn
to hold her form when she is hurt or
angry he lifts his holy symbol to his
lips speaking a word of thanks to helm
helm the watcher helm who is called the
vigilant one and to the strangers who
gave him a new life on the longest night
of the year
hey that is our Christmas special
prepare yourself for season two of
acquisitions incorporated the c-team
debuting at PAX South live on stage full
costume
and from then on expect us regularly
every week on the Penny Arcade twitch
channel thank you so much for coming
[Applause]
[Music]