oh hello friend I'm sorry I left to
return during business hours
I was just collecting my own thoughts
about the sea team's recent endeavors
it's rescuing omens sister from the
wandering crypt we thought things might
be slowing down here around the Tron and
quartier but then our first job arrived
the B teams okay true strike maybe a pen
name devised as a child requested
interdepartmental assistance locating
Brahma Lu da their cartographer as a
pair courtesy we traveled with oak to
Brahmas last-known whereabouts the town
of West bridge can we explore the
neglected Church of lysander but beneath
the church a different kind of service
was being held there we glimpsed Brahma
corrupted by some force who has sailed
the party with the X living and then
vanished walnut received word from the
Home Office that the B teams exclusive
license had been revoked and that oak
true strike was now a wanted man we
captured him dragging him back to Webb
March but he eluded us by using a quirk
of the acquisitions incorporated test
market system we pursued ending up in a
maddening fractal plane which led us
unexpectedly into the realm of the
sanguinis my patron God in protest who
imprisoned my true deity it was oak who
sought to come here paid by rival drawn
enterprises to do so but the Sangh
willis trapped him in Crystal along with
the other gods some errors were made and
attempting to free him and then a couple
of a minha bulgaricus explained that
hoax blood had been changed turning him
into kind of a deity bait for purposes
unknown
as we made our exit before the sanguinis
woke we found ourselves horribly
detoured teleported to the Underdark a
place I never wanted to return to but
capricious destiny had other plans as
our arrival was bafflingly foretold by a
dwarven king's prophecy in Alcazar
proving our case we accepted an
unremarkable mythril pick from them but
upon departing we found the road barred
by a goblin army and AM under dark druid
known as Carver a Gaul turned out to be
an a okay mind flare on a quest that
mirrored my own my new best friend's
task required us to travel into the
blackest heart of Walt's domain Gowalla
dearth my birthplace and where my
tyrannical priest his mother would kill
for a chance to kill me for my escape
but we were ill-equipped for the
Underdark
even with the use of one of galls goblin
supplicants tasty the home office also
sent help in the form of a powerful
sorcerer on retainer by the name of
Strix she's okay but I'm not crazy
better methods from outfitter and relic
enthusiasts morale we acquired drought
disguises for entry into guala dearth
and they could not have been worse
disguises but they did transmute tasty
into taste full we got a heaping helping
of that savory meat anyway House Rosalie
my former home had fallen into such
disfavor that the city condemned it to
reclamation by the wilds of the
Underdark it's ruins now home to a host
of writers one of which had been my
mother exploring the house I discovered
that my father's heresy closely matched
my own and he had cleverly hidden a
fully appointed study Arkana Klee folded
inside the blade of a knife where he
researched that which indoors the god of
carver Gaul as we prepared to deliver
our findings dinar and I were slain by a
dormant member of walnuts Grove who
shared a vision of the ancient past of
rosy and walnut and we learned that
walnuts kind and mine were once mortal
enemies pretty small world a thing about
it
the priestess Nilayam revived and Arne
myself and upon returning to the lake of
radiant mists we were able to free that
which endures
who strangely consumed all the goblins
from Gauls army turning limited gentle
green beans and ignored goal entirely
you know it's a lot to process you're
pretty much all caught up now I'm sorry
I made a mistake oh so this was the
toilet this is the wrong door Oh
across the hall friend enjoy urinating
perhaps it but if you put a sign on the
door people would not keep making this
mistake oh I don't mind