[Music]
the time as the enemy of the past
attracts the fastest women you wouldn't
make it past a second and ask the
question
play it brash and reckless to choose a
card a solution you saw was proven in
any sepulcher poker doodle become the
future it's that well said I pursue in
no mountain too steep production too
deep to send expanded then marks up to
the top of the peak of beneath they see
you they come like sharks to it while I
swim in that money blown by Carl Barks
ruin so center national parks do it I'll
send him home in a natural box with the
clothes tie the most of the parts
included
there's a lesson like a certain
confessor
but have you seeking my efficiently by
sign on the dotted line mission the
twice
shadow council may our Labor's please
you let me introduce your servants to my
right Dragonborn narcissist dinar
Blitzen
where are you gonna fucking put that for
you is it yeah bulwark a leader right
you just set it down
nobody trip on it there's a pip there's
a huge sort to the right of my right
reppin the natural world walnut dog
grass
you got your level two documents a bag
in tow of course very nice very nice
to my left not your grandma's grandma
except in those rare cases where she is
your grandma's grandma Rosie bee stinger
to the left of my left emerging is those
from a mist shroud cthe risk drow
all right now sometimes when I sit on my
massive cloak of rat flesh I
progressively slide down lower and lower
in the chair like a water slide
ultimately my suspicion is that within
two and a half hours I will have slid
under the table and will be in the front
row so where the game will continue I'm
gonna I'm gonna have a kind of gangster
lean now obviously it's not gonna stop
the game I'm just saying if you could
just get a seat open for me there in the
front for me to continue running the
game as per usual gathered friends are
we ready to begin season two of the
alright there is not a bathroom break
but I mean I suspect that some of these
fabrics are deeply absorbent and you
won't even know exactly all this it's
just gonna grease my path to the now no
no indeed now friends he heed my words
so imagine you may recall that there was
a brief period in a place a grove in
tribal where the veil between the worlds
is very very thin indeed it is a place
where Guerre on the hunter and Maliki
hold sway it is a small grove called
guerre on slumber it is a place where
cthe risk could not physically gain
entrance such were the powers that held
sway there and there was a moment of
intimacy of a sort between walnut and
Catherine's where walnut fashioned a
kind of natural couch and then you were
heaped upon one another and there was a
cradling motion now imagine that our
scene opens there and let me give you
some more details about what is
occurring in this place please do very
briefly let me give you the container
object that we will use imagine if you
will I will enlarge no the wedding of
Brahma Lu da and walnut Don grass
[Applause]
hold up wait a minute your visions
getting blurry yeah yeah so in the very
center of this growth you can see almost
a diorama of the Grove itself so imagine
there's a smaller version of it in the
center on a wide Dyess and imagine that
it is composed entirely of cake cake
Grove in the middle right off to the
side there is a beaming briella predator
a famous Baker of tribe or slapping
children who come too close to the cake
they are not allowed to eat this cake
yet and in fact she may never allow
someone to eat it this cake is her is
her is the apex of her baking career and
she may do her best simply to bring it
home with her at the end
Chris you still cannot gain entrance to
this Grove which is full of people your
friends everyone you know maximizing
their revelry potential in a context
where fun has clearly been set to 10 but
on occasion your little mouse your tiny
servant ligado sneaks in gives the cake
wide berth he has been taught his even
instructed by Greta not to try to nip
this cake not to try to dominate this
cake in his way but he occasionally
succeeds at bringing you empty glasses
that were full of wine when he
originally secured them and wet
partially eaten bits of cracker
good boy so he is doing he is doing his
best to make you feel incorporated into
these proceedings but understand that it
is in the moments before a wedding it's
very much like thee it's very much like
the hour before a an oncoming storm
there's a lot of tension a lot of
movement you can almost smell the
crackle of ozone in the air but you have
some faith that things will go according
to plan
because in your deep wisdom you have
assigned team nye adds thin they're
classic dangerous obviate er a person
whose primary skill is defeating
impossible obstacles as the director of
security for this wedding and so she is
occasionally coming up she is trying to
leave you alone as much as possible but
Rosie she is often approaching you and
Denar with questions about how things
should proceed good right she has got
real questions about how things should
go okay and so she most of what she
needs to do at this place can be
accomplished simply by a stern look you
can see that wherever she goes there's a
kind of beam that hastens activity no
one wants to get on fens wrong side so
she approaches you and asks you if you
know where and then she pauses in the
middle she says your novel effective son
is oh boy effective are we talking about
the same son I have been reading a book
about being diplomatic
[Laughter]
well that's very generous of you you're
not talking about I need to know where
drivas be stinger is because you told me
that he could be entrusted with the
Rings
okay and I trusted you against my better
judgment and now I don't know where he
is
and I don't know where the Rings I don't
worry I've got this don't worry about it
okay three must be stinger I don't see
well it's about time hey mom do you have
the room you could see Finn's hand go
for her sword and then immediately think
better of it it's like you don't trust
me or something mom it's it's like that
I am responsible enough to take care of
these rings mom it's okay everything's
fine everything's fine
grievous fee stinger I want you to show
me the Rings right now I want you to put
them in your palm put them in the palm
of your hand and show me these rings
Draper's piece no this I am responsible
for the physical security of this
wedding but I am also responsible for
the emotional security of this wedding I
happen to know for a fact that it is bad
luck for anyone to see the Rings before
the way right right don't help him you
[Music]
think that Finn doesn't know if that's
true or not make make a bluff
what is your deception am I here send
waits patiently while you look over your
shitty it's that one level of rogues
yeah yeah
she says acceptable thank you and then
she pulls back and she approaches you
dinar and she says there is a woman at
the threshold of the Grove she has a
child with her but she also has one of
the seven ancient blades I don't know if
it's a bad omen or not but I wouldn't
allow it at my wedding I would like your
authorization to allow her entrance well
she says that she is quite familiar with
the wedding party it's good she's fine
okay
she's fine everything's fine yeah she
backs oh you bet her face does not
change an inch and she backs away and
then you see her
trundle over to the edge of the of the
gathered group and she allows princess
sorsha and kronar to enter they are in
relatively plain clothes for an event of
this kind but you are aware that their
anonymity in cases like this is of vital
importance but they have done their best
to enunciate the version of Crenn our
that is optimally wedding ready it looks
like you can sort of tell me you've seen
these flowers from the area around here
you can tell that flowers have been
gathered from many places perhaps on
their journey to here and then she hands
them to you and then curtsies which you
haven't seen yet as you say is the first
time I've seen them since it's been it's
been a while yeah it's been a while
around rustler pin her down yeah it's
sort of much authority no exactly it
becomes it becomes like a golden lion
tamarin to scenario very quickly where
she's thrown up but then she finds a way
to land a little bit out of the grip and
then she is just trying to be unable to
seize all together grievous B stinger
you've got no fucking idea where these
rings are at all you don't know at all
you you know what a ring is you have
thought about this in great detail you
know that they are round and small and
that you don't have them two facts about
range I I you know magic we're magic you
like you're like calling out to me -
yeah like across the field oh he's right
at the edge you can you can you have
pure accent to make eye contact and just
wave me down and I'll and I'll get on Oh
young bee stinger yes Jesus mom have you
found a way to friends or creepy as fuck
that's not true but now that I'm in your
mind what do you have strong suspicions
that there are dark forces at play
trying to sabotage this wedding powers
that are looking to perhaps feel vital
resources like blood the bridal parties
viscera perhaps but they've started with
- ringing rings - the wedding rings
someone has used dark magics to obscure
them or or teleport them or take them or
make me put them down somewhere see I
was my mom you can't tell my mom I was
concerned about this from the beginning
right Rox I have a familiar who is
shaped as a ring holder and yet I was
not interested with these or permitted
to get my own half-eaten scraps of
cracker what were you what do you want
to do about it are these rings important
um hey I say yes say I thought I thought
I thought sort of important but
apparently like super important what
what did they what did they look like
and I hustle some up real quick using
materials I found throughout yeah can
you do that yeah that would be great
probably um like like yay big can you
see it in my mind no no don't look at
that don't look at that
[Laughter]
hold my hands up but that big okay
no no it's like the finger rings ring
ruff or off or a finger finger right
yeah you do two rings yeah four
different fingers of different people
that's numerable possibilities and I'll
do what I can I can just start making
loops of grasses no mark no no there
okay okay now don't think that suited
why okay uh thank you I really
appreciate you consulting me on this
matter of grave cosmic importance this
whole time by the way rosie is watching
rebus just like stand staring blankly
hearing actress my turn yeah mom Jesus
make some noise sometimes can I get a
real quick perception role
13 you're obliterated snow no you're not
you're not obliterated but you don't
think if you don't remember or consider
even for a moment anything of
consequence please continue right right
I okay yeah thank you thank you if you
see here's the thing maybe if you saw
shit yeah no here no kit here here here
now let me let me add a piece of
information a piece of information that
might be useful for you and the shadow
Council to know Chris can see perfectly
well but his eyes are not like the sorts
of eyes you would like to look at where
eyes
classically are on the sorts of people
that we know he has a spread of
apparently random red jewels that fill
the entire socket and then even spill
out slightly around the edge gross
disgusting
pick it up show everyone know at this
time during this period of time cthe
wrist drought can see with something
like an eye but on something I don't
have to use ligarius something I
adjacent you can if you want to and
occasionally it's fun yeah Wow so like
you've got like these magic gem eyes
going on and I was thinking can you
fashion one of them into a ring yes okay
like I went to the buffet real briefly
like just one I just I just walked by
the buffet I talked to this like half
health girl and then I hung out with
right hand a little bit like I've been
all over this place right but do those
magic eyes you like see true
you can like it cuz you I'm assuming you
have like massive oracular like all
vision you can't just ask people if they
can see through things my field of
vision is slightly greater than that of
mere mortals where your field of views
like this mines like I mean what
peripheral vision mean wha it's
incredible what I'm getting at is like
Deus have you seen some rings around no
oh okay yeah now you think about where
these rings might be think about the
life you've lived think about the person
you are walnut on grass it's me Finn
approaches you she has been trying to
give you as much time as you need in
comfort you have a small place away from
the festivities themselves you're free
to mingle of course but the Grove has
allowed you a private special place
indeed you have a place that is distinct
from Brahmas place right it has
constructed and made space for each of
you before the handfasting now when she
approaches she hands you these flowers
and you can tell immediately here can I
get a perception role uh surely you can
16 plus I don't know where is it
6 she's all flustered plus 7 so over 23
so her eyes the center core of them yes
are perfectly black and infinitely deep
and she says this is a gift from the
shadow Council and then and then they
return to their ordinary color and she
says now I have a warning for you
something to keep in mind okay there are
creatures
unrelenting creatures creatures of
infinite hunger sure who only hunt
married people no one knows why but
that's no one knows why that's all they
like and up until today you've been
perfectly safe from them but from now on
this is something you're gonna have to
consider and I just wanted to give you a
heads up I have a lot of questions
please okay why have I never heard of
these before they're completely
invisible ok inaudible no sense that we
know of and what it could be here right
now but they could be waiting at the
periphery for the ritual to commence and
then just as we have feasted they will
feast as well something to consider I
could hold them off for a minute or two
probably I mean I think I think I could
handle myself in a fight oh oh of course
of course
oh and one that gets really serious she
goes you are director of security oh
absolutely absolutely
yes oh absolutely but I mean there are
limitations silent inaudible invisible
assassins who could blame me
so what can I do a role to see if I've
ever heard of such a thing or fine no
yeah absolutely I do it can I do insight
to see if she's messing with me yeah
yeah yeah
let's see big money wha-wha-wha-what up
now she is as serious as she can
possibly be good God okay yeah exactly
well so don't dull drama comes up from
the side and she's like oh girl
and then she's like then fin go kill
something go just move away and she says
walnut don't drama doc you buddies now
obviously this you are about to enter
into one of the most sacred most
romantic contracts you can possibly sign
and I just wanted to check in with you
girl steamy oh I know I know I'm it's
everyone every little girl dreams of the
day that they sign this document and
it's like I know it's it's for the
couple to see but you okay there's this
I'm sorry I should never have listened I
know that it's just something that you
guys will do privately but know that I'm
there in spirit and if you want anyone
to look over it make sure that the t's
are dotted girl this contract is binding
yeah puts it up then she turns around
and wanders back seeking snacks some you
can see a cart has wheeled in it goes
right past you
kethry strapped into it into the place
where where the parties dwell and I've
fashioned like like some frantic veggies
of a party look just to be with like
Nativity of stick yeah exactly represent
yeah exactly a little diorama for you to
enjoy
yeah I'm watching the movement of the
the party within and I did matching it
and there is a there is a piece of
statuary wheeled in and you can see that
hair of and our dragon huh is right
there and he is he is directing he is
directing the men the incredibly hot men
he has brought with him it's like these
men and the statue look like they're
made of the same material
really so they're heaping it off the
gifts for Rosie of a ride exactly so
they are setting them they are setting
it out there and it is an incredibly
beautiful statue of walnut and Brahma
buck-ass naked do I see this oh yes does
everyone see it yeah yeah well you know
no I know and he's he's like if if you
had chosen to have your nuptials in a
proper town no they'd be peeing right
now if from me and proud
of course sure but look this is what
this is what marriage can do oh my
goodness and it looks so great and I'm
gonna use oh my god I don't have an
equipment I'm gonna use cover boobies
and but the fondue film yeah this is
there's nothing I can wall net this is
your wedding if you want to say that you
have prepared a spell I will allow it
under these conditions no it's okay it's
fine for you I do have it oh thank god
this is my level 3 spells um I don't
have an idea shoot our unit or unicorn
whip them okay I would like to choose
plant growth so that very tasteful vines
flowers come up and cover them in just
like the most dignified way without
disrupting the statuary absolutely and
then she goes the Grove blessed us
[Laughter]
he tilts his head he moves around he's
sort of like sizes it up sort of like in
a sumo way he started shifting around
the edge it's like blessings to you on
this day there are rings that need to be
found during this what's going on with
these rings
[Music]
the situation where you like look across
the group of people and you see fen and
then she's always like locking eyes with
you and starting to move towards you
can I get a perception role maybe 12 no
you think you think very briefly about a
girl that you once showered in glass in
West bridge from us underway
I remember her what's the music like
here there's not much are you ready to
provide some no way that would be a
great way to make up for losing no one
would even think I could not I could get
the band here yeah yeah exactly you two
aren't allowed to talk anymore that
dragon man I bet you he could play some
bitchin bass I never have seen one but I
could don't know what it is I don't even
know what it is already an expert but
I'm the best okay I think pretty sure
I've been to the buffet like four times
so if the rings are gonna be anywhere
they're at the buffet weight could be
deep in the pie right at the box oh yeah
I'll kind of circle the buffet like a
like a shark okay give me a give me a
perception role but yours you're
slightly scooting these trays of baked
products around that's it 30:13 that's
so low pretty much no it's it's
insufficient okay um as insufficient and
somebody but you're you've adjusted like
you have like
deeply wounded that the Chi that
surrounds this like meticulously
arranged table right your umbrella is
over and she's just moving things
micrometers left and right and she's
like no no Rosie did your child I'm on
you like a shadow like I'm very
suspicious of this whole thing I don't
think he has this I think that's a
reasonable assessment it is at this
point that you start to hear something
like wind chime the wind blowing through
the leaves of a tree sort of in the
middle distance and you can see it erupt
in green flame and you can see a month
and you can you can see the leaves take
on a different sort of timbre and color
it sort of flash like panes of glass and
then a tree near erupts in the same
flame what color it's shit holy fucking
shit
[Applause]
is that your rig does give you effect
cloud
that's that chunky chowder yeah listen
I'm disappointed in real life dude he
keeps going back for more
like I don't know if it's intact I don't
know if Pat Rothfuss vapes yeah like I
don't hear he babe hey babe you he's a
he bait right now and he's got those
ohms okay now listen
those are all the faith words we know
yeah okay we're done with that yeah we
ran out so that there is a tree smoke
rings big smoke ring on mom that's why I
was I was thinking what like that is
ephemeral and beautiful as their loves
[Laughter]
next okay mom I think you guys have
fallen in with there's a ring of thieves
I know something about thieves mom nope
I think I fear I wanted to let you know
first
uh-huh that there are as for a ring of
thieves that have infiltrated the
wedding really and they've been stealing
a lot of things like what I imagine
presence oh if there was more than one
cake I think they've stolen some cake
there was only one cake
see he doesn't know he doesn't know how
chris is really enjoying this it was a
prophecy the whole time no okay my like
okay the Rings are here the wings are at
the wedding
okay I'm sure of that wonderful I'm so
happy to hear it
we're at the wedding are they I do there
it is yeah you don't know the Friends of
as abiding as the earth itself how long
have you been here rings of made of mud
and earth don't worry your foot anything
on it he seems super competent this is
it it is though it is it's the real one
it's it the one I made yeah of dirt I
made it
of dirt I don't know throw your dirt
ring on the ground I do that I pockets
no you're not a tree yeah exactly so
situated between the place that has been
created for you and Brahma to prepare
and get into the ritual space there is a
tree in the center of the growth that is
now alight with that same flame and
every leaf on it is shining like a like
a chunk of stained glass and it's just
ringing like a bell and the tree itself
the trunk unfolds almost like a like a
flower opening and from it steps Grove
keeper in the land who you have met in
the past and she is perhaps the only
person capable of manifesting the proper
EPA ritual when as she emerges she has a
arraignment of silver and
the crown that she wears is it recalls
the destruction of the city of Mnemosyne
so there are great trunks of braided
razor-sharp wire that erupt from the top
of this crown and then come down around
and then at the base of it you can see
that Nana's ear seeds are placed roughly
every inch like this is a crown that
this is a crown that could sunder the
earth wearing a bomb she is wearing
about ten nuclear bombs that's amazing
it's bad news she so she as she she
emerges and looks over to your place of
preparation and looks over to Brahmas
place of preparation and then looks out
at all these other people who she
suspects are not sufficiently reverent
and she shouts and every tree shouts
along with her it is time oh my goodness
rosy drops the snacks off with go
through so you still can't come inside
and runs back in she can't she's front
row she can't miss it
hold on when she says it's time okay now
you did are these rings are they in my
pockets
look
when your real pockets do I do that with
dice I don't know oh there's nothing in
the pocket now go ahead and roll a
perception roll okay now I would have
taken this super seriously yes my ass
quite
I didn't keister these rings did I know
you would know that right that wouldn't
require a perception roll okay what does
it mean to keister a ring nature's
pocket what just become look you don't
want a cold ring
I wanna hand some on a cold ring it's
bad luck bad luck a ring wedding ring no
oh oh oh is there anyone super fancy
around here who's wearing rings that
look pretty much like the rings that I
should have there's got to be fancy
people here dressed up right it's a
pretty low-key wedding you know the four
stud
if you roll the dice maybe somebody good
will happen for you once we got 16 16 is
enough as you are as you are walking
toward the center of the Grove to what
you are sure is your death you feel
something sort of fall in your left boot
did I like talk him way in the secret my
I got kid I got the roughest reference
man I read your book right so as I know
it's happening right now so it's like
while you're walking toward you sort of
feel them shift in your boot okay right
so I'm real casually like real cool I
keep going but I take my boot off so I'm
kind of hopping like half way yeah half
hopping but like but like stealthy I
will make a roll for that if you need me
to no no it's all good
yeah and then I pulled the boot off
[Laughter]
and but it's it's way on the DL and I
pulled it oh man did I put one in each
you only find one ring yeah that's right
so I I I got to tuck that first boot
under my arm and then you don't worry
about a stealth roll on the on the
perimeter where I am I'm watching and I
have a hand on lagari and I just say
it's a beautiful ritual awesome I love
it so much so I get the the other boot
off and and then the sock too because
they knew this one is the fancier ring
right see it's got to be like yeah and
it's like I get that one up to Rosie's
watching all of this she's like just for
not again there's one rule at weddings
keep the socks and shoes on right so
completely barefoot now oh I got one
sock on yeah well at least you got one
sock on it's like being a civilized
person in some ways oh my gosh
absolutely got that corn change email in
B oh yeah yeah yeah that fresh foot
that's that zone walnut don't grass yes
I would like you to tell me what your
Maliki wedding raiment is oh so it's
light colors for once right it's it's
like this is like if you would if you
like went to get like the season two
figurines yes this would be like they're
rare yes figure other skin yeah so she's
wearing pastels and it looks like this
beautiful white and like gradiated like
light blues and purples oh wow and then
she has this wreath of different herbs
snow flower egrant fragrant and then
a horn that's made of the different
twigs and branches and stuff and it just
looks really tasteful and it curves up
like a like a unicorn absolutely so you
the first right it's a fresh so clean
clean No
so you emerge from your place of
preparation your myth your own your
personal miss trout and there you are
hanging on the bush the whole time ya
know you must know where we're trying to
attack the food table like Raptors in
Jurassic Park I'm going to the other
yeah
Saoirse is just like trying to sort of
like a racehorse
oh yeah I'm like just trying to put up a
kind of psychic shield between her in
this she's learned it's not a productive
way to spend her time trying to keep
things like this from happening
bad fun dance mm-hmm and it's there's a
few moments where you are the only one
that has emerged and if you think I mean
perceptually it's some millennia but it
can't be more than a few seconds and
when you see brahma emerge her blonde
hair has been folded into massive tight
braids that sort of create the base of a
black helm adorned with like Ruta Lee
sharp antlers that come up and seem
impossible impossible to wear and she is
managing it with absolute
professionalism the rest of her
arraignment is the exact moment where
fall becomes winter it is a kind of
plate mail all individual leaves but not
one type of leaf it looks like the
forest floor and it is glinting in the
late light here in this moment
as night is approaching and grove keeper
Malayan looks at the Sun that is
attempting to dip its way below the edge
and steal this moment and she points at
it and says you will not and then she
drops her hand and then she looks and
she says the rings and then she gives
you a ring and she gives a Brahma a ring
for you guys to place it and she says
this is not our custom but I understand
that the youth engage in it so Brahma
like hands shaking it's like trying
desperately to find like the right
finger like you know that in and she
like looks at her own hand and then
she's like listen my hands out and just
use a hand to guide her and then turned
her hand over and like in the only
moment of stoical miss Wilma has ever
had just slides it on first try yes nice
just like perfect like putting a mic
like right in the yeah right in the
ditch done and then she she grows keep
her nail and watches this with some
interest just like in an anthropological
way and then from her pouch she
retrieves several feet of green and red
silk cord and she brings them out and
then she she wraps them around your held
hands and they're loose like there there
sure and certain but they're loose you
can still move inside the hand fast and
then she looks at you and says your
words
oh man a lot of stuff in there I do many
wonders so I look at Brahma and it's
clear that I've prepared something and
I'm not as eloquent as most but I look
her dead in the eyes and I say my words
may not be sweet and my looks may not be
fair but I have loved enough to give and
a life enough to share and then she says
yeah nice nice nice nice
she says saying she with she has this
hand here and then her left hand comes
around and just seizes the back of your
neck and pulls you in would we like to
find out how we got up to this wedding
point yeah let's investigate it and
rebus be stinger thank you so much
Oh got her yeah yeah you know so you
have recently returned to the drawn and
courtier with a new pet now my
presumption you tell me my presumption
is that you emerged from the jungles the
hot and steamy jungles of coal salts
yeah it's a deeply erotic jungles of so
erotic a different kind of show you know
what I'm talking about its acquisitions
incorporated not naive now I have my
presumption is that you utilized your
second level cartography powers correct
so tell me the story that you told the
tiny lizard that's Sebastian that you
have brought back with you all right oh
geez okay any story you like because
it's magic and it works I think I think
that my preference would be to speak the
language that Sebastian speech
oh geez I don't know if I have that many
you do your best son whered listen take
your time okay and feel free to chime in
you from you for um so I I leaned down
to Sebastian and I go you look down him
and as you're about to speak he says
destination acquisition I don't know the
corporation home station incorporation
home station there we go
it's a a help me wordsmith he's writing
him down he looks up in Sicily
raishin raishin what I dig in my pocket
go station a gas station
yeah I'm sorry all I have is this jar of
eyeballs what I picked some grass and I
offer it yeah he'll nibble on it okay
it's gonna sticks out and proclaims okay
wonderful vacation so yeah I will I will
do that super well cuz Rosie knows a lot
of those work yeah and so the words all
end with Shawn yeah all the words end
with Shawn it's great nice and and it
takes an hour it's a full hour of you
relating this to this lizard yeah
skillful it's fine you in you know in
the in a chamber off to your left you
can hear a sort of larval God sausage
you know being consistently pureed by a
phalanx of divine angels yeah all right
every now and then like you take like
that's happening you're like let's just
let's get back to the story I like that
because that's just Jerry flaying omen
here in his game
now walnut dawn grass as I suggested so
you urea merge in your room upstairs
okay with your tiny friend you come down
you only been gone for a few days really
okay she looks remarkably refreshed he
does indeed she is only a hundred years
old it's just you know good night's rest
yeah you're glowing it's like my secret
lots of water hydration exercise of a
sex glow about you
[Applause]
well I remember that yes I exfoliated
exactly right now walnut as I suggested
before at the Christmas Extravaganza yes
jobs have come in
jobs have come in jobs documents indeed
if you were to open up your documents
there's kit I think that you would find
that I snuck I want you to open the
envelope marked one oh my goodness this
is my that's right this is acquisitions
incorporated legis this is like a legacy
gift you should put it in the show
there's a lot of stuff in there forget
that die scam oh maybe you can't yeah
yeah I don't know that it's embossed
right wait that one too late yeah
exactly
no it says WD that's right now open it
up oh no oh no here so would you like
would you like to read that or put it in
the dice tray and my god
I will put it in the Dre straight and
then I will also read it there it is
okay aid in finding Brahma Ludi a
secured value 100 PP Ranger Oak true
strike of acquisitions incorporated team
Bellerophon seems assistance in the
matter of a lost employee the
cartographer brahma secret whoa here he
has utilized all proper channels in the
creation of this task in a way that is
for him disturbingly professional oh but
it's from the secretary right okay well
I hate the idea of aiding oak but it is
for a very good cause is it is it what
I'm just saying sure she's no dummy she
probably don't wanna be yeah she's fine
and she's running it she I don't know
she's not she hasn't been the best to
you so maybe you know no I don't want to
see you get hurt that's all well I mean
we should still find out where she is
we don't have to turn her in we would
never do that I see okay all right that
sounds like a very important job that we
should do uh just you don't forget the
other jobs slings no it's just like this
you just open up the document see back
in the emptied into the stove that's all
burned up what if she was avoiding oak
what if she doesn't want to be found
ya see her then she founds out oak sent
you what do you think do you think this
is gonna end in huh he's gonna love you
know something you guys gonna get
married
that what you think'll happen that's
great it's just great it's low-hanging
fruit but I like the institution of
marriage
listen it's premium it's so choice okay
so Rosie yeah you have come down the
stairs he stretched out yeah and you
here wait introduction in production so
that's John yeah and he looks at
everyone and says Sebastian and he licks
his eyeballs yes he does that right yeah
he's great he's he's marvelous and I
take it seizes the tail and like hold
them up like introduction they just
start licking each other's faces but do
you think it's okay it's working for us
we're like you can see you can see that
auspicious as returned from the market
with things for the kitchen these days
she's wearing her hair very much like
omen wears his hair she has nine balls
yeah
completely shaved Oh on all sides you
imagine that she looks something like a
young prophet you imagine that she looks
something like profit during her
military days she's putting on she's
putting on a lot of a lot of meat yeah
she is she is she is definitely coming
into her own she had these few states
for a very long time where she would
sort of be dreaming Lea looking off and
then return or have that last part of a
conversation at the beginning and these
days she's a little quieter but there's
fewer of these sort of dreamy there's
fewer of the dreamy distance moments
that were occurring previously Rosie
likes to sidle up to to ah sufficient
and they they talk about their gains
yeah and like how many reps they can do
that kind of thing yeah they train
together yeah she reaches down and and
like holds her hand like this and you
know that that means it's time to
workout yeah she can take your hands and
then just lift you up
yeah put you down lift you up these are
those rosie reps yeah when she lifts me
out then I push yeah lift myself up
double workout exactly it's it's it's
Cirque de Soleil in the common room of
the drawn-in courtier every day you're
like a kettlebell yeah exactly
she just holds your hands like this and
you're ready to go it's like it's like
you know a lot of times when you get
away from home it's like oh your workout
regimen sort of falls apart not here no
you hear what you think it's Cory under
Winnie out front out front yeah in the
character well yeah I mean you can hear
you can hear corriander very plainly
okay I'll go investigate absolutely when
you go out you can see that the front
doors of the carriage house which is
really just like a rude Shack you can
see that they are open and you can see
someone you have not seen since the doom
gate in standing in front of coriander
okay
is it mom the spider no is it
Saint Benedictus the talking
god no is it the bony French skeleton
pin fruit no well that only leaves clad
in black studded leather - wicked claw
like daggers at his side a bow attached
to the back ready to seize you can see
oak true strike rate hey I was hoping I
was Trevor yeah dinar gets excited
dinars not here it's nice in stuff I can
feel it close this oh I know he's here
he's near oh he's so cool my my
expression goes from like open and I was
reaching in my pouch to I was like yeah
girl I got you don't worry I got reached
and reaching in for a gold piece and as
soon as I see oak the hand is on the
staff exactly and not for support no for
beating down do you um what are you
doing here I'm here for the job I mean
you should have you know me I understand
that you know doc you man see maybe
isn't what it was in the heyday but you
should have the document what we don't
need a document sir what are you what
are you talking about well I'm just
saying you're here for the job I routed
a job through the secretary and yeah you
should have it yeah what let's go wait
we have to go with you yeah we work
better alone
not this time mm okay uh did you feed
this horse Oh a promise ring doesn't
sound like something we would do no no
even a little bit who's Brahma who are
you
what's the horse oh all right I'm gonna
stand he's looking at the cart and he's
like it's probably fine
it's very it's very fine thank you
it's not as good as the one that I
wanted to keep but it's still it's still
fine how about those things you'd change
about it though right I mean here yeah
but I don't I'm not trying no I don't
wanna be friends with you miss meet miss
be stinger tell me that this graveyard
chic please call me business bee stinger
if you nasty no I'm gonna tell coriander
to bite him just fight him around the
butt no I
coriander uh I'll be like you keep an
eye on him you don't move if he moves
you make lots of horse sounds and then I
I'll go I'll go back inside as fast as
my little legs can carry me and I'm like
her okay folks outside okay just I told
him we don't want any of that mess but
he's outside he said something about
Brahmas ring he asked me if we'd fed it
to coriander yeah I thought it was like
what did you know that's ridiculous
it's ridiculous so you fed Cory okay you
seem fine it's not like chocolate or
something the fee of reminds me from
fine okay outside right now yeah my
guess is that Brahmas ring brought him
here oh well I did not think that one
through
I usually thinks me things through so
well well we we can't do this we can't
do this with him no of course not no I
look at the guys like maybe they're yeah
I look at dinar like yeah no of course
you ignoring us I like he's good at what
he does yes he's not he's flashy and
gross they're like oh yeah air band yeah
yeah he thinks he's so cool and
he's up there humming singing to himself
he's just he's he's humming oh yeah he's
he's the sort of motherfucker that would
wear his own bands shirt Oh where's
jinora is like yeah Rosie cast violence
over her shoulder so we don't have to
yeah yeah but he's like but he's like
humming to the horse
scratching like I don't like him either
but since when have has anybody liked
anybody it makes a really great point of
liking that was so funny Chris that I
actually like saw spots for a second
[Laughter]
I've been looking over this document and
it is from the secretary an and it is on
official acquisitions incorporated
stationery and it does say as much as I
hate to say it that he is seeking
assistance in doing this a hundred pp
though it is the first for your for your
use walnut it's the first time you have
ever seen platinum pieces referred to on
a piece official a station yeah like
you've never seen it this is a huge
bounty it's bonkers
I'm gonna ask the bastion like what do
you think we should do
and he goes compromise a show like
that's not a word whatever you're a
lizard
fuck do you know he talked to him yeah
he's out there given Iran do those
scratches decision is diamond let's go
feel very uncomfortable as we work with
him in a true fashion and strong
friendship know that yeah I don't I
don't like him I like walk out there and
he's given me these like he's doing his
cool songs oh yeah yeah he's like
nodding back he's like BAM and I knock
you with the staff just ask him on the
knee just I did I'm so sorry absolutely
just smacked him really hard without and
I let my silence down so we can hear a
stupid song I'm done I'm gonna walk out
there and I'm gonna walk right up to him
and I'm gonna get in his face and I'm
gonna say look we're gonna find Brahma
but she is not going with you yeah I
don't think she would what
well then why are you looking for I
you're not gonna believe me but I think
that she's in a lot of trouble and I
think that if I try to help her she
won't let me and I think if I bring you
maybe I'll get out of it alive no I
don't want to be likeable okay
additionally like whatever you come out
he's like so no yeah oh yeah it wasn't
even a fucking self
but if him only you find her and but she
sees that you're with us would she not
run away I mean doesn't that it gets the
whole point you should just send us to
do it you don't know how to find her
you can tell us and then we'll just do
that yeah just tell us how to forget
more creepy tracking devices you hit on
her it won't make sense you'll see what
I mean when we go okay
he's got me there I want to make a
psychic okay yeah that was like tapping
my temple yes you guys think we could
take him like when we find her do you
think that maybe we could just you know
oh yeah thank you oh yeah yeah can I do
can I do like an insight on him to try
to figure out what level he is it
doesn't work that way
but you're welcome to do insight all
right no not that man okay it's an 11 do
I think I do I think we could take him
as a group yeah
Rhian - that was really good
get off this call dinar we can just
destroy his mind he'll be alive to kill
him I like it
oh boy yeah you see you think you think
that you think that you would win out
eventually but you don't know if you
would all survive okay but you think
back you think back to what he's capable
of in a small space with just the two
daggers right and it's not a good memory
it was like Jackson Pollock okay I don't
think this is gonna be a fight we can
win yeah you think that he is stroking
coriander with something akin to
authentic affection I am immediately
jealous you see him reach down into his
pouch for a coin what a bastard
it's getting closer I do it I reach out
sweat him with this with my staff Wow
don't you feed her she doesn't eat that
she does that's her favorite thing
favorite thing but I'm not gonna tell
him she doesn't that's poison what are
you doing you can't feed and then I go
up to her and I make a big show of like
are you okay oh no I'm sorry about the
bad man who's trying to feed you goes
yeah yeah she's rubbing her face all
over you she's giving you a couple dry
licks with that great Ungh yeah I wait
until Oaks not looking I pick up the
coin that I'd made him drop and I feed
it to her
my horse he's like the sooner we leave
the sooner we can leave fine
you got it find a point a checks out
what can happen are you sure I think
that we need to do this job I think it's
an important job and I think that there
will be a plethora of opportunities
along the way for whatever yeah anything
could happen
you could you could happen all right
worried he's like all right on top of
problem with that that's traditionally
my station you can ride inside okay
what's these guys yeah yeah well yeah
let's get it yeah he goes right inside
he gets it fiddles with it jumps inside
is a cat it's better in here I guess
right Wow all right as long as you know
what you're doing form follows function
Rosie's grumbling there's a lot of words
coming out she's like we're gonna open
strike what kind of name is that so
stupid spelling on his real name Rama
she's not even good for walnut Sebastian
you gotta come with me on this trip I I
also sit inside but I send Lagasse up
with my vision yeah and my consciousness
that's right she up to the roof to sit
with you oh because I know there's just
an some static I'm like and I see this
is like a secret and like you know like
a secret note from first I'm like you
get it and I put a hand on legate and
it's disgusting oh yeah that guy's a
piece of shit
[Laughter]
so you're like body unconscious in the
car no no hehe has sent him up he's like
seated on the velour right smile smiles
there and then it just like like one of
those you push the bottom of the thing
in the world all goes yep yeah so he is
like like like an inchworm
he has folded up on the floor of the
cart yeah which would be fair if I was
still in that body I was that's what I
probably anything to me
looks like man like he do that yeah it's
just normal come in place that's just re
how we get in the cart yeah I just like
slide over and you just collapse right
and he he opens up this slide to speak
to you in the driver's chair mmm and he
says supposedly she is in the Chapel of
Lysander in Westbridge Oh North below it
great i slide it back I don't need any
more information from you and he was
like I mean I think the best way
probably all right we go I send you uh I
send you a message via lagari it's that
I think you can get there any faster
involving a story maybe about how he
falls out of the cart a lot I think that
the trick to Westbridge is pretty short
right that's not should I should I use
the telephone it would be a day
otherwise yeah they're fast
all right all right so so tell me a
brief story about how we get to
Westbridge okay that can involve any man
or of hijackers okay I leaned down to
coriander and I say we leave with oak in
the back but oak has terrible diarrhea
and
we have to we have to stop 10 20 times
for him to odd evacuate at least we
stopped it just feels you can see in the
glass window it's just like a meter but
like at that point like that's
impressive
yeah yeah yeah I broke up on top of it
yeah okay Wow
yeah then oh and then there was there's
one part we're almost to Westbridge and
a cart pulls up next to us and it has
it's filled with the most beautiful
elves you've ever seen and they they
look at oak they can see him through the
windows and they all barf simultaneous
like a chorus yeah they just all like a
vomit choir yeah and he's embarrassed
and and oak starts to cry and then we
get to Westbridge
so you you can see immediately as you
sort of emerge that sort of soap bubble
has formed it around in the carriage
house and you're seeing these images off
to the right you can see these beautiful
elven maidens their face is contorted
with vomit you can see the shit rise
inside that finite space you can see the
Placid face of faith like like inert but
a grim smile it's what you can tell is
that it's new it's new information and
he didn't have before and that is
apparently sufficient now but as you as
the bubble pops you are on the road
right outside West bridge and there's a
cart behind you that is that has to pull
back hard on the reins or else mash
directly into coriander's cart you are
pulling into West bridge generally
speaking you have driven either straight
through West bridge into the central
courtyard where there at one point where
two warring Inns with custom statuary
now there is a single statue in the
middle that we saw during the wedding
that was unveiled but it has that sort
of bizarre like that sort of comic book
pose where it's like somehow the bottom
somehow like the ass and the face are
like both yeah yeah exactly yeah yeah
exactly and say they found some way to
make this you know show its best asset
to each of these different places here
in the middle it's a it's a contortion
but they've done their best to make it
have a semi human silhouette but like I
say so before you've gone up there and
then obviously when you were able to
construct your wagon you had gone east
on the stone road across the bridge
you've also gone north from here to
places like NEMA's ear generis there
scholars even farther in
earth here there is a new temple clearly
a manifestation of the glory of Lysander
the morning Lord here on torille this is
this is not a this this is not a revered
place this is clearly a place basically
like this is where your tithes go
functionally speaking this is it's like
it's like the Scientology Center you
know what I mean
and it's a lot of people outside that
wants you to think levander is the best
and this new cathedral is just here down
on the south to greet people who are
coming up from places like Waterdeep on
the long road and so as soon as you
approach and open up the door oak leaps
out and he is looking with great intent
at the building you can saw he's just
sort of circling it trying to find
something immediately after him like I
want to be like yeah like right behind
him just time me too yeah I was like I
want to help so close and he's he is he
has gotten like back around to the back
like where the topiaries aren't quite
where they should be right now it's like
there so they're planning it's like this
these these are the bushes that are
gonna look great a couple years from now
this is fresh fresh yeah exactly but the
facade is exquisite and he is clear he
is plainly frustrated as he is looking
upon this what do you what are we
looking for here it's a shape there's
going to be a shape what kind of shape
he's like ah and he kneels down in the
fresh soil near these these young plants
around the back and he draws something
that looks like a crown
inverted there's a thick base the base
of the crown is obviously the top of it
in this and it comes down into five
jagged points
it's either teeth or something like that
but the the five points of it are very
very clear and he's like it's going to
look like this it can be hidden anywhere
this image can be hidden anywhere and
when we find it we're going to find
Brahma oh he's right this is weird this
is weird can I do a perception check see
absolutely absolutely so there so
because as you're looking around there's
so many like when you start to hear him
talk about it it's like you you start to
really process things that are in your
visual space like every step to the left
or right you take is slightly altering
these your your perception of these
things you're coming around the side of
the building now this is this building
is being occluded by a building next to
it that has a roof maybe that's it see
the top of this roof and then it has a
broken window like he is it's like
apophenia like you don't know if he is
correct or if he had or if he is miss
perceiving something gravely well the
the template of lysander is he's the
morning lord which i mean i could be way
off here but the there's it seems like
there would be a lot of Sun imagery
which would look if it was broken in
half or occluded somehow it would be
like the bottom of a Sun is what he's
drawn didn't even have to do no that's
clever for that yeah that's very clever
Thanks rosie has no idea about any of
that
yeah well Rosie does a perception role
to know she knows that and it's a that's
like you know the fifteen does she know
that stuff but you're basically you can
see this the Sun iconography is
absolutely plain but Lysander's son
would have to many points along the
bottom for it to map correctly even
broken for it to map correctly you don't
think that it would look
the right way okay so explore explore
the space yeah let me do a roll real
quick of what I want I said I went to
perception you say oh yeah absolutely
absolutely I just want to feel good and
I can I play the game I just wanna roll
god damn it yeah I'm gonna do so there's
there is sweat standing out on his brow
he is getting more and more desperate as
he circles this OH
as he circles this building probably
it's yeah it's just that if the
after-effects I'm feeling good no no no
he has those yes those shit visions yeah
we haven't gotten after-effects yet I
didn't I didn't I never send my story
that he was done shitting I've been
granted a kind of limited flight it's
like Iceman but shit like shit like shit
man shit me basically yeah
long story short shit man classic
classic Marvel character yes
what was your I got a 23 to my
perception role oh wow yeah so you are
so now you are circling around the front
trying to see more and then once you get
around to the west side of the building
you can see that there is a procession
coming down the street like in your mind
like you're trying to match up these
images just this in space and you can
see that there is a procession of people
singing there are sensors of incense and
they are clearly taking honored dead
from somewhere like this is this
procession this is the kind of
procession that cost money like this is
this is not a practical matter this is
this is something this is the premium
service that you can expect from the
upper echelons and so you can see them
sort of moving them like and you can see
this this is a long procession
and it's coming down the middle of the
road the one that you would typically
take to drive straight through and you
can see that it actually snakes a little
bit off to the left from the main
courtyard could i I know just someone
and ask yeah absolutely who this
procession is for this is just something
so you just not someone there just like
watching it it's like the opposite of a
parade in some respects right in most
respects I think it's just be an anti
parade and so you know somebody and you
ask what the who's this honored dead I
say people with more gold than you or me
lady okay it's all right cool it's okay
okay just a story they're not really
dead yeah this symbol is it symmetrical
oh no one we've seen not exactly okay
okay no it isn't perfect do I get
anything from it as having eyes of the
room keeper does it have a meaning that
I can discern or is adjusted its it
appears to it appears to merely be an
icon you haven't you haven't seen this
exam this configuration okay okay we
inferred some icon yeah yeah you know we
go to a lookout and know that the
buildings actually make the shavers
right can I do any kind of business
dungeons and motherfucking dragons all
right you can do it what is it I find
that I like find the thing I got it in
fact I do cuz I want to use locate
objects oh just give it go that's I mean
strong I look at it if it's a thing if
it's a good drawing I can like get an
object from it right interesting I go
right okay you can try I got you yeah
yeah you're this is an awesome drawing
so I'm gonna use locate object based on
your drawing so I'm gonna absorb this
this symbol into my brain and then it
can sense the direction of the obviously
Haitian along the object is within a
thousand feet okay
so you are taking this shape and you are
thinking about it can you are meditating
on this shape and extending your
awareness to
as you hold the shape in your mind and
begin to concentrate on it and try to
find it in this place you can see the
tines of this of this sort of corrupt
crown begin to arrive and hiss in your
mind going on in there big guy yeah so
use your words and I describe that I do
what I say what he just said that oak
get you 6 okay so you're describing this
crown is that the tines are writhing
like yeah oh yeah so tentacular I try to
I try to look for it I guess I can't
find it and then the the thing I started
thinking about starts changing itself in
my brain okay more in your wheelhouse
yeah hmm get in there get inside yeah
okay I'll climb in hop in yeah well I
don't know if I can see get it right
along it yeah what do i yeah it doesn't
work exactly like that yeah like I say
so VR Can I grab a perception check from
you Rosita a tent no no no so you can
see that from that from that distant
path you can see the end of the
procession okay in any kind of like
processional flags or family crests yeah
yeah it's it's it's all it's all
petitioners and clergy of lysander all
the iconography okay is based on that
it's all a sander could I ask someone
who's a member of the proceeding like
yeah walking folks I want to come in at
the tail end might be rude but you can
try I've never stopped me before
yeah so I I will come in and I will try
to look as like grave and honorific as
possible well here here at the end you
can find a few people that have clearly
just sort of bolted themselves on like
me it's imagine if you will a dark limbo
how spooky as hell so so these these
people they're not they are not killing
that of the priesthood yeah but they are
they are dressed to the nines like it's
almost like they are holding the last
rites again here this sort of like
wealthy caboose okay attached to the
rest of this funeral serpent okay I'm
gonna try the one who looks the most
gullible like you you use your grandma
techniques yeah yeah and I'll all sidle
in next to that person and all I'll say
oh well it is such a sad day I our
losses great here in Westbridge for this
this fine soul wouldn't you agree
I hate I hated him and oh I meet you I
deeply resent oh not only this
interaction but also the fact that I
have to make a great show of this
remorse such it is such a relief to find
someone else who also hated him Oh God
you don't even get me started fuck him
fuck him
thank you well and it's and it's twice
as bad as you think
really it's twice as bad as you think
how so because we had to front it we had
to front the money to get him moved out
of the old church God that is so him
isn't it I can't he's fucking me after
Jane years after death years after death
has it been 10 years already amazing
good yeah and that's it listen lady yeah
it wasn't 10 gold pieces I'll tell you
that much
hey you know what though I have to say I
know you had to front it but this is a
nice ceremony you didn't it's very
tasteful you did a good job yeah yeah
I know I get it I get it but when you
got to do it you do it up it's like
listen there is an inn near the church
yeah I'm really looking forward to that
part yeah that's where this ends and
that's where I'm going
that's where you're going we're gonna go
together
let's talk babe we're gonna have some
words all right
see you there what name by the way
[Laughter]
[Applause]
master work I was gonna say that I see
you go to the back of the line and I'm
like that's a very smart idea so but I
approach the center of the procession
where where the where the pallbearers it
would be in the pallbearers and I start
kind of like you know walking like then
give give one a nudge and I go he got in
there as if I was comparing like school
lunches with someone
yeah yeah what you got in there you you
give him a nudge and you think that he
here very near the end of this
procession do you think that his
strength is at a low ebb and he stumbles
for a second whip and the casket slides
straight off onto the cobble and you see
an arm bit decked in jewels and
bracelets come out the side and he
kneels and start spraying very quickly
as he tries to stuff this corpse back in
am I able to get a get a quick peek how
fast does this happen
can I help it's happening in seconds can
I help by sticking the I end of legate
in there to help right the casket but
actually I just wanna get like a dentist
mirror just want to take a look and I go
oh no whoever it is in there just
wearing a golden death mask so this is
this is yeah it's like if it's like some
people to expend a lot of money like on
vacations or like their home apparently
you can spend a lot of money just dying
yeah okay
chin up it's gonna be okay yeah he's
just like no no no he's just trying to
pull out there some using he touches the
Cuddy and he goes I'm Sebastian's
watching all this and I he shakes his
head he goes cremation
[Laughter]
[Applause]
so other people are coming over clearly
people higher up in the in the mechanism
of this church
I only ever chastising him deeply for
this I vanished somebody's yeah see you
later
Steve but like fantasy Steve I should
have just said fantasy Steve yeah no
that's actively yeah I'm fantasy Steve
find out why they call me that I'll say
you are
tonight all right to night right let's
do it
alright fair enough we fuck no
[Applause]
and I see I see what he's up to and then
I gives me an idea I get back in the car
so unbeknownst to you during this
conversation that you have had with
fantasy Steve as he is sort of branching
off and he's gonna make his way toward
this in right which might just be his
house I mean who knows oak is with you
and he says there's two fucking churches
yeah it sounds like they're moving this
dead fella from the old one to the new
one and to be honest with you he sounds
like kind of a son of a bitch what am i
confiding in you get out there dammit
oh you think maybe the other church
dammit
and he's like we're not done we knew we
need to go we need to find out where
that we need to find out where the end
of this is we need to find out where the
other church is okay I mean it's a big
city is probably more than two churches
you think this one through
all right just going from one of the
other didn't just follow them I think
they're coming from the other one so we
can follow the trail yeah exactly so you
can so you ease corriander so as you get
up into the cart corriander doesn't move
an inch
uh-oh what's up girl she goes again
we just went this morning
all right I I don't know what fuck
coriander ones gold yeah shit you break
it off there's so much get rich boy I
Anna
alright just you're gonna what you're
gonna be done horse I like get all get
mad and but I coin Xin her face okay
until it's done
eat him eat it you stupid horse I change
it on your inventory nope until yeah why
is it my money to you who knows until 10
coins are consumed what he's into
motherfucker this is oh listen it's not
eaten any platinum this is classic MMO
game design this is a gold sync we use
our real life money and give it to Jerry
but I love this plan we could buy loot
boxes yeah yeah yeah yeah that's right
Wow wait listen
obviously they say there's gonna be a
tokenized currency and we'll discuss it
so 10 coins later the dry tongue licks
those brass lips and she's ready to roll
and so you're pulling out alongside the
road you pass through the center
courtyard and then off to the left where
that procession is so sort of trailing
out you see a vision of a Lysander
Church that is in disrepair so this is
what it looks like
after they move the operation somewhere
else the old chapel looks like this
so this Lysander temple you don't know
if there was a fire of some kind or if
the fire occurred after they left it but
it is in profound disrepair
do we see if they've unearthed anybody
else or was this like the only one fit
to be moved oh no this doesn't that
procession had many but you were all you
only managed to destroy one taxi but you
could have destroyed as many as 30 it's
like that scene in Raiders of the Lost
Ark where Indies knocking baskets over
yeah yeah whoo and then so even before
the cart has stopped in front of this
place oak is out and he wipes his brow
with his thumb and he says he's going in
and he's like don't touch anything in
here just look just try to find it he's
doing slack I love it so as you enter an
era fine for this yeah yeah exactly
it is shredded just shredded pews it's
like there's a there's a bunch of
rodents more or less where parishioners
might be you don't know if now it's a
mouse church you know it's hard to know
but just imagery in here there's a lot
of blackened stone and a lot of a lot of
ruin okay like it is it is it has fallen
into disrepair incredibly quickly
friends would it be wise for me to get a
view from higher up sure oh yeah that's
in credit I love that but then I uh I
will cast fly now describe it in detail
yeah please season two I make a request
to this this God that even I do not know
the name of this force that you can see
extend a black slender tentacle down
from so far up in the sky and it finds
me and circles me and I immediately lose
a lot of control of my body go very limp
so and I can die take to the heavens
down like bait no exactly oh yeah yeah
definitely
because it's not smooth so it comes down
through a hole in what was once this
blessed dome and then as it does so it
comes down and it Yanks you up it Yanks
up your limp - all like form and you hit
your head on part of the stone coming
out and then just sort of start to swing
around inside like a wrecking ball like
coming into contact with bent
chandeliers you take for damage as you
as you crash directly through the single
remaining stained glass facing the east
of Lysander's dome through I'm through
[Laughter]
right here so yeah dish up the
perception and because you are so high I
will give you advantage yeah alright
here we go
before not bad not bad almost over
that's gonna be nice so that's gonna be
a nineteen that's very good so as you're
sort of swinging back and forth there is
a but you know sort of a pendulum motion
there is a point in the center of this
pendulum motion where the altar that a
chunk of the ceiling has sundered
becomes the shape he suggested but it's
only when it's viewed from a very
specific perspective and as soon as you
see it it's as though the symbol holds
itself there for a second longer than it
should right so it sort of is a concept
that is fixed in space it consistent yes
guys get up here so he so oak tree
strike is looking up at you as you're
swinging down and then he's like looking
where you're looking yeah
and then he stands out in the middle of
the room and he says yes yes and yes he
is loving it dress some and so you can
see it too once you draws your attention
to it this sundered altar has this very
clear teeth we can wait hello you can
see these jagged tooth light shapes and
again they're not uniform they are they
are slightly longer or shorter or
thinner than they would be if they had
been an intentional sigil okay you want
to do some perceptional nose yeah sure
you got the good perception yes oh look
at it give it a discerning eye 17 yeah
yeah it's it's cobbled together from
seemingly random shapes but you can see
it you can see it too and as soon as you
see it it's like that is it stands out
from its surroundings puzzle yeah it's
that is exactly like a magic eye puzzle
it seems like you you immediately parse
it as important so it's above us right
but just this is we're down here is the
whole place is a wreck I sit right up on
this altered sort of Dyess okay once
you've seen it now you know where it is
you see it yeah yeah
so I everyone seems to be having this
revelation and I'm looking around and I
don't I don't see a Brahma Oak seems
like you said that we see the shape and
then we find Brahma but don't really see
her no she's got to be here
well she that's my information he walks
over and he's like dinar yo bro
let's move this shit all right yes
so yes sir yeah
bro Arif oh yeah exactly don't you dare
[Music]
and then I move everything with a big
smile on my face beneath beneath these
this wrecked and ruined stone you can
find an entrance down through the Dyess
into darkness that's way more our speed
yeah okay going down yeah let's go I'm
like immediately like okay let's go
um can I hop on your shoulders in ride
yes yes deal Rosie's on my back and
we're both muttering about oak tree
strike can't believe it so he is so he
has gone down immediately as soon as
there is a path downward he is ready to
commit sure and so he moves down and you
can tell immediately that once you go
down this catacomb has recesses for
names and then plates for names that
have been ground away by time like this
is this is an ancient sort of almost
like a cistern depth it's just massive
and as you go down it sort of seems to
go out in a ring you can see that the
two paths sort of curve past and you can
and you can tell this is the other thing
that is immediately apparent is that
none of the people on this floor could
apparently afford to get placed in the
new catacomb I see there's a whole lot
of people here and a whole lot of no
gold or masks okay I mean I assumed I
assumed Carthoris could find plenty of
things to enjoy the true treasure like
it's it's like hell surrounded by bodies
but nothing to loot
that's dungeon hell so we'll be right on
oak like almost like I'm trying to like
I'm trying to pass him yeah I'm ready
first yes absolutely so you come around
the side and you can see that there are
certain points on the right side of this
path that are open and look into a
central volume of space a central sort
of cylindrical volume and as you peek in
you can see that there are tiny lights
shifting around in the deep deep bass
what looks to be a couple floors down
and you can look across and see the
layers of this thing imagine if you were
a dark cake I'm fine with it and I'm
gonna leverage it yeah so but you can
sort of see it go down sort of layer by
layer and then down at the base of this
you can see what looked to be like a
pair of like what is left of a statue
that must have at one point reached the
entire height and now there's just this
just a pair of like shattered legs and
then a sort of stone and rubble around
the base time was not kind to this no it
was the enemy yeah Wow
I think the funniest curse about this
armor of yours and it's really hard for
you to self high-five over that chest
piece as you come around to the end of
this ring yes you can see that it splits
into two stairs deeper that then go down
to the second rung of this thing do we
want to pick one do we want to split the
party you know I love that so look on
Oaks face when we we come upon that does
he seem too rich which part when we see
that there are now two sets of stairs
going down this heap well once you reach
the end yeah there's sort of a landing
and then those both sets of those stairs
just go down to the next it's not a it's
not a classic choice it's just an
architectural note meaning a picture
with your words yeah I admire it it's
gonna say sweet perception for sure
yes dungeon dragons baby alright I well
I'm the one not to do it eight no no no
it's it's dinar it's like it's fine
yeah yeah it's dark down here so I'm
pretty useless I don't know if I've ever
seen stairs before I'm so no it's it's
uh it's like a saw you would walk on
rather than do perception I'm gonna do
an hour can I check because I just want
to perceive if there's any like latent
mm-hm
anything I get us get a taste of there
she is there she is so close yeah it's
not great it's probably seven it's a
seven handsome fine three no no no I
mean this is clean this is it's very
safe and fresh you know I have the Glade
plugin
as we're getting down deeper into a
scary hole full of dead bodies I will
divine sense just to try to get a get a
little little note on this there's
anything fucking down what are you
trying to what are you trying to pull
trying to detect presence of strong evil
registers of my senses so if there are
celestial fee nan dead so have you ever
seen those novelty have you ever seen
those novelty cocktails that have them
multiple layers in it Yeah right like
different viscosities float on top of
each other exactly that's that's your
sense of this tomb you can tell that the
layer you're on exists in one divine
space and is defined by a divine power
that is not evil and then the lower it
gets down and you and you've seen this
through that sort of portal that looks
in you can tell that each layer is more
and more compromised by a profound
chaotic force just a slippery skulking
evil okay so standing next to the dead
body is in this dark hallway I'm like
it's evil down there guys a hot tip
Rosie completely misunderstands she's
like no it's not it's actually perfectly
healthy and normal it happens to every
young dragon all this down here yeah
that is what I meant also fiends that's
a separate conversation and it was the
one I was starting I'm just so confused
yeah yeah it's just like it's almost
that's like anxious okay
viscous evil just like collapsing and
increasing and density so let's run get
our weapons out yeah
do you have a cool sound you'd like to
make Chris because he still chirps even
up on the end yeah of the staff
everyone's he still has a lot to say if
it's evil down there and Brahmas down
there and when I get that okay well I
want to get down there as soon as as
possible okay so let's get going I'm
gonna do dark kruseman on myself that's
a great idea
need it real bad so all the as you get
down to this next level the torches are
alight but the color of the flame shifts
it's almost like the the surface like an
oil slick the color is constantly
shifting between a host of colors it
can't seem to decide it's party lights
oh nice yeah yeah exactly
can I get a perception check from you
Rosie you over at the ethics it's a six
that is terrible can I get a perception
role from you walnut come on oh yay 22
would you please open your documents you
satchel yes and get the legacy key and
get the envelope marked - gladly
[Laughter]
so you so as you are as you withdraw for
mother and her green light is cast it
seems to it seems to it can hold its own
against these strange torches but you
feel a little scribble inside your
document see satchel okay so I take it
out and I immediately I know that this
scribble has got to be
the secretary right yeah because that's
the only thing I've experienced but I
get this note and it's in here this is
for immediate distribution document sirs
noticed here all tears the wild card
license of team Bellerophon is hereby
revoked oke true strike Phoenix anvil
and Pendragon b-string obtained
Bellerophon are to be considered
separate and potentially hostile to
Accra is incorporated and its operations
any registered tests issued in these
names are hereby and old a bounty of 700
gold is being made available for the
capture of each member
documents are seal ohd so we know that's
[Music]
and it says dead or alive right
preferred dead you know it doesn't say
so what does well not tell us about that
yeah you waive it
no I'm yeah I immediately waive it
because I look at this and I go oh this
seems to be just some memo about new I'm
saying this out loud it's a new memo
about regulation pens that we need to be
using he's dripping sweat and he's like
see this is why I don't have a document
sir
and I'm like I asked for you guy but
then I read you the note as soon as
possible
like you know as my eyes are going over
and I say we need to take oke take yes
yes
take it in err no he's a delightful man
if you like him so much let's just let's
just we have to capture him that's what
it says here and it is is from omen and
you know that that's very important I
believe Oh H D hmm okay never me trying
- me either way I they don't have a wild
card license they're not part of
acquisition incorporated anymore
Wow why this just came through this just
now it says stop stop what we're doing
so we establish a Brahma well I mean we
should still look for Brahma but we
could just take him and leave
he's dangerous he's dangerous keep
acting like we're doing it thank you hey
papi Oh true strike is like what are you
guys doing oh we're all scratching the
same itch stay back he's like Brahma is
here okay and we gotta find her guys
let's go Oh lead the way
let's let's get her and then uh like
like well it has like her hand on like
the place where she keeps the rope in
her pocket or something just like
waiting for that Missy so she's she's
gonna try to like make a traps to to
know just like subdue him to get him
okay well so you know when the
opportunity yeah
look there's evil down there and he's a
good fighter are you yes are you saying
this outlet should capture okay I mean
he turns around and looks at the four of
you who have clearly had some kind of
conversation no way I sense the evil of
this place it's trying to take you over
to our of course we're not gonna capture
oak he's our friend cohort love you love
him you high five to him what are you
talking about dude
coworker I do and don't forget you still
as an active wildcard licensed right
official business member in good
standing press onward your you sir
yeah Oh cliff fine Brahma she said she's
in trouble let's go he gets his daggers
out ooh and breaks into a run down the
hall around going back basically around
in the catacomb to the other side the
way that we went you know now that we're
down the floor you're coming back around
the other way
guys oh you may or may not have to
capture him but house really fast he's
really cool was you hear you hear what
rumbling sounds as soon as he runs back
as soon as he runs down that path you
hear rumbling sounds like heavy stones
falling and collapsing and then it
sounds like it sounds like just like
stone on stone like not grinding but
smooth motion you can sort of feel it
you can sort of feel it in your feet
this seems like a pretty good place to
trap him if we need to but let's let's
go let's go let's run okay I was gonna
say what's the what's the span between
these two stairs like how does it work
wouldn't be able to jump over will be
able no no so basically each one each
item is each tier of the cake is
distinct with a set of double stairs on
the opposite side that go down and then
if it looks like the other one okay
there will be another path down to this
third floor I can't cut him off we have
to chase him yeah yeah okay so you hear
his footfalls and you can hear these you
can hear this Stone rumbling on the way
back okay
I feel like maybe I want to catch up to
him right yes yeah okay and I want to
get him so I'm gonna go ahead and take
this time to you're still on my
shoulders
you wild shape into a wolf oh we got
some Midna type shit and I can
immediately I feel like maybe I could do
I could smell him there are so many
powerful smells down here that's true is
walnut still corrupted she has been able
to cast spells for the last month or so
right but there the spells have been all
weird
no you she got a hold on it okay
whatever that was appears to have passed
she's on a new regimen I can get
advantage on perception you can't if I
want to sniff him out so I'm gonna try
and sniff him out that was a for Chris
get over my dice Oh fifteen plus seven
so 22 yeah absolutely
okay so yeah just it's it's perfect so
it's like there's sort of imagine that
there's a kind of olfactory Symphony yes
going on and you just you identify the
piccolo inside this massive stack of
sensory input and your feet are just
padding along this smooth stone and as
you do so you can sort of feel that
there are almost like ruts worn into the
stone floor almost like get a couple
different rings almost like a track oh I
just have this I'm just telling you
what's there I mean you know uh maybe
it's fine I'm gonna do crafts without
trace on us to give us all +10 bonus to
self to give you an umbral froude yes
you bet is it so it would be you and
experiencing it because I don't think
we're we can't can't run as fast yeah
sure it's it within 30 feet so keep up
slowpoke
what's your run speed as a as a mega
wolf's fast 50 feet oh let me ask you a
question can i I haven't ever tried to
use my tentacle fly beneath the ground
is there a way that that tentacle would
have enough tensile strength or perhaps
it could pierce through
to permit me to move at that speed which
i think is 60 I can't read through this
thing should I count yeah would you
applying speed of 60 feet right the
duration and it's ten minutes
is it ten minutes maybe I don't have
access no I think yeah I think you're
okay but here's let me try to sell you
on this concept okay okay what can I do
to get you into a flight spell today so
there is a there is this central
cylindrical volume as I've described
before where once a statue
perhaps of Lysander did stand proudly
now up above you had flown ya down and
so imagine that it's imagine that you
have sort of like stumbled sort of
dumbly and weekly down with this thread
and the same way that like a child might
tie a thread to remember where they had
been right okay imagine that once you
get to a certain point down like a
couple it becomes taut and slices in an
almost monomolecular way through
sheering the middle of this cake right
like a cheese like a cheese knife yeah
right inside the central core of this
you can see that there is a almost like
a stroke of frozen black or purple
lightning that shoots and bore straight
down through the center of it down into
the Dyess that held the statue and what
it is doing is you try to move is it is
reaching a tendril through these
regularly spaced portals and it is
reaching through and throwing you to be
caught by the other to be caught by
another tentacle and you have absolutely
no control whatsoever it is it is
basically playing racquetball with you
inside this maze and I pass without
trace yeah so you are basically like a
airborne ball of mist and shadow that is
being flung
regularly from grip to grip each time
like there's a few moments of sensation
right and then you're getting and you're
like oh no here comes again and it just
snatches you again whenever I whenever I
am returned to my senses I know to
tighten up into a ball I trust this
thing but when I am grabbed I start to
go loose again but I just do it again
only the two of you could come up with
this just because Chris wants to move a
little faster yeah but mostly crawling
or essentially talking about a Sonic the
Hedgehog type scenario where you're
moving from piece to piece love it
you're riding on this and you're like
hey what's going on hey wait ten minutes
[Laughter]
yeah exactly and then near the end of
these stairs you can see that oak true
strike is actually lying flat down on
his face oh yeah as you as you pull
around and he as you get closer he tries
to get up on his on his hands and knees
and he looks back and he's like no look
out keep to the side keep it aside yeah
and he--exactly just gonna like scrabble
is that sort of dog Scrabble on that
like yeah just like pulling yourself up
on this thing Chris you have it fling
you like right into one of these places
where the bodies are are kept right
you're welcome to just lie down and do
what do what's necessary if you like
take your end now not yet to do so he
rolls himself over and just as he does
so two boulders run along these tracks
and it's almost like they're racing each
other back and forth rolling around in
this circle sometimes changing lanes and
scooting around and then once they pass
the party the rolling stops and then
they roll back even faster and then when
they get over to you they sort of unfold
backward and look at the party and say
get here there go get here no yes I'm
dead too I belong here that's why I'm in
one of these things you're fine you can
be here if you're dead if you're not
dead that's the rules I'm sorry you
gotta go I wanna ball make it I'll kill
you put you one of the holes look it's
just a job lady it's just a job what I I
want to try an intimidation yeah okay
yes all right
13 bad let's see let's see how they
resist it okay they're like well you
could stay for 10 minutes maybe and you
gotta go you can't be here after that
you got to leave the second floor always
we regard the second floor you hear
another roll you hear another rock
deeper more profound rolling up and it
unfolds it is slightly larger than the
other two my cherry well this is
hundreds of dragons I tell you what's
happening yeah listen I'm not saying
it's bad heroes what he unrolls himself
and he's slightly larger and clearly
just from the gem eyes more intelligent
than these and he says I'm sorry about
these boys thank you they're good boys
they mean they mean the best I can tell
but they're not the brightest they only
live for ten minutes or so so they don't
have a lot of time to pick up on some of
the subtle nuances I understand now that
they took all the bodies out of the
second floor there's really nothing to
protect so yeah
hangout I guess I mean yeah I'm just
some kind of a floor to guy you know
yeah I do know what you mean
wait what's what's your name Caleb Durr
Galib Durr nice to meet you yeah these
are my sons Caleb Durr and gala girl
wonderful to meet all you boys we need
to keep going we need to pass through
down to another floor yeah and Cena
mm-hmm we also need to do we want to
delay okay do we want to capture him now
or do we want to pretend we're still on
his side I don't think he thinks we're
yeah woof woof woof woof all right we'll
keep we'll keep it going
we'll keep they'll keep the ruse yeah
our friend here and I'm like helping oak
to his feet we need to continue he's
kidnapping he's just like fuck you guys
would you get him yeah yeah look it did
the two smaller Ghaleb d'oeuvre yeah
high-five each other yeah
ah anyway so yeah we need to we need to
keep passing through do you have an idea
of like what slower down here like I
told you ma'am you guys I understand I
understand you know how it is I do know
how it is I saw two guys and there's
guys that aren't floor two guys and I'm
a floor two guy
alright Caleb's or Otis we come back up
here and you got two new boys you just
let him know not to smush us on the way
back up
oh they like I said they live for ten
minutes or so and then they you know
evaporate or break up or okay okay well
well we'll be back this way okay well if
there's any new ones up in that in that
brief window I'll try to make sure they
know not to kill anybody each of one
thing Parenthood I mean that's it's
right off it's a tough road oh you
should meet my children anyway are the
dynamics so much like summer rocks
really all right okay cool
so we are gonna I'm gonna brush oak off
but my hands are actually slightly
dirtier than he was so he's getting
dirtier now I'll inject in the island I
got it boy this Lennar I feel like are
you okay yeah she don't talk to you sure
you're safe now
no I'm listen now yeah okay I need ya I
needed your help and you got it
[Laughter]
painful he's he sort of straightens out
the straps on his studded leather and
starts it just takes one last look at
this rock family and decides it's not
for him
yeah you're welcome finds the join
staircase at the other end of this ring
and heads downstairs okay okay keep
going
mm-hmm we're we're all still plus ten
stuff oh yeah you're still fee for ooh
no as you as you reach down to this
floor it is of a distinct construction
from the other layers of this evil cake
insofar as you have reached the base of
this cylinder and you are now looking at
these massive feet from a position
slightly below them up into this Dyess
and you can see that the ruined shavings
and chunks of this statue have been
cobbled in multiple places like anywhere
you walk through here you can see that
they've repurposed this stone into minor
dwellings profane altars but everywhere
you walk down here there isn't a place
where you do not feel the presence of
this symbol upon your mind
everywhere you lock as soon as you as
soon as you move past one you can see
another variant of it here you know you
passed by another one you can look up
and you can see that the very inside of
the cylinder you can see that the
portals themselves and scraping chunks
you can see vine columns that have tried
to reach up inside here you know seeking
light have made this shape inside it's
it's some kind of a it's some kind of a
corruption that reaches beyond physical
space do I recognize the construction of
any of the
in my time beneath the soil no no this
is this is not of drow construction this
is cobbled together from the literal
remnants like the shattered remnants of
another temple and the symbol that we
can't help but see is this symbol that
this inverse inverse crown exactly and
so now and he's just looking up in this
cylinder and he's like you see it right
it's everywhere yeah I see it what does
it mean he's just a shout Brahmas name
okay okay and you can you can just hear
it and then by the time that voice rises
to the heights inside this cylinder it
sounds something like fractured laughs
like the higher it bounces up like the
echo that comes back from this place is
not true okay perception rule 19 is very
good practically 20 yeah it is you
haven't you have a perception bonus nope
no I guess your your dinner Blitzen yeah
in Iceland yeah you know in certain
decrepit churches you know ninety cents
counters place sure that's the thing
look at some video look it up right now
look it up everyone Google exactly so
peeking out from all from all these
shattered vial altars that they have
constructed you can see figures rising
each of which bears a mask that they
wear across the forehead that reaches
down over the eyes that has no
perceivable there's no way to look
through it from your perspective it
looks entirely solid and it's pretty
clear that this is a
kind of war and they've manufactured
something like an anti temple in the
face of this cistern hmm I say we're in
luck everybody these guys must be
completely blind yeah absolutely I would
love to see some initiative rolls if I
could okay
I'm old friend come on brand
I got an 18 yeah
six five oh wow oh yeah yeah well nuts
murder in it again if three turns before
we get to go okay
this is how it goes each of them seems
to be waiting Stockstill for someone to
move first and in the center
emerging from between these two legs you
see Rama Lou da with a red kerchief down
low here and you can see just up the
left side of her cheek you can see what
looks like a tattoo would if it were in
fact completely white Oh
reaching up along her cheek and when she
sees the party she zeroes in on Walnut
dawn grass and she says attack and she
pulls the kerchief up and disappears
behind the statuary it is your turn
walnut done grass how many are there
there are five five great
I'm gonna take the closest one how far
away are they there are an assortment if
you will from from basically any target
that you want in front of you you can
get to because you are still a dog I
think I am still a wolf sir a wolf wolf
nut as they say yes I'm gonna go ahead
and try and do a bite on a close one
yep Oh seven that's not a high number
great
it's a I said nipple thank you
then I um I don't pack I don't have pack
tactics unless I'm within five feet of
my people oh you read brand out well the
closest one is he Oh first of all right
I'm not writing out oh I see yeah Chris
wrists route I am gonna be do we notice
that they're waiting for motion yeah
they're basically waiting for the
command and now they ate it for the okay
well then I will go ahead and cast fairy
fire mm-hmm how many of them can I hit I
got a 20 foot 2015 box yeah three of
them yeah okay so we can go ahead and
and get advantage on tax on that hmm I
think that's it it's all I got right now
okay let's take a look at you Rosie be
stinger how many will you kill this
round so we get if we get advantage on
all just three of them you can get
basically freebie advantage hits on
three okay well then I'll go for those
three and they're dead that's what yeah
but it's a change well you you think
that you may be more correct than you
think
because as you as you approach you know
conscious meditative way to deliver your
sacred monastic arts underneath these
masks
the skin is not whole I see okay so
Brahma has animated undead and has
commanded them to attack walnut alright
I'm gonna do attacks on I'll start with
one of the ones tuck-in folks gonna be a
long round so this is going to be that
whatever the one that's closest it's
very fired and I got you and that's
gonna be a twelve plus seven nineteen
quite good so that's one hit I will
enjoy the real damage or just go ahead
an get a bunch of hits and then walk
okay that's gonna be a 25 Jesus Christ
another 25 all right dude
you know alright so we'll stop Dennis in
you know save some targets for the rest
of your party like we do get what it's
just okay so the last one was a nineteen
that's also good that's four attacks
okay and two of them are staff of the
master two of them are unarmed strike
okay
so sad the master they're both 1d8 let's
see it it's gonna be a 1 d 8 plus 4 it's
11 mm-hmm that's a 12 that's an 11 and
that's an 8 right now are you directing
them all toward individual yeah so
probably the way it's gonna go is the
first one's gonna get two strikes from
my staff pow pow and then immediately
push off with the staff and then the
feet go into the face of one and then
the other you just split yeah exactly
that's how it works so the first one as
soon as she's the first one you make a
note a mental note that the skin is not
completely covering this person right
and you make a mental note not to judge
them you know is it's not there for god
bless their God bless their little
hearts
right right exactly and so the staff wax
once on one side once on the other side
the head comes completely off oh you
then keep off of that still standing
torso and then
the two kicks on to other targets cracks
that's pretty good stuff is that all
right over the first the first one is
dead and then the other two don't like
it the other two deeply resented that's
fine but dinar blitz in time to go to
work I will also kill something
I believe it do it go to one of the area
it's still in the ferry fire hmm so I
can advantage yeah you do I'm not gonna
do I'm just gonna do a standard great
sort attack toothbrush nothing fancy no
razzle-dazzle this shopping along it's
just just right out of that right out of
the box you know that's a three
do it again try again that's a four
how'd I do
but what's your plus six so that ten no
no we're doing the work over here
yes I had such grand ambitions there I
was like oh man I'm gonna tack this on
an aniline they're mine no it just seems
like the the toothbrush just sings as it
sails and glints off of the torchlight
but they're they know don't watch don't
look at me exactly
oak leaps into attacks oh yeah oh that's
right yeah yeah you got advantage but
you rolled twice but keep going okay
thank you
see I like playing live people no
playing with live people kick-ass team
yeah I got it don't you you definitely
have it ready to go to d6 + three were
so four so nine and then of course we're
gonna attack a little less looks like
sauce on there I'll burn a level-two
that'll be a 3d eight Jesus dude no one
that's me 914 yep I was getting there my
god I knew that one I know an extra one
another eight so you know you need to so
there's the first slash like I say it's
just singing the toothbrushes coming
through just singing through the
darkness and then it just hisses at you
from underneath the mask
and then the sword just connects
straight through any living target would
have been sundered by a blow like this
to the abdomen and then it hisses again
and raises its blade and then the divine
smite just right down in the middle of
this cylinder just just smashes it into
the ground obliterating it now yeah it's
true no I killed something that was dead
it took its second life yeah oak leaps
at one of the nearer one or one of the
newer ones that is not in engulfed in
fairy fire and goes to fucking work it's
just it's like Thanksgiving it's like
it's like it's like it's like dad going
to work at Thanksgiving right on the
media spore shion's
of this creature just just splitting it
straight up the middle and kicking it to
the ground here that one falls down
hearing all these dice roll makes me
real glad we didn't attack him yeah
now if I miss my first one I was like
he's gonna be so cool I get the streak
ended I was thinking about how cool he
was gonna be probably what now the other
two bad guys descend on you walnut dawn
grass was a he was a keen interest fight
me fight me IRL fight me fight me fight
me multi attack two slashes with this
dagger and as the dagger plunges in to
your shaggy coat you can feel vital
energy like it's almost a tap like as
soon as it goes in you can feel vital
energy being sucked out into the blade
and then it pulls it out blood runs
freely from the the wound you know my AC
or anything I just trust me it's pretty
healthy oh that is gonna be seven points
of damage
yikes and it regains that health Oh
yeah good skill that yeah it ain't that
the other one also descends on you
what is your AC 1414 this dagger cuts
deep and plunges in and it just pulls
hard out of the side an arc of blood
following it that's six points that is
the rest of their turn because you ate
the rest of them
walnut Don grass how many are left there
are two left one that don't grass are
you gonna put up in this shit absolutely
not
am i close to one of my allies oh yeah
wonderful and then I'm gonna try and
bite whatever one looks healthier do a
bite yeah you ate one singular bite
that's a three hang on one more time
that's very good those jaws down on this
thing okay 65 is 11 plus 3 is 14 oh
that's very good it's hit 14 so you bite
just down right on the haunch and then
you pull your teeth away just your mouth
is full of rotting flesh as you just
spit out just slide a trailing off of
the chunk easy wait is he done oh no
then he needs to succeed on a DC 13
strength saving throw or be knocked
prone or be sad
yeah or be just SuperDuper sad no you
you pull his leg out from under him yes
hisses Chris trapper who still stands
have we have two left one with fair fire
on them and one without which is the
prone one the ferry fire the prone one
does not have the ferry fire okay okay
I'm gonna go after the ferry fire 29 the
water snake uh I'm gonna do do I just
I do see what I do dissonant whispers
yeah this on this on this guy right and
I I reach into it's rotted mind yeah and
I say you had it so good down there you
should have just stayed dead
you had it so good you figured it out
I'm not doing there is a response from
the mind this is just one of my puppets
kill as many as you like you have taken
the first step to your own grave sounds
like a plan to me
all right let's see some dice all right
that's gonna be a 5d 6 make sure I got
it right oh you've got a it's a wisdom
saving throw for it Oh frappe yeah it
sucks okay
so choice a dumb piece of shit so enjoy
yeah you're gonna love that okay
we're pullin out twos so what was that
somebody who's counting
I don't know there's one plus one plus
not his wrists drought mad enough to
kill eight yeah okay ten someone said
ten I'll take that ten sounds great to
me
yeah you're right plus four get the
replay back that's ten no it's not okay
this one more go yeah that's 15 I'll
count he had 14 nice nice
if it's determined button he says
there's a moment of me with you yes so
the head just crushes in on itself as it
pushes it's that's its hands into the
sides of its head we are talking about
rosy bee stinger there's one Lazarus one
left with ferry fire I think Chris just
killed the one with very fire yeah I did
okay there's one there's one other
freebie here laying down there prone
prone and yeah hurtin and thrown do I
get advantage automatically okay
excellent
that's what it says on my dungeon master
screen so since it's prone I'm gonna
take my sow wheat time getting over
there just really enjoy it yeah I'm
really gonna savor it
like a reservoir dogs' okay just pacing
around around them yeah that's a 20 and
I'm gonna just take the staff of the
master straight through the ribcage it's
like a pound taken two pounds now and
don't know no yuck that's not I was
gonna say it and it's so white like this
is not what we're looking for
that's 12 there's a lot of like unique
enthusiasms I feel like this is a rare
one it's rare not unheard of it's it
that's twelve twelve points of damage
very nice Denard Blitzen oh he's not
done I don't know many more attacks
oh yeah oh jeez I thought he was done -
I know listen she loosened the jar oh I
eat it up for you I got my staff planted
right through his ribcage yeah advantage
on two attacks so all right nope that's
plus six so 14 me four teams the best oh
oh well did 14 hit and we can use hit
yeah okay then I will be with my second
attack well if he doesn't die oh yeah is
it gonna say I mean don't listen don't
just go for it yeah you know six what's
gonna be nine twelve twelve okay
that's tough so so Rosa so Rosa so Rosie
has put the staff like straight through
down even a couple inches into the earth
below and then how do you how do you
come on phonetically how do you come up
and finish this off and take this sword
like a like turn it on its flat side and
just hammer this exactly cuz it's it's
hot up its up so high above Rosie yeah
you can do that without any danger to
your party member and it taught me to
it's already lined up yeah just
piledrive it and I go for the high five
exactly so it is it is that it is quiet
devastation it is yeah it is quiet here
in the base of it and the shapes and
images that you thought you saw down
here are no longer apparent when you
look up it looks as though this these
reaching vines are simply doing their
best to survive in this evil place the
the hastily manufactured altars and
constructions from this shattered stone
no longer have this easily readable
import where's oak he is wandering
around like a lost child trying to find
Brahma so you see him going behind the
legs of this statue and he begins to
just stab his knife into the side of the
leg as he's going around and looking for
her down here yeah see if I smell her
see if I smell some strawberries five no
i don't i eleven plus an 18th yeah
there is the faintest hint like that
presents the memory of strawberries in
summer
but it is no longer here okay I had
where could she have gone
what kind of exits do we see what's
going on do it come here I say like does
he know what's going on say what's
what's the deal dude it's like why is
she attacking us yeah yeah she he said
something happened to her in Scala in
the fight against it didn't in the fight
against the Tiamat cult she held out
longer than anyone would have guessed
and now I think we know why do we why
why do you saw that mark yeah you saw
the temple sure you heard the call to
attack you think she's an agent of
Tiamat if she isn't she's doing a very
good impression all right we got we need
to get out of here and we need to find
more leads and we need to get to work
he's right I don't know okay here's the
thing
I don't think I trust oak I don't know
why Brahma would attack walnut but I
certainly don't trust oak why are we
trusting his word plus he just got his
wild card license revoked so this fool
might be making it up I go back we go
back into a one-legged sorry I'm not
saying this out okay this is Kate at the
table to you Oh Kate Welsh with for
energy and we try to discern if he's I
don't see how truthful in sight yeah
yeah absolutely
truth alright you have better insight to
me okay I'll do in say it's superfast
that's Jack Jack Jack
all right well nothing then all right
I'm gonna do an inside joke then cuz I'm
hidden mega grandma yeah ooh that's a 21
you think in whatever weird catacombs
have become of his mind he believes what
he's saying now that's interesting
do I detect that there is a madness
about him
does it seem irrational
you think that he's been spending a lot
of time on Reddit can oke he would he
would we love you reddit okay
he's like get out of here we get back in
your cart so called
and we find Brahma alright my head
bitching I just OH
did it bite us again God Oh bad what is
this like lay on him aren't you a druid
can't you don't you have like some herbs
or something it's very bug repellent
yeah we should get some of that as soon
as I can see from my own get back I just
think we should use him to get Brahma
yeah he's scared like we could turn on
it
okay I mean I got command at any point
you let me know we'll need it okay we
have to clear his name
refresh no longer ah it's just relieved
let's go okay
alright we we go so he C stands at the
top of the stairs and he looks back and
he says you come in yeah watch out for
goal of derp I'm still enjoying the
mental image of him getting knocked over
by rocks
yes thanks so much guys that is the
premiere what team season
oh no I gotta do it the right way hate
that's our game for today
exactly hey I came up with a new square
though oh you did what is it
doldrum it Oh told him it's very good
Hey
if you would like to continue to join us
and have fun and figure out what is
going on with all this crazy shit it is
gonna be on the twitches on Wednesdays
from 4:00 to 7:00
PST come hang out with us thanks so much
penny okay
[Applause]
you