[Applause]
this podcast features adults using adult
language you have been warned
they were the ultimate crew of cut-ups
and no dungeon or dragon could stand in
their way
you wouldn't be the first wizard I'd
field today we were searching for a
device called the soul monger that
happens to a lot of guys yeah that's
right when I trade a certain asset older
right yeah their HP you know what I mean
like it goes down yeah right yeah yeah
it goes down and sometimes it doesn't
ever come back up what they found thanks
for the tip was a grandmother monk who
might just be I wanted to keep business
business but I'd say you're looking well
[Music]
what happens in arpan I was gonna bring
the money back
sure you were oh it's not what I thought
it was yeah it might be both think
exactly what they needed do you guys
know each other what the hell she owns a
franchise incorporated she posed
I see your contract later you can see my
contract later BRE full-on bluff to the
hair and then you have likeness it's
like one color after springing a curse
trap and the jungles of cult you caster
detect magic spell and as soon as you
cast the spell there is a pulse of
energy that bleeds out you are all
engulfed by its match all three of you
are now children versions of yourselves
those adventures you don't still get
younger they're all babies with strange
phobias you have a childhood fear of the
color purple
[Applause]
you have two childhood fears fear of
ruin or ruins so far free you have a
fear of penises
it's called Paulo phobia and it's up to
Rosie B stinger Youth blend yeah to keep
everything my children are
extraordinarily dexterous this is what's
referred to in our game ads that Pat
Rothfuss bullshit I'm not in control
here but are they really more
coordinated from blowing up in their
tiny boy faces from fighting off day
cultists the baby Triceratops comes
wandering over to your neck of the woods
and goes over to one of the wizards next
for you and she kicks it in the head
[Music]
[Laughter]
and when they encounter a lich in the
ruins of an uptown maze we believe we
know the source of the death curse that
plagues this land the soul monger yes
and you will bring it to me wait wait I
don't know if I don't know if you thing
happens a lot Jim I don't know if we
want a killer not a killer
I said I say I said Jim there's every
possibility that I have miscalculated
yeah what's your initiative they'll find
that sometimes a little help her name is
Val end rechannel mantle she is one of
the most powerful ancient legends in
this part of the world I'm not
insignificant
I'm Jim fucking dark patch
your gym dark magic of the New Hampshire
darkness can come from unexpected places
underneath the city after a ser Iraq
killed the gods of these people and
trapped them in a tomb they are below
this city now we believe that the yuan t
have a lair under the ruined palace and
we have found a back door fantastic
yeah and that the greatest treasure of
all honorable guy whose name you just
pulled me from the pillows we are allies
against a common foe who has afflicted
you and one of us as well he says of a
CEREC and I thought we were friends
is double-crossing a skeleton elf and a
snake man to cure your rotting wizard
friend yeah it's like that I come out of
the toes I'm like yeah see that's lit
just for you I'm gonna save me I can
save my friend and that will save you
that works for me drawing pictures
presents acquisitions incorporated in
theaters now in this theater right now
[Applause]
you all know me you know what I do for a
living this tomb of annihilation it's a
big dungeon swallow a whole little
shaken a little tenderizing and down you
go today I'm going to be taking these
four fine folks into the biggest meanest
dungeon in the Forgotten Realms and I
don't know if we're going to survive but
I'm cool with that
first allow me to introduce to you the
CEO of acquisitions incorporated ohm and
Ron
[Applause]
[Music]
VRE played by Patrick Rothfuss
my croelick as jim dark magic
and last but not least Kate Welch as not
your grandma's grandma rosy bee stinger
and it's been 10 years and they don't
look a day older crazy alright so last
time when we played you guys had kind of
struck a deal with the wanting warlord
Rossi see that he would give you these
puzzle cubes to get into the tomb of
annihilation in exchange for destroying
the device that is not only affecting
him but your dear friend Jen dark magic
and there's also a super-powerful Lich
that thinks we are going to bring her
the device that's right ok so that's
what makes it a heist movie didn't we
really agree to go in and die there for
clearing the way for more competent
people I remember that was the agreement
I sort of signed up hey man the night's
young also I thought we thought that the
soul monger was a dude not a same yeah I
didn't know it was the thing hold on
like a fishmonger yeah I thought that he
was like the sole longer like oh I'm
just gonna go down to the soul monger
yeah get some souls no I think it's it's
a thing it's a device welcome to the
game guys yeah so in addition to Henning
you omen a handful of stone cubes 9 to
be exact
ra's nisi offers to make sure that you
get to the tomb entrance safely under
escort by these serpent folk that's
great news because we are all babies
we're still babies you're still young
yeah baby all right cool
yeah and so you leave the you auntie
dungeon in the company of a you want a
pureblood which basically he looks like
a man but his skin is covered with these
black iron like scales well and he he
seems to sort of carry himself like
somebody important maybe one of Ra's
niecy's main bodyguards or advisers but
he's not a he's not a biped he still
he's a biped yeah my other you want to
you around you to what you see as you
leave
underground yeah dungeon there they've
all got serpent bodies their way sneaky
for real exactly but this guy no he's
basically if he wasn't wearing this iron
skin of scales he basically looked human
the folks who look more humanoid or like
lower-class aren't they um your general
perception as you make your way through
the dungeon is yeah they are generally
of a lower order but this guy is
obviously not okay and the only thing
you know about him is his name is psycho
lock before we had parted ways with like
this powerful magic II dude I'm assuming
we sort of exhausted the conversational
opportunities of getting turned back
into grown-ass men funny I never came up
that we had plenty of time to rest and
heal up though you are one hip up to
your current maximum yes which is single
digits 57 I believe you up like we're
hip points god there's just so many it's
too many it's an embarrassment of riches
yeah so you are still pretty darn frail
so do we have like a maxed out hit dice
plus our Constitution bonus no you know
that's right I roll so this for here is
for real it my Matt says yes
and how many points you have omen
refresh my memory I well I'm looking for
this number if he doesn't have it it's
probably 50 that's the deed I mean I
like one it didn't go the way I hope I
remember one yeah alright yeah so you
you could try to catch Ross and ECE on
the sly as your party is climbing on the
backs of snake men and preferring to
ride out toward the dungeon it was sort
of on the forefront to my mind like hey
you know the ruins and we've been cursed
by an artifact and so hi I am a I am a
child and to do good work for you right
for you be at my best I want to work for
you at optimum proficient we want to
deliver a great product at a great price
also I would I you stab hair down there
and now I don't it's kind of freaking me
out
all right well he will come he will
confide in you that that is beyond his
power but but you know how to fix this
right like is there like an appointment
or something a cream topical as he as he
sort of puts one of his arms around you
his scaly arms you see like his thumb
fall off that and he's like I can't even
fix myself you should definitely get it
you should definitely like get his thumb
and it's only the thumb oh and also
he also confides in you and says and
other adventurers will come I'm not
counting
you know I appreciate your candor is
this like the dungeon equivalent of
loosening a jar okay hey I'm gonna write
this on my CV as Vanguard
yeah all right so you are led out of the
dungeon across the jungle infested ruins
of omou past a vine wrapped obelisk of
black stone to the edge of the cliffs
where you see a large gaping opening and
there in you are told lies the tomb and
as you make your way inside small tiny
figures that you are you find that the
vaulted Hall above your head as you
descend into this cliff seems very very
high and there are little streams of
light coming through cracks in the
ceiling and roots and vines that have
broken in through the walls and coiled
down around the floor and your feet you
also notice that the place is littered
with old bones many of them appear to be
serpentine or serpentine humanoid in
this continuum of young yes yeah and
confronted by the outer door of the tomb
you see that there are slots in which to
place your cubes and after spending a
good long time contemplating it over you
put them in the exact configuration you
need to which I'm not going to share
because I don't want to spoil the
adventure yeah I worked really hard on
this adventure you guys a lot of DMS out
there counting on me now yeah yeah yeah
no I got it I'd like to roleplay that
down yeah finally I got it finally I got
it completely alone and as you sneak
deeper into the tomb past the entrance
door you make your way down a hall where
you can see corpses fresh ones that
appear to have been crushed
stabbed shot burnt decapitated immolated
and partially dissolved all the same
corpse this place sucks yeah there is he
had a bad cold it one of them was like a
12th level adventure so that's probably
true you do yeah yeah you know well
after that it would be like look a pile
of campfires how would you even tell
their corpses now you did not use the
word looted
[Laughter]
bodies wizard when he told me about all
the corpses I thought for sure there
must be a corpse monger down making fun
of the fact that I think I'm longer the
longer as a person we're on the same
page like and to be fair we haven't
found this thing yet it could be a
person well gather round it's me the
corpse longer yes you laddie four for me
Pat this is never good are these men
okay one okay now we're all percentile
dice yeah what it takes cat whoo 83 83
okay you find a glass vial with a bubbly
clear liquid inside of it and the top of
the vial is as a stopper with a little
heart champagne we're gonna use this to
celebrate after we have a big victory
we're gonna pop the top back in the day
you needed like to identify stuff I will
admit I don't how does it work in fifth
edition now identify spell but if you
want Jim to take a little you know dab
with his finger you might be able to
tell you what it is yeah okay yeah you
want some yeah I get a little bit and I
and I'm a little curious to can actually
kind of think about it huh yeah what's
it taste like for the future if I run
into this again I want to know what it
is yeah I'll let you both make our
context I'll let you both make
intelligence a rule of the night mother
afternoon oh yeah this afternoon
I have tasted this shit before you
believe that this is a filter of love oh
yes
love potion Micro yes and as you as you
gaze into VRE spies
[Applause]
okay I get lost in them you do you find
yourself completely entranced and
charmed by him and more so than normal
yeah gaze into Jim's eyes VRE they are
the most beautiful shade you have ever
seen in your life
they are day me and those lips those
lips my my mind so yes no how could you
not notice that you know these little
boys no note it's act the aliens
incorporated yeah and the rosy and omen
you see little hearts coming up off of
them wow I mean I I knew that you were
handsome but you and your prime like in
youth listen they're both mostly nude at
this point yeah Jim is almost completely
naked yeah the heart sort of disappear
and then it fades okay hooli took a
little like yeah yeah who fades a little
fades a little yeah you're still in
attractive yeah boy you're good-looking
young man
[Laughter]
so you gonna keep that yeah you sure
don't I'm be a team not taking sips of
random I find in a Crip okay okay as you
were masked the corpses you get to the
end of this crumbling Hall which is
break basically goes off in two
directions to the left and right kind of
forming a t-intersection on the wall
facing you at the intersection set into
it is a giant green devil face no does
this sort of map to the gargoyles we had
seen out with the heirs yes okay and the
face is about seven eight feet tall it's
made it looks like it's made of green
green copper or possibly bronze but it's
embedded in the stone it's staring at
you with kind of big staring eyes but
its mouth is a gate and you just see a
dark void inside its mouth and hanging
out of the void are two pairs of legs oh
okay humanoid looking legs humanoid legs
you see they're wearing leather boots
okay and then it looks like like
somebody may have stuck their upper body
in yeah just die like that these are
dead legs they look pretty dead okay are
they attached to anything you're not
clear because they when they hit when
they hit be sort of the edge of the void
yeah it's an abrupt end oh so they just
look like they're cut off so there may
be there may be more inside but you
can't see into the darkness I think this
is basically like a chipper shredder
formatter
I would like to use mage hand and just
reach out and grab the legs just yank it
out of there see what's okay when you do
you're able to kind of pull on the leg
and tug on the leg because of the 10
pound weight limit of the hand you can
actually pull it off
oh he's in there pretty good I reach oh
there to help I'll be like it's like I
really want to poke this with a stick
but I've got to pull it out first so you
sort of grab him by his pant bottoms and
just try to pull him out what was the
dead body
we're didn't you stand by me now yeah
alright when you do you can see that
there is a top half to this dead person
but they're all shriveled and decayed
like they they were all the life was
just sucked out of them completely
turning their upper body into just sort
of a desiccated grayish corpse husk stay
but the legs themselves are well they're
clothed yeah exactly but I mean I'm
chucking on them it feels like a normal
person laying a dead person but feels
like a dead but kind of fade wiry super
good legs yeah got legs and he knows how
to use them yeah that's weird
so yes so I think that this mouse must
operate like a mouth like a classic
mouth like a winter fresh mouth yes your
mouth ages things we need to put them in
it well it has an effect on the things
that I put in yeah well I guess that's
true to desiccate them ideally yeah not
exactly I guess I take a magical look at
this
sure mouth yep nineteen your best guess
is that this dark barrier that you can't
see into is the result of some kind of
permanent darkness spell hmm you think
it is possibly dispel a ball oh yeah I
mean is because I know about like
magical darkness is it is there a
possibility that this is magical
darkness that also turns you into a
shriveled husk is that a magic thing
you're not sensing that the darkness
itself has any there's no necromantic
energy though maybe he's just been there
a long time this doesn't look like a
natural decay I take off his shoes he's
got shriveled feet okay so he's like he
shriveled all the way something with
something Tribble him up he's been in
the pool you guys did want to get older
that's true if we just if
just stick it in for for a second yeah
it's one of these things where it's like
it's I mean obviously we need to set a
timer or tie a rope to me ya know me out
okay you guys like when I hear the ding
yeah that's when you're done when I'm in
awe just when to for just yank me out
I'd like you all to make perception
she's gonna be an intelligence check
what's didn't bode well I'm rolling like
a champion 2002 this side of the table
happened know that is 20 as well very
good
I'm a perceiver 22 you be perceived as
[Music]
[Laughter]
you notice two things one to your right
down the passageway that goes that
direction it goes to the edge of your
light source whatever that may be I
guess your lights up I have a light Phil
yeah you see a flickering green light in
some distance down there and it it's
clearly moving so there is movement in
that direction the passage to your left
also goes down about as far as your
light will shine but fairly close to you
about 10 feet away sort of scuttling up
on a root that's broken out of a wall is
a small green lizard about that long and
it just stares at you they're blinking
eyes I grabbed it all right make a melee
attack roll 17 you grab it all right
when you do it says you're a taste young
what it's French
listen that is a hateful caricature are
you thinking of frog oh oh okay you guys
heard that right yeah yeah you all heard
that we do we speak French and then it
turns you with the blinking eyes says
salutation
just you here maybe maybe his language
isn't like a language like we think of
it but maybe it's just words that end
with shun get at it writer come on yeah
it's like when somebody asks you to
write gimme give me a couple years here
[Laughter]
no it's like I can't write when
someone's watching yeah congratulation
[Applause]
and I take a rope and I start tying it
around the mouth and I'm like
exploration
[Laughter]
conformation expectation confusion
hydration and you're still holding on
them though right okay are we gonna put
him in this are you put in the mouth
before he talked that was totally cool
with it
no now it's different now I'm still
taking him over to the dark mouth of the
thing he says annihilation confirmation
it's just it's a it's a pretty cool job
[Laughter]
expediate shoes can you understand me if
I talk normal comprehension
conversation approbation I put him on my
shoulder and I kind of I kind of put him
there like is he cool to stay there yeah
he just sort of kind of rubs himself on
your shoulder okay
[Laughter]
I'm not gonna roofie this poor lizard
with the pull-up potion he looks at
Jim's light illumination now that fine
why would we why would we take him yeah
okay infiltration yeah
infiltration information information
direction expedient suggestion
suggestion he'll start to crawl down you
okay and he makes his way down the hall
whence he came follow that hey yeah and
Jim has you both rolled in at 20 as
you're following the lizard down one way
something has tried to creep up on you
from the other direction possibly drawn
by the noise Oh guys are making and you
see it is a blackened shriveled severed
hand walking like thing from the app
yeah and then it immediately tries to
rush off
okay I I would like to try to throw my
staff the master at it just and at least
disable it because I think it's a scout
yeah okay make an attack roll okay 22
okay yes you hit it roll damage okay
[Music]
okay that's a 9
all right you do you hit it and it just
sort of you've knock it over and just
sort of lies
on its back on it's on the back of the
tan okay uh it's not moving doesn't know
okay I can't want to go collect it so
that it can't like revitalize itself and
go tell on us we should pick up and
befriend every organism we are gonna
turn the tomb of annihilation into
Pokemon yeah like a shiny hands we want
to be the very best like no one like no
one
so as you pick it up it is a desiccated
rotting hand okay
what do you want to do with it once you
have it moving it's just lying on your
hand I wish I look back and I go
salutation Ellis of the lizard I I guess
I want to make sure can I do some kind
of I don't have Arkana
can I do a I can look at it yeah yeah
I'm gonna bring it I'm gonna like pull
my arm wraps over my hands okay and
bring you this disgusting rotting hands
and rule of Arcana
yeah I don't anything about and because
it could be a hand might not be yeah
yeah all you know without even a roll is
that it was obviously created through
some sort of necromancy and animate dead
spell of some kind yeah incantation I
think that it's going to reanimate or is
it is it dead
it looks like that it looks like that
the evil necromantic life has been
whacked out of it step on it wouldn't be
the first time it's dead wow yeah it's
my hand
sorry aggravation I say rosy I'm sure we
can find you another dead hand in the
tomb of annihilation that's just I mean
don't it's a it's just a hunch
we had better
you deserve a much better hand than that
um no actually I'm curious we're like
eight yeah and keep the pickup lines to
a minimum because I'm curious BRE has
acclimated a little bit and Rosie is
normally much shorter than him but like
are we of a height now yeah why because
I think I'm a little into that I don't
want to you know it's like a mom thing
well no it's like you know because
before I mean I mean I haven't really
seen you in this light before and you're
looking okay just slightly less wrinkly
I mean you always look good Rosie but
yeah you're saying this in a real
high-pitched voice wearing like boys
tighty whities canonically they are red
I just want okay fine
red tighty whities that is you know
roses into a lot of shit but this isn't
one she goes that's nice but I take this
I take this moment to reject
[Laughter]
I I do take this moment in an equally
high voice just to remind both of you
about the policy about dating inside the
company yeah yeah you not see the
handbook Mike my documentary has the
forms all filled over later Wow the
lizard is trying to lead you off
oh let's follow this lizard is that the
only solution yeah
something all things to itself dr.
Duchamp OSHA tail action it goes over to
this cracked wall and sort of runs up to
a piece of it that kind of just looks
like this odd shaped geometric
indentation dentist and it says stone
party song see there's a there's a what
in the wall now so the stones that make
the wall aren't yeah aren't like
beautiful rectangular bricks they've all
got weird shapes to them right now he's
sort of on a weird-shaped stone embedded
in with all those this isn't like an
incan stonework like this is chaotic
yeah this is chaotic and when you at
least this part of the dungeon is and
when you walk up to it you can feel
coming through one of the cracks where
it doesn't quite fit perfectly or hasn't
been mortared perfectly with the rock
adjacent to it that there is like a soft
breeze coming through the wall that's
just bad construction yeah construction
ventilation you're losing a lot of heat
through this yeah cost you in the winter
they do a reception to see if I can it's
never gonna end
two more hours of this
bitch this carries to the c-team that's
a 1919 person you can tell that this
stone has been taken out and put back in
many times yeah hmm like its it it's
almost like supposed to hide something
it's like a badly designed secret door
or whatever oh it's just like it's a
it's a poor secret door okay so you're
saying that someone like moved but
physically moved it it looks like it has
been slid out and many times can I hear
anything beyond with that 19 yes you can
hear what sounds like mechanisms like
heavy heavy stone things going clunk oh
okay I turn to the lizard I go
contraption on and he says yes all right
here so if you're gonna be I'm trying to
figure out is this is this something
that is operated by a mechanism or is
this something that can easily be
shifted so we need to examine can you
take a look at that whole secret secret
doors your secret doors I did maybe not
we appear normally this would be like
right here but I'm through my dice in
anger I was not rolling it has slap at
it okay it's perfectly slappable in the
most ill-advised I'm assuming it's kind
of like at regular human like it would
be like this it's a hole about maybe or
it's oh it's a piece of stone maybe
about three feet tall and two feet wide
and about two feet off the floor right
so I reach out yes and I start pulling
it out towards myself oh okay just make
a strange yeah remember your strength is
no longer what it used to be yeah I know
it's mine is negative three
yeah negative three modifier try
you do it you got this sweetie and I
literally this is I grab it and I start
pulling it directly and I look at Rosie
because I am obviously waiting for her
to tell him that this is a bad idea I'm
like what's wrong with you
I see VRE struggling and I'm gonna go up
and pull on vrv all right on the stone
all right three so the stone comes down
on top of both of you just both fall
back compacting on top of each other and
are now pinned underneath this stone
together that's right ice cream how much
does it hurt
it doesn't take damage to which you are
not resistant spinal compression so so
yeah yeah so I'm just gonna try to push
it off of this Mound
yeah of them so there's we have gained
entree and yes and when you look in all
of you sort of that scoubidou boo boo
yeah thing and you peer in it looks like
that the lizard has shown you behind the
dungeon oh oh this is like where the cat
that's right yes sir past members only
yeah yes we're back slay backstage in
the tomb annihilation
you can hear so there is a chamber
behind this one you can see the back
wall and below you and above you you can
hear grinding gears and mechanism stones
yes and there's all kinds of webs back
here like this place has never been
cleaned no at all so dust and webs
everywhere and you can also see
protruding from the walls or all of
these some of them intact and some of
them broken off stone
rungs they're just like little like one
foot long no no this is this is
maintenance of stone sticking out of the
wall yeah that's what the Joffrey - yeah
yeah exactly you are in the job and the
lizard sort of scuttles on the inside
wall and is now inside these secret
ducts you said it looked like the door
had been open and closed many times but
there's webs and dust back here yeah
back here yeah okay so the doors been
open but no one who's been through here
at all as you appeared out as you shine
your light in ya and see that through
the rubs some of them have been pushed
away and cleared okay creating through
the webbing these kind of weird passages
yeah like a trend or a spider type yeah
exactly like a trapdoor spider that's
not good you don't do that okay
now does it look like things have slid
through here or walk throughs yeah we
see that dust on the ground what kind of
track though you don't see any floor you
just see the rungs so this thing you can
go down underneath quite far looks like
okay but you get the impression that
whatever moves through here uses the
rungs to basically as handholds and
footholds there's no indication of
slithering okay we gotta pull this back
in so that his next team doesn't come up
behind us and show us and we're staying
in here ha okay I'll do that
how heavy is that block it's really
awkward for a bunch of kids might be
awkward for Rosie to or you know what
you get two five something I could do
was don't shape right would be two
exactly would be to convert it into a
form that I can use to bring back up
here and form correctly yeah in fact I
could make it even worse you could seal
it so if somebody couldn't come in
behind us right you could never get back
out again no no this will be our tomb I
love it I mean it is a tomb yeah this is
on branch right but but I'm saying that
I could seal it up for now so that we
don't have a follow on scenario I like
that being being sure of what's back
again yeah later
okay so
yeah stones we'll bring it back in and
then just kill it off solid nice all
right
you are now trapped in this dusty choke
wet show perfect backs off the snake
hole snake don't think that I know that
you did not that's not your insurance
policy right we're getting out of here
but we need to make sure we bring you
back to this yeah listen don't shape it
hush now it's in the contract does it
seem like moving around on these pegs is
gonna be difficult no more difficult
than monkey bars
okay this jungle gym can't believe we
didn't make a jungle gym joke before
jungle gym and now we're out of hunger
too late me can we just edit that back
into the yeah yeah well here I'll cast
on shape okay we'll get back out and
then we'll get by um you know wet plants
yeah and then I guess you could call me
jungle gym full rest eight hours and yep
all right destination yeah okay so he's
let's see
he's I mean he's basically like a
doorman for this place but he's he's a
probably knows he probably knows where
we need to go like if we can give him a
sense using words that end in tion if we
can give him a sense that what we need
is the soul monger introduction
[Laughter]
incorporation what you song proposition
shun shun let's see so okay well yeah
collaboration is also very good so
basically what we need to do is we're
trying to get in here get to this monger
whatever it might be I just grabbed this
lizard now go where's the salt locker
goddamnit I don't know this word shit
okay I sort of bulge out yeah yeah like
one of those stress balls yeah
if he says aggression I slap him there's
no escape there's no sow you were in my
room yeah he doesn't say anything about
anything while you're squeezing this can
I do the jungle gym yeah I'm gonna do it
a climate I keep talking to your lizard
that's okay too
most of the sounds that you're hearing
seem to be echoing down from below so
you think that's probably where most of
the action is okay
so yeah you can just make a dexterity
acrobatics check oh I will or athletics
if you prefer I do not that's an 11
that's good enough yeah you amble down
okay
you see here disappearing through the
webs oh yeah I'll have done - yeah yeah
yeah we'll use him like a dowsing rod
once we get down there second that's
like 28 oh yeah
next arity or acrobatics acrobatics or
athletic yeah hold on haters gym have
good acrobatics he does for some reason
I'm +6 he's a stage magician right so
he's got to be able to get into some
weird shit all right all right so you
ace it that was Jack it was it would've
been like 14 but that's fine okay you're
good again yeah I throw the lizard on
the ground no ground oh yeah I just toss
him he's the knight to the rope that the
are he's got oh oh yes your your robe
lizard goes III won't catch poor he
needs a name I need a name for the
lizard his name is
[Applause]
[Laughter]
it was terrifying be good
everybody okay none of you have
requested power words stunned alright so
you catch Sebastian Sebastian who's yeah
get some of the web's and here are so
thick you think they could practically
catch you they're not everywhere of
course but as you make your way down you
come upon what appears to be this
conglomeration of gears attached to
walls with other things like stone
Pistons going up and down and you know
in order to continue on from here you
think you're gonna have to navigate
through that bit of stone chaos that's
like that scene from galaxy no I know
exactly what it is it's Galaxy Quest
bumpers has you've gone down you notice
a little bit above you about 20 feet
above you through the curtains of webs
and the cracks in one of the walls you
see green light just sort of filtering
through as if somebody is on the other
side of the wall or two ya mean lights
that we saw exactly but you're only
seeing little flashes of it through the
cracks pink sounds like it's moving
around it it's it's above you moving on
one side of you past the store on the
other side of the mall now there's
cracks can I get in I want to look like
looter crack I want to see this enemy
what is a party yeah okay when you look
through and like there's a practice big
enough of your eye to peer through you
see you're kind of looking out into a
big chamber with maybe some sort of
balcony and then you have to kind of
move to keep up with the figure because
it's walking on the other side of the
wall parallel to the wall so you're kind
of like doing this and just put it
moving from hole to hole and trying to
get a good glimpse of it I'd like you to
make a stealth check as you do this okay
and then a perception check like this
excellent one aim twenty plus all grace
and perception it's still 14 that's good
geez what you're able to make out is the
there are two figures one of them is
taller but hunched and clutching
something around his neck whose you
can't make out like a amulet or
something and then you see he's got
crawling claws more of those severed
hands a sort of emblem over his body and
his robes and things suggest maybe a
wizard but this guy's like just you
could smell him and he's been dead like
a long time and behind behind him is a
what looks like maybe a dwarf wearing
some sort of visor or mask very similar
to the demon face you saw or the devil
face and he's carrying a torch that
burns with a green flame and the the
withered guy you hear him say no I
thought they said he was a wizard the
withered withered is he says you're not
even sure he's talking to he says you
need to send another team down to level
3 section 32 one of the traps is jammed
damn adventurous oh I don't even thought
about the maintenance they have a mate
right yeah
I mean these somebody would have to
somebody would have to oil it or
whatever right at Disneyland they got to
take the trash underground gotta go
somewhere right then he stops and he
says say no yes make lizard noises the
dwarf stands there with the torch
listens nothing and then they continue
moving the lizard three crap this absorb
the audio right so I'll I'll head back
that was kind of like up you know I'll
head back down okay Mike so yeah there's
active I just think I just saw the
foreman yeah well there's two what's
interesting is you think you may have
seen him before in a mirror or a
reflective piece of steel in razza eyes
okay this guy yeah that guy that you
talked to a little bit yeah and he's
covered in hands these hands more of
those severed hands they see if I'm
crawling all over him yeah anyways do
you want to yeah so - so I mean we have
no idea where this so longer is right
like how are we supposed to well I think
no matter what we're safer in here
yeah out there with all of the traps so
monger must be an incredibly powerful
magical item right I mean is there any
way that I can sense if not its location
its general direction make a
intelligence check mm-hmm do you have
detect magic or anything small range Oh
twenty all of your instincts both as a
fledgling dungeon builder yeah
you build them out of medieval Legos and
things like that all Wizards do yeah and
planning for the future with Ashley yeah
I'll need my own dungeons are gonna
build themselves right okay so you
believe down is always good yeah I mean
there was me I would hide it as far down
it's like place is designed to hold it I
mean here's my concern I saw these
machines I was thinking it might be a
scenario where we could block one of
these up and try to get safer passage
through this mechanism right it's pretty
clear they know everything that happens
in here if we did block it we would be
giving away our whole path yeah right
what is the cup what is the best way for
us what's the best way for a team of you
know mostly non rogues yeah to get
through you'll be fine yeah I suspect
that you'll be okay
I can go invisible if I need to but the
crushing stone blocks aren't gonna
they're not gonna care too much about
that that's true yeah that's yeah so
what necessary like looking at all of
the everything up down up down I want to
I'm gonna start building what do you
call those things we like have like a
candle and then it burns through a rope
and then the Rope gobbler yeah Rube
Goldberg machine heavy on the
contraption that will like gum up this
works in like three hours yeah so like
we're gone and then something gets
screwed up here and it draws their
attention
thanks so a diversion intelligence check
terrible 17 you think that you could
MacGyver something so that when a rope
burns away to like to a sufficient
extent it could drop something heavy
into a gear to sort of try to lodge it
and then cause the whole contraption to
Beto bung up okay so but it would take
you about an hour to build it yeah
to rig it well I pitch this and I'm like
we could do this we could count on this
going off in two hours we might be able
to play to that that is it worth the
time or do we want it just like Forge
Boulder they had I mean we're in no
danger of being discovered back here are
we're not yet and my fear is that I mean
this is the one way we know out as well
right it will draw attention the fact
that we are behind the wall given a
whole hour that is there is gonna be a
scenario where we do want to mess this
up right and this is not wasted labor
okay but I don't think we want to do it
yet oh they're so so basically we need
to push through these mechanisms in
order to continue down and guts to this
thing get through the mechanisms you
unless you have some spell like gaseous
form or something like that where you
can just circumvent them pretty easily
will require a dexterity acrobatics
check to avoid potentially being caught
between a gear or mashed against a wall
or hey I have raised dad everybody so
doesn't work right now as you know well
oh that's right
but I tried and doesn't isn't that
enough no to go down through all this
stuff yeah 16 plus 6 yeah you slip
through the mechanisms no problem and
when you're on the other side below easy
guys underneath them you can see there
is kind of a floor
you only got maybe like two and a half
feet of height above the spinning gears
mechanism you actually land on something
solid and then you see it goes off in
two directions into what are essentially
small little ventilation shafts right
which only a child could fit in oh so
clever fortuitous okay I'm gonna bring
up the rear and I am waiting for him to
go through okay and I am going to tackle
him out of danger if need be okay oh
that is great that's great news and it
will be reflected in your bonus and I -
can I do a stuff for the wind to get
through this so read to me the ability
as a bonus action I can either
- were disengaged my jump distance
doubles when I do so is that useful here
yeah I still have you make a check but
I'll give you advantage smooth Pat
Rothfuss bullshit oh okay so that's 26
no problem no problem
omen yes lawyers have to it's gonna move
a lot faster - okay any danger to you
o'clock right
so my dexterity Akram is negative one so
we're looking for the big role yeah yeah
on this and so seeing him I literally
I'm gonna like I get my foot planted on
something which off and I'm ready to
like bury that axe oh yeah all right
it's like I'm watching the cone to keep
cool cool and just like I will let you
get through them if you prefer with
another skill if you're trying to track
higher patterns intelligence oh do you
have an applicable skill perception
maybe perception Michael perception is
is +8 hey yeah yeah so accessing cycle
yeah exactly I watch this thing for a
couple cycles and then I sort of time a
sort of time a song to it exactly
exactly it's like it's like a Mario
jumpers yeah and it's just like I'm
tapping and getting ready to do it and
then I go that is 17 yeah yes yeah okay
good
I see him just step out and then step
again I'm like what and I absolutely
body tackle him all the way through okay
cuz I'm I'm primed I'm sure I'm gonna
have to save his Jerry I'd like you to
roll again same thing sitting current
yeah I scream I'm like I got you don't
whine no no no I'm fine what you're
telling me is you anticipated my fucking
up exactly Feige if he jumps in he jumps
in after me and I'm doing the step so
instead of like running through like gym
yeah or instead of just sailing through
like Rosie I'm taking like one or two
steps it's almost like a waltz your guy
dude and so then he comes in and then
he's like I got you and then I just take
him under my arm like this
[Laughter]
VRE I treasure you as an employer you as
an employee if you make any move inside
this process I do not specifically
authorize we will both be killed as a
result two three one two
exactly and then we get to doing we get
to the end of it and I get this passed
it out and I spin a little bit and then
I
[Laughter]
but I take three steps down they're safe
all right we're next nice this is
actually a good time to remind you that
we have some tokens here yellow children
mathilde the kids notice we're using to
basically serve a mechanic in this game
which is a get out of trouble mechanic
so for kids or kit for kids or kids at
heart for kids at heart to really up yes
everybody gets to play and these so
that's a pool and if you need to get out
of trouble
you can take one yeah and so it's
basically we can use these to buy cool
RP things right yes and don't involve a
fucking liquefied or if you're gonna get
smooshed by something yeah okay your
other way to get out of that okay so
you're all down below you've got a vent
going off in one direction and event
going off in the opposite direction and
loud machinery above your head really no
down they're both they're both kind of
going off laterally okay um but you you
feel more air coming from one than the
other so it's sort of there's a flow
under here I would like to sit right in
the middle okay and sort of try to focus
and see if I can just like sit
cross-legged yeah and I tell them to
shut up just let me focus for a second
yeah concentration concentration Jack
plus our cannon that's eight so 1920 you
think it's probably better to go with
the flow yeah my guess I feel I guess is
that the air is B is coming in and needs
to get down into the lower power so we
get down get down get down
jungle boogie okay
right yeah so we need so whenever we
have a whenever we have a question a
question that the lizard cannot answer
then we need to follow the air okay I
guess as you make your way following the
air you see it kind of slopes down into
a little bit of a slide not enough that
you'll lose your footing but it does it
does slant down yeah and then it opens
into a large hockey puck shaped room see
I got fucked on this puck stuff last
time
it's just shaped like that it's shaped
like that so it's a disc shaped room
with some height to it and you're coming
out near the top of it there are more of
these stone rods coming out of the wall
so you can lower yourself down to the
floor but then there are also Nets
strung out at various points to catch
creatures or things that fall but there
is something in the ceiling some large
rig that looks like a wheel or a giant
gear attached to other gears that seems
to move what may be a hallway or
something oh it's gonna be a part of a
maze yeah so there's like it's actually
moving parts of the dungeon and it's
making a huge tyrannical sound that
fills the room but this chamber that
we're in does it have a floor you said
we can't yes yeah it does have a floor
below you it's sort of it's dusty there
are weird blocks and columns coming out
of it attached to gears and things this
is all meant to be part of the apparatus
under what seems to be a chamber a
series of passages that move around yes
the whole thing I'm sorry is this
intended to be the thing that catches
the adventurers when they fall into them
no you think it's for mechanics so when
they're upscaling around on the ceiling
trying to its OSHA OSHA yeah yeah it
basically catches them if they fall so
they're security nets okay you see a
door similar to what we came out of on
the opposite side of this chamber you
can see what appears to be a chute or a
square hole in the middle of the floor
about how big it's like a ladder chute
so it's not very big maybe
a half-two PA so it's basically we can
use that yeah thank you and you can see
the iron rungs of the ladder poking up
and then descending down into it down if
we're heading down oh no gasps oh good
right do a quick perception check to
make sure there's not some kind of trap
going on it absolutely this is all a
little too convenient is it lit you know
no you've just got your little light
yeah kind of shiny okay I'll make one
okay Rosie you don't see anything and
it's so loud in here you couldn't
possibly hear anything ten is all I got
okay I'm more curious not about traps
but like somebody like has like a worker
is like hold up here or doing something
quietly in a corner and we don't see him
until we come out yeah lunch break lunch
break not persuasion fifteen okay and
did you want to make a check as well I
think I'm better now as I'll get you
something after these performances
twenty-seven all right you two can see
that there are two dwarves up in the top
works they're both wearing these sort of
bronze green double masks with horns
covering their visitors now that you can
catch it a little bit more of a glimpse
of them they've got they're almost like
albino they're so pale or grey oh yeah
yeah no light and the other thing that
you notice is hanging down strategically
from the ceiling on chains are Gothic
chandeliers but now you're not lit not
lit but do they have candles in them
their candles are all kind of melted
down so they're kind of dripping with
wax but they don't have any lit candles
or light able candles on them right now
okay right there that might actually be
candle stumps you can't tell with like a
little bit of a wick or anything left on
them if there is it's really low okay
all right well I can't I mean I can't
mmm I can't try to stop you like that's
it's not right like as a friend what I
I'm making elaborate I'm like
we're like weenie wants you to bond it
yeah he wants me to make a bunch and
it's a long drop down to the floor it's
about 20 feet down from where you are
would that seem like they would catch us
yes okay yeah yeah and but also like
we're in full view of them I want yeah I
want to take a few steps back yeah from
them and is this is this thing that
we're in tall enough for me to stand up
in as a child or am I just crawling in
here you're crawling in here you have to
go out into the room okay you guys want
to fight these dudes we can do that but
I can also do pass of that trace which
will give us plus all +10 to stealth I
would say if we can sneak by these yes I
think you can give us all that Plus yeah
rates from asking you and your
companions from detection for the
duration each creature which is an hour
each creature you choose within 30 feet
of you including you has a +10 bonus to
dexterity stealth checks that can't be
tracked except by magical means lost and
that's pretty solid
I mean bet so but I feel like this is I
feel like this is if we don't have to
expend our one hit point yeah you don't
have to fight them I say we don't okay a
stealth mission now that said if maybe
they go first there's two of them up
there you and I probably have the chance
if they're spotted till I close the
distance and we can just like you know
oh come on Joe chromatic before they
make too much noise okay and as you sort
of as she's casting the spell and yours
keeping an eye on them you can see that
they've got like little rigs and things
like belts with ropes and they're sort
of hooking themselves onto the ceiling
as they move across oh you have to fix
certain stuff yeah like exactly you
imagine that that corridor that's
spinning corridor like what it must have
to get oiled every day yeah Oh daily so
you're super stealthy yes you begin to
lower yourselves down as you cross as
you lower yourself down or land in nets
and then tumble off and then make your
way to the ladder going down the chute
everybody make a stealth check to see if
you are if you pass on your active at
attends you're not your normal role 24
beautiful you are a ghost
don't worry that's a 21 you need to
understand this roseyd Stingers MLG yeah
hey 19
yeah very good oh yeah 36 down you go
yeah geez not bad
so what order you're just gonna descend
this chef because you kind of go in
single file I'm gonna go down first okay
how many bringing up the rear okay
probably I'm second yeah third all right
you descend down this shaft and it goes
down quite a ways there are some side
ventilators that you can basically go
into if you want to but when you reach
the very bottom it comes to a stone
floor and it looks like the stone is a
plug that can be pried up yeah yeah yeah
it's a it's basically a manhole cover
yes okay yes that's there's nothing else
in this space no just dust and cobwebs
can you don't shoot you're the first one
yeah you're the one who can probably
reach the plug and there's an iron
handle on it you can try to heave it up
[Music]
down ahead of you it's a six seems like
a stone plug I would I actually want to
scope it out more it's like has this
been opened recently like is this in any
way part of the regular service corridor
and it's functional like the other thing
or is this yeah are you supposed to
actually take one of those upper off
branches right and not do this where is
this gonna like we pull it up and this
is the thing that attaches the top of
the chandelier in dudes bedroom yeah
yeah it could be a situation where it's
like the can of snakes but they're all
but instead of like Springs there's like
snakes yeah
right you're expecting to be like that
and then but you think they would put
traps backstage I would that's true yeah
little tester you you went to you look
yeah I got a psych job I just want to
see how 25 yeah that's very good you
believe that this is a maintenance
access point that it hasn't been opened
in a long time okay
a while at least months okay so like I
think we're we're okay but it is down
exactly you may need to you may need to
pry this with the staff of the master
like I think it I think it's it might be
something where we mean is it designed
to you slide out easily like if I go
over and just grab this metal handle if
you think it's you think it's heavy
hmm like a burly dwarf or somebody could
pop it up yeah exactly
did you blow stone shape no I've got
more sun shade but let's just but this
really is it this really is a cap yeah
we should be able to get it I'm just
thinking that the acquisitions in corpus
just made up strong so it's just heavy
sorry and it's like a plug so you kind
of have to lift it up yeah like a
manhole take it to the side I'm not much
for strength but since I'm using the
staff of the master can I can I get some
kind of advantage on the the pry bar
yeah you have a tool you can use yes
advantage which I used X for that are
strengths that be strength okay so
that's gonna be either a 16 or oh I
would take that one yeah do the second
one the second one and I'm gonna 28 I
would take the 20 go with the 20 all
right if 20s all right yes you use that
thing
there's a little bit of pressure as air
is just comes whooshing you gotta past
you so we're still into the row of air
yes exactly so you pull it up against
the air coming down and there's this
sound as it unplugs that's how you know
a tomb is fresh right yeah yeah and when
you shift it to the side there is now at
you assume a nice one and a half foot
square hole
sealing of a room of this room below and
as you peer down into the chamber below
you can see it is a tomb like chamber
there are frescoes on the walls but
they're covered with dust and cobwebs
and there is a contraption in the middle
of this chamber that looks like it's a
series of interlocking golden globes or
brass bronze globes Wow some combination
- and they're all sort of interconnected
to one another in a bizarre and
confusing way there's some Skeksis type
shit are they moving is it it's
perfectly still okay but it looks like
it's meant to move in some way you would
might call it an orrery or an ARMA Larry
yeah that like like planets there is a
name there is a large central orb in the
middle and then smaller orbs orbiting it
one has these sort of bright brassy
prongs suggesting maybe a Sun nice
another one is the sort of dark shape
gray thing that could be a moon made out
of what looks like adamantine or mithril
or something tarnished mithril and then
there are other planets some have their
own rings with their own or their own
small moons around them at least one of
those other planets is flat and disc
shaped I knew it
what did I fucking tell you but the
devices the entire device is perfectly
perfectly still and the main globe or
world has the sort of embossed rough
patterns all over it's suggestive of
coastlines and mountains oh yes you poke
your head down for like three seconds
poke your head back up and go I saw how
far down to the floor is it it's about a
30-foot drop and is there anything
between us and the floor besides these
this mechanism that's a good question
there is not much more than that's or
anything like there are no more nuts in
this room but you've got the latter next
to you it wouldn't be hard to tie a rope
off on it just yeah that magic broke so
I have slow fall as one of my abilities
and you guys are pretty little I could
just grab you and we also want to get up
like I have a rope I'll tie off a rope
there's no other exit from this room
except for this I'd rather be certain
you can see what appears to be a metal
door okay
blocking off yeah opening and one I
think it's I think it's definitely
correlated with this thing so this man I
gotta save this seems in some ways like
some mage type shit mm-hmm I mean I
think this is a this is a solar system
type scenario here the first question is
you know can we invent astronomy while
we're in this room the second question
and get on that Jim yeah the second
question is is there going to be any
clues in these dusty frescoes I let me
go down there cuz if something is like
gonna you know beartrap Compu in half
yeah so you get drop a rope and go first
yeah oh I'm like Oh what we'll do
we'll do a rope tie the rope off I'm
like I'm like there you go and I just
like hoop and I'd like tip in there okay
and I just want to like tip off of
things all the way down okay thirty feet
like come on
ha all right you guys do have an
astronomer in you and you're adventuring
party right now that's exactly right
you do astronomy no no no a second in
astronomy pastrami distinction between
these two Jim the left side you see the
re go sort of tumbling down the rope to
the bottom of the floor you see in the
wall in the shaft here what looks like a
depression almost like a little button
Oh up here where we are yeah Oh
[Laughter]
not after I go into the hole man
is anyone looking at me do they see oh
they're all looking down the hole and
you're just sort of cast your eyes to
the science like I don't the buttons
wrong with my elbow why do you do that
[Laughter]
Bowers VRE yeah exactly it's a mixture
of a scorpion and a bat and Satan
Burgess and it's ravenous with a
thousand years of hunger as soon as you
push the button in the wall below you
okay in this room in the room below you
you see all these stone rods come out of
the wall all the way down especially
creating a ladder down
[Music]
I'm down that okay yeah okay man I
thought something else is gonna happen
to me - hey look everybody laughs what
are the chances I start climbing down
past the are you trying yeah because if
we're gonna maintain the kid metaphor
it's like the first to touch robot or
even yeah do you wanna be the first to
touch the gold Marie well no but I get
to the ground and I want to make sure
that VRE I'm there before VRE does all
right yes you you land a split second
before vr8 oh nice of you to join us
just like proud yeah we're late only an
eight-year-old can yeah
nobody wanted to but I want to do it
anyways I've never gotten to use it I do
a slow fall nice is it Batman
yes yeah holding our staff the position
doesn't change at all yeah and then
you're just down yeah I love it yeah I'm
plant your feet softly upon this child
no but there's but there may well be a
scenario for you to cut straight through
this astrology yeah I mean we can fraud
this thing for an hour
astronomy the fresco it's all this other
starship you know like be the frescoes
on the wall show humanoid figures with
their arms up like this but they're
missing their heads ah heads look like
they've been cut off and where their
heads should be floating above their
shoulders is a star Oh like a star for
each of them yep a star atop each how
many shoulder they sort of run along
both of the long walls of this room you
count like four on each side okay and
these are like giant men and women yeah
yeah twelve thirteen feet tall there's
like holding the sky up is do I
recognize that imagery at all have I
seen a person with a star for a head
oh my I'd go to school with any of these
guys now now in 3/4 time nope none of
this seems that all familiar you don't
have any star heads in your family could
I do some kind of history check on this
with yes you can absolutely try okay
what the hell that's the natural twenty
shit okay just gonna go over and just
fucking kick it BAM it could be that
these are images of like some sort of
grand makers universe and this our
malaria sphere brought to you by them
and this the this large central sphere
you see enough recognizable landforms to
think that is Pharaon Arturo
yeah the planets that you're that you
live on this is the flat one no this is
the big central round one around which
all the other ones orbit okay it's got
it's a moon right to itself the moon is
about seven feet in diameter it
represents a it represents a discredited
torille centric model of the universe
right right yes but this this mechanism
I mean is it held in place by it all
sort of comes up out of the floor yeah
the floor so there is you you do see
underneath the central globe machinery
to suggest that it and all the things
attached to it can move can I go over
there and see if there's like a another
one of these buttons or something as you
make your way over to it you get within
five feet of it and it's it looks you
you don't know how I just find something
the apparatus suddenly begins to swing
around its rings rotating out of the way
as the surface of the globe peels back
to reveal a dark hollow interior and
inside the world inside this cavity is a
padded bronze chair with levers built
into its arm rests I mean if I'm in a
class
clamors yeah I'm on it before it so I
want to make sure that everybody
understands this what you're talking
about is a chandelier that comes from
the globe that's okay the inverted
chandelier inverted chandelier it's you
it's always been theorized this is the
Fifty Shades of Grey trainer inverted
chandelier so you hop in your air
inverted channel okay and you start
pulling that's what I saw I'm looking at
him and I'm like swinging my feet and
I'm like I'm like I've been looking at
all of you like I'm like I write tonight
that you gotta solve this puzzle right
right no no no it's a oh man I'm gonna
I'm looking right at you do it do it do
it do it
no are there petals - no there no there
no petals which is good there's just the
levers on the armrest and the even
though there's only the one chair in the
center of the globe the central globe is
about almost 10 feet diameter so you can
fit Wow multiple people inside the
platform jeez this might be a good idea
I'll get in there if let's say that we
do this correctly we don't know where it
goes we might all want to be there at
the same time yeah I say I ask Rosie I
say is there a way that all of this
should look uh is there is there a
configuration that's more appropriate to
be no not intuitively okay um but the
lizard is still on your shoulder says
conjunction when single signs the triple
Sun right
I'm already in there I'm gonna climb in
right all right look I've lived a long
life let's do this okay so I'm like as
soon as you start or anting the levers
the entire contraption begins to move
well first thing that happens is the
peeled away section closes up so you're
encased in the sphere is it black is it
completely dark in here
no it becomes transparent it turns
transparent and as you can see all the
things around you circling around on
there mechanisms rings and moons and
everything and as you do you can see
everything is sort of coming into an
arrangement gradually over time like
you're moving through the motions of
years yeah yeah that's and then great
image bursting out of the moon orbiting
the world like part of the moon just
breaks away and a demon sort of comes
crashing down upon the ground outside
yes this demon stands about nine and a
half feet tall and is wielding a
gigantic axe and he's looking around
you're all in this this is not like like
a cuckoo clock this is not a mechanical
thing real demon he comes out up the
moon moon breaks open outside of the
sphere that you're in and this real-life
demon pops onto the ground amid the
wreckage and just starts looking for
things to kill but he's not looking he
can't see us
Hey doesn't look like it sorry got in
but okay and he's like stalking all
right he sees the device moving yeah
he's just sort of stalking around and
looking for something with his axe over
his shoulder and you see that he's got
green skin large fangs bat-like ears
really bloodshot beady eyes big bat-like
wings over his back and four big
muscular arms all this is demon style
yeah it was like shit even AF yeah right
it looks like just turn to m4
motherfucker
he's only got two arms sorry two arms
there is this guy oh yeah he's using a
real dick yeah yeah he does seem like a
big dick okay I actually kind of like
like it would be if it stopped right now
hold on I just I just mentioned if we
keep going are we just going to release
more never and more demons into this
room there's a lot of moves they could
pop out on here but then but then they
would fight each other I would okay
let's maintain our Pokemon motif yeah
all right Matt no no you're just gonna
be it's gonna be a situation where it's
like you know I met an old woman who
swallowed a fly all right maybe we can
get anything bigger than the demon to
come out the thing it becomes like a pub
G situation and then we got to kill
whoever gets to continue that's not good
yeah yeah all right so you're gonna keep
it rotating I maintain the current
whatever all right then as revolve
around nothing else nothing else pops
out but eventually as you watch all of
the other things come into a line and as
soon as that happens it falls off yes
your deck pop the device hums and then
suddenly there is a crackling all around
you and the entire room is gone and you
find yourself in a device falling
through space we're in this sphere do we
still see the mechanism around us or
we're just to the it's all as soon as it
hits the conjunction a kind of locks in
that position everything is now frozen
and you're just falling and as stars
begin to whip past you you also seen
what appear to be streams of color like
nebulae or something just kind of
blowing what the fuck was in that vial
Oh me
[Laughter]
be more and a momentary flash later and
you go boom you hit something hard can
we see what it is outside yeah through
the transparent dome you moments before
you crashed
you saw what appeared to be like clouds
being passed
okay so we've actually we have and then
sort of here yeah what looks like like
evening sky okay
birds and then boom you hit the ground
and you appear to be in some sort of
weird City okay
weird how but like Omo yeah buildings
shelters the buildings have sort of
they're sort of flat and a sluggish but
it's not all crap you lint and decrepit
I'd correct yeah riders over here we
know what's going on and you think we've
landed on the roof of one of these
structures quite high up you think like
do we see the story it's it's getting
kind of dark outside so you can't really
see much okay so what do you think just
happened I think that we I think that I
just drove up through time through time
this is a time machine sweet and I think
this I think that we have arrived at an
earlier point in almost history okay
that's my guess so we can't kill our
grandpa or anything like that and you
know your grandpa kill our grandpa yes
I'm just saying that would you would be
was that something that you is there
something that you really want to do
like should we be I'm just saying time
travel is dangerous and we need to be
very careful so based on what you see
out on these buildings how much time do
you feel like has well we won't know
until we get out there okay
open the levers actually don't move
oh okay Jim you want to find a button
well I start walking towards the side
that we came in okay hoping it's like
one of it like an ad or this is gonna
sense my presence and you know yeah you
see it goes and it opens up and then the
sphere becomes solid you can't see
through it any there a little bit of
smoke there is yeah yeah exactly
no no and so on and so as he walks out
I'm pointing at you and I'm putting at
you and I'm saying as you step out yeah
it's sort of pebble a ground on the roof
topping there's a little bit of a Ledge
around the edge of the roof you also see
the roof is quite vast this you're sort
of on one corner of this building on the
roof but there are other like
protrusions coming up out of the
building some of them sort of gleam and
the dying Twilight light you also hear
crows lots and lots of crows and you see
whole flocks of them flying around and
it does not feel tropical knows who's
gonna say that's not a chill tissue
borough the sky overhead is kind of
cloudy and I mask time this is nope
that's not what I thought okay and it
could still be time I guess a couple
birds are on the ledge like a whole row
of crows and they're just sort of
calling and giving each other a hard
time and they don't seem at all perturb
my ear is it you sort of scare them and
they go but as you get to the edge and
you look down you see that the ground
around the building is black and there
are these thin iron or metal spires
coming up that shed a downward light
upon what looked like chariots made of
glistening metal all completely enclosed
oh I get it yeah yeah yeah chariots are
cars yeah we're we're in San Antonio
I don't get it there is something on
lights when you when you look you saw
whoa-ho-ho right now this building seems
to be situated in the in the middle of
this black landscape paper fields around
it and you must be about four stories up
on this building and as you kind of cast
your eyes downward you see that the
building's walls are made of glass
do I see looking around at this building
and do I see eight buildings around me I
can see there are distant buildings off
in the distance do I see any iconography
you do you see what appear to be lit
signs okay all right Shack gold goes in
our ears egg there is a glowing sign
right on the side of the building below
you i mounted to the wall of the
building you would know that this
general thing can you give me the shape
of it color it's got a weird curve it's
sort of a yellow black and purple and
the biggest word you see on it is
wizards
[Laughter]
okay we're in Trenton so you went too
far you went too far and we need to go
back well there's there's wizards here
you can talk with that recognize the
word though as Wizards yes and you don't
get us home
I turn around I go we're safe above some
sort of Conclave these wizards here will
no doubt be able to help us I think we
should investigation do we still have
the lizard anticipate yes no temptation
see now you're into it yeah destination
listening
I think apprehension yeah I think that
you went too far I think this is too far
yeah I have a kind of a mistrust of
wizards my son has taken some wizard
level birthday not all Wizards
[Laughter]
I mean well these aren't moving right so
we need like one year people to like do
they're right this is like their place
this one has it go in this right okay so
you don't have the magic you don't know
enough spells to Oh what are you what
just I'm just verifying that your
wizardry is not enough to fix us to send
us streaming through time no I am NOT I
don't know man sir right
do I see any kind of hatch or anything
on this rooftop that might allow us
access yes you do
yeah yep do you find one I told him to
come out right like you guys can come
out and I pretend that there's no
breathable oxygen all right I will I
will come out of there wow this is
really weird it's genuinely weird like
hold on you said that this look kind of
like omou insofar as they're all sort of
squares we're yeah low-lying okay
squared I'm excited to me I can feel the
wizards so I'm gonna try to open this
okay it appears to be locked yeah it's
right up right okay good 13 okay you are
unable to budget it's stronger than that
mmm crap I'm gonna take a step back and
try just give it a sack with the with a
magic missile
all right now the spell works yes it
does the other thing you notice is now
that you're actually close to the trap
door and actually being on the roof Jim
you didn't notice this before when you
first landed because you're getting
acclimated and your senses were
overloading but there's a weird tingling
sensation that you feel kind of coming
from the building and you're not sure
why okay and by the only one feeling you
guys feel like a little tingle
so special some special down south you
guys getting that yeah you might you
might you think there might be something
there you're sure there's something
there I feel when you hit the door with
your magic missle leaves so like a
little black force mark indentation in
it but it doesn't do enough damage to
open it they're like magical protection
on this building maybe there are wizards
yeah they would guard it we don't they
they guard it against magic but you know
I look over I'm like well there's a
glass window I can get I think I can get
in windows sure right here like hold
hold this rope like the end of it right
and hand it to an eight-year-old do you
have another rope who has another rope I
can make a rope yeah or a long rope
magic rope okay
yeah and so I do like stick second-story
job all right like I some like it I
heart I go I go looking for like the the
land I'm like oh this is like it can I
pick the lock on this window you can see
that these windows are big and they're
between sort of little flat bars of
metal so their panels essentially laid
out you're the on the fourth floor you
can see that there is light coming out
of some of the windows on the floor
below the fourth floor a little bit slow
Hey all right I let him down a little
bit all right as you are lowers down the
window you can see through and it's sort
of a tinted glass what appears to be
some sort of weird library complex or
something there are desks and they're
separated with all these into all these
cube like seems like it's like a maze
hell is this a lab but as you glide down
to the window you can see a person
facing you they they're lit by some
device
in front of them and they've got
something over their ears and they're
kind of doing this and then they
artifact as you just sort of up against
the glass what does this person look
like me
oh my god
and I'd not exactly like you okay I'll
go I'll come over to the window bran
door am I still in my underwear yeah
okay so we're learning a lot about Chris
Perkins yeah naked person is available
at the window right so ordered
I'm you want me to lower you all the way
down yeah like I need to get all the way
down yes to get down as you're waiting
to be lowered down you can see I get
away from my desk I make my way through
the labyrinth I before I get to where
I'm going and sort of underneath the
pool of light you see me get stopped
briefly by what appears to be a gnome
who has got some papers that she's
ruffling through and we just have this
sort of briefest of exchange we both
kind of laugh and then I go continue on
my way and the gnome continues on its
way okay I go all the way yeah I lower
me down alright how does this magic rope
thing work I mean I I have I can make
whatever I want
okay and it's real like okay so yeah he
lowers you down if you get down to the
ground
I just Matt you're like well the
entrance must be on some side you don't
know which you kind of circle the
building very quickly there's a little
fenced-in playground off to one side
I hope this is all shoes or something
because there are little bushes and
things when you get around to the front
of the building you do see some people
and are leaving you can see one of them
has the satchel another one has a small
kid and they're making their way off
with one of these metal chair eating
carrots
I stay in the bushes okay well I have I
am more scared now and as you wait the
people have become more infrequent
there's crows everywhere they're all out
in the parking lot on the cars squawking
loudly make the amount of growth there's
a key amount of crows there are
thousands upon thousands of crows
congregating as the light as the
Twilight fades but you make it to the
door
they're all glass and you can sort of
hear that kind of thrumming or feel that
thrumming as you reach the threshold and
the door kind of rattles like it's held
shut you can't open it but beyond the
doors but forty feet beyond do you see
me coming out of what appears to be some
sliding doors and walking toward them
and I come over to the door and I open
it for you do you say to him
do you say anything what home fair
wizard
with polar wizard come alone I it know
where Joe my companions are harmony and
fearsome they lay in wait can you
contact them yes at a moment's notice
there's a little chilly out here
actually I didn't come prepared for this
weather all right we we humbly request
the services of your guild there you go
to re-energize our time machine and our
youth our bodies we need to be also I am
under a terrible curse because normally
I'm not naked in this old you came in
the machine
yeah Time Machine I drove it I was
wondering what happened to that was
yours
oh no it's not ours oh we found it in
the TSR warehouse
it disappeared after the second nerf war
so yeah I'm obviously a pussy and two
wizards
such as yourself should have no trouble
ooh
dispelling my cursive my lack of clothes
and being eight years old I'm sure that
can be arranged that would be really
great I'm not gonna lie to you here this
is it's been this has been a fucking day
[Applause]
we really had to go of it one thing
after another I mean like you go to the
obelisk right and it's a statue Jimmy
you're gonna touch it right and then
suddenly you're eight years old like who
the fuck does that
so you've been to omou right oh so you
you know about Omo that's of course of
course wizard right right you seem to
wizard so we release the product about
it the product yeah
based on our travels to Omo
you don't think we actually make stuff
up here do you
[Laughter]
I'm I'm like nodding and making like
really like his almond with you oh I get
it
and that I'm suddenly furious I'm like
fucking ohm and of course he is getting
a piece of this weird fucked-up
interdimensional action and he's you
know let me know he is oh man I contact
you with ascending spell and I say the
re is down by the front entrance do you
and everybody else want to come for a
tour yes a tour of what he said I say of
Wizards of the coast is this the third
level we're going to the third level
then I accept my voice is much higher I
say well can you come up to the can you
come up to the roof and open this magic
door you can't come down I can feather
fall down I could flip fall down yes we
can come down so so we we combine
techniques yeah all right
you land you make it to the entrance VRE
shivering waiting for you inside the
lobby I'm standing there yeah I'm trying
to look as confident as possible which
is gonna be hard as you cross into the
building from the outside you feel that
tingling again like you're going through
something okay tangible can I cast
detect magic you sure can well fuck 20
he came to play Dungeons &amp; Dragons
motherfucker
side of the table like you're connected
to the earth Korea you you think it is a
protective field designed to hedge
things out oh but you're not sure what
obviously not danger so I walk up to you
and I say hey I can't help but notice
the fine workmanship on your defensive
spells here this is quite the the shield
you've put up yeah we have a it's called
an antipathy spell to keep out the
trolls and the phyrexian x' it's good
work good work I'll take you into an a
cubicle doors part that these doors have
a picture on them that looks like
warrior or somebody fighting and I lead
you into a tiny little chamber a metal
box and I say this will take us up to
level three yes I see I've seen this
before and then I push all the buttons
yeah I turned to you and I say I'm well
versed in this it's not as advanced as
some I've seen but it will suffice
all right I'm stopped on the second
floor doors open there's some art on the
wall then all doors closed so then they
go I will return later to see it yeah it
looks like I have to wave some sort of
badge over something to make us a long
red floor flat white yes a white little
device and I lead you into the third
floor to our labyrinth the third level
yes maintenance had to have this right
yes I get through some arcane locked
doors and lead you through seeing any
other people or once you come it's
getting late though - yeah it's getting
late normally we'd go up to the fourth
floor to get you all signed in but it's
it's closed now and there's a dragon up
there I thought you were third no I'm I
got I got scaled up tonight's level
oh yeah oh we're on the third level yeah
maybe you should talk to your damn about
giving you some more magic items magic
items in my game scale with love we can
have a conversation about this later
I'll have to talk to Jerry about that
when I lead you on to the level you can
see in the kitchen area two elves
talking near a vending machine and what
appears to be some sort of glass flask
yeah
and one of them has a mug in its hand
and on the mug it says to thine own elf
be true and I will take you to our
corner of the labyrinth but before that
happens you see you here screams off in
the distance and then what appeared to
be a bunch of gnomes chasing after a
green-skinned goblin with a stick of
dynamite oh I give them full birth I
know what dynamite is it's this stick
with a flashing in the sparkle and it
seems to be getting slimmer and slimmer
and slimmer it's a thick wand this is
awesome they got and that the gnomes are
like stop em he's heading to the magic
area I'll tackle him all right poo
making a got him
I got attack role or I sorry a athletics
check to grapple him is 21 you succeed
haha see right
I'm up got this guy
I'll take the stick of dynamite and
putting in the washing machine yeah yeah
so Jim's gonna come to you and he says
listen I saw obviously you're all
Wizards here we have to encouraged is
there any way you can return us to our
proper shapes oh yeah that's easy can we
do that now
here yeah no we have to go to the third
and a third floor okay the three and a
third floor that's where I'm completely
like yeah it's it's another it's a type
of floor it's a special floor well you
can only get there by teleportation
circle but we have one in the DMV area
so let's go all right the D&amp;D area we
follow you it stands for deeper and
deeper into the third floor to the third
of third yeah and I'll take you past
some in the labyrinth all these cubes
which have these weird toys in them like
there's weirdly constructed things that
have blocks there are all kinds of
little figurines I don't steal a bunch
of stuff I just hold you just hold your
hand out it is the creats and I did it
I'm like
guys I just started to like tanks I
start to drop it and then I kind of like
try to put it all wrong there's a
there's like a letter opener with like a
made of this sort of red metal there are
more of these toys there are books that
look exactly like this
I grab the ones there's tomb of
annihilation
and then while we're walking I'm
flipping madly trying to match up what I
know with it in terms of the orrery
terms of what's required to defeat a
sara rack in terms of rocks neecy's
weaknesses yeah yeah yeah I get the soul
monger page and I tear it out are there
any of those when when the re saw you
you were lit by a screen oh you know
he's late he's lit he's lit us out yes
okay thank you
Rosi Rosi goes up and she she interacts
with it and it immediately gets three
viruses because she's old yeah somehow
you find the AOL client yeah
like there's no way all client on there
somehow you connect to AOL here a modem
loaded that there is a different kind of
magic that's and so make a
sleight-of-hand check
hmm 25 all right you're able to score a
bunch of miscellaneous items and stuff
the swag Duffin in is tighty whities
worth it go I'm assuming I still have my
pack yeah the zone oh yeah guys right
all right you can see that there is a
large sitting area there are some
enclosed cube areas with glass windows
peering into them you can also see
asleep over what appears to be a wooden
table a large four five foot diameter
creature circular with eye stalks its
central eye closed tight
how many eye stalks are we dealing with
10 and it just sort of snores okay so
wait is it is not a it is not like these
other trinkets this is a real creature
this is a real creature I took on your
shirt yeah and I go are we concerned
about the beholder no he's on our side
okay what's his name I got him dad
what's his name fuck you that's his name
fuck you Chauncey his name is Enoch yeah
xanax
oh I'm a big fan is there I'm assuming
there is a t-shirt like there gotta be
holla dude there's like that's the swag
there's a mountain of t-shirts in the
seating area yeah I will grab I'm cuz
I'm buck-ass naked but I will grab a
shirt okay alright and just try to cover
up a little bit yeah as you dawn clothes
quickly and I take you past an office
that has the name Nathan Stewart on it
you can see a portrait of you hanging up
on his wall whoa I got fans everywhere
that's got to be pretty much of a
Tuesday for you though yeah well I can
tell you've got good taste here so I
will take you to oh I go to my desk I
get a I look around for a sticky note
that has the teleportation sequence on
it next to my password which is I love
my dog
right and I will take that teleportation
sequence over to another chamber that
has a a coded door that I have to run my
card in front of you and when I take you
in there there is a glowing circle upon
the floor I recognise it as a
teleportation you doing something I can
make yes yes this is legit yeah
teleportation sir this is a nice one
this will take us down third in three
and a third floor okay you guys trust
this full night rested I trust Jim trust
you trust Jim yeah it comes to magic
like yeah yeah this is this is a legit
teleportation circle alright I want to
be a real boy again right yeah I'm ready
to get out of this body yeah okay when
you stand on the circle I will enter the
code into a keypad next and we are all
transported into a gigantic
Okin library that looks like it's about
three stories tall with a huge crystal
and gold dome on the top with light
beaming down upon rows upon rows of
shelves with balconies all around them
and ladders on wheels that sort of roll
around and I'll say this is the old TSR
archive combined with wizards products
from recent years and we have some
Scrolls that might help you as we've
been moving like you know like starting
with the beholder and as we've gone
through and then there's the keypad then
there's the teleportation was the
teleportation seamless or was there like
a bump or a jog it was just like a flash
of green light and then you appear okay
you can see that all around the interior
on the ground floor here there are
pillars supporting all the balconies
mounted to them are iearned torch
brackets with torches in them that have
green flame billowing up out of them and
all around the room you can see elves
dwarves paths wings and other creatures
ever since the beholder the re has been
becoming more and more anxious like he
got a shirt on and it's not a huge deal
but he's getting sort of like and then
there's more and more creatures and more
and he's getting sort of like you know I
know not shy but like he's like there is
a lot of stuff here there's a lot of
people here overwhelming a little you
can tell it's like this is a little much
and he doesn't want to admit it and he's
just thickened a little closer to your
side okay and then before I will I will
also up next you just be like this is
all really cool and I'm excited to be
normal again
it seems like you know us yeah I mean
we've never been here I would remember
yeah but as I said tales of our
adventurers reached you is that okay
absolutely in a manner of speaking and
that's the rest of the story
a small sprite comes over to you a
butterfly wings little woman okay I'm
just sort of flutter she's got a little
ball she's sort of let see you talk to
you in a quick squeaky voice hi can you
help us find something in this library
yeah sure okay
we need three spells of non bonus and
and that's it I'm good
[Laughter]
[Applause]
and I'll also tell you that here is
where we can find equipment to repair
your device oh so we get you back home
do you want to do the device I don't
know I want to be a man first and then
we will worry about the device alright
you go off with some other Wizards they
take you into rooms and you emerge a man
[Laughter]
[Applause]
I am exhausted
[Laughter]
do I have my rope my clothes my like my
tights my purple tights and everything
no but there is a set of there is a gym
dark magic Halloween costume here that
you can wear now am I still am I still
dying though your your curse continues
to affect you no matter what world
you're on I'll put the bastards know
anything about how to cure your curse
yeah I mean while I'm here no no the
other documents we need we need
equipment that can solve they can repair
the device yeah we need spells of like
boys to men and each of you gets the
boys to men see exactly ABC BBD back
yeah yeah but we also need every piece
of information they have on the soul
monger yeah oh sure yeah there's a bunch
of stuff that didn't get into the
printed book yeah yeah
yeah well then I'm gonna ask I'm gonna
ask Chris Perkins directly which one is
a real one
which ones let him figure that that's
that's the ambiguity that's at the core
of this tail paint so what I do is I ask
I ask you hold on you hear as I asked I
asked you say what is the quickest way
to destroy a soul monger you saw one
like across the street and you were like
whoa so longer and it's like so longer
is just the device that contains Souls
within it so the device can itself be
destroyed the problem is is is currently
being guarded by this horrific undead
monstrosity this sort of unborn god that
could larval sort of like God yeah sort
of a proto God that never quite came out
your typical larval God see this yeah
that's so I'm saying so that's so that's
actually the bigger problem destroying
the soil monger is not hard right
particularly since it's conveniently
suspended over a pit of lava oh that is
convenient is to be yeah well we have
devices here that might be able to help
you okay we'll give us those yeah and
we'll put them in our chrono orb okay
that's what we caught her own orb Crone
orb
all right I would say like do for the
manifestation do we do you like ship us
off to like other wizards yeah because
like the re is actually like following
you around like a little kid in the
kitchen where it's like when you turn
around you bump into him because he's
following you too close yeah I'm not
gonna make you a man Bri what's that I'm
not gonna make you a man
he's just he's always on my bucket list
Chris yeah you know you can see also
we're sort of in this part of the
library where these giant framed
portraits of great Wizards you see
Morden Kainan you see elminster like
that Raistlin race won by the way yeah
yeah okay so like if you do kind of like
you know shoo me away it is at that
moment that I will try to pick your
pocket I figure and I assumed that this
is like fresh news like I'm doing the
little kid eyes and I'm like I'm like
he's never gonna see this coming
maker make your sleight of hand check
[Laughter]
just give him your one kinda that's
about 24 all right it's not what you
need to pickpocket God that's just it
I'm not God I'm just a guy who writes
stuff so are you making a grab for my
wand or my wallet
[Music]
[Applause]
you'd grab the lawns so the wand being
the thing that's granted you access to
all of these things no I'm just using my
security keycard for that Oh God have a
one I am a wizard of course I do
so hey you know the truth is like as a I
am an opportunist I do I do the like
like no no don't send me away and I'm
just sort of like if I can get a hold of
something that's what I'm gonna take I'm
not I'm having a little bit of a rummage
so I'm not I don't have a target I'm
just seeing what today a scoop yeah all
right all right what you got in there so
like if I if I end up with such
tremendous intimacy why you feel so off
though no no - hold on everybody's here
gets to pick his pocket here use the use
the dice tray there you go I would
detect magic on the little yeah the
phone glows he glows yes be magic and
you know probably like four even before
I get in there you do eventually turn
turn around and you see me like put it
lights off vibrates or something
and I just threw it and like it all
falls down it's like I drop it all and
I'm like it's it's the one with the
green door right for the man-things and
I pick it all up okay thank you give it
all back to you except for some of the
cards in the wallet I don't know what
they're for but I just ain't gonna be
safe and I run off looking all right
what is VISAA
it's like a Vizier okay and you emerge a
man I will keep the t-shirt personally
yeah yeah it's a little tight but yeah
you're doing t-shirt undies
underoos oh I can I've got the goods
back I mean I don't need to hide those
the merchandise they're on display
so wait t-shirt no undies on these I'm
assuming the undies transmogrify with me
okay well you said you didn't have to
hide the goods anymore okay all right
all right good OOP that's the other
chandelier that's the Aries but also the
shirt it's a little tight it looks good
on BRE all right all right whatever
I'm already grossed out all right men
yep yeah a of quasi mechanical creatures
that kind of look like Spears with eyes
in them and little wings
I love EE a little leg or a thin little
legs basically mode Ron's I'm into it
I'm into it they come sort of they come
out with they're sort of more boxy shape
to leader and they ask me where your
device is and I tell them it's on the
roof and then they go trundling off
again I got a tug on you listen wizard
one wizard to another like I have to say
that it seems like the the magic that
you have here is on a scale far beyond
what I'm used to like that your your
well your magic is just beyond anything
I've ever seen where are we
we're on a planet called Earth one of
several planets that coexist in a
material plane
you lost me alright never mind forget I
asked
his eyes are just glazing over if I say
you used to get here didn't so much take
you through time it just took you to a
different place okay okay from one of
the many worlds that we have visited and
chronicled everything you see around you
all these books are chronicles of the
worlds that we have seen you are telling
the stories of all these other places
actually you visited that's right do you
use the chrono orb to do it we have
multiple methods of doing it that was a
device built basically for that purpose
it was the device that was used to
discover a number of early worlds
including Blackmore yeah fans out there
they know yeah so I think I may have
been used to get the gray Hawk to yeah
did you have you sign the contract with
him not with him good yeah if he tries
to get you to sign yeah all right well
since we're kind of wrapped up here and
your device is gonna be ready soon we
should probably head back out
yeah returned into the third floor I can
grade around some more stuff yeah oh
yeah we're waiting on we're waiting on
the other strolls there's other stuff
that I can get that off of my come my
magical device yes well we can you tell
our story leave out the little kid part
if you wouldn't mind sure we do that
information and also I have sheets from
the tomb of a knight this kind of a dumb
story line isn't it yeah I have sheets
from that that time you tore it out yeah
exactly when I take you back to the
third floor and we've got a I go over to
my computer and I send to the printer
some reams of paper that have the
unedited manuscript of tomb of
annihilation with information about the
soul monger that you can use perfect and
he says I say then let me show you
something else and I take you over to a
big screen that I turn on with a remote
device that looks kind of like a wand
and pictures an image comes up and then
there's like a device in front of it
some sort of scrying mirror
and the lizard says ooh PlayStation
[Laughter]
[Applause]
that's the apex right there oh oh and
you guys can spend the rest of the
evening playing PlayStation until your
device is ready yeah excellent all right
I'm not doing that I am reading about
larval gods and yeah so much so you're
able to figure out that Asura RAC is
using these captured souls to feed this
God to basically continue its
development it's up to a real god of
death oh he's trying to found a God yes
he is he is feeding at hundreds
thousands millions of souls to basically
continue it on its course to evolving
into a Living God Oh rule and destroy
the world that you live on yes that was
our problem it's not a soul monger it's
a soul monger yeah it's like yeah so
manga yes and that everyone is
destructible you just have to go and
destroy out yes say where yeah there's
map so it's clear I have all the maps
let's go get it okay oh and the
solutions yeah exactly and any
weaknesses to this larval god creature
uh yeah he'll give you all everything
absolutely its powers step block yeah I
feel like we've made a real connection
wizard wizard
is there a way I can get in contact with
you again like once I once I return to
my my world will is there some way I can
reach you again okay
[Laughter]
are you on Twitter though I like birds
I'm always on Twitter it's five six
seven five three oh nine right nine
eight seven oh yeah we do have a system
for contacting us if you're outside of
the building but it's imperceptible no
one's been able to figure it out mm-hmm
sounds like a challenge
it could be okay customers here enough
yeah yeah for those out there in the
audience it's literally first name dot
last name I'm cracked the code that's
our pride that's our secret code all
right
yes I'm itching to get back up to it
okay yeah when I get back up to the
device it peels open for you it seems to
be functional again the mode ron's
retreat down in through the hatch in the
roof I thank him it's the night outside
yeah exactly it's actually kind of misty
rain now I'm quite familiar who wants to
drive this on the way back it was a whoo
I tell ya well you want to come with us
not in that thing wouldn't be caught
dead in that thing sterilization Rosie's
actually gonna try an intimidation check
against you to try to intimidate you
into joining us how's it gonna go
you know I a sweetheart you might not be
totally familiar with what can happen if
you cross me but we're gonna need you to
come with us because we want to validate
that this information is correct so
unless you'd like to take your chances
with my family why don't you want to eat
stuff inside the vehicle please
Oh used up all those twenties early did
you got should have saved one should
have saved to 20 but it is any
intimidation use the potion you can
drink it
the lizard's like magic potion no he's
toast to our I happen to have a vial on
me of something you could drink you have
the vial right I do he does not feel
comfortable in his body he's so agitated
he knows that you were asking to do
something profoundly immoral listen to
his squeak yeah and I don't think we
should kidnap him one of the
all-powerful God magicians of the
multiverse this little he's gonna like
like that so she odd I'm like I'm just
I'm looking at ro I'm like I'm like
[Laughter]
I'm disappointed I'm like if you were my
son after I fixed this rotting curse I
would love to come back and stay here
like this hope this wizards building is
like where I belong yeah yeah you'd fit
right in here can I come back yeah
anytime
Wow worked out good
it worked out good so before I before I
head back into the machine I take a look
out from the roof and just make a quick
note of any franchise opportunities
places that I might want to found a
chapter yeah la makeup lot yeah there's
a vacant lot right next door it's right
next to that strip club exactly I make a
mental note yeah hmm there you go
how do you know Starbucks is not an
acquisitions incorporated products one
of the things you would have found by
the way probably in down on the third
floor was a model of your acquisitions
and care ship that's spooky
yeah I mean I'm in the thing yeah yep
okay cool I'll do the same thing but
backwards no Chris when we came it was
joke joke joke and never gonna it was
good yeah it's like Mountain motorcycle
yeah after we leave in your wallet
there's a little note that says I'm so
sorry
before when Rosie tries to seduce and or
intimidate you just it's just the way
she is she's from a different age
before I before I step in I walk up to
you mm-hmm
I just want to say thank you for
everything
oh wow way to make it classy yeah yeah
all right you all sort of disappear into
the folds of this globe
there's the grinding motion I'll take a
few steps back yeah you see me through
the apparent dome yeah cover up your
product out yeah there's a raise and
[Laughter]
I'll just walk away on my phone yeah all
right I get my selfie and then there is
another flash once the conjunction lines
up and you guys vanish and so the device
is working a little better than it did
before
it's grazed little grease yes so it's
missing with a ride yeah exactly
and is there anything you want to do
different or you're just basically
trying to go back to the point you left
oh it feels probably like at this point
I know how to steer this a little right
yeah yeah well if we have a map yes so
longer and so it's not now I know it's
not a crow no thing if this moves us we
have to mention right right yeah you
mind like jigging a little directly to
the yeah here's the thing
but I'm super good at this yeah clearly
I did hear the term lava pit there's a
lot of lava yeah it's one thing to like
end up like one tunnel over mm-hmm but
lava pit so the soul monger is this will
definitely use guidance so longer is
this kind of canister shaped thing
suspended by three struts over the lava
there's like a metal belt that
struts meet that sort of grips the
canister around its waist and then
coming out of the canister is an
umbilical cord attached to this thing
that the souls are drawn up out of and
fed into the giant bloated God carcass
yeah floating nearby yuck yes this is
gross yuck a lot of things one of the
things you know is a vorpal weapon can
cut that umbilical cord but you can also
if you have negative energy protection
that's also helpful I know no I don't
have that energy I've never even heard
that granted I've only been playing D&amp;D
for a decade campaigns infused with
negative energy and we don't nobody here
has any vorpal shit right and you know
what I like okay I hold this one yeah
I want to like but I'm like did you put
me in a situation where I have not only
the wheel but the map yeah imma just I
start rooting through my pack
yeah I want to look at all this stuff
yeah then I grabbed kind of just like
higgledy-piggledy right is my pocalypse
tagger in there this letter opener sure
okay
[Laughter]
[Applause]
it's Pat yeah this is Matt Matt is this
I mean like it would this be a negative
energy I've seen a lot of negative have
that as the secondary plan okay primary
plan guide to the device itself through
space and have it materialized in such a
way that it occludes part or whole of
the device I don't want to overlap the
soul monger I don't want my my body
mm-hmm to overlap
yeah it would really suck to get that
curse wouldn't it the Mong Holly be
horrible nobody wants that like if I I
can imagine my body like partway stuck
into the maunder VRE i' you said your
body before and i want to make sure that
you understand some of the connotations
that are incumbent upon you as an
adjunct gear in the incredible machine
that I've built so you're saying you
want this machine that we're in to
materialize in such a way that the
sector itself is inside don't know that
it materializes and takes that space and
on each side of it what was there is
severed and gone so it sounds like you
might need someone with exquisite
navigation skills yes this is gonna be
something we all have to do together not
nope
I've got the map you've got the
navigation sophistication you will be
allowed to handle the device and I want
you to just cross your arms and be
impressed at what I've accomplished
actually know what I want to do is I
want you to navigate time I want you to
navigate space temporal navigation okay
Shawn I want you I have the power of
heart
[Laughter]
Captain Planet GRE and you make love to
this device you you get me there and I
can I can seduce it all right
you and I are going over this map in
incredible detail multiple floors I want
you to know every inch of it you I want
you to enter a meditative state where
you travel back you are conscious of the
mystic energy as this swirl around this
device you are gonna fuck this machine
so we are in 100% teen detective
research road finding these maps making
all kinds of I don't think that I don't
think that we have the equipment to
actually destroy it with weapons I don't
think we're equipped in that way I think
the best weapon we have is this device
okay so you think that if it arrives in
the exact same space and exactly there's
this cable is cable and severs it I
think that did I think that it will not
function well there's some of these so I
see the umbilical itself exactly right
got it
you know I don't want the umbilical
through no acquisitions Incorporated's
bodies body remember now in the contract
it does say that I have a full access to
and use of my body the body thickly you
own as the body I know you have you have
a license to use mice and women too
limited license hereafter known as VRE
right with this option to legal then I
bought from the option cannot appear
inside I don't think that I don't think
that we go there and then that shit is
also here I think we are trading space
okay there's no reason for me to but we
went there that came back yes I do
okay for me
no you may think you make a great case I
can't argue with that
daddy's working okay okay so so we are
folding we are leafy a through every
floor of this thing we are achieving
yeah exactly we're achieving a kind of
of conscious like a fully conscious
cognizance of this of this dungeon as it
goes down okay we just this is basically
like golf but with a time machine the re
is discovering you can't actually power
in a corner in a spherical armor I just
constantly slide around the edge do like
slow laps I've got like my knife out and
I'm just the body like even the feet
don't shift just like basically cleaning
it is this is this your seduction
technique yeah exactly so I am going
through and I'm casting guidance on each
member of the party just to give them a
little bit of extra juice on the checks
no it's not advantage in the classic
sense insofar as it's not advantage at
all but it does provide just a little
bit of extra love on their role okay so
for my boy VRE we're looking at a plus
two and I get to pick when I use that or
it'll be on your next skill ability
check after rolling during the duration
so soon we're gonna do this
okay um you if you end up using a skill
in the prosecution of your duties you
get a plus for the prosecution of you
did not like that ya motherfucker you
know who you're talkin +34 Rosie bee
sting or not your grandma's grandma in
between you casting it on me and on
Rosie
I look at Rosie and I'm like I think
don't use the skill I'm like I'm really
worried that I might die virgin Rosie
oh no we know Jim and omen are just like
I don't think that's a concern and I'm
like well I mean this is a whole new
body Rosie hey Jerry now that counts
that's true cuz I was like and now like
we couldn't get your virginity back
because I'm saying I have this my
precious flower Rosie we only have so
much time this could be our last night
on earth it's tempting but it was like
15 minutes ago that you were a child and
your underwear but now Rosie and I rip
the t-shirt off I'm not Rosie I'm brand
spankin new yeah and like and plus now
how you know we did it once in a tree
and you're like hey first time in a tree
yeah well in that tree like
interdimensional first time in a time
machine gate right all right
[Laughter]
[Applause]
listen know I've watched the entire
thing I've got I cast
silence huddle in the corner and even
though I've cast silence my hands are on
my ears and just like I have become a
sphere in the just as low as I can and I
just sort of rolled back and forth just
like a weeble in ajan that a weeble has
fallen down wait how long does silence
take the cast oh it's not long Oh an
action but I noticed your guidance spell
requires concentration so oh they're
probably not up anymore because I really
wanted you to have a bonus gear skill
check very fast yeah yeah yeah yeah just
I just I get safe I just become as safe
as possible yeah I will say the Aries
expression is stunned and amazed did it
work because it's just like it's like
and there's just like joy halfway
through you recognize that Jim is
rubbing your back
[Laughter]
[Applause]
this is supposed to happen after you've
killed a month okay anyway this has
never happened in the game I've run
before so no because it's perfectly fine
sorry because it's perfectly silent
every now and then I have to like crack
and I open to see this oh it's not which
so you get like a glimpse and they get
and it's all different everything is
different and then and then it's oh it's
oh you didn't you you read about that
the book ones but it's totally plus
there's there's some weird time dilation
so they like slow down for a while like
really it's like I've seen at the
beginning of Antichrist it's just like
yeah wherever okay are we are we having
fun or what
all right exactly
[Music]
[Laughter]
no no no so it's like okay okay okay
exactly I'm just like all right all
right are we is it did it happen
oh yeah yes for a song okay I say right
now you guys fucked all this up and now
I have to cast all these spells again
all right I say you Jim huh
remember because because the spell
requires concentration you can only do
guidance once you leave you're gonna win
if I can do guidance once I'm doing it
on this gentleman okay one Gwent great
hurry I use cutting action to just I get
a bonus action I want to make full use
of all my skills all right
so Jerry
yes Chris how can I help your cunning
action your cunning accent yeah so Jerry
yeah where did you want to land this
mofo my name is omen all right I know
you is Jerry exactly so inside so we
have this diagram and yes we can see
that this device occupies a certain
amount of space because I had the
literal map right that's you can do
measurements and the exact determine how
far down how far off so where this hose
and pipe we have the where this
umbilical is attached to this device yes
the optimal scenario is that we appear
right there or we crack this thing open
and the umbilical is destroyed okay but
anywhere along this umbilical should
interrupt this flow of souls and allow
escape that's my hope okay you I would
like you to make an intelligence check
to make sure your calculus calculations
are correct my my calculates
mathematician I'm not very good at that
I'm good at telling people what to do
but what anyone else like to do math
Jim's not doing math I'll tell you that
right now
all right what would I have I have all
the information I have all the stuff you
can do it you can roll that die yeah you
can nail this you're gonna nail this
it's kinda like Toronto it's like
throwing a beanbag the whole
no don't do that
all right it looks good what does that
add up to five all right
is five enough your device appears and
all around you outside you see molten
lava hang on one second
pull it all around what about up yeah up
to where am i I'm not a kid anymore am I
no don't you're a kid at heart Toys R Us
kid I don't know kid
so but we're not being destroyed by the
lava is this thing the lava is all
outside you but it does not seem to be
entering the globe that you're all in
okay so heal the device just sort of
listing and kind of tilting and you're
all just sort of tilting toward the back
of it as it kind of sinks the other try
again it's jammed hmm are we are we in
the lava like rolling who are under the
lava we're under the lava okay it's
getting warm can I use the power of
heart on the machine
[Music]
[Laughter]
but in so completely submerged
completely submerged okay um oh wait
wait wait wait everybody for 25 gold
pieces
I can create a false identity so I'll do
that and I would either like to be
somebody who is in water deep or like a
super competent transdimensional shift
wizard I didn't have enough money for
that can I just cross that off okay I
would like to know it's a new era then
at first
this could be a turning point yeah
I would like to conjure three minor fire
elementals okay outside home - and then
tell them to push us I yes would like to
ask you a philosophical question about
the nature of love oh I see is lava not
stone
[Laughter]
[Applause]
I can feel some real synergy happening
here yes go on is lava not stone stone
that can be shaped well you already got
the second part okay you want me to do
the elemental oh yeah okay yeah no no
they come up yeah and then all right
you're going to sew a surface yeah the
dome comes up and the lava just sort of
begins to drip off and huge clumps and
you are now floating below the canister
which has obviously soul energy trapped
inside of it you could see the
adamantine struts coming out of the
walls and holding it above the lot
exactly I am going to create a
essentially a kind of Iron Maiden out of
this thick cheese like hot rock that is
sliding off I am basically going to make
a pair of jaws out of this out of this
hot stone that reach up from the craft
continuously warmed by the fire element
and I am going to basically just try to
chomp this thing imagine like I'm making
a bear trap yeah out of hot lava and I
just wanna I'm not concerned about the
struts I understand that they have to
keep that in place I'm saying I want
this hot and this hot lava basically
just to wrap around this thing and click
on mouth
yes devour it all right you know that
the spell stone shape fourth level spell
lets you basically shape stone that's
five feet in any dimension that sounds
like exactly what he describes there's
five yet it's a what's a five it's a
five foot so like you know this table
yes exactly but it's a five foot cube
right yeah I can easily what I'm talking
about it's making a bunch of spikes
okay spikes themselves do not constitute
a substantial amount for my constructs
to function at all there must be space
within to consume the soul longer yes
I think I might have transferred some of
your energy and how would you like to
get this transformed set of stone jaws
up to it well as we as we're right here
yes raising up we're still being lifted
by these creatures okay and metal is
slagging off okay so you're kind of
using I'm using on a big fight exactly
the device off of earrings its frosted
if you will okay with hot cheese like
rock imagine imagine a kind of dark
pizzas imagine a dark lava yeah exactly
and so I'm imagine that the in the
shaping process hot waking up that that
lava and I'm basically trying to make a
kind of jaw or scissor
okay that comes up beneath it where I
assume it is most vulnerable mm-hmm yes
so your elementals are holding up
there's the lighting that's high up on
the top of the lava as they can you've
got these jaws made out of the slag on
top of ice and reaching up for the soul
longer all I have to do is poke a hole
in this thing right and I assumed it
much like a child's balloon it will sail
around the room yeah it could you just
drive a single site higher straight up
yeah yeah like whatever the opposite of
a not sharp thing is a sharp thing yes
just wicked ice no I'm the only non
writer it's functionally speaking I like
this we're all we're talking about is a
kind of stalagmite yeah right yeah and
you're just going to form itself up into
this like there's a pillar pointing yeah
and then basically this is gonna be like
a pith helmet that rises up boom by
these beasts and then I just wanted to
drive itself through the bottom of this
thing very cool
you see while this is going on Rosie and
VRE that some of the shell just sort of
melts away and lava begins to pour it
around your feet
yeah I'll shape that later
[Laughter]
like is there right now it's closed how
did I open the door you just went
towards this right yeah okay mallamma is
already coming in how far up isn't we're
being lifted right now buoyed right
we're sort of tilted back so he's kind
of making us into the air or there just
got us through the top I just got you
too they can't fly
ya can fire elementals fly rope falls
out of a invisible space above a rope
trick yeah above this thing and I just
climb my ass up into it yeah yeah you
see me disappear and you just see my
hand come down and go okay yeah okay
like you got a like I can I will make
this but I should go last
we should go last because we can climb
real fast okay yeah okay you go up into
the Rope trick in your in Jim's
extra-dimensional party parlor very like
shag rug that beanbags music high up is
there like a catwalk in the walkways up
there whatever it looks like that the
struts that actually come out to the
device are wide enough that a person
could walk across them like in those
stupid and the it's like we gotta go out
here and turn the screws do you want to
go up in there and want me to throw you
up there
wait what there's no way to go in the
dimension or on the up to the thing like
we're gonna need to get like we can't
live in his party shag no you can't so
won't allow it how dark is
how dark is that these walkways how much
longer would you say it's dim light uh
it's it's kind of bright light from
underneath sort of lit red by the lava
ha ha yeah atop them like on top on top
of them there's a shadow okay yeah so
then right now you're still in the
sphere okay so the shadow step I can
teleport from and into dim light or
darkness within sixty feet and it does
not say that I have to have line of
sight on that okay all right yeah so you
offer to throw me and I'm like what am I
do you trust me all right so you do that
yeah you bamps out of the sphere you are
on top of one of the struts
okay staring at this amorphous bloated
thing from the edge of space and time
okay it is the size of an elephant this
malformed creature and it sort of
Jimmer's at you with its oversized head
young black occur from its mouth okay do
I understand what it's saying it's it's
giving it's just sort of gibbering
obscenities oh I I throw some back
obscenity war with this thing yeah yeah
I was like alright social old man what
do you also feel just waves of horrible
necrotic energy coming off this creature
okay and as you kind of stand in its
very presence you take some necrotic
damage some a slow basting of necrotic
alright an exfoliating wave get a clear
10 necrotic damage Oh Mike oh you help
y'all continue to take home normal
healthy again right normal health again
you'll continue to take the damage if
you stay here oh gee turn okay so now
you exchange unpleasant trees with it
okay
I yell up at the wrote this
things got a real attitude problem all
right and you see this stone spike
coming up out of the lava and hit the
bottom of the soul monger and punched
through its underside yes and what
happens at that point eats food right
yeah it does at that point in time as it
breaches you see all of these lights
kind of bleed out through cracks that
are forming in its sides as this thing
you use this pressure builds up and this
thing continues to spear upward it also
causes the strut that you're on the
other she starts to sort of bend upward
slightly as it pushes its weight oh yeah
up tumble latias the whole thing is
being bent in the challenge right now
yeah sorry no because I'm just holier on
the rope
you're just hanging out in my pocket
right well I'm not Sophie I met them
kind of the bottom of the road cuz I was
gonna help you out now your thing is
like a transdimensional cul-de-sac
there's no back door out of it no you
you go in there and that's it it only
advantages its above the lava so right
which is pretty good advantage I would
say it's a plus five stars on Yelp but I
don't want to get stuck in your
cubbyhole not able to like do anything
out here can I can I like Kip off this
off the thing that's in the lava like
like with my hair oh so it's inside you
didn't do his thing outside of them you
did it I did it just above the center Oh
outside outside yeah yeah open the
sphere up climbed out before you you
said that it I'm saying yeah cool I need
the rope
yeah and then I want to I'm gonna I'm
gonna kick and I want the Rope kind of
attached to me because they got to get
out with the rope yeah and then I want
to just kick off how far is it up there
it's about 30 feet 30 feet I can do
because I have a rod of immobility oh
yeah I jump off the ice and if I can't
jump an entire day I jump in entire 30
feet
sure honestly probably in here would be
my guess
30 feet yeah that's not terrible this
isn't like some of your other shit
but yeah wait of the rod if you were to
leap up hit the rod and then spring off
the rod and that's my thought is if I
can what are you I don't want to leave
it I don't want to lose my rod Oh boohoo
well no but so here's I want to do it
and then like tramp ease up yes
and then uncommanded then bring it along
with you I see so after you've got the
momentum fucking crank it up you're
actually literally able to do the thing
I just fucked with you about looking
cool image saw nothing well done I land
on another strut okay I will happily
make a mole sure make a roll whatever
you want paddy fucked up kid you fucker
don't yeah why why bother why you
succeeded go ahead run the gate make a
roll you win the Indy pad
it doesn't work if I don't make a boy I
can't finish if I don't earn dit hey
alright it's 25 yeah that's pretty good
[Laughter]
I know the penalty for insufficient
failure would be that I would probably
lose the rod and it would be fair
no you land on the strut and ya know I
know you have two runs so you're in
you're in my space
yeah I'm zoning out watching this shit
yeah we can see out of it I don't know
there was a three foot by five no and in
fact I am going to cast a spell from you
can't cast spells out of it what if I
like hang out if you're hanging off the
rope you can yeah if you're outside my
pocket yeah if I hang out fifth rope
he's gonna kill me I just bills can't
cross the plane there's no spell barrier
yeah I do have the rope like you could
climb up the rope now to here yeah I
just I feel like spirit Guardians mm
would basically create a kind of it
would transform this larval God and do a
kind of mulch Jim yes sir
you sitting on a beanbag right now yeah
you awakened inside some sort of coffin
okay so he can do whatever he wants I do
a legitimate smell yeah follow all the
rules yep then he put me in a coffin
it's like some sir it's like it's like
this kind of beautiful glass sarcophagus
that you're in hey it's a nice coffin
you piece of shit it's not any amount of
that it's got the acquisitions Inc logo
that you could see through the
transparent lid that that's opened up
now you see looking down upon you a
figure who is part humanoid part cat
welcome to my ship he says my ship we're
on a most excellent voyage
we're chasing after a big dragon and as
soon as you regain consciousness you
instantly become aware just you just
know instantly that there is another Jim
dark magic out there and you want to
kill him you want to kill him dead Jim
in your in your rope trick spell you
suddenly become aware that in the world
there is another Jim dark magic and you
want him dead it's okay yeah Chris I'm
not a smart person you can make an
Arcana check please let me you know make
it twice because there are two of you
I would like eats
[Laughter]
like each gym to making our can achieve
and every year old now
that was new gym obviously obviously old
gym
get him classic 16 plus 8 you believe
that the other gym is a magically
created clone losing the clone spell a
very very high level spell what did you
do this okay now before you become very
angry or if you are already angry I am
or you become angrier I want you to
understand that because I love you I did
make a magical clone of you in case
anything bad happened to this gym is
this you did this yes and you worked it
out with him yes what the fuck
I didn't know
a hundred percent if we would be able to
destroy the soul monger good on me good
job on you everybody did a great job we
came together teamwork makes it this is
happening the soul mongers got this
spire of rock stuck in and all the souls
are leaking out of it and it's just kind
of collapsing in on it yes it's like a
sub in the - well I feel my curse fading
like is my face going back to normal my
skin coming back your soul probably went
into the other one
[Applause]
you piece of shit
I could not abide by a world where there
was not a gym dark magic yeah but I
think two is too many don't I out of my
fuck a dexterity bro that's just goddamn
broke oh can I swing down on the rope
and catch him yeah hold on so I fly out
of this hole
yes and it sucks
so you see him fall out of the Rope
trick go tumbling down the glassy slope
of the world of the Ori you want to
swing down and try to have it yeah like
I know he might pull a magic rabbit out
of his hat but I would prefer to be on
my right down to swoop him up like the
damn foolish I would like you to make a
strength athletics check okay that's to
grapple him that's that's why I fucked
up I rolled your dice okay that is a 20
you grab him okay okay I say I'm not
letting a look at your face they're both
hanging from the road I don't look at
your face but I say welcome to the
company
[Laughter]
I poked my head out can I say he's made
magical clones of us no just him just
him just you and it's because I love you
where is this fucking clone it is in the
airship in what I thought would be a
very nice coffin where is our airship
right now I got last I saw I was outside
this outside of um oh yeah I got all the
upgrades but you don't remember well
yeah yeah I got all the upgrades for
this coffin I spared no expense oh man
you stole my soul Rosa you hear this
exchange down below the creature is is
kind of turning toward the soul monger
it's tethered to this thing is that the
creatures in pop oh no it's like don't
know don't mind me if you stay close to
it you're probably gonna take some more
damage I get away from it does it seem
like it's been weakened by this no it
just seems like it's really really
annoyed okay
I'd you two want a bicker about all of
this you can you can fight later we
really need to get out of this room
see I was I I did I was hoping I would
swing down and like scoop you up and
then finished the arc yeah but I forgot
that you weigh like 400 pounds with your
armor yeah I'll grab the rope - so it's
like quite literally I went at week
like a kid trying to kick his
Kickstarter swing back up it's not
working I start slowly letting out more
rope okay we gonna fix this omen how are
we gonna fix this each time they're
getting close to the lava no no I think
no listen Jim Jim yeah this is a big
mistake
and you know it's a big mistake do i I
hope so
I hope that that's what you know because
I'm allergic to lava I would say that
this is a pretty huge fucking deal
I say Jim hang on one second
and I cast spirit guardians in the area
around this larval God so that it begins
being chipper shredded by radiant damage
I say all right now that that's handled
what we have is incredible and I could
not stand to lose it can I look pretty
can I get am I starting to swing
slightly black and put this yeah yes you
are another exit I've just had it I'm
like you guys were awake way more fun
when you were children I'll do a
perception roll 12 to find any other
exit out of here
you can you basically run to the end of
the bridge yeah you can see that there
are there is a staircase okay going up
out of here that you can run up okay you
don't know where it goes all right you
can make a beeline for that I recognize
that this is sort of like Russian
nesting dolls but can I cast
teleportation circle inside my
dimensional my space
no because you could only teleport to
another place within that space that
plane that plane okay you you probably
have like fly I'm guessing I don't think
I can fly I'll say Jim I can fall
gracefully but Jim
I will use stone shape I'm done being
angry and now I'm just disappointed I
will use stone shape so the bottom of
the rope is like sin I will use stone
shape to make a disc the size that you
need for the television partition circle
over the lava I need 10 feet I got it I
can flattens five by five by five I can
flatten it out you make that circle we
all leave we have a conversation you we
have a conversation about how to kill
Jim dark magic rosy as you run up the
stairs you can see that I guess the last
time VRE hopped up on his ledge the
lizard must have scuttled down because
it's following you oh okay so liberation
alright it will sort of lead you out to
another one of these escape hatches
okay hein the scenes thing all right I'm
gonna use sama Turchi okay which up to
allow my voice to boom up to three times
as loud as normal and I say hey idiots
there's an exit over here follow me
they'll never fit oh no just kidding
vine
[Laughter]
[Applause]
all right so Rosie wrote with the help
of her new lizard companion that you can
take with you wherever you go
I say Jim Jim I I can take it in to my
other campaign yes I say Jim we have the
rest of our lives to argue about this
come down so you're sorry
what the fuck are you talking about it
doesn't mean you were wrong but you can
you can be sorry you can be shy
you can be a loser and he needs these
Jim the Ori just sort of sinks down Jim
I'm sorry can we leave the tomb of
annihilation I'm sorry for manufacturing
a mystical clone of you without your
knowledge that I would have loved a
little more and was wrong I want you to
remember one thing
cloning requires consent
I'm with you can we leave yeah you make
a stone disk on the lava yeah exactly I
stone disk right on top of the lava and
move on down the Rope yeah I have a
teleportation circle in my house you
inscribe the teleportation circle on
this disk of hard hot yeah magma but
you're sort of tiptoeing around I feel
like Full Metal Alchemist you slam your
hand down it goes soul yeah yeah and
then I just walk off the rope you do
that morbid creature above you hang in
there just sort of mouthing trying to
get the souls that are sort of floating
and he is making the inscription and I'm
just like and you can see some wraiths
come out of its body and start to fly
around down toward you but by then you
activate your spell okay and in a flash
of light you are all vanished
Hey
[Laughter]
everybody thank you so much
thank you everyone great having you as
an audience enjoy the rest of your show
and come back tomorrow for acquisitions
Inc the C team
you