this podcast features adults using adult
language you have been warned
remember when Olman created a clone of
Jim without him knowing I'm sure that
will end well
[Music]
[Applause]
oh boy hello welcome to acquisitions
incorporated please allow me to
introduce my players for this evening
Jerry Hawkins playing omen drawn
Holly Conrad playing Strix
Morgan Webb playing more game
in Patrick Rothfuss playing VRE
oh boy are you guys ready to play
Dungeons &amp; Dragons absolutely that's too
bad I thought because that's not what
I've got here I didn't know we would
have different seats
I don't usually carry this is its I
promise that this is it's me just like
from another angle I feel like I'm
cheating like I'm like so when I think
of Dungeons and Dragons I like to think
of that as a starting point like
Hamburger Helper yeah really that's
where we begin D&amp;D is the helper and
I've added the hamburger is that our
bodies yes so I'm gonna go ahead and say
that right now you guys have been you've
been wrangled into this team-building
exercise by omen and you are currently
falling through the sky towards an
island that you have never seen before
in your life so pretty much a Tuesday
pretty much a Tuesday I'm screaming yeah
can we get a sample see you guys are
falling towards this island and oh man
you recognize that you have a map that
came with sort of the the starter like
an oriental orient can see yeah yeah but
falling towards this island you hear
I like I like the image of him like a
plummeting yo yeah his death and he's
like oh wait unfair yo so as we're
falling I say alright team meeting team
meeting yes you guys hear a voice
echoing through the sky it is i wizard
unknown ma'am you know who you are yeah
I think no I'm unknown my bad no we know
who you are no we saw the intro yeah
well but still it could be anybody
you don't know you are currently falling
towards a magical island of my own
creation on this island you will find
many traps and dangers you will also
find treasure oh man yes you have a map
of the island yes I'm looking at it okay
and on that map you will find the named
location sort of the points of interest
mm-hmm it is in these locations that you
will find treasure chest containing
valuable loot okay something to think
about that's all I'm saying
now it isn't very important that you do
not split the party there are four of
you in this group and in total there are
100 souls currently plummeting towards
their death on my island there can be
only one party at the end that will win
the final prize which is your lives and
the revealing of who wizard unknown
actually is
is that Wow this deck yeah is there a
value associated with that information
like a monetary value No
who could put a value on such suspensive
main reward we like don't want to know
it's pret you're gonna know I'm not
saying you if you win you will find out
who I am wizard unknown it's priceless
all right now the first thing you need
to decide as you're plummeting towards
this islands is where you would like to
land I've got so many bad impulses cuz I
I played pub G with a bunch of people
and there's always that guy who like
scythes off to like his favourite place
no matter where the team decides to go
it's not gonna be you I'm not that guy
okay so IIST i establish i tell you that
if you have a moment just think back to
your contract particularly the anti
skiving ordinances that i feel were very
clear in subsection C but yes so it
looks like it looks like these are our
situations here and we can we can choose
any one you're yeah you are falling
towards this island you can see it
spread out before you there's a forest
sort of in the north you can see what
looks like the lights of a village to
the east a volcano with lava smoke
blooming out of it in the South I mean
these are all valid locations
yeah I'm gonna knit my brow because
there I just I just let everybody know
ahead of time I say listen there is a
negative adjectives associated with each
of these I don't I mean I don't want to
I don't want to talk out of school but I
feel like they're all bad I don't think
there is a good one I mean I guess there
could be a case to be made that
crumbling is better than frightening or
corrupt violent is probably not good no
no it's not defensible say people can
hide in the trees around it so like the
good looting
locations are gonna be a little
dangerous no okay so that's that is
actually I think that that's wise I
think that there's probably a case to be
made that we want to land someplace
where we stand a chance to have some
obstruction between us and the rest of
this situation so how you thinking where
where are you aiming yourselves as
you're sort of falling now in freefall
you're heading towards this island at a
ridiculous speed you gotta you gotta
pick a location so I'm guessing not many
people cuz I like to start just like
anywhere where I can get some gear cuz i
suck it up geez
yeah yeah yeah we know we want to get
some shit I'm like who in their right
mind would go to the maddening map go to
the map mapping so we double think it
and nobody who only up only a maddening
person would go there or or a person who
had already been previously maddened yes
that's me all right no I think this is a
huge yes and my suspicion is that the
the you know choking clouds of dark mist
over this might also provide some cover
for our descending bodies now in my
actual poison damage from the sole
frisky okay well thanks a lot Ranger am
I actually make it I need to feel the
need to establish this would you would
you like a loincloth there's something I
can give you a little we could fashion
you I care less about the it's just like
if I'm going towards a volcano and you
want a hat on or something well I have a
hat specifically is what I was thinking
of yeah I ever had you know I'm good
with that could I be wearing a hat sure
okay the lava which would be some kind
of a Joschka but it's a it's like a
branded wizard unknown it came and it
came with the kit came with the kit yeah
my god can we find different outfits on
the island you guys are gonna have to
explore oh now I'm excited okay now
are we good are we are we down to get
maddened in this way yeah
all right right aye aye aye yo call the
meeting to order I jabbed my finger that
maddening Mountains
marker on the spot exactly and then
we'll start guiding ourselves over
coordinating a landing like this is not
easy okay
so I'm gonna need some acrobatics checks
anchor what a crew are in freefall
trying to link up with each other and
fall to a designated place I'm gonna
need an acrobatics check okay here's
what I'd like to propose I would like
you know if you see those skydivers in
teams and they all like join hands they
form like a flower yeah we can try I
think that you might have I think that
that is like the dexterity side of the
table and this is this not next I'm just
really trying not to think about my junk
out with all this yeah it's like a wind
sock or know it's like the wave YouTube
man at like a user Park just like it's
just going crazy yeah it's going crazy
there are deals here no it's generating
lift yeah you might be able to grab onto
that look I know she is but there's a
blind spot that she is placing here no
so so people often describe the wind is
wild sure do you think animal handling
no I appreciate the effort maybe it's
just that seat like to the right of the
GM no here here's you dexterity people
you need to fix this can I take one of
these poor flailing I haven't seen a
roll you undermine please don't take me
oh no I'm going for Jerian you want to
grab I'm coming for you all right
I cover my face neck yeah you know they
get it in the eyes well I want to get
lacerated No
why is it sure I didn't ask him well I
will happily make make this acrobatics
roll okay jack robotics hey that's the
number on the dice get ready for this
shit that's an 18 that's a 6 ok you go
you're going for me right yeah yari
you're able absolutely to grab on to
omens risk and me
never mind kid continue please war game
is sort of pulling away from you guys
I'd like to think that we had we looked
at each other we're like you good right
we were gonna get them and then I went
off and I look back I thought we had a
communication it was a plan yeah her
hairs in her eyes can tell what's up and
down Strix do you have an acrobatics
role for sure Wow I mean that's plus
deck so it's a 13 that's good that's
good yeah you grabbed onto omen so we
got omen VRE omen do you want to roll
anything you want to roll me something
sure I mean you're trying to maintain
the sort of you know this ring of people
okay I have a negative 1 2 acrobatics
okay but let you use but athletics he
throw me
all right I like athletics I'm just a
fight against these wins and I'm
basically gonna use him as like a cat's
paw to secure the Ranger the fuck is the
cat's paw he's gonna be like my paw like
a real cat I don't think that's what a
what is what a cat that's a thing dice
now didn't help no all right plus 3 I am
toast oh I love that I love that the
most absolute kiss oh he's great holding
on to you by the way I wanted that I
wanted that so bad oh great that's great
you actually managed to slip out of the
Ahri's grass but we're still together
yeah oh just been wheeling through the
year guys you guys are currently
plummeting towards the maddening
mountains you had intended upon landing
right in the Cal right in the Yeah right
in the caldera but you don't do that
you land close to it so this little red
AI marker wises your view guys
technology right there so you have
landed in a square just outside the
maddening mountains okay as you descend
you can feel when you're about 300 yards
above the ground feather fall a magical
effect takes over and you sort of gently
land upon the grass
I assume this tricks is doing this and I
think her profusely I'm mad that it's
not mine
do you take credit for it though I just
don't say anything and just look scared
so upon landing you can see in front of
you the maddening mountains rising up
huge peaks with a volcano at the top
just spewing out black smoke and all
around you though it's just green grass
couple trees bushes it's a beautiful
open field
rich rich lush grass and you guys are
free to explore this area now let me
explain how this is kind of
I have here a deck of cards that I call
the exploration deck okay if you would
like to explore a square that you were
on and look for cool weapons don't
looking for stuff
yeah I'm just I want to make sure that
okay also get it I benefit it's easy all
you have to do is roll me a perception
check or any other check that you think
might aid you in finding cool stuff on a
magic island maybe you have that skill
yeah this is this is a collection of all
the good stuff that you'll be able to
find on this island including pants
probably yeah would anyone like to
explore the square that you have lived
in and please remember that there is no
time pressure at all really you guys
should explore the space I feel like
your time I feel like the number went
down and then also someone annihilated
someone else they're dying that's true
but you guys don't need to worry about
that not us okay
time yeah I know I'll and like full like
neo like awesome me over here Oh landed
yeah that's fair sharing me into a tree
effectively probably yeah I'm
immediately looking for all the places
that you would put a premium chest I'm
listening for that that twinkling sound
over the roaring of the volcano you
cannot hear the twinkle chest great but
you know because wizard unknown told you
so yeah that in these these named
locations there there are chests there
are riches yeah so you can explore this
safe I'm going to I'm going to explore
this stuff with my perception check my
perception is much better than my
acrobatics
[Laughter]
I want that sign yeah you should you
can't write this you it's some kind of
aura that you exude I don't know what it
is so what do I find
what's what is that add up to nine okay
draw the first card off the top of the
exploration deck this is called a stupid
mace it's plus zero to hit and the
damage is to d6 is that it's just why
would you say to this 1 d6 26 and what
are the two squares that's interesting
what are the two squares I don't know
durability what time you use that mace
you piece of shit
[Laughter]
each time you that stupid mace I need
you to mark off one of those boxes you
put this on top didn't you I shuffled
these cards my friends these are the
fates I don't trust them
so can we each search in each square
absolutely would you like to search 20
20 I would like for you to take the top
two cards choose one oh and just guard
the other eye I found a rock that looks
kind of like a dog I want that I want it
and they didn't rapier Wow now the
important thing to remember is that each
of you may only hold four cards at one
time so right now that's not a big deal
you couldn't absolutely hold on to that
rock that looks kind of like a dog want
it for now
you know one of those items so you do
need to discard I'm taking the rock
okay
there's a decent rapier what have you
ever played D&amp;D before this is gonna be
super important before the end of this
is obvious this is a wondrous figurine
of some sort no I mean is maybe a god no
I wrote it in gray because it's trash
[Music]
[Applause]
you can't use it how big is it
no it's about that that last there's no
this last forever yeah yeah no
durability durability you got that rock
now yep
cuz your rock that looks kind of like it
does I'm a little dazed because I was
thrown naked into a tree team-building
team-building all right I'm going whoa
very healthy too yeah top two choose one
discard the other well you got enough
flavor get the heat I really do want to
bow but I also want a health potion or a
human taking the potion okay Trix are
you gonna check I love I just imagine I
just landed like hat first like like a
jerk 16 let's hop to take one discard
the other alright I'm ready
give me some trash yeah an empty basket
I demand that one of you to take a
useful but it's trash just Rick's got a
trash empty basket know what you could
use that for crazy-ass Warhammer okay
but if I get this can I can I give it to
omen yet Trading is absolutely allowed
okay do you have any trash if I would
argue that a stupid mace with plus zero
to hit and 1d6 damage constitutes trash
yes I you know I'm fair with that I'll
trade you this sweet-ass water first
take it okay
and we'll talk about trading okay I'll
take that away but I'm only doing it
because I want to survive all right so
you you've discarded the empty basket oh
man are you gonna look around here at
all but it was the same as not doing it
now if you would like to trade an item
you guys can trade whatever you want now
moving from square to square and trading
items in Battle Royale can be eventful
so if you move or if you trade you have
to draw a card from the event deck
because who knows what might happen just
point of clarification do we all get to
trade or only two people one card gets
drawn from the event deck and anybody
can trade you can trade it back and
forth however many times you like is it
possible to search a box it looks like
that do you want to keep searching
there's no time limit there's nothing
there's no independent of any kind this
island is all yours at no point will it
be restricted geographically
we have to look we have we have to look
one more time maybe then we'll explore I
wanna get getting up into up into that
that the yellow you want to move up into
the maddening mount oh yeah yeah there
with with my my spirit animal here this
rock that kind of looks like a dog
well would you guys like to explore this
square or would you like to move north
up into the maddening mountains or would
you like to trade well this one does a
lot of damage so we should trade well
and here's the other night we'll have so
much more to trade all of you can use
any weapon Owen if you find a trash
shortbow use it however you only have
access to your entire character sheet if
you use the weapon appropriate for your
character so you will find in this game
staves so I say it staves stance - find
Stoker's yeah we'll find malls and
hammers of different kinds you will find
boughs of various sorts and you will
find swords of different kinds now you
could like I said you can use anything
but if you want access to your entire
entire character sheet all your
abilities you've got to have the right
weapons Oh like including all of the
abilities all of your abilities
otherwise it's just whatever you've got
whatever the card says so I'm kind of
like a naked baby again first the second
oh you have a rock it looks kind of like
a dog
okay yeah that is a bonus all right here
I would say the right call is to search
one more time here because if there's
another party or another group out there
when we flip this card I want to make
sure that we are not annihilated that's
fair
can we just double search the same air
absolutely you can stay in this square
and search as long I don't there's no
reason to I don't like this yeah I'm
gonna search again do we hear screams
every once in a while you do hear a
stream okay okay all right
scared well that says liquefied all
right here we go you ready yep let's see
explore Oh 23 top two cards of the
exploration deck health potion and
worthless quarter staff oh ah but that
would give Strix access to all her
spells it would yeah worthless cord of
staff or plus 10 health potion no yeah
we have to keep the worthless quarter
staff I think just so we can give you
your your juice does anybody else wanna
stretch here 14:14 geez yeah top two
cards pick one that's yes please do not
ooh sweet-ass Warhammer you have a pilot
I'm up or a decent rapier Oh
c31 already haven't asked for him have
you are you repair with you yeah I would
be I might have made a different choice
if I hadn't known that like I couldn't
use like evasion or like any of my know
anything don't worry don't worry Pat
I'll be making up I'm sorry
explaining
as we go okay so with that rapier I will
hand this to him
that will be the final piece that we
need so once we trade we will be able to
all be able to use our abilities even if
the individual weapons are not the maybe
I'll get lucky I'll find out yeah first
you yeah you can discard the sweet-ass
Warhammer and you're gonna keep the
rapier yes okay okay
Pat you're gonna you're gonna poke
around here look up ten top card off the
deck oh I'm sorry that's that was a lie
that is a there's a nine still top card
off the deck yeah a broken Cup can I can
i I'm assuming that I'm like rummaging
through like you're just looking through
bushes oh shit old ruins all kinds of
stuff back by the rock that looked like
a dog I did find a rapier and that I
just kind of I mean I hoped it away
disappear oh isn't that crazy
yeah a wizard did it yeah I wonder which
one here he's unknown find some trash
wait wait no I look around strict I mean
yeah I'm really Joseph er he's trash oh
that's only a six top card off the
exploration deck please be trash I'm
like showing everyone look yeah all
right here now it's time now we should
need to trade so do we have the right
ship that we need to do us all right and
then we're out of here I will let you
trade first and then I will have you
draw from the event deck okay I would
trade broking Cup for the same button no
this is mine
I will trade you the quarter staff for
this war hammer thank you very much for
this but I won't even demand the rock
yeah that would be a hard one for me but
you might be able to get some mileage
out of this with strikes later if you
she's just eyeing all the tracks the
currency right sorry oh yeah have you
guys traded I would say maybe if you
have another weapon she's flying empty
right now she doesn't have a bow
we don't have a shitty shouldn't have
that I know I took the health potion
okay stupid mace it's a it's a d6
that's not terrible eating nothing all
right no but seems like to draw the
event card oh man you wonder oh yeah
you're having great luck so far why
don't you get on that yes screen open
field happens oh you will find that
there you will find that there are three
types of cards in the event deck green
which means hey keep going you having a
great time yellow which is gonna slow
you down and red it's gonna be a real
pain in the fucking ass now yeah guys
you guys are fine you've traded there's
nothing here to worry about would you
like to move would you like to explore I
say now let's move up into this
interesting yellow box and see if
there's anything cool in that square
that's it's probably nothing but good
there yeah if it's a just universe then
we'll probably get advantage on those
rules in the yellow boxes what I'm
guessing yeah you move up one yeah
alright so you move towards the
maddening mountains and you can see that
there is an entrance sort of a cave that
takes you inside the mountain and as you
enter you can feel the heat from the
magma that's flowing around in here yes
a magma but you can also hear a tinkling
sounds a sound that draws you towards it
and as you move deeper into these caves
you see a treasure chest
a massive treasure wooden treasure chest
beautifully tinkling just waiting to be
opened however you also see four elves
all of them ladies coming towards you
from a different cavern they've also
spotted this oh there's multiple
entrances just a warren of entrances
right Warren G weren't a Warren G now
there are four of these elven warriors
they are like you unarmed unarmored but
they have got their eyes on this
what's this horseshit did something
happen
oh that's interesting
I don't wouldn't worry about that it's
alright yeah we need to kill these
people real fast
oh you're fine we're not fine fine not
fine totally good now there's four of
these belts Oh fine
nah I would like my ball to roll for
initiative initiative but I you got 13
also all the same each time so 15 can I
get a roll off or something you know Dex
my Dex is negative all right we're gonna
have the re go then yeah you have very
strict something need um are we all kind
of like this is close quarters I'm
assuming your cave relative yeah it's a
cave it's close quarters
yeah so you see that now that they're
closer to you you can see that all of
these elephant worriers have tattoos on
their faces one of them that seems like
the leader she's the one in front she
has a star over one of her eyes one of
the ones in the back has sort of animal
on is tattooed over her eyes there's
another one that has diamonds and
there's one that has a crescent moon
okay what's what
[Laughter]
the one was the star is the one that has
spotted you she directs her her friends
to get the chest while she comes up on
you guys we got to deal with this check
but first is more game you have a stupid
mace I do and a broken Cup and a broken
Cup the stupid mace is plus zero to hit
it feels damn sweet but the elven
warrior in front of you has nothing
she's just balling up her fists okay 14
oh yeah that hit two damage okay she
grunts a little bit but she's not she
doesn't see him put out really by it and
she's gonna try to punch you in the face
now because you have no armor on you
your ACS are a little bit different yeah
special but I still don't think a ten
hits more game No
so she takes the swing at you and you
take a step back it's not hard to avoid
VRE you can see that the other elves are
sort of making a beeline the one
specifically with the Moon the crescent
moon over her eye is going towards the
chest
is she close enough that I can get like
sneak attack okay yeah we're all we're
all in a very close environment okay you
can jump on her then I'll do that oh I
can't do do wildung available because
you have a decent rape you it's just
your normal character she's never your
plus to hit all that stuff don't worry
about the damage that's only if you
don't okay you're not VRE uh-oh well
that'll data that's like a 20/20 in
change one two three just whatever ones
you want
in there that doesn't matter pick your
favorite dice take all the colors you
like
so yes how'd you do that is 20-20-20
Amman julienned murdered
I do 27 and I scum I am I am also just
extremely naked and I and I just like
just she fountain of blood and I'm like
kill everyone
[Laughter]
perfect see what's left of her falls
against the chest and then settles to
the ground I would like you to take your
sharpie and Mark off one of those boxes
[Music]
yeah we gotta go next is you want a
fireball all the elves LDLs okay so I
don't hit my party you can do that right
yeah I have yeah I already I already
rolled I didn't 33 damage you dilt 33
damage - how many people all of them all
of them all the elves yeah okay taken
save for half they could say for half
your they're gonna have to try yes I
already ate d6 huh what's your save oh
it is it should be 18 18 Oh 16 sorry sir
I need to save Dimond is okay well
Huntress rolled in 19 she's okay wow
he's got half you know it's a ton I'm
super impressed half damage
I was like I can't do that math it's
gonna be fine don't worry about it
I can't do math under pressure how much
how much damage it was 33 so half of 33
yeah yeah so it's 1616 okay I can't do
math my why plus one of them is taken a
couple from more game uh yeah diamond is
destroyed you mean literally erupts in
flames and she is killed huntresses star
hurt pretty bad Huntress is the one with
the eyes okay I know screaming so I
don't know I said so nice they're gonna
go next though uh Huntress is going to
go after omen she has nothing so she's
gonna try to punch you in the face
mm-hmm and here's the interesting thing
I rolled the 12 but almond without any
armor yeah your DC is nine yeah mine
yeah I know it's not high that's why
we're plate yeah so I hit damage is
eight man just BAM right to the jaw it's
tough lean and oh man you are up last
okay now oh man you noticed that you can
feel sort of a vibration in them in the
map and you can see what looks like a
green flame eight points eight points of
damage
alright so so she she punches me and I
can't just right in the jaw lets you
have it alright so it's gonna come up
like as though from nowhere your sweet
ass your sweet ass Warhammer okay it
emerges okay and you do a spell like
they can kill both of them in one turn I
can try so that plenty of time are they
both close enough to really really hurt
I don't think they're both close enough
to you for a melee that would hit both
of them no that's crazy but you could
absolutely pick either Huntress or star
yeah exactly
don't you have like your column flame
you call I have a
solemn but it only doesn't hit like all
people everywhere well there this is
these are close quarters yeah yeah
that's not my business I have employees
for that I tell you what I might be
close but like I can take a hit if it
means you can kill both of them
no I don't have it I don't have that
that's how I do stuff so here well
here's what I'm gonna do I am gonna
sacred flame them because that doesn't
require that role so that dish is up 1d8
radiant damage
let's get seven huntresses destroyed
star is on her last legs she's bleeding
she's got looks like a broken arm like
she's in bad shape but she's not down
yet
and we are gonna go back up to the top
with more game I'm gonna use my stupid
mace what's that oh right right right
sorry
you guys have killed oh no you know it's
okay three people already and let's see
VRE you killed somebody right yep Strix
killed somebody that's awesome
I did it nice work all right star is
left or game would you like to do walk
away in shame at my one that's tough
that's bad luck yeah uh stars up next
she's gonna try to punch you in the face
fair I mean it's totally fair ya know
even even without armor your AC is like
14 we're hard to hit you're still a cool
and she is bones she's hurt so bad you
she tries to punch you but it's really
just like a flailing of her arms like a
little bad it's sad it's really sad
she's like
the wizard brought me here just like you
yeah where's my children anyway
VRE you're up next yow killer you still
got your distance no they're 14 yeah
14 hits okay and I do I just all the
damage late not gonna take a lot it's
like one of those six one is really good
okay yeah she is beheaded oh you
Julian's her Oh her name was Julian hey
we got it like we gotta open the chest
and we have yeah you want to you want to
open the chest
yeah I'm just gonna take her head yeah
okay
I don't have a card for that you want to
make note on your character
imitating go ahead and open your
treasure chest done and push healing
potion where in there is there not
there's not I'll give you the wrong
chest give me that Gold's and purples
and purples this is a man what that
means these treasure chests are
incredible these are awesome sound to
dry then the rod rate sort that sort is
great um chief of staff that's very nice
and Maul of the year
mell of the year you can only hold four
items and you have a rock someone who
needs you to make some hard choices
oh you I want you to I want you to end
up with four cards you son of them I
know I know
now while you're thinking about that I'm
going to talk to the rest of you saw how
incredible that chest was right yeah I
have a stack of chest here if you would
like to open one it's five dollars Oh
God it's five US tons of them oh my god
what's in this one
Gold's Purple's oh you want chess
that you're making money bacon money
thank you buddy can I just like grind
for an hour
you've got there's no time restraint
here that's really coming in we do
nothing in on you old and longbow okay
so I have it good you can have a long
time I'm gonna I'm gonna keep them all
the year ever you betrayed I'm gonna get
rid of the great sword and the splendid
rod woof
but then I'll keep these and I'm gonna
give these to you guys yeah okay okay
hold no home so you got rid of a
splendid rod and a great story these are
two purples and you have kept the rock
that looks it doesn't I want to
emphasize this in the moments we have
left it looks kind of like a bog it
doesn't look like a dog it's like it's
like the bird organ it represents yes
it's all right here get that shit okay
get that shit get that shit get that we
could trade right now and now no a trade
are we gonna do a trade event yes we
should we should but you have to have
four cards before we can trade right
yeah I did you see your four cards
what's your in your inventory I'm gonna
keep two longbows I feel like I want to
hand this to you
whoa radial pushin unless you want the
terrific mall you know this one's plus
silks I'm gonna be okay let me take that
one because of all of the year okay you
can get rid of that Molly now you're
good yeah those here four cards yeah
please feel free to trade and then I
would like for you to draw from the
event deck all the year bori bori we
super gotta go no now we gotta draw this
card have to drive that card it'll
probably be green nope blessings of
unicorns a blessing of unicorn so as you
are as you are here in the caves all of
a sudden you notice unicorns just start
coming in from all the different
entrances into this cave until there is
a herd of them I say fear not friends
the Unicorn is a gentle creature now you
are currently surrounded by a herd of
unicorns is called a blessing
a blessing of unicorns to exit this area
I will need all of you to make an animal
handling check or stealth or kill the
unicorn seduction I wouldn't allow it I
actually I'm assuming I had disadvantage
with the unicorns I'm gonna handle are
gonna handle up on this unicorn I was
gonna do stealth check okay let's get to
it else that works yeah whoa one blob
one
yeah you you are crawling underneath
hooves unicorn dongs they're all there
just right underneath them well it's
like a beaded curtain yeah trotting them
get through without any trouble go go go
here we go I'm gonna handle these beasts
okay oh yeah absolutely - one hand on
the snout and you pass through I'm misty
step oh that worked I don't want to do
anything I don't want this at all okay
yuck oh I can do stuff yeah yeah
13 13 is there no 17 17 yeah absolutely
no hey you know what you're just kidding
we gotta go we're leaving really north
south east or west north east all right
we got to go up down left or right okay
North nor I'm like beating every time
you move I need you to draw from the
event deck here's there's this thing
open field all right East or North no
where's my strong event garden great a
crumble her lone Rando Oh No so you can
see this guy he's covered in blood he's
obviously lost his entire party it is
the only one I've been driven mad he's
been driven mad by it you guys I'm gonna
keep the same initiative order so we
have two reroll that Morgaine would you
like to this guy is he comes up on you
yeah I'm in a longbow with my +6 to hit
Turkey I can add my Colossus layer
because he's already been damaged right
yeah absolutely there's a lot all right
so 16 16 hits yes okay so now we're
gonna do 2d 8 plus 4
and I'll need you to make a mark on that
bow so that you lost some dirt for five
plus six seven eight nine plus nine ten
eleven twelve thirteen for my favorite
week ow
yeah murdered zero right between the
eyes good all right
what action would you like to go we're
gonna go north yeah yeah okay take his
head - I tie them to my back all right
all right we're gonna go north yep
glowing obelisk is that a good kind of a
blue screen yes so you arrive at this
obelisk and you can feel that your
weapons as you get close to it are sort
of regaining their durability so each of
you can regain one durability on an item
I'm gonna put a smiley face next to me
exactly does anything happened to the
rock that looks like okay yeah it still
looks it actually honestly now that you
look at again account looks less like a
dog like if I did the light kind of less
I'm just gonna write alright hey so what
do you think about East folks you guys
want to keep moving or you can explore
right yeah let's uh
yes yeah over in that you're in a circle
that's no no no this is this we if we're
ever gonna explore this is the
opportunity right now no no no we want
to get into one of those chests places
do we want to do testing or also spend
five dollars at any time you know I
gotta say I respect the commitment here
no you're right if we're gonna take the
time to search we want to be getting we
want to be opening the cheezy II yeah
okay all right now how deep is this
water I mean you haven't you haven't
approached it all right we're gonna go
north then I got no acceptable actually
I say more in you'll I go in in towards
like the crumbling Terry either way you
know I can't summon four crocodiles that
we could then ride it's kind of like a
car oh I love that it's like a scaly car
yeah
this sounds fine we might have our own
dude I am in today I want this the most
well I need it's like it's like a it's
like a pool floatie exactly right
we're gonna let's hit the savage see
you're going north yeah yeah we're gonna
let's go on to the island with our Crocs
okay is that cool yeah very hard please
as you move north but you cloud of
poison oh I need everybody to make me a
constitution check as this green cloud
of poisonous gas rolls onto the field is
their constitution saving thrower to sit
Constitution save 300 20s great yeah
yeah we got team throw up over here okay
that's 11 I'm fine you guys just
something I ate
you're okay yeah you guys both take six
damage as you just coughing up gawking
your lungs something looks like maybe it
belongs the inside you pick it up put it
back in Strix tries to take it first no
no no any bad of that yeah do you want
to summon alligator crocodiles to travel
across this water yes I do
absolutely please do so the each of you
gets a crocodile yep you look under your
seat what direction you wanna go north
oh yeah we want to get into that box so
we can get that gold chest yeah all
right
draw an event card you move north cool
unflinching eye of earth SOG jeez so as
you guys are sailing out into the water
a stock comes up out of the sea with a
massive eyeball on top of it I say no
it's just scanning in all directions
obviously looking for anyone who might
be out here I need stealth checks what
can I just close my eyes and pretend
it's not there know if you it still sees
you it says so in the rules that hurts
that's not great good I'm surprisingly
stealthy actually yeah 19 you're fine I
didn't see you at all
9 yeah you're gonna take
mm-hm eight damage from the eye of her
sog whoo eight damage yeah I'm just
closing my eyes I can state oh but you
rolled a 9 oh yeah yeah I know
I'm not take your eight damage I'm not
proud of it I'm just that's just what is
up yeah would you guys like to move up
one more space into the savage sea
oh yes oh yeah that's what we're about
more event card please put you abandoned
campsite Oh you each everybody gets to
draw one card off the exploration deck
that's succulent you want to do you want
to distribute thank you throwing cards
is so satisfying golden longbow can she
do a wield those long absolutely health
potion here lucky rabbit's foot
that's exciting whoa but it shouldn't be
gray I never know it seems like useful
item you know a sweet ass hold on you
guys can also hear the tinkling of a
chair what the fuck yeah just in the
wind the water this is the entire water
square yeah I'd like everyone to imagine
that campsite
there's a tiny island out there who
would like to open this chest okay who's
got you got I mean you have ever I mean
we all have stuff I'm trying to think it
Artie Artie here you know here here here
here
wait can I drink my shield potion up
open up a slot here I'm gonna drink my
shield potion +5 10:45 temp HP right now
I have a space open now I can open up
you want to pop up in the chef e please
remember extra chests are only five
dollars yes okay terrific terrific mall
now is it the mall of the year no right
but it's good
here is a second mall of the year that's
a plus splendid ass rod and a golden is
there mama there yeah
splendid Astro Astro here here so does
anybody here lucky rabbit's foot right
in the trash Oh yuck no here
terrific mall also trash sweet-ass
Warhammer you're filth actually and then
I'm gonna get the terrific Maul and keep
that sweet that's where amorous garbage
it's in the current meta like nobody you
said nobody uses it I have a splendid
rod now you have a chisim chief-of-staff
so you're good I'm gonna keep this
scimitar to trade out this entire case
more game needs it if I if we get a
chance to trade if I had two weapons I
could use to think about you guys are
always welcome to trade whenever you
feel like you want to take some time
it's safe made your eye it's totally
safe now here's your thing you can hear
more tinkling I've never been more
fuckin tense in my kill it probably oh
did ya you I did I did reddit more
twinkling yeah you hear more twinkling
and as you sort of look up onto this
island that's out here in the savage see
you can see that on the islands is a
statue okay
approaching it you see that the statue
is of sort of a humanoid figure about
life-size maybe a little larger and it's
on a pedestal and it's holding a chalice
up to its mouth and you can hear from
below it that tinkling that treasure
sound I don't want to go there cuz he
feel free to bunny here's to time and
explore what secrets could it hold is
the chalice part of the stone of the
statute yes it is all made of stone so
we think there's some I'm just gonna
break the statue down right I wanna I
will I will do acrobatics against the
statue I don't know what I would do
investigation investigation sure
absolutely you can move up on it okay
take a closer look on a pitched
investigation
[Laughter]
seven just a seven yeah pretty cool
statue this is a bitch instead yeah it's
made of like marble got a great cup yes
look at it yeah I'm gonna look at it but
I'm gonna use the skill perception I
like it yes so now you're right up on
this statue you can see that it has the
stone chalice up to its mouth but sort
of in its mouth you can see two fangs oh
okay
it just needs some blood I'm covered in
blood right sure yeah you did kill that
you hated that lady that squeeze talking
about some like juice stereotype shit
like really good in there squeezing him
out yeah the whole time I was but you
guys don't trust me you know it was
brilliant play yes who's the blood fills
up the chalice the statue begins to
drink it and once it's done the statue
slides back on invisible rails and you
can see another chest I just drink throw
the heads in there I didn't even have to
pay five dollars
oh sweet there's a health potion and
another help to health pots another
Chiefs double up on the chief in a
terrific multi think you have a bar do
you have a terrific mall alright good so
down to four cards
yes well I'm going to take a health
potion and get rid of my worthless
reporter staff yeah that's fair um I
don't need this anymore
don't so I'm all gonna take another
chief of staff I think yeah double up on
that and I'm just keeping my shiny
button thank you guys that's mine
alright
I I can't sign I can't say boo I mean
you you delivered an A+ product here and
I want to support you thank you the
shiny button is mine you don't hear any
more tinkling hmm gosh okay so over off
the east over off on the east side of
whip out the map real quick yeah yeah
look close it looks like you are well
within this circle whatever it means
dorm yeah and there's really no reason
to think that it will constrict again I
do is there a house with a bathroom with
a door that I could close you just want
to hide I'm not saying hide I'm saying
tactically hide in the bathroom
[Laughter]
how large like that how large is the
area below the statue oh that held the
chest just big enough for a chest in the
chest is occupying it so it was open oh
the stuff out that would be funny though
like one of us could get in the chest
there's a great different ya know then
you say glow glow probably better yeah
yeah okay so over on the over off on the
east it seems like there's a kind of
landing that'll give us access to some
paths into the interior I don't know I
we could ride these crocodiles all the
way up the river you're not wrong you're
not wrong and that's I want to get a lot
of value out of these Crocs yeah so I
say we go north and the north and then
try to go inland via that River event
card please it's probably uneventful I
can see that it's red alright yeah what
do you mean by razor vine
oh now as you move onto the island you
can see it before in front of you this
whole area just erupts with briar
covered in razor sharp thorns Wow brah I
need everybody to make me a dexterity
check to see if you avoid being slashed
by these by the
vines 19 yeah so you feel and you look
at and feel you're fine you hop right
over them nimbly is there any skills
that you think these razor vines might
respond to you're fine any more of a
stat than a skill all right 1110 damaged
by these razor vine and I'm glad I drank
that potion now moving through them is
going to be interesting you still have
to cross this space so pushing your way
through these razor vines I'm gonna say
that there's 20 damage that I would like
for you to divide amongst yourselves
Olman do you want to go in front and
just take it all sick how many is there
listen there another way do 10 here you
can absolutely use a healing potion in
here now there's only 10 to device so
you took 10 and healed it and also take
tenant heal it you'll take 10 and
healing fantastic so you're running
through these vines being /r increments
as fast as you can
[Applause]
would you guys like to move again or are
you gonna stay here Yeah right no reason
to move no I think the best plan let's
go one more north and then we'll start
moving east inland on our crocodile
conveyance mechanism you know the cards
you got a draw it's probably fine wild
arrows so the Sun is momentarily blocked
out by a hail of arrows Rosco I need
everybody to make a dexterity check
tonight asshole
throw my crocodile on top of me just
roll over are they they're like came
they're my summoned babies that take
fade creatures that take the form of
animals
they have you want to roll over they
have hit points but then they also have
attack so they're good to use later
oh that's turning me I still roll it
over I do I imagine her just kind of
laying out it anyway and then she's like
it is kind of what they're there for
yeah yeah so you're gonna let the
alligator take the hit yeah okay yeah I
don't know how much damage they have but
it is impaled by arrows else they have
19 okay still alive there's not a lot of
alligators left he just told me that he
was happy that he could do now I feel
bad I'm just under water 14 its
dexterity saving throw yeah woo nice
whoa
yeah so VRE and more gain you guys just
sort of turn sideways just right into
the ground you ready - oh you're fine I
just hurt an animal yeah ten eight
damage alright it's time to really
really use some heels that's totally
fine you can trade whenever you want I
brought more cast to the stage look I
know magic guys like
I can heal I can I can heal
let's see anyway you guys don't know oh
[Applause]
that's odd
boy the circle is so far away from where
you are it's almost like I can place it
wherever
[Laughter]
[Applause]
what the audience doesn't realize that
we have this up there the clock the
ticker a live button the circle and over
here there's the the show clock the
ticking clock that so you have a
separate level aside the game just just
so you know I hope you're enjoying
yourself because this game goes another
twenty two here I I am gonna hit well
fair enough
buckle up I am gonna cast cure wounds on
myself
that's smart at third level so that I
can not die okay fuck uh-huh okay no I'm
good I'm good I'm good okay you'll back
up yeah yeah okay the last the last two
we're not shit so there's we need to get
the fuck out of here there's no reason
that you guys have two strikes is
already running okay she is not carrying
the alligators what direction would you
like to go when a woman you were gonna
cast those he's good oh here
so let's yeah so let's move inland yeah
no doubt these these precious crops will
give us some advantage into these
conditions
well yeah I'm moving through water would
have been difficult but I haven't made
you guys roll or anything like that
you're just stealing around on these
crocodiles you're having a great time we
have the drinks with the little
umbrellas yeah one space so I need an
event card a lingering fog that has
assumed a humanoid form
that's weird I agree with you yeah
absolutely
now he is so this this humanoid shaped
fog is going to attack you what knocks
it just it just emerges yeah
so the fog sort of coalesce is into one
a humanoid shape and it comes swiping at
you oh man we should do that it rolled a
9 though and that's not that's not
that's no that's good enough
actually yeah
as hard as it might be to believe this
is why we need to start searching boy
without your armor
uh yeah damage is high twelve foggy good
lord
and now I'm gonna go ahead and say that
it's up to you guys who would like more
gain you're at the top does a longbow
effect lingering fog if it's good for
you the question is did two long bows
cuz I did actually say you could do a
wield them and I would ride that until
he's pretty good he did I pitched it and
he said yeah sure why not
well when you say dual wield what like
Bayonetta yeah I don't know how how you
I don't know how either but I heard the
GM say I do have both a attack so I get
two attacks anyway oh yeah it's fine
18:18 hits okay and then since it's
humanoid that is my favorite enemy okay
so I'm gonna do one D eight plus eight
classic lambs your technique sixteen
damage oh and you get one more attack
yeah still alive nine does not hit it
would mean can she change your mind in
the tech Jerry yeah the lingering fog
assumed a humanoid shape on you know are
we are we on they're not to bring
logistics into this but are we on the
river all standing on crocodiles no yeah
you are you are currently on the shore
it looks like okay get to go to hmm yeah
fuck you form yeah I'm guessing people
nobody is within 5 feet of it right cuz
that's what I need to get my mic sneak
attack well yeah no you shot with a bow
I think it's close to omen because they
attacked omen oh it's right ok and
there's a croc a lot in you throw the
crocodile at him yes
get back yeah okay here catch this whoa
that is 26 it's don't work yeah that's
gonna hit and I get this much before 21
don't look at the timer if we wheel 44
damage uh sure yeah this father was 21
eggs why not well either way it's plenty
to disperse this lingering fog that is
assumed to humanoid shape yeah yeah no
now it's we need that's not what I want
that isn't what I want all right no so
we are you guys want to look or an
explorer or this for once we're gonna
explore once everybody get your dice
wide out screaming no no we're not
accounting perception right yeah option
three top card one shitty dagger
it's actually called a shitty dagger
okay oh I got another one these I don't
need that shit no my shiny button my
shiny button you got rid of your part of
a spoon I did what okay Shanee button no
I don't know why I don't either nice
pretty bow 21 gets me talk to cards
choose one no hope I got the frying pan
do you want to see a potion cuz I want
that I'm gonna give you a +3 to HC I'll
give you a shield potion for that fine
Franklin oh maybe later we give we trade
we'll get ya good trade right now I'm
nobody stopping you you can trade it put
a shiny button I mean come on come on no
I need it D hoarders fine I'm gonna take
you just I don't have doubles that okay
I'm fine you are okay all right it's
fine great six of those no let's listen
we're gonna move east a couple squares
and then we're gonna start turning this
place over so you want to move east you
do event cart yes
Oh chests and paste in crystal Oh a huge
crystalline stone some rising up out of
the ground and embedded in it you can
still hear the tinkling is a treasure
chest there's no reason not to stop and
take a minute to just ship this thing
out right I see no reason me neither
chisel this out would anyone like to
take a whack at it yes it has it has an
AC even though it's just a rock and it
has damage so here if you can crack this
chest I'm gonna dump a bunch of this
terrific mall into it okay okay I've
considered it is not crystal stone no
it's not that's ten ten I'll hit whoa
just two d65
okay and please make note of your
durability yep I'm just gonna keep on
whacking it do we all everybody who
wants to continue swing at this thing
I'll let you guys with more than one
during museum fucking kidding me
free free damage I mean yeah
[Applause]
there's no rec I guess I could just like
like fireball wait sure absolutely
what's gonna happen to the chest that's
a tough chest I get it one more time
yeah that's future us problem hit oh
that's the number of the beast all right
that's nine points okay this is all
there
does that help at all is its it do we
yeah you're using a mall right yeah yeah
so you get your normal day I get all my
real shit here that and nine points
another nine yeah it is you can see
cracks ready do it for the entire thing
there we are enjoy that's eight points
destroyed yeah this thing cracks all of
the shards fall to the ground and the
chest is just sitting there humming I'm
like ready to fire them all I'm like no
no I got it I got it
now who has it here you're the one who
has the most I have poor see a chest
back here remember you want to get
another chest there's as easy as five
dollars can i you're the one that has
the most horseshit but he's got the
frying pan is worth plus three two AC
yes but you have a worthless quarter
staff and a rock that I will I will
remind you does not but it actually look
like a dog yeah not anymore really at
the moment it did
so here's it can I can I spend five
dollars to get in another item slot
[Applause]
although it
I know he's giving in right I'm using
his staff got change for a 20 Jim
getting this money to red domes I don't
know I'll take the 20 get extra slot and
a chest hey I'm not a super field dirty
[Laughter]
you've never played the Indians of
microtransaction that's weird
oh man now I feel like I feel when I
always buy shit online ha ha ha ha all
right
I'm gonna I'm gonna toss these back and
I'm gonna drink this health potion and
get back up to max yep Oh
this sword is great don't you try and
reflect through the garden button to the
Sun to try and say it will help it's
really shiny it's just like holding it
to the sky it's surprisingly oh honey
you're like gonna take Kent golden
longbow you got your four items Oh
actually I get five five now right
because you be the upgrade but the
upgrade the expansion oh no no no he's a
premium customer does he get a discount
on future chests
oh absolutely this is satanic and I
think you know that yeah I do
oh no no it's worse if things are worse
nope it's time to go easy gonna explore
east you're going to each time there's
only 48 left hidden pit I guess we found
it oh great hidden hit yeah you did find
it yes it was hidden I need everybody to
make me a deck stage a quite well I'm
going in the pit you specifically loaded
this with all dexterity chicks didn't
you then I just realized I just realized
that was deliberate yeah
I hate him so much sorry you just got
caught in the explosion this early about
hating omen it's Haley so six let's see
so if we're talking about athletics this
team it's like it's like whoa I might
jump in like wool like no like what like
that like I don't think you see it you
like it's acrobatics all right so I got
an eight which means that I was looking
at my shiny button yeah he's like come
on button it'll be okay nine damage
districts as you fall into this pit Wow
good roll no damage for you and would
you like to explore this space there's
no it's time to go east go east again
okay
hey abandoned games I don't let you draw
one card you know it's time to drive one
card
John one card hey pretty nice why you
always get the good stuff yeah there we
go
a few bits of string okay nice pretty
nice boat it's not like the best bow but
it's like now handle that's premium as
you guys as you guys come into this area
you can see often the distance running
away from you a group of players there's
four of them they don't they haven't
spotted you they are running away from
you and you can see that the one in the
in the lead is being followed by what
looks like a floating eye and in this
space the his voice carries and you can
you can hear even though he's far away
and he goes what's up it's your boy Oh
foe Reaper
shout-out to everybody watching me on
which
[Laughter]
we're going for the chicken dinner and
then they are off they're over the hill
i following there's a magical high
presumably for the people on which one
would assume can i fireball them there
they're too far away at this way they're
over the hill and go away his name was
he said what's up it's your boy Oh
Philippe er oh oh
free wafer this is yeah you guys want
explore that's good you know I'd like to
get into one of the one of the things
before we explore again I mean even
though you like gold yeah gold tier
uh-huh so maybe get along that crumbling
castle yeah let's go let's go let's just
keep moving east and then try to get
more juice but I would recommend on the
way there we'd search at least one time
just to try to get some armor out yeah
yeah yeah I shuffled the car minutes
he's got that he's got that pants got +3
lacy right now can I just can I use the
few bits of string to tie the frying-pan
in front of my groin yes absolutely yeah
so it's just sort of hanging there like
a pendulum
yeah or just a target can you imagine if
your vine yeah yeah you've been there
it's a dexterity check it it is again
okay oh you murdered him okay oh you
guys are fine everybody's fine probably
how about you ooh you're still great
even if you 13 Oh totally it's not a
problem
[Laughter]
No
all right now you still do need to push
your way through this razor vine all
right which is 20 damage that needs to
be absorbed by the party I got 10 here
healing potion that was the last feeling
push on the table though whoops we gotta
get some you have 60 I'm okay I can take
this I think we probably left the gun if
you want to shove the Gators and I will
allow for them to be destroyed and allow
you to get through without I can summon
cotton more crocodiles poisonous snakes
that's great two giant spiders I mean we
have options so that's like yeah yeah
yeah feed these crocs into the furnace
what I don't like is the sound I'm
imagining from the a/c it's a bad sound
pushing them into that razor vine it's
like BAM no no no cuz there's a four of
them right it's like we're just taking
it but it's like you got two legs I've
got two legs in this it's like and then
it's like we just keep feeding them in
and then it's like we all it only takes
two and then the other two are like and
we're like should we do it
[Laughter]
smear you buddy yeah that's gross you
guys are evil there's they're just
they're just babies
sure they live to serve they want to do
it I'm very into it
north you can see a fog forest and to
your east you can see the crumbling
towers of an ancient castle yeah what's
your what's your druthers well in the
crumbling castle that's one thing in the
frightening forest strange as it may be
it might be that more gain is going to
give us a leg up
[Music]
I can't I mean we can only I can only
give you a leg up if the DM is really
obsessed with like travel distance and
speed oh yeah that's not me but the
crumbling castle might be more
defensible now that is something to say
especially as we're getting down down to
the end only 42 left alive I know if we
find a good spot there all right hold it
hold it hold a second so all this actor
oh yeah we're doing work both it's a
fucking murderer believe it he says it's
your boy and I play boy I don't like him
olan olan boy was he heading north or
was he heading east he was heading north
I say east we're gonna crumble up on
this castle you want to go east yeah
event card cloud of poison Constitution
jerk all right I have that save that
Constitution eight final 17 11 damage
yeah oh it's not good 11 yeah 7 for me
11 this place grinds another guy sir
just choking coughing on this poisonous
gas you can hear all thin the distance
just laughing it up he's just he knows
yeah and the crumbling castle is closer
than it was would you like to go is
there an eye watching us as well no
we're not that cool Yeah right
can there be you want to explore east
what do you mean if we pull the yellow
card whose might as well get something
out right all right activate the
exploration device okay let me see those
perception checks if it's over 13 its
top two cards just card one so grab two
for that tender draw see you snatch one
more game I get eight yeah 14 so I get
two yeah here packing you oh sorry about
to break your heart you got yes
I feel like I got too many a handful of
teeth oh you know what I'm gonna keep it
and only give it to her 20 gonna be
hooked yay
now 28 does that help did you roll a
natural 20 yeah top two cards you can
keep them both whoa cargo shorts I'll
give you plus one a seat for the cargo
can AC motherfuckers yeah it's not a
frying pan but it's pretty good
you got you kept the boot I kept the
boot I'll give you one ac do a few bits
is what do I get for a handful of teeth
I really just have a hanging them
jealously oh you got their breath well
I'm wondering can I drink this potion
yeah you have to okay can I do that
just drink it and then and then have
your five cards just get topped up well
as a premium member I mean it comes with
their privileges so we're gonna let
let's keep moving east toward this
castle
more chest does anybody want to break
this chest real fast you guys if I were
buying so you can move if you want or
you can stay and destroy this crystal to
try to get the chest out do me a
fireball it yeah I'd rather you save
this fireball for old foe breaker or
whatever the fuck is Reaper yeah well
whatever it's you know watches which
channel yeah yeah you're falling on
which all right so here we could all
just flail away at this yeah yeah no no
we want this it's a chest so we want it
VRE I'm gonna take a swing at it with
your decent rapier no I'm saving the
rapier for a real fight I'll shoot out
with this longbow though okay you can
all just cd8 there we go at it
Sophie re you pull out the bow Quang
Quang sorry it doesn't make that noise
no but you say it
+6 to hit you rolled a six so it's 12
you hit to d8 okay three sinks okay
let's see other professionals do it
cracks start to form in the crystalline
structure here okay I'm gonna try with
my awesome longbow 13 yep eight seven
and I did I get to add anything else
since you're using a longbow yeah you
get your normal you're vicious
that's eight nine eleven is your feel of
I mean crystal towers that contain
chests should be this is is almost
destroyed there's cracks running all
through this thing all right
it's fall damage yeah cracked are you
keeping track of your durability yes
excellent yeah do you want to open the
chest yeah yeah who has a who has a heap
of stuff that they can trade out I am
starting to look at that Premium
Membership at the low levels like you
can sort of play it like no fqp but like
you said now that we're higher level we
just need more stuff the truth is if I
can find something to swap out I've only
got one user dream your yeah yeah I know
you crack it yeah I mean I'm not giving
up my button longbow mall scimitar
golden scimitar I will swap that out
actually I'll keep does the frying pan
and a few bits of string now count as
one item no and you are you I will say
that because you have combined them and
created a sort of kilt that yes there
was a crafting system yeah there's a
craft implemented it wait
in this version in this version dude
here how can you combine a boot in the
shrine yes I don't have my hat my witch
hat so I can I'm gonna put the boot you
want to put the button on the boot and
put on my head sweet okay I'm now a boot
which all right so we're looking good
maybe head east a couple squares yeah if
you can get in there okay yeah yeah yeah
easy abandoned campsite everybody draw
card tricks I got another chief of staff
oh these stack handful of teeth yeah you
have two hands you could get it in one
hand oh okay now we have to trade yes
just to get cool shit now listen I don't
want to fucking I don't want to create
any kind of fucking problem here but I
do have animal stole crafting and fancy
hat oh man in order to trade now in to
decide what I am out of her inventory I
don't need my boot hat button not if
you've got the teeth could be a nice
addition to the hey can I interest you
in a golden scimitar you can like I'll
say this if you're gonna be bowing all
over yeah I have to scimitars
I'll drift it I
[Laughter]
: I'm what know just drink it
I'm a face it's five temporary hit
points so they would go on to your HP
and then yeah the first they'd be the
first thing to come on but yeah maybe
you can drink it get the benefit and
then then you have an open slot true
okay here so I'm gonna I'm gonna spare
long ago just in case if we're shooting
and shooting you take that I'm so after
all of our trade and venerated so event
fuck
it's a lingering fog it's assumed to
humanoids like Chris with a like black
hat yeah yeah he's like a cameo more
games here at the top and you have been
confronted with the lingering fog it is
assumed the humanoid shape Morgan could
you please kill this fog yes absolutely
oh whoa yes that hit in the fog is to d8
that's five six seven eight plus nine
eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen
sixteen G's right now two attacks yeah
on dis fog well you get another one yeah
that hurt oh yeah that is 11 17 17 hits
F this fog beast a 12 plus 13 14 15 16
plus G's plus another d8 why cuz he's
already taking damage so yeah
this fog is dispersed but it's that's
exactly how it goes to say Morgan could
you please deal with this fog she's like
absolutely and I say Thank You Morgan
and then we continue east into that
crumbling castle one more event card
wild arrows here they come dexterity
yeah I know I have a hat now
what was that noise for Oh No okay all
right here you have your dice let's just
take our medicine get this shit over
with oh nine damaged districts from the
arrow you are impaled 10/10 is good
you're okay alright ready 20 something
you're fine you grab an arrow you need
it yeah you're okay
all right feels good as you move into
the crumbling castle you can hear that
familiar tinkling I love that I love
that would like to open the chest that
is in the crumbling castle so who's got
you got open spot I haven't no cargo
fine yeah exactly
another do the cargo shorts allow me to
have more items now no they don't work
like that there those cargo shorts where
the pockets are sewn share decorative
yeah there just look no goddamnit
they're just really a utility oh I got F
done these thank you time go through
them nope we're not gonna do that really
think about you know what you want
here's what other people could you can I
drink this shield potion yeah absolutely
okay temp mm-hmm I have 21 hit points
yeah what's your max although we can we
can okay no no so a tweet so after after
we do this let's let's get a healing
let's get a masculine yeah this right it
says is a splendid rod but it's a purple
item so no there is a chief of staff
here but there's already there's also a
mall of the year I've got three moles of
the Year cool so I mean can it really be
them all of the year so you've cracked
open this chest you've taken out its
loot but you can still hear tinkling and
if you look deeper into the crumbling
Castle here you can see that in the
center of it there's sort of a low stone
well and this well is made up of
loose stones that have been stacked up
it's very simple but you can hear the
tinkling coming from this well we don't
have any water or heads to juice
somebody's somebody with a lot of
dexterity is gonna have to go down there
or acrobatics we need to just put liquid
in it though it's a well we have a piece
of string we could string won't lower
anybody down BRE does want to look okay
well as you peer over the side you can
see that the water comes up there's
maybe about five feet and then the water
starts and it is a thick black gross
looking water brackish brackish brackish
for real is there a is there a chest
down there you can hear the tinkling I
mean it's definitely coming down the
water
what's the mimic version of the gold
chest I would like to make a perception
out wish perception role to see if I'm
being fucked with okay like I don't want
like some some dude with like to hit
points left standing behind a rock going
take and I jump in there anyways ooh
21 I think for perception yeah I mean
this is this is a well it's just a well
there's nobody else around it it's just
your party here there is a thick what
looks like a thick black murky water
comes up almost to the top if we had a
crocodile really yeah need anything as
much as this chest like sure okay spit
in it that's water I'm gonna you notices
you so you lean over and this big loogie
right really gross
and it drops down and it goes right
through the water and there's no splash
there's no anything it just goes right
through and the water doesn't move it
could be an illusion illusion
okay okay I'm fine oh no that was out
loud I can polymorph myself into a swarm
of rats if you don't want to do that oh
yeah that's pretty good that's pretty
sweeping yeah yeah okay yeah do that
okay
I do that you polymorph into a group of
rats you're just looking over and then
just like passing through the water you
realize that it was in fact a loser oh
and there is a very short distance down
and then there's an open area with
another Chester all right aluminum as
rats some little rats just use a little
hands but Oh another she'll get a sip
golden scimitar I'm okay I've got great
swords but I'll just take this shield
potion yeah you can drink it then keep
it okay yeah hop up and drink it take
that and then you know that's a Roger
great Rock okay here explore there's
lots of good stuff the line in the
crumbling castle all right now it's time
to go
yeah I don't know hold on we're gonna
all heal up right yes so I'm gonna cast
the mass healing word oh nice and just
try to get people topped up 28 left
alive I know I'm gonna cast I'm gonna
cast it at fifth level yeah but does
that mean for everybody it means it
means more healing for at a fraction of
the price of those other guys
okay take 25 whoa Wow
everybody gets 25 yes it turned out hot
at the end yeah I'll say great I'm all
right all right so let's get the fuck
out of here
my Explorer there we go we're gonna go
north you go north it's pot all right
ready
gluing obelisk everybody gets one
durability square refilled on their
items under decent rapier yeah but no
but Morgan was using hers her awesome
bows does my rock look a little more
like a dog again now honestly pet
looking at it you like dog
I can't maybe maybe maybe a cat but this
is not a dog this rock is it even a rock
it's like you're just showing off yes my
dog is what I say right here so let's
let's while we're still here in these
woods before we get into something like
this final circle appear I think that we
should try to dig around a little bit
more just so we can try to get more
armor armor would be nice right I like
would you like to go first go let's go
one more north farther north one more
North fuck can you can you um can you
round up a few more alligators feed him
to the razor vine here okay wait what's
not first let's do our first time hold
on hold on what if I do I hope we have
well first of all I need dexterity Jay
pass about a trace can I cast past that
a trace because then everybody including
me he gets a tenth plus ten too
dirty yeah thanks thanks you stuff the
roll yeah but it's +10 to dexterity
checks absolutely
oh and we can't be tracked so you can
play the month sure yeah honestly this
is this is baller because we're gonna
need this in this yeah in the dark times
right here so let's get these rolls out
of the way because we got the plus ten
okay and it feels great 25 yeah 15 yeah
fucking nice work more game nobody is
damaged by the initial eruption of rays
Irvine I would just like to say I rolled
a 36 you don't get to say that very
often you rolled a 17 and got to 36 yeah
yeah it was pretty it feels good
yeah oh thank you more game thank you
for I never thought I'd reached this
level
how long has passed without a trace last
an hour okay so you guys can you guys
can continue to move through this so
tell me about this yeah would it be
possible if it you know what let's just
take a minute a breather
no what did he talk about no whatever
problem you have right now Michael I
don't they don't would like to have saw
because I don't like a dungeon master
I'm the one who's in control of the game
and I can I fly the answers I'll answer
all the questions that you might ask it
doesn't matter if your questions about
the game like some some weird rule of
the game okay
just a life question just general
information here is there a scenario
whereby I can utilize stone shape to
create a small bridge over the razor
vine interesting I was gonna allow you
to go through the razor bite anyway
because of her past without trace
I I'll allow it the fan I say you know
what we're passing another trace here
let's just pass without that truce yeah
there's no trace here uh would you guys
like to explore yeah yes actually before
we enter that final circle what do we
say about one more grip and gripping it
down while that fire all right ready
everybody good let's roll more clothes
more frying pans whoo Wow that's ten top
two cards topping you card see ya
everybody everybody everybody get
stopped to set well let's see
No just take the top one worthless
quarter staff awesome steel rod you
gonna hang on to that health potion get
five slots yeah I know but I've got
really sentimental attachments as deep
what did the guy take you're decent
rapier and I throw it into the wood like
you're looking at it and I just take it
and I throw them you wanna make a
strength check no no first I try to
break it open it doesn't happen anything
no and I throw it I could glare at you
that was hard for him ya know again it's
like it's the hoarders it's like the
person who comes in is like yeah listen
you're living like a beast huh you're
just keeping the gear because of the
steady
you're just the person that wants to
look cool in the game let's make the
gear is really crappy he does look cool
though you've got golden scimitars on
your back but you're naked covered in
blood please write a frying pan so we
gotta go you want to go north north
doors like up yes we find a glowing
obelisk glowing obelisk yes one
durability point one regenerator if only
I had my decent rapier don't you second
if you go back for that ring I can see
it it just glowed up it's no now it's
extra decent no all right who wants to
explore I think okay I don't know it's
very hard to hear up here would you yell
I love you all
something about omen what you throw the
rock Ullman always wondering if my rock
I'm guessing like it I'm not gonna ask
about my rock yeah let's go north one we
go north one that's an event card
I know oh it's that Jeff know another
right yep just took a shit in this game
let me blow it up alright well boy you
sure you use your chief of staff for
your splendid rod yeah oh I can hit it
with my chief of staff yeah exactly hit
it double da I don't usually get the hit
bangs that's fun oh yeah so six that's 8
damage okay take that I don't even see
any cracks no come on
hello can i fireball it absolutely okay
I'm gonna fireball I like that you hit
it first walk up crack just want to
loosen it I can't do this alright so six
seven eight five nine so eight plus nine
mmm-hmm 17 17 six plus another 9 okay
this is this is
fire damage yeah to a to a crystal to a
rock come on I just want to make sure
that we're on the same page
fire how much fire it's green fire it's
green fire you try dan I appreciate how
much damage did you do 35 a fire yeah
all right so the the rock is it is a
golf tin flame and when the fire recedes
very little difference is visible it's
it's blackens in some spots looks better
in others all right well I just start
crying polished or something yeah I got
oh it's just it's burning yeah I beat
the shit out of this thing that hits
it's like I'm not employee of the month
Oh fourteen okay oh that's right that's
right seventeen
okay it's lots of cracks oh yeah running
through this thing I know how it works
um god damn that's 18 now are you
marking durability on these of course of
the year yeah did you hit like twice
yeah it cracks and chest appears I love
chess give it to me the golden scimitar
awesome longbow how are you fixed on
long bows tender okay
there's golden it's great you are doing
great on your scimitars I drink this
potion I throw the rest of these mystic
artifacts in the garbage okay hold on if
there's if there's this she could maybe
have a I liked how you couldn't even
make it out I really tried here so now
is it I think so generally speaking
there is this sort of Hill here yeah
that is cool do we like the hill I don't
know typically this is at this point I
just laying around no I shot and I don't
know where it came from and it's right
and then I get angry and quit the game
right
here so I think that we probably want to
be I mean generally speaking it's just
everybody hiding and laying down behind
trees and I feel like the trees are to
the left yeah we should go to the high
ground in the trees yeah yeah yeah I'm
down bruised laying on the ground
whoo another crystal chest how do we
feel about this it's practice buddy open
you know I can't get away from the pub G
mindset here of like we've got 19 people
in this circle and we're gonna stand
around and wail on this chest and
somebody's gonna snipe me oh definitely
this is like when the box comes down
you're like a box yeah and it's like oh
it's just like a type of corner no wait
wait
we want to be those those dicks yes yes
now we hide yes heads up somebody cast
light on this chest encasing crystal I
can do that yeah yeah there we go
okay night I hide by his cheering up and
you're the sniper oh yeah I only gonna
connect scope right here right and
remember without trace so we are where
we roll we are ready for this last
circle like a plus 100% let's fucking
get it I could even do silent image on
the chest and make it look like a bigger
chest chest yeah I want you to make it
look like one of those exclusive
seasonal chest oh yeah nice kind of a
jack-o'-lantern theme on there yeah yeah
yeah it's like a rat chess that's
seasonal for Strix so this chest encased
in crystal you have magically made look
even grander oh my god and the rest of
you are we are now hiding with our
cloaked as we are is the pass without
trays you're laying in wait yes I can't
I go that chest looks too good I go
[Applause]
this is also how I play funky no no no
if he for even a second if he comes out
from behind this jaw I put him in
sleeper Wow no I don't go sleep
you guys are laying in wait around this
crystalline structure yeah yeah you see
you see to see two people come up to
this crystal chest and they are I mean
they're drooling over this thing like oh
yeah they can't wait no they cannot wait
and so they come up one of them has a
sword he starts hacking on this crystal
and he's not doing much damage you can
hear it right what would you guys like
to do how many of the party two of them
they've lost a lot of their crew so
should we left him they use up all their
durability on their weapons on the other
hand if it's still close well no but the
people know it's a trap because they'll
be dead bodies around oh don't worry
we're gonna take all their shit yeah
that's happening tip where are we being
evil okay so imagine your mind imagine
that they to our chests they have chests
a person is a sort of chest alright get
it yeah okay so there they are hacking
away on this thing both of them one of
them has a sword the other one has a
mall and he's just banging on this thing
after a couple minutes it finally cracks
open and the chest is revealed you
Morgaine you want to go yep 13 hits okay
[Music]
are they humanoid they are humans yeah
that's 10 damage okay um and then I'm
into my second attack
oh well then yes tim is not hit okay yes
you hit the first one who was just about
to open the chest yeah
arrow goes right into his side so he
pulls away from the chest turns around
they've spotted you guys now and the one
with the mall is going to charge towards
you some mall a trip to the mall trip to
the mall lovely
oh I cover the archer I wasn't here yeah
yeah so he charges up on Morgaine 10
misses though and then the other one oh
that's a natural 20 he hits you with the
sword highest numbers on the dice well
damaged it was crit yeah yeah I didn't
have to roll right it's max damage but I
did I still rolled max damage no then
you didn't think it's more than that
it's all of it oh it's example remember
you yes all you get like the value and
then you're rolling a dice again yeah if
it was a 2024 damage that's my
understanding
[Laughter]
you did you did get it next up is VRE so
you've got the one with the mall who has
not been hurt and he had the one with
the sword who took an arrow to the side
for more game the mall guy seems a
little bit dangerous I'm gonna attack
him yeah yeah I've got two swords no
used to have three wait what happened to
that third sword it's got a 20 and a
[Music]
16 both hit you what why is it still up
there it's not
always far away from you guys how that
works some weird something weird going
on protecting the person who designed it
7 17 8 17 23 28 30
are you just saying members and if I
never really a pumpkin acorn a codes 35
I did hit with both yeah sword guy is
murdered or that was mall guy
oh you went after mall guy right I'm
sorry mall guy is murdered here's this
terrific mall terrific that drops on the
grounds and sword guy is still up Strix
sorry guys still up Oh yep kill view I
gotta kill oh yeah there you go yeah
that never happens in the real game
listen dude just take this I know I am
I'm loaded inside your heart polymorph
sword guy okay into what a chicken as
always chicken dinner
yeah no now don't kill them they're too
cute here's what I'm going to the forest
so he has a saving throw to make right
yeah and it's yeah
that's a toughy no he's a chicken no I
take the chicken
he's like a silkie chicken because he's
really soft yep how long is that last an
hour okay yeah you're good so you have a
chicken now and the chest they cracked
open is still sitting there if somebody
would like to open it I think it should
be right over there hopefully there's a
potion in there for you to drink let's
see we have a shield potion which I will
drink definitely we have an awesome
longbow not as awesome as my longboats
splendid rod I seen your day I will take
the Scimitar for sure
nice I mean I would drink this and then
there's your for yes that's good gear
here at the end uh alright
one explored
no not you I'm gonna work yes
let's explore hold on we got another
kill oh yeah I'm sorry yeah here so
let's let's explore one time their
chicken technically oh right yeah it's
true
Oh unless you killed the chicken I'm
gonna be hungry I'll count it he's no
longer in the fight now I say we do one
more search just to see if we can get
any armor bits before the end right
let's go up first
okay earth one north one event card
pluck what AZ lone Rando oh no now this
lone Rando actually looks different from
the other ones
this one is an elf and he sees you VRE
he goes oh puri it's me fleeting I'm
your biggest fan
shoot him no no it's carrying a real
nice looking scimitar and he's running
towards you guys yeah that would be
great
hey we've got a I'm sorry we got a
surprise for you and I'm like bugging
[Laughter]
distracted that's awesome good okay I
got another one it's all good
wait why do I have advantage Oh
because why yes they think that he's
being distracted by VRE oh yeah oh wow
it sure you got advantage yeah here we
go all right that one as well
for my first attack well no okay so now
I get to my second account but not Flynn
Dhin come on 20 Flynn who pulls that one
though Yeah right no okay
to clarify Flint as a person who donated
to charity and won an appearance as like
my assistant or friend in the game just
just so that you all can it's all fun
well now you know all those dice Oh 16
damage yes
he's not dead no okay so now I'm gonna
do my second attack Rick's is like ready
to polymorph like yeah so it's 12:12
does not hit welcome okay way to get
have it Daniel so 4k now okay sorry I'm
sorry you missed on your yes okay which
is now going to suck his shot at you
it's like he's confused we are I
understand
hero's good past him and but not all of
them oh and I look up it like where this
place is awful isn't it man also naked
and covered in blood he comes up and
swings on Morgaine misses and now we're
gonna go to be a hard
I didn't like tag me in it's your turn
can I take her in polymorph er if you
want yeah I mean if you want to not go
or if you want to use your turn to sort
of parlor I lost my whole party I'm in a
real bad spot here oh man man oh look at
that's right in your shoulder I got a
potion come here come here come here and
then I grabbed him real hard
do it do it do it do it yeah I mean all
right but I don't know if Morgan's gonna
kill the chicken
I don't like she's the other chicken's
still alive I don't know about their
safety but I'll do it okay all right so
it has to be a DC 16 I like I like the
thought of me green like debate what cut
two chickens down okay I think the
chicken it's another silkie chicken but
this one is white you just use time it's
like animal degraded him no Rick's got a
kill though we're gonna call that a kill
out of the game seven left alive now Hey
now there's four of you hey tell me
about this great scimitar it's great
that he had is there anything oh yeah
sorry
he dropped it when he became a chicken
there's only seven left no I think the
suits are false and he's just like
hopping around on this there's only four
of you and so you know that the other
three are out there someone the Sun this
is like on our map right yes you're
seeing basically what you see here you
can see on your magical map so you're
down like a bunch of points no we have
to we have to fix you up like right now
I've temporarily
that is not gonna 48 plus 5 yeah here
we're gonna we're gonna get you cured up
okay I can also do cure wound so I have
lots of one with level 1 spell so I can
also do that I'm gonna you can do
everything you can do but not as good my
healing spells are for sure not as good
as your healing well here here I'm gonna
you're gonna guess it on you for level 3
so 3 plus you piece of 10 I'll take a
that's not bad that's amazing I really
hate pushing me to chicken slidden cuz
he took a bad air you want to hold this
you guys are healing over somewhere else
hey I take my scimitar and I murder both
of the she marked the durability I say
Morgan no no not the chickens these
precious birds they were the best of us
let's go
what direction you want to go we're
gonna go east go east I put the chickens
in my fancy hat what did you a blessing
of unicorns a blessing of unicorns we
have good tents you know how this works
yeah I need to see you're gonna love
these beasts yeah I'm misty step again I
don't want anything we have plus ten
also dicks dirty stuff
oh yes oh so meadow so you want to try
this oh for ultra sneaks yeah yeah but I
might still see someone so let's roll
dice yeah oh oh no you're fine okay well
I'll just roll my 18 and then we'll be
done you're good all right I still just
on the other side oh yeah you you right
missed you step yeah I don't want to
deal with that all right you guys are
through the blessing of unicorns without
any damage being taken or would you like
to go next
so we're tooled I mean you want to
explore are you good yeah I mean we're
we're we're tooled the F up right yeah
that the square that you're in is still
technically gonna be out part of it will
be outside the circle yeah so we want to
go north one step yeah we could also
stay here for a few minutes since
nothing bad is happening and wait yeah
but we can also get shredded by you got
razor vine we all know how this works
oh you're so plus ten let's see the
rules though I want to see that one from
1623 you're fine nice okay you're good
how do you deal with the 20 damage
though that you have to take as a party
to move through the razor vine now cut
those chickens who have been great right
now I still have them in my hat the
bodies the bodies their bodies their
souls are somewhere else
we just we just throw the super-sad
their souls or something really five
right I don't take five damage actually
I'm good I'm good that's fine if you
guys want you that yeah I'll just she'll
just get chewed up on the 5hp
okay I'll Nick why Strix are going like
take your five I know I have more hit
points than you like probably so do a
cure wounds on people cuz I have lots of
slots and I feel like we're getting to
the end at this point it might be a good
idea I'm gonna do it on yourself yeah at
this point you can see coming up along
in front of you both and his magic
floating I and two of his party members
one of the members of his clan now that
they're closer you can see that these
are look like barbarians like oath is a
big guy and the dudes that are with him
are just ripped one of them is bald old
himself has just long flowing blonde
hair he's always looking smiling at the
eye and then the third one has a long
braid of red hair down his back and
they're sinner right in front of you
guys how does your gear look their gear
looks awesome yeah they've got they've
got one of them has a bow one of them
has a sword and the other has a mall do
they are they I did I actually have
pants and stuff - oh yeah they've got
frying pans they've got everything you
could want so they didn't keep a bunch
of gray items just for fun any cool
animal skulls or anything like that I
mean they're lost really okay uh this
might be time to call forth some giant
spiders more game you are gonna be up
first what are you guys feeling like I
think that giant spiders just having
extra things to hit and they're also
gross I also have eight constrictor
snakes which have a grapple ability this
is so fun you guys it's hard to go wrong
with giant spiders poisonous answer
Panther right direwolf Panther they're
just all Jumanji and we're gonna have
four Panthers four Panthers it's pretty
baller but again like you could have
like doubled wrist with the pants a you
cast that our party immediately doubles
in size right like there's a case to be
made
alright so Olsen's looking at the eye
he's like hey everybody out there seven
left looks like this is the party we're
gonna smoke them it's gonna be great we
got chicken dude or technically we have
the chicken but Morgaine you're up first
alright I'm gonna do Panthers Panthers
okay score Panthers AC is 12 they have
13 hit points speed is 50 feet do they
act on your turn they roll them for
themselves
Wow so I will roll initiative for the
Panthers please do 16 jeez those are
fast Panthers bro these standards are
MLG they're actually going next
I love that like he's like at the
cameras like yeah we read out of the
frame and jumps in midair round yes so
tell me about what your Panthers tell me
what they do okay so they do bite +42
hit and they do 1 d6 + 2 claw is plus 4
and then 1 d 4 plus 2 all right we'll
try they run for 20 feet then they knock
prone on a DC 12 Wow bear him to the
ground oh there it is they're traveling
you've got off with his flowing blonde
hair I'm you know I'm going straight for
that for sure
should we all roll one Panther just to
expedite yes yes my pants is the best so
yeah roll this okay so they're gonna
fight so it's gonna be 20 so they're
first they're gonna do 20 feet run okay
at him my or my dudes gonna go 20 feet
so he has to do as DC 12 strength check
okay I know but first I'm gonna I guess
do the buddy so this is to stay standing
up when I am after appaled by a panther
yeah
okay so plus where to hit so that's it's
just like right on the neck and then
just like clamps down with his hair - oh
yeah yeah okay so now I get to d6 I just
want to thank my sponsor so that 608
damage plus he has to succeed in a DC 12
strength check so right you guys are so
right yep three again okay five six
seven eight nine ten total ten thanks
guys
plus ya DC 12-string check alright oh
[Laughter]
all right
yeah next up is all wait did he survive
his check oh yeah he got a 14 there's
three more cats oh that's right alright
let's see these are cats yeah that's a
bite 17 that's a bite that's a bite it's
1d six plus two okay
add it all up 43 5 yes 6 9 plus 6 15 15
okay let's just make three it's really
mean he's down right so the first music
okay so then he does a point I the
person gets a bonus bite action on being
stream Snipes d6 + 2 7 there was the
first 15 yeah
there's 22 points total and he's on the
ground and then do two cats so after the
first 15 what did you do for the second
way that it's 20 it's um it's just went
total okay okay he's hurt bad had a year
he's being mauled by four cats in the in
the magic eye is just floating right
above him he's like hey if you like this
balling throw a gold coin into the
fountain that you're watching this in
next is BRE it's free with which prime
[Laughter]
don't forget your free coin you've got
all suits on the ground being torn to
shreds by Panthers and then you have the
bald-headed guy with a mall who is fine
and you have the long braided guy who
has a sword on one hand I imagine it
would be super easy to sneak attack a
man we get sad by 4:00 p.m.
yeah I would allow that and I I like I
like but on the other hand we've got a
guy with red hair here which is really
biting on my style yeah and you have to
protect that brand so what it's braided
I mean it's not flowing no it's not
about that breeze and there's problems
yeah I agree
oh yeah I'll head over to him I'll kind
of square up okay maybe like you ready
he's like I was born ready
sit macho Panthers he's bullshit and
then I'll attack him is that enough to
get advantage for I can't help myself
oh my god Pat it was meant to be yeah
I'll take that I'll think about it now
they're both bad well it was Jack well
Steve advantage you should roll again
should I roll again you can roll he's
looking at these panties like oh damn
these imaginary Panthers oh okay so now
anyway that for our fair it doesn't add
up to 14 with my normal what Jack pluses
you get from 4 to 14 that's a hit
against the red-haired guy I'm a good
sword sword er it's like a called strike
on the braid yes oh I'm just I want to
get that braid off yeah that's fair okay
[Music]
I'm sorry I keep grabbing your dice that
I'm a gun green yes thank you
it's
so that's 5 10 11 16 16 16 damaged yeah
headaches teen and then another eight
Jesus okay yeah he is destroyed he's
killed outright joined up with the brave
got the braids I feel really bad about
the braids after I do it it's actually
really soft
oh like that I feel good like a pan like
you're almost like I wish I wouldn't
know like I could ask him what he uses
in here something I can use this for a
weave later and we already got a kill
this extension Strix we have the
bald-headed barbarian with a maul and we
have if we have the bald-headed guy and
then we have meow Mix well I feel like I
don't know if my careful spell is gonna
like really be able to do all of those
Panthers so that might be a waste is
that eyes still floating around oh yeah
it's just right above all this is Strix
this is great thanks ice wolf for the
sub can I can I run up and take that I
yeah yeah you want to just grab that
eyeball and grab it
sure yeah I'm just gonna grab it and
take it and just like face it towards me
okay I'm just look at it be like fuck
you Jim and take it away from him like
that's it's trying to turn back but you
can absolutely hang on to it is that
what you want to do for your turn yes
okay oh office like the Panthers he was
okay with the matter now that the eye is
gone he has lost his switch is also
complaining about the chickens being
killed in the eye and it's like I really
don't think that's that nice why we're
here and it's getting really sad for
really like grading on his brand yeah
here comes a mall do your face
my face your face yep and then oh man
you are up yes good I know I roll the
two it happens I say listen I can
understand the desire and the enthusiasm
to build a global brand yeah let me show
you how I did it I like the hustle kid
yeah
and then the mall just comes straight
yeah so it's all my regular pluses are
legit okay and you're wearing the cargo
shorts oh fuck yeah I'm wearing the
cargo shorts
well you do that strix just turns the I
if I still like on how does eleven
eleven does not yeah I have two attacks
okay around because I'm that war prison
you're eating the bald guy are you
getting old oh oh oh this prone then you
absolutely do hit yeah yeah you can have
advantage I'll give you advantage double
another well who's the one who's the one
who tried to hit me with the mall that's
the ball ball never hit the ball guy
okay well that's but I have my second
one I say that's not how that's not what
I meant what I meant is 16 oh yeah I hit
yeah you're good okay
2d six ooh that's the number of the
beast that's also good eleven twelve
thirteen fourteen okay
okay mm-hmm he's not dead but he has
hurt pretty bad
we're back up to the top with more game
summon another four Panthers and I can't
summon anything else well I got
crocodiles and Panthers how close them
I'm pretty close to the blonde eight huh
yeah yeah I'm gonna have to get in there
with a scimitar I think okay he's he's
screaming for his eye back no no I
thought the Panthers finished him
actually I'm gonna go for the bald guy
[Music]
another oh never mind man right okay
8:16 he's already hurt actually yeah
he's hurt so then I get to add a d8 fuck
me 18 another total 18 a total 18 dude
you never know yeah I do
he's he's barely clinging on to life
he has arrows sticking out of him like a
like a pincushion in all directions
VRE no I would take my second Oh second
attack sorry that hits yeah six seven
eight there are sixteen plus another d8
okay you know what I'm gonna go ahead
we're game pretty to your point
liquefied
Oh feels so good oh they have custom do
that they have custom names oh yeah it
is it is only off left and he is the lat
or not I'm sorry it's Panthers all right
everybody ready
get your Panthers get your paper d6 + -
Oh already prone yeah okay
so he is he gets bit yep yeah it's just
a decent he can't defend himself against
these Panthers 8 he has advantage
because he's prone right yeah that's
probably good anyway so tell me if
someone bit him 8x8 damaged she's still
alive another 8 still alive 7 he's dead
[Laughter]
I want to get in front of this I yeah
yeah yeah I'd say a Strix will hold it
up and say like I say friends this is a
service we can provide for you any
problem you may have tell them R which
channel yeah exactly yeah I'm with it's
which obviously which TV forward slash
hacking alright so at this point the the
island is still there but you can see
coming down from the sky a robed figure
this capability bean wizard unknown so
he comes down and he's completely
enshrouded in a dark cloak and he says
design wizard unknown you have one which
means you will leave this island with
your lives and you will learn my true
identity I cannot wait the cloak throws
it off and it's jim dark the whole time
the whole time it was Jim Wow and he
walks up to you omen and he says I've
been wanting to talk to you but I wasn't
sure like how to get you alone or like
the right time to do it we're not we're
not alone at all thousands watching this
from mystic wells in their village and I
have some questions for you this clone
that you made of me without my knowledge
it has all my abilities and all my all
my spells everything everything that I
like about you yeah
it has as well does it have the same
death curse that I have no so he's fine
he's doing as far as I know he's doing
great
alright he's doing as well as you would
if you didn't have the death curse so
Jim Jim takes a second you should kill
me like 10,000 viewers now I think if
he's got all my spells and he doesn't
have the death curse maybe he should be
your new Jim this is a trick this is a
trap for sure go do it and with that we
end this
[Applause]
no fire for these chickens can I answer
Jim yeah I told him the old hymn we are
not the good ones the never would once
we're the ones that kill with the skill
in the dungeons union like an engine of
sin and then ghost back at the end with
an ale and a toast colder than a gale on
the coast I'm not sayin a boast but I'm
a letter man like a male in the post now
there's no respite no rest for the
decrepit you better buckle up for the
next bid in Omo I was gonna kill him on
the airship
he's never he doesn't know the answer
he's never heard this before it got
stole I had his clone in the hold in
folded in gold sarcophagus here's where
the soundtrack might get ominous my Maul
would reveal his inner workings like an
omnibus I pitch him over the side
unconscious fall like Babylon and stare
as he's caught midair Pteranodon
you misheard I don't need anybody's help
to kill a wizard I've had people ask
does this doesn't the clone spell need
Matt's like don't you need a cubic inch
of flesh to clone attack trying to put a
damper but pop the shampoos if I need is
jeans I mean that's any sock in his
hamper
it's true is it really murder when you
kill somebody if you spent a lot of
money on a less dumb body
don't answer why'd I try the only thing
I could never I could never really buy
was Jim it's not for lack of wealth it's
like a fucking game of solitaire I
played myself
are these Jim's the same person is there
a better or a worse one I don't know but
my soul says to stay with the first one
oh shit
thanks so much
I want to thank everybody for coming out
tonight want to thank LevelUp dice for
giving us really really heavy dice to
roll in these trays I also want to thank
Dean D beyond this is a game that you
can play this is our tradition come be a
part of it thanks so much thank you
[Applause]
you