[Music]
[Applause]
you
[Music]
hello oh boy yes
hello packs Australia
welcome to acquisitions incorporated my
name is Mike croolik and I will be the
game master this evening I would like to
introduce you to my players first up
playing omen drawing is Jerry Hawkins
[Applause]
yeah that's okay he's a cool guy
next up playing k3 RS Chris Stroud
next we have sticks being played by
Holly Conrad so many Holly fans in the
audience last but certainly not least
Jesse Cox playing seven
all right we are going to be playing
edge of the Empire this evening and it's
very new to us at the table I've played
it before with my family mostly my
children so hopefully you guys will be
better than an eight year old okay but
yeah so we start with the my Knock now
Jerry I'm sorry omen I'm sorry omen
thank you the my Knock who's Jerry I
don't even know that guy the my Knock
has unfortunately been captured
we just started yeah I know it's not a
great start we arrived with the crew of
the my knock down on the bottom deck you
as a smuggler captain obviously have
some secret places for a board for
special special cargo cargo you're in
them now yeah so you are down inside one
of these compartments and you are
looking up at a very smug looking trend
ocean this is a lizard man head rows of
sharp teeth he's got a blaster on his
hip and you can see that he has taken
all of your weapons and given them to
one of his cohorts who's an aqua wish
these are they've got the tusks remember
the guy was like and I don't like you my
friend doesn't want to give me that's
that that other dude was the aqua yeah
he's got the tusks anyway
he gives him your weapons and he says
omen nothing personal it's just a job
it's my ship it was your ship now
if you just relax down here and you make
things easy for me I'll be happy to drop
your crew off at the spin and then I'll
deliver the minot to her new owner if
you make
is difficult for me we're gonna have a
hard time the problem Ohman is I know
you and you're gonna make things
difficult at this point he draws his
blaster and he points it right at you
and he says I'm gonna have to give you
something else to think about and shoot
you right in the leg
Wow I want you to take six damage dude
you were working some things out here
like some emotional yes feels really
good yeah it looks collapse down in my
own secret compartments which I now
regret having installed yeah he seemed
surprised omen
did you think he knew how this story was
gonna go I had some thoughts about how
things were gonna go with my own ship
and my own crew yes I had some I had the
occasional thought about how it might go
yes I'm gonna ask you one time to do
what's right for your crew and just sit
tight with that he reaches over double
taps a secret panel on the wall and my
secret panel your secret panel and the
door above you slams shut now you can
hear him his footsteps trailing away but
you can also you also recognized that
the thug that he had with him is still
outside you hear him say keep an eye on
him to give you any trouble
shoot him so now you guys are trapped in
this very dark space this is one of the
smuggling compartments aboard the my
Knock and you're in a real bad situation
you really stepped in the pudhu which is
a Star Wars term I think so well thanks
already things are worse I'm upset in
hiding okay I'm covered in garbage this
might even be my room I don't even
is my bunk yeah yeah there's a way out
of this easy I just have to use my Jedi
Mind Tricks yeah this oh my god again
let me Jedi Mind Tricks
let me up there there's no force stop
this that's not real this is so dumb
very ho but there is there but there is
[Laughter]
[Applause]
it's over there too it's in both places
yes I just had this I had this part of
the ship gutted yeah install this I'm
assuming I installed a secret apartment
inside the secret compartment a lot of
weapons but a high-tech stuff I can
control the ship from inside the secret
no I don't think that's a part of the
plan okay you were you were smuggling
something though well and you can hear
sort of a tiny scratch but I am pretty
familiar with this ship that's true it's
mechanic
oh that's absolutely true so you would
probably know what omen was was
transporting yeah is that information
that you would allow yeah yeah well it
wouldn't be too hard to find out I don't
think if it scratches yeah you've got a
couple crates full of cohoon these are
little like centipede looking bugs that
assassins will occasionally use because
they're poison mimics the results of
like a cardiac arrest they are
completely 100% outlawed and totally
illegal to have on board incredibly
dangerous they make great pets it's you
have to get a bad rap it's okay yeah you
know you have to it's like those little
mandibles it's like oh like don't melt
your heart
when you look into those chumps okay so
so where are we in a are we in a
compartment with two crates of cohoon
yes yeah okay I say watch and learn Zee
and I knock on the door okay scare him
away yeah I say it's I'm not gonna
create any trouble down here but I mean
a bare minimum I need a stim pack we
need some I mean the best-case scenario
that I can see is some calf horderves
jogan fruit by the foot do you wanna
make a coercion check for me yeah
absolutely
okay so I'm gonna say that okay so
audience can you guys see our dice not
at the moment let's make sure that they
can see dice buffet oh hey okay this guy
is not the brightest I'm not gonna court
I'll try to charm him okay that would be
like you know hey listen I mean
obviously we got off on the wrong foot
just cuz I have just because I have some
beef obviously you know with your friend
who stole my ship I mean I think that
makes sense that you know we're gonna be
at loggerheads but there's no reason for
you and I to start our relationship off
on that
Clawd foot we're gonna be chatting here
forever eating my arm you have a charm
role for me I do i do my charm role is
to yellow dice Wow
to green dice
if you try to apply a black I'm not
gonna and it goes away again
because I'm the best so here's your dice
pool we've rolled everything you come
away with two successes in one failure
which means that you have one success
left over yeah okay so you succeed in
charming him
you also come out of here with four
advantage and two threat now these
cancel each other out
yeah I come out with two advantage right
so not only did you charm the pants off
of this guy but it's not literal well if
you want to use your advantage yeah I'll
allow it
yeah so how do you want to use your
advantage the advantage that I'm looking
for is in this in this encounter I mean
I'm hoping that it will improve
relations like the next time I want to
yeah with him about something I want to
have a leg up you have a new best friend
yeah in this thug yeah so he he says the
multistage process says we're gonna be
here forever
yeah really not supposed to do this but
what do you need I said well like any
one in a dark hole in the ground
mhm I need friends okay
I'd say do you think this is the only
secret compartment I have on this ship
yeah we looked it's my ship the entire
third floor of this ship was made to my
exacting specifications one of the
things that I keep in there well let's
just say it's very very valuable well
we'll take that too we're taking the
whole ship no I don't think I don't
listen I don't think down inside audibly
look up but I say I don't think you
understand what I'm talking about
let me help you I want you to imagine
yourself what's your name whip
swip that sounds like an aqua lish name
i think yeah yeah yeah it's a classic
one I say flip the next time you return
to your clan I want you to imagine doing
it in your own ship with your own gang
and this trend ocean that's running
things right now well right right now
he's down in the bottom of your ship you
mean risk yeah he's down in the bottom
of the ship and he's working very very
hard for you well right now right now
we're called risks gang do you do you
think I could I could call it's whips
game I think I think that Grist gang
doesn't sound like a tough organization
if I just heard it I'm just saying this
yeah if I had the choice between joining
risks gang uh-huh and joining flips gang
you know which one I joined whoo out of
those two which one do you think I would
join all right I joined Griff's gang I
wouldn't I wouldn't really yeah you know
right I'd go swim
alright alright so you hear you hear a
double tap and the the door above you
opens and he says man it's whips gang
man you and me were the first two right
no no I'm I am your I am your trusted
lieutenant mm-hmm absolutely what do we
need to do man how do we get to this
other compartment you've got well here
this other compartment obviously we just
met I can't take you know you don't want
to have a situation where I've got a lot
of the weapons yeah I'm gonna take you
to our secret weapon cache okay it is
actually up it is actually it sad not
down here of course this is your secret
compartment but the secret compartment
is here in this room it does require
that I use my own hand on it I gotta let
you out yeah but just for a second well
I get into the secret compartment where
your future begins I mean I mean as long
as you'll go back into the Camorra you
know I why would I leave okay all right
yeah he reaches a hand down to help to
help sort of haul you out thank you
thank you so much it's just right over
here yeah I'm gonna push him down into
the three-on-one dad all right yeah so
you you shove him down there and he
sprawled out on the ground and now he
knows that oh yeah things have gone
south it's not gonna be flips game the
sort of main compartment of your ship
you've got cargo containers stacked up
you can see that there's a lift in the
back that will take you up to the second
and then the third floor of your ship
and you can see that all of your gear
has been piled up sort of in a corner oh
okay this is great news everybody
did you guys to deal with him down there
what are you guys gonna do a swim I
guess he's on his back looking up at you
I probably like wrestled people in the
garbage pit before I don't know like
like yell at him I'm gonna yell at him
no we need to keep him on home inside
you fell down just making it worse you
should I'm gonna try and coerce him that
he fell down okay listen
actually can I assist like you listen
pretend the force is real out of
character my charm is not high that's
more of a flavor okay flip does know
that he was pushed into this hole so if
you want to try to convince him
otherwise it's going to be a difficult
check what if I tell me I was a phantom
hand that would also be hard yeah but he
wants a phantom hand right no one wants
that so you the problem you grab their
equipment I assume right yeah yeah are
you guys mobilizing swip I mean I'm
lucky he's prone he's not fighting right
now he felt no I don't want any part of
this okay Frank if I go over and get a
handful no I was gonna say it's its
course and I don't care for it but I
will just sit upon him okay okay
I'm party to this yeah
so you're up grabbing the equipment you
hear the lift behind you start coming
down okay so I drop I grab this bundle
of equipment okay and I start parting it
out as it trips it
cheer up remember these all right
I continue dropping everybody else their
staff chimp and I tell flip that after
we have chased the rest of these people
off the ship I will be much much kinder
to him
but until then yeah we can't be friends
he's obviously hurt now Keith Reyes
you're sitting on him and as you look
down he turns his head and all four of
his big black ball Desai's begin to cry
exactly the equipment I'm helping them
up yeah out of there
we're gonna close this okay say not a
peep flip so you say that I say maximum
sustained whimpering he's obviously hurt
like deeply hurt yeah by what transpired
yeah I want to let him know that he of
course Ullman had to make it look as
though you were overpowered oh not that
we're working together
he likes that actually that makes a lot
of sense to cook she kind of he wipes
his tusks
you know cleans off all four of his eyes
yeah I looked down to say yeah what the
Droid said everybody out not youth with
everybody else out except you at this
point the lift door opens and four more
of these thugs come out
Haislip we're yet
right so in this in this room is there a
scenario via which we can provide a
ambush situation we're down into storage
like we got some crates a situation
where they're coming in and we can try
to just make it as merry as possible
down there you know in our cohoon wanna
lay in wait yes okay yeah then I won't
even I won't even have you roll for
initiative I'll just have you guys are
gonna go first and then these four new
thugs that came they come in
unsuspecting we'll go after so we'll go
alright so the way edge of the empire
works
you guys get to choose who is going to
take this first initiative slot alright
so who would you like to go first so
these thugs are coming around the corner
you guys have sort of secret of
yourselves behind some massive cargo
boxes crates they don't see you yet but
you could very easily sort of pop out in
ambush do you have any ideas you
absolutely can aim and I will give you a
bonus die for doing some aiming okay I
pop out from behind cover you know let's
do it okay so you're gonna go first
yes okay I have a bonus as well okay two
quick strike which means that when I do
this I get a boost die oh alright I'll
give you a boost so the first thug here
so you get a boost and then what's your
attack - yellow - green good lord
so the yellow were that have the most
chances for success just for those of
the audience knows and the Green is very
very good yeah so you end up with five
successes and only one failure okay so
you succeed at this and you generate
three advantage okay so how would you
like to first of all how much damage do
you deal to the first thug that you saw
well I I don't kill I entertain myself
by shooting hands and legs
blasters out of hands so I don't want to
actually hit them
okay so I don't know if you need to add
black dye to that to make it even more
difficult I'm gonna give you a setback
die thank you yeah okay
you still succeed it's okay great so I
shoot one of the bugs blasters right out
of his hand and my amazing skill freaks
out the other three thugs so you want to
spend your advantage to sort of start
all these other ones I will give them
setback dies on their attacks against
you okay it's because of my yeah who
does that who attacks like this what's
going on next
yeah I'm aiming so there's there's still
four of these thugs one of them blaster
lists now straight okay okay all right
what is your attack it is one yellow and
two green okay what are we looking at
here oh just barely succeeded so tell me
how much damage you deal I do
geez that is a big blaster I also have a
stun setting it looks like a broom now
was it on stun okay so you deal damage
and success extra point of damage so you
have one success here after canceling
out the failure right so 10 damage to
the kill so he's like oh boom just right
between the eyes
yeah smoking crater in his face now just
laying on the ground I'm just like
that's how you do it I've said this fine
aim again ers here's the thing I don't
have any energy weapons now if you could
use your maneuver to sort of close the
distance on these guys if you wanted to
and channel them I bet yeah how did what
is key 3rs like in a fight nothing he's
not a he's not a violent droid okay even
though he's built for violence yeah
would you like to spend your turn but I
will use my maneuver to act as though
I'm evading its combat oh dear oh you
you you look like you don't know what's
going on but if you're actually closing
to just yes I'm like I'm like they're
madmen Oh provided that I'm able to get
up close on one yeah and that's their
mind yeah I just wanted to deck them
okay yeah so I mean with your with your
nook like vibrant vibro knuckles okay
but it's like Intel until you get too
close and then it just goes the fist
yeah so I will say that when you are
engaged with someone the difficulty of
hitting them is only one purple dye okay
but that purple dye did generate to
failure already you're in the hole what
is your melee what is your vibro knuckle
attack which one would that just be
melee melee attack oh that's that's
three green three green one come on
Chris oh you're yeah you canceled those
out too there's an advantage Oh two more
success Wow
your rules your Matta quite well so
what's the damage on your knuckles
it's four okay and you have two
successes here so six damage total is
not quite enough to kill him but the one
that you punched is now prone on the
ground just holding his face this
reddish black gut falling out of his no
what was this tusk area right testicle
region what we call the t-zone Tuscany
more like that you also came out of this
was an advantage so how would you like
to use that yeah now as somebody new to
this game yeah what is the best place
for me to there's all kinds of cool
stuff and you know we're way Pro yeah
yeah you could give it to someone else
and they have a blue dye on their turn
you come up with creative ways of
finding uses for that like this guy now
because everyone saw that you're up in
their face now they all focus on you
instead of us things like that yeah you
can be story stuff it doesn't have to be
right yeah no it's not crazy time like
we win so we got he's my new friend yeah
I hit him so good in our way to his
birthday party no okay space climb to
space no that makes a lot of sense we
have two guys who are not injured yes
and they've got blasters oh yeah
absolutely
this guy's on the ground hurt yeah let's
let's do it that way where now the other
two spin okay focus on me okay
absolutely
so you've taunted yes see that was omen
all right so you just watched k3 just
pound a guy into the ground and you
notice the other two now have drawn
their blasters and they're turning on
the Droid exactly oh how did that happen
right I said III leverage my holdout
blaster kept pretty close a close range
yeah in their faces own this is an easy
shot exactly and I say fellas that's how
the first three seconds win I can make
it look like you had no choice in the
matter
I've got a perfectly nice hole you might
remember hahahaha it's the one that you
put me in very recently yeah I have a
very nice hole should accommodate all of
you you can get in that hole or me and
my friends will continue killing you I
stopped when I go great hole
[Laughter]
No are you trying to coerce or charge
charm charm just like hey listen these
guys are there their dander is up
they're in a fight they're spaced and ER
they're spaced standard one of them just
got killed the other ones on the ground
I'm gonna say the difficulty on this is
to purple yeah
you've generated one threat and two
failures already yeah
what is your charm - yellow - green -
one black okay - green and one yellow
zone - two yellow charm
I came to play some advantage that
doesn't count as successes another
yellow bull still no successes though
you're getting a lot of advantage but
you have not actually succeeded and one
green or two - green oh my gosh what is
happening here I'm going to push it one
more time oh okay you have failed oh but
you have generated for advantage how
would you like to spend that that's it
that is a significant amount of
advantage it is you can use it to give
some boost dye to your allies on their
roles yeah or if you have what I'm gonna
do I'm gonna do because it's a whole
heap of advantage yeah so it doesn't
work so I'm just gonna pull back behind
a thing and say alright no didn't work
maybe there maybe they heard it and
they're like nah we gotta kill them but
they're now nervous dead yeah so like
they're shake it well they already have
setback die when they attack oh it's
true yeah exactly so it's just like no
but it's pull back it's like hey okay
that didn't work do do this the other
thing do the thing we were doing before
alright I'll give a bonus die on the
next round I love it okay help me
remember that I will don't worry cuz I'm
gonna try to forget
[Music]
next up are our three thugs so the one
that is in front of you
k3 he's gonna stand up and he got he has
brass knuckles so since he's engaged
with you he's just gonna try to
congratulations he's gonna you haven't
picked a date yet but yeah he's he's
gonna slam these knuckles right into
your droid face once to have the first
thing I think to do to a drama to give
him a setback die okay he's already got
two failures and interesting you know he
does not succeed but he does generate
advantage so I feel bad for him I'm
gonna say that he does not deal any
damage to you but his attack does
actually bring you down onto the ground
no you are you are prone on the ground
okay
next thug these do you have blasters and
their intent on shooting you when
they're actually gonna be at a
disadvantage shooting you know that
you're prone and when I go prone do I go
prone on top of the prone guy I think
you're sort of interconnected you're
just its energy legs and arms it's a
very sensor but it should be it should
be like face down though like yeah
setback one difficulty and then and to
yellow for their blasters man okay so
they're pros yeah oh boy like that
so try was here why don't you tell them
about this awesome new symbol you've
discovered that's called the triumph
symbol and it's not good what's I it's a
triumph for me so k three RS you are hit
and I am going to do a critical injury
on
hmm so we need to roll the percentile
dice I have one let's just roll trust
you
777 C no b7 oh it's just the number 7
yeah I can't count the target can only
act during the last allied initiative
slot on his next turn okay so he's your
slowed down
yeah I mean it goes it goes from slowed
down all the way to horrific injury
gruesome injury I guess there's a
distinction there and maiming is
different from those oh absolutely yeah
all right and the damage is 7 so you
should soak value got a soak of yeah
oh really yeah he's a robot yeah you're
a robot so you so Christ when you take 2
damage yeah all right not bad
all right and then the last thug bring
it on who does not hit you it does
generate advantage I'm gonna give him a
boost I I'm on his next attack all right
then we're back up to the top with Zev I
do a little blow on my last missiles and
look over watch out this is done and I
attempt to flip while shooting
at one of the blaster pistols okay okay
I don't know no Michael you said that
you were going to forget but I'm going
to remind okay first let me determine
how difficult I produced I am they have
black right but you're trying you're
trying to flip yes and shoot a blaster
out and shooter bless okay I'm giving
you a red and two Purple's great so
you're starting off with a threat and
three failures now you have a boost I
yes let's start with that a great role
you're looking good so far
now what's next to yellow to green start
with the start the green some advantage
hey a whole lot of nothing okay there's
a success hey hey
alright now something is interesting
well now let's take a look at what we've
got you haven't failed okay so you did
not shoot any blasters but you have
generated one advantage and one triumph
to spend these as I flip I shoot these
blaster pistols off and they totally
miss yeah but hit the fire suppression
system and foam so all three of them
plus you are just covered in foam and
that's bad oh yeah it's like a
quick-drying fire suppression foams okay
yeah they are now all hardened ROTC
all right it's like asbestos yeah in 20
years
yeah
you got them good okay nail them all
right so the fire suppression system
goes off and sprays the entire deck with
this quick drying foam and you can feel
it sort of hardening around your body
next is stick oh man these guys are now
just trying to get this guck off of them
as fast as they can before it hardens go
for it yeah one yellow and two green
okay I'm gonna give you your boost dye
sweet one yellow to green whoo see and
these cancel each other out so no threat
or advantage but you do succeed so
damage is nine damage find damage every
time she pulls that thing back I imagine
house like a recoil to you like it's
really cool yeah absolutely like you
pushing you back and then it also
encases them in a coffin and another one
just died it shoots coffins okay three
you cannot go next because of your
critical injury so oh man you will go
next it's me
there are two left the one that cthe
wrists I'm sorry case three RS thank you
is is just you know engaged with leg
yeah
and then the other one you saw has a
blaster drawn but now he's got this
stuff this fire something go you wait it
out I love them tusks I mean I lean back
outside this may be slipping slightly on
this foam yeah and I say there was a
there was another way there was another
way but now it's this way yeah and I'm
gonna try to blast them with my blaster
okay no I get the boost I also yeah
because they're so great I'll give you a
boost I owe a great guy oh thanks pal
alright so yeah so toss some blue in
there and then my
range seeing some favorite alright dude
love that love the boost eyes these are
hacks and you know it I'm just pushing
buttons here three green three green ah
okay I like that
you have succeeded I have and you have
generated to advantage incredible what
is your damage my damage on that weapon
is five okay so it ends up being seven
okay
does not that's gonna kill exactly what
hurts very bad and he doesn't like it
does not like it at all
why do you want to spend your advantage
you have to advantage let's see I can
perform let's see I'm gonna throw an
extra boost died okay over two K three
Rs nice okay case three RS you've got
the one that you're engaged with and the
other one they're both hurts yeah
ridiculously bad now just from behind
cover I'm like wrap this up k3 yeah
let's see is there anything I can do to
like to split that really not yeah what
I want to do is I want to I want to if
he's within reach of me and you were
thrown yeah right is he is he beside me
absolutely I would love to just punch
straight up okay
into this softest part right
yeah there's sort of a furry region
around the abdomen that you can go this
is ready okay let it go if you are tiny
they'll be a really sweet kaiju battle
yeah now I am gonna give you a setback
time because you're covered phone phone
oh that's okay what is your mailing oh
um let's see here
you know I'll tell you what it is but
what's the difference between brawl and
mailing it's a great question
give me your brawl I'm a brawl man well
brawl is a characteristic I think brawl
is gonna be punching mail is going to be
a sword or oh then I write brawl brawl
alright we'll enjoy to green and one
yellow oh goodness
that's what I need to be doing yeah yeah
and then throwing that boost
[Applause]
kcra's this is gruesome little jets I
don't even need you to tell me the
damage he's just obliterated but I am
going to give you to strain okay because
I'm going to use the threat to give you
strain so in Star Wars edge of the
Empire there are sort of two different
health tracks you have health and then
you also have strings right yeah you
have strain which is more representation
of your physical exertion your mental
strain that sort of thing right so I
think that I think that when you punched
into him you felt something sort of
break inside and it just really grossed
you out like being being it a droid
feeling this organic and things like it
was like oh what is that for like maybe
I'm like I'll knock him out yeah take
him out of commission we can interrogate
him later so you've got to strain
remember that if you want on your turn
you can spend your advantage to heal
strain okay very very easy code the
strain cometh and the strain goeth yeah
next up is my one remaining thug and he
is going to take a shot at Katherine I'm
sorry Katherine so it's really hard for
like that's a who I think of you as a 3k
three yeah
we need like in that cruel spell that
way yeah okay why Oh
oh my oh no wow basically I get to do
whatever you are my Troy dude he liked
that guy yeah he liked him a lot you
were gonna take eight damage and I'm
gonna use that triumph for a critical
injury if you could roll the percentile
for me yeah
plus ten
this time wait how how does he attack
blaster yeah is it a energy yeah okay
cuz I get one I think I get another soak
off of that that's a huge yeah man
one oh no that's hang on a second
it's been so long since I've used these
can't you just no I did I did I did
I think that's where'd you get it is
that in here yeah it is 1 then 0 0 I
think that both zeros are a hundred is
it a hundred I think it's a hundred no
it can't be a hundred I see what you're
saying I see what you're saying this
can't be six hundred I don't think so
that would be sixty right no this has to
be this is the tens place do it again I
liked one one years ago is 12 12 12 plus
10 because when he could have a crown
jury takes you to 22 okay see I had a
hundred sided dice that's how cool
people do you are off balance I'm gonna
add a setback guy to your next check
okay you're doing fine
yeah I'm not worried Oh terrific we
maimed and did you take your damage yes
with your soak fantastic medicine it was
in a being like - yeah that's a huge
soak zev
looks around and he's he's done
everything just murder everywhere I'm
like cackling yeah he puts his blaster
pistols away and walks up to the
remaining guy yeah and slaps him okay
just right across the face just open
hands just pop okay are you attempting
to deal any damage
no I'm frustrated but I can't slap my
crew member so he gets it okay
so he he takes a shot at k3 and then he
turns across the board across the place
right across the Tusk yes look at this
look at this we're gonna throw you in a
hole and there's worms in there and
there's enough this is insane I don't
know what's going on he is stunned he is
not I don't mean in-game terms like he's
stunned I mean he's just like strong
this is a very surprising he's very
surprising to him is is that your is
that your action my action is yes okay
yes he he responds by rubbing the
affected rieta whiskery sort of area on
the side of his face it's like just get
in the hole
what's his what's his rub die school he
went to a like a four-year institution
or something yeah kostik how would you
like to handle this last don't you do it
don't you do it
oculus thug I just like I watch him slap
slap the thug and I'm just like I'm just
like takes I'm like the one from the
ground on my face
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay now you don't have any more boost I
know I do not you don't so you're just
looking at yellow and too green okay now
you've already generated two failures
yeah Bevo yellow oh don't I'm like right
in front of him please one green there's
a success oh nothing happens
Oh am i leg in my blaster just like
smokes yeah it discharges but the bolt
flies over his head and he doesn't even
notice he's so shocked that someone
would open hand slap him in the middle
of a fight I turn around I'm busy k3 um
Kendall I'm gonna I'm still prone right
I'm just gonna sweep the leg like Johnny
your leg Johnny yeah okay can I get my
shoe
yeah that's gonna be that's gonna be a
brawl now you have a setback dying whoa
I already got some threat oh boy yeah he
doesn't like that oh man what is your
brawl again it's uh it's too green and
one yellow Hey wow wow wow you got rid
of that threat hey free RS yeah it's
just like like in a circus yeah see you
trip him he falls down and hits the back
of his head and dies yeah he just he
gives one one sort of car and then dead
he has to look over his head all right
so you guys tell with the the thugs you
are now in this in the compartment the
storage area in the bottom of the ship
of the my knock what would you like to
do next
these guys have any parts I can take off
Homer you could you could absolutely
snatch a tusk yeah I do I'm gonna take
one of them screams Shaw yeah yeah I
like tie it onto my weird scarf
she's on the glitch yeah take them
upstairs yeah so there's a I can tell
that you're upset and I I say that the
problem is you keep shooting the guns
we're supposed to be the good guys
that's what we do but you're honestly
trying to help yeah you think that he's
he's just not good you could shoot him
here here any one of these soft it's
very soft I walk over to the lift and I
turn around this is happening here and
he's also continuing to think about
mortality and I hit the I hit the lift
button okay and I called the lift down
and I turn around and I say Zev we are
the good guys
that's been made fairy appearance we
have a hole filled with deaf slugs this
is death centipedes yeah they are right
you're right they're really cute yeah
yeah I'll burrow right into your heart
and the way I'm laying love eggs yeah
now so I'm a three-floor there's 3/4 the
second floor is really just open air
it's just a huge compartment for
fourscore go right yeah and then the
third floor of the my Knock is where
you've got the sort of the crew quarters
you've got the community area the
cockpit captains quarters all that good
stuff
do I miss gris-gris urn do I know
[Music]
Griscom in a canteen or something you
you know him as another fellow smuggler
in the outer rim yeah so it's sort of
like just I mean it's a courtesy right I
mean this is not normal this would not
be normal no he mentioned that it was a
job but normally smugglers would not
doesn't seem like a trend ocean thing
either especially keeping people in
holds like none of this lines up for me
yeah okay well do I think that knowing
what I know about the ship do I think
that we might be able to get into the
bridge via the open area weather would
there be a way for us to get into a
tunnel vent shaft people are always
doing that
sure would there be a way would there be
a way for us to it's all the rage it's
all the rage would there be a way for us
to get up to the 3rd up to the top
without without having to take the
elevator up and then leave and go into
bed oh you wanna you want to find a
circuitous route yes yes yeah I would
absolutely allow you guys to do that
it's probably gonna get I'm gonna give
you strain right like climbing through
the ductwork of the my knock exactly
accepting each other up hoisting each
other
[Laughter]
no but there where we my thinking is
that I mean I know how to fly the ship
hmm I know where to keep the stuff my
thinking is that sticks is probably
gonna be better at knowing like the
shimmy the guts them yeah
the shimmy zones if you will it's
probably true yeah exactly because
that's we gonna be their most delicious
stowaways our family that's true
Styx also probably knows that she has
not cleaned these ducts even though she
was told to but you still okay letting
everyone go through them yeah okay
because they're not cleaned I'm gonna
make it too strange to everybody as you
pull yourselves through these disgusting
air shafts not me okay okay so here's
the question can you yeah yeah I think
you can yeah absolutely
if you take some work so sticks you kick
out this great and you just covered in
gross sludge and you roll out and you
look up and you're in the common area
there's sort of a big round table and so
is sitting at the table he's got a cup
of cash feet up feet up probably I was
like crawl out yeah and so you all sort
of tumble out of this shaft and you're
in the the main sort of common area of
the my Knock ahead of you down this hall
is the crew quarters the your room is
gonna be at the end of that and then the
the cockpit at the very end just behind
you you can see there's a ladder that
leads up to the like access port yeah of
the ship and the latter being down tells
you that that portal is probably open oh
so there's somebody or there's somebody
up in the access I'm telling you that
it's open all right
somebody didn't tidy up yeah
I'm sorry yeah this would be like the
the docking port where you would
transfer between two ships Oh between
two yeah
oh this is great news they may be moving
through both ships this is very good
news so I could go up the ladder close
that port put the ladder back up and
then maybe go to the front and go to the
cockpit should you want to move to the
ladder
well first thing I want to do is I'm
going to get out a handkerchief okay and
I'm going to rigorously profound
enthusiasm yeah make sure that my Lecco
are spotless because I got I got a
little something on there okay when I
was climbing through the hole yeah now
you don't want to dirty like who no no
no no I don't think that's a drink no no
exactly I just I just throw that
handkerchief away okay like this there's
no reason to keep that yeah so yeah I'm
gonna look up the letter so looking up
the ladder you can see that that there
served to like an airlock yes sir
both of them are open and you can see
out above you what looks like the
interior of another ship another larger
ship for metal catwalks is there is
there any way is it a three RS is there
any way that from back here or maybe
even from my own quarters is there any
way that you could talk to the ship or
get some idea about the external like
what what we're looking at like what
type of ship yeah yes so forth yeah I
think so
so we want it we want to move quite
quickly and quietly back to the back to
my quarters okay where I am assuming I
have access to the to the the technology
of the ship yeah absolutely yes you guys
move back there
you recognize so KTRS you want to log
you want to what exactly are you looking
for in here
I'm trying to determine what this ship
is above us like okay what make like how
maybe how many crew there would be why
don't you make me a computers I'd love
to
it's a great check that I do it is three
green and one yellow one one difficulty
dye has already given you a failure and
a threat okay and you said you are three
green one yellow I like that I like that
too that's great so what do we have with
here murder a success and two advantage
so you're able to get into the Minox
sensors and see that the ship that has
you contained is is actually Grist ship
which is a Marauder class assault
Corvette there's a huge freighter right
and normally the interior these ships
are designed to hold like a squadron of
Fighters yeah but it has been completely
redone to hold large specifically more
like another freighter one single large
ship okay and for your advantage I will
I will say that you also recognize that
the Minox locked inside this Bay so
there are clamps holding the my Knock in
place inside risk ship and you notice
that Grist ship is called the green
flame Wow yeah it doesn't interest me is
that notable I informed you omen of this
okay so in order to I mean we have some
the my Knock has some weapons but we're
talking about physical kprs let's you
know too that the my Knock has basically
been shut down at this point you don't
you don't have access to any weaponry or
anything like that it's completely
slaved to the green flame
with the grips with this grip massive
mechanical clamp yes so we have to get
out of here sounds like a job for a hero
I'll do it yes send me out there in
space we're in their ship we're inside
of another ship yeah yeah you are in the
bay of a larger ship you've you've been
swallowed exactly so we need exactly
like a nesting doll of ship yeah I got
there you did all right now well done
thanks pal
so what my thinking is that we're gonna
have to we're never gonna survive unless
we get a little crazy first of all I
like that so what we should do is we're
gonna need to head up this umbilical
we're gonna have to deactivate this
other we're gonna activate these
clamps yeah and maybe even open are we
hanging like and then it's over space
well you haven't gone out yeah okay you
could have you could have cut me some
slack there man I mean what I've known
you for 20 years I mean it's like you
know you don't know what's out there yet
okay so fine it's gonna be like that I
guess so yes it is going to be like that
so we're so my thinking is let's let's
head up this sneaky Times Nicky Times
sneaky entire Bay so we're gonna have to
get a cut we can't leave you here so
what we should do is head out there try
to deactivate these clamps if we have to
open up the other the other dock then we
have to do that as well that's the plan
okay so you guys want to go back to the
ladder yeah okay and climb climb up it
are you taking any special care in
climbing this ladder to avoid detection
they just maximum care okay do you wanna
get stealth
yeah yeah okay hey I'll have to make one
uh who's first use it to who's going up
the ladder first out first yeah cuz I'm
a hero
okay and are you attempting to be sneaky
at all yes okay I don't wanna get caught
I'm sure here oh yeah yeah you've
generated three threat already just on
the difficulty of sneaking out of this
ship I am one yellow three green hey I
like what I'm seeing
good lord
oh so you have succeeded but you have
generated two threat so I'm gonna say
that I'm gonna say that you pull it you
sneak up right you rung over rung you
poked your head up and what you see out
here is a massive Bey inside this
freighter right and it's criss-crossed
by these catwalks okay
the particular catwalk that your ship is
connected to extends in both directions
and at one end it looks like there's
sort of a room like a security room or a
computer room that would have some
controls and stuff in it and you can see
guards sort of patrolling these catwalks
at various places for your threat I'm
gonna give you strain just because
sneaking I don't think is your forte
good yeah it's really good okay you got
string to string right before it so
before you go up yeah I say sir listen
they had a stealth of one green okay
they're gonna know is there a way I
think I might have to leave you here
yeah or no that's a good idea
I'm gonna leave him here operating the
computers assessing them my Knock will
have him on comlink Jeff so so that he
you can do what you can
continuing to access the computers and
trying to discover anything else you can
you can be like the person in the chair
like you just just sit there yeah but I
don't sit you didn't really sell it man
you can be like you know like the person
in the chair yeah the guy who doesn't
come person the person who stays yeah
you can enhance yeah zoom in yeah so do
you guys want to climb up and out onto
the catwalk so what's next what's next
for the crew of my Namek how do you want
to handle this
obviously there are there are guards
patrolling this Bay they're keeping an
eye on the my NOC I would imagine how
many cards do we know you probably saw
at least four it doesn't look like there
are any on on the catwalk dijanna click
International your ship
I want to stealth my way sneak over to
the control control okay they're
watching I mean this they're on patrol
and their job is to watch true so they
are guards one two three this is a
difficult okay
whoa this is a nightmare you've got four
failures already tell me about this
stealth three green one yellow one whoa
good start two three Wow and a yellow Oh
[Applause]
Wow two successes Wow everything else
cancels everything yeah so do it yeah
yeah I want to hear about this I look
back at everyone I'm the hero and I jump
out and roll in dodge and twirl and spin
yeah and like lay prone and then flip up
and keep going
dramatically and ridiculously okay where
it's obvious someone should have seen it
no one got it no noise yeah okay you you
arrived at the control room at the end
and you can see that it's definitely
full of computer consoles and it is it
is well protected from the prying eyes
of the guards outside so you roll into
it and then you pop up yes okay
would anyone like to follow I'm like
where did he go he's disappeared
yeah I'm gonna I'm gonna pull you up on
the comics here over there and you may
be able to create some kind of a
distraction that might ease our checks
to get out of here what kind of
distraction look around in there look at
that consoles got you got I pulled my
blaster to shoot one of the concert
[Applause]
yeah I know disruption distraction
understood and I'm I'm on the comlink at
the same time and I'm saying like now
there's this schematic shows us that
you're gonna want to find this consult a
specific type and I shot the one with
the red button a klaxon a klaxon starts
sounding outside of the page and all the
guards now are on high alert and they
turn they're looking or they don't
understand what's going on what you're
in there you succeeded at the important
part yeah what what was that what did
you turn on turn it off pop out now
what's your how stealthy are you oh man
I doubt that I'm very stealthy but oh
three green that's okay but they're
looking but they're throwing their
throwing three purples which is the
problem there's other consoles in here I
can shoot you have no idea no no I say I
say I say okay we're gonna try to come
over there sticks you have your tools
yeah no you know what Zev I want you to
make me that roll for the shot and let's
see if it generates threat or advantage
all right so just so there's miss you
can't miss there's no difficulty here we
just want to basically what am I wrong
I'm gonna give you one because ya roll
like a roll your ranged attack okay -
yellow - green a you could pop up with a
triumph here or something
well nobody didn't you really got
nothing you really just shot some
freedoms console and now there's an
alarm blaring outside
I kind of know what I'm doing yeah I
could have the ship could have fallen
into space for all we know they could
have yeah I think now the microwave
doesn't work really like this there's an
oculus trying to make a burrito and he's
just like rubbing his tusks he'll always
remember that day you could make a
breathe that's gonna be endgame right
through the campaign ten years from now
emesis k3 I want you to try to help Zev
I want you to try to talk him through
turning off the klaxon please I'll give
you a boost I absolutely if you wanna
make a computers check with a booth what
does that look like well I'm gonna have
your your telling him how to do it I'm
gonna I'm gonna give is I have a boost
what's your computer's too green all
right it's got buttons you can shoot
them it's all looking the same to me I
don't know you and a boost hey that's
really you succeed but you have
generated stress so the alarm goes off
but now all the guards are aware that
something is going on in the control
room they see another blast yep smoke is
coming out of it I got it yeah and they
all are gonna start moving sort of in
that general direction okay so do I
think that is there another console that
I can see from the little hatch like I
see that they're over there in this
command zone right do I do I see do I
think that that would be where this
these clamps would be controlled from
yeah yeah absolutely it's sort of the
control center for this Bay if I can see
them - I might be able to like do
something I need to get you there yeah
you can see that the clamps are actually
attached to the sides of the my Knock if
you were to sort of scramble across the
top of it you could probably get to them
physically right Oh
this is a thousand times better because
they're not gonna be looking at the ship
they're gonna be looking over here right
now their attention is on whatever the
heck is going on looks like a Daft Punk
concert just lights coming up smoke
we need a raid I was gonna say that's my
deal yeah yeah because like I have I'm
sure you do as well but like I have bad
motivator which will cause another
system to fail all right so with that
distraction you're welcome should I just
come up yes now you come up I need I
need the two of you to put your heads
together and I need the clamps gone and
most importantly I need access to the
turret I need the weapon systems because
that might that might make quick work of
the for people who are now closing in on
Zeb yeah yes so what do you want uk3 I
just started clanking up that ladder now
they're focused yeah yeah hopefully you
guys can get this I do it in time to the
alarm okay I try to make the sound I'm
in a wall yeah so you're up on top of
them I knock now and you can see that
the clamps there's one clamp on to your
right and there's another massive
clamped I mean these are like seven feet
is huge right did you want do you want
to go to one of them yeah absolutely
okay and then are you making a
mechanic's check a computers check what
are you trying to do to this thing um so
the bad motivator talent is once per
session
Wow I make a hard mechanics check and I
cause a targeted device to fail all
right let's start that's really cool
it's hard so I could pop one of them one
two three okay what's your mechanics
mechanics is you know of it it's a to
green to yellow and to negated black dye
so you remove them there were none
what are we looking at you do not
succeed but you don't fail but you
generate to advantage so I'll let you
remove strain if you want or you could
spend it in some other way it's up to
you I'm gonna hang out on my strain yes
you see maybe it's a situation where
it's like you know how it's like if you
start working on a jar and then you give
it to somebody else that's a guy
loosened it could he could he offer him
could he give himself a boost on his
next attempt to work on it something
like that or or something okay yeah I
say I tell I can tell it once to fail
[Laughter]
you're hearing this alright so you want
to come over and make a mechanic as well
yes getting these things to disengage
mechanically from the ship is very
difficult I think what's your mechanics
though it is to yellow and one green
okay nobody we're conferring a boost
right and a boost
come on boost no but you Gerry one
advantage you could remove some strain
you have strain that is true we can
remove a couple points of string if you
want or you could imagine some other way
to spend that advantage hmm could I
maybe help it help loosen the clamp that
k3 is working on there's like brute
force yeah I could make the check easier
next yes yeah I'll make it yeah instead
of difficult it'll be the middle tier
yeah
don't work that's no go I'm gonna help
my team this fail check I don't think I
can do it again
yeah you can't I still hold on at this
point the guards have arrived at the
control room in there there sure
sneaking around they're not sure what's
going on sir they're being very careful
what are you doing
peeking out the doorway saying nothing
to see here everything is fine good
looking they look in the see if there's
a closet or something get a good get the
right kind of hat oh I'm definitely I'm
in a jacket that's about three sizes too
big okay
and the Hat that sort of looks like a
intergalactic cowboy hat okay that's
what they they're that's what the gang
wears so you're trying to look like them
yes in in this control room you've
snatched somebody's you left they're
coated for whatever they're and I'm also
a human so I definitely don't look like
them at all usually taking these tusks
man and just shove them up there yeah
and you made fun of me yeah I never do
that a blaster bolt comes into the room
and sizzle against the wall next to you
all right shoot back yeah yeah just
blindly out the door well I mean I'm
talented so it's not blindly I shoot
back all right
hitting anybody like this is gonna be
pretty difficult
what's your ranged attack it's too
yellow to green nope get one advantage
but you do not hit anybody what you want
to do I fire back out through the door
and they see that even though it didn't
hit them yeah boy it could have hit them
ha ha ha whoa they can tell they're ISM
I mean he didn't hit me this time but
this guy can shoot yes yeah it was a
precise miss I'm sure they were like
there were four guys here and they went
right through yeah
they were gung-ho on just barging in
here and taking out and now they've
decided to sort of stop take up
positions and be a little bit careful
this guy in here can shoot Oh
[Music]
okay here we go here we go I am going to
I'm going to try to inspire my team okay
how are you gonna do that I'm gonna
inspire them using the inspiring
rhetoric action some I'm looking out
firing Redick is so omen yeah I'm
looking out from the top of the thing
it's just my head no mouth top in the
ice I look over and Stix is banging on
something k3 just look over here now
there were just four people running and
now they've taken up a hardened position
but they're looking away from you and
there they are 100% focused on their
truly incredible marksman yeah I had one
bad shot but it was probably intentional
it's like if he wanted to he could yes
so I am going to the inspiring Riddick
lets me take the inspiring rhetoric
action I can make an average leadership
check okay
for each success one Ally recovers one
strain for each advantage one ally
recovers one additional strain okay so
I'm gonna use congenial okay to
downgrade the difficulty of a chip
really but I have to take strain in
order to do it so I'm gonna take my
point of strain now it's down there now
I am rolling too yellow and too green
okay yeah you succeed and you succeed
with three advantage yeah exactly so
what I'm gonna do and I have two
successes yes so I'm gonna give I'm
gonna use inspiring rhetoric on sticks
and inspiring rhetoric on Zev okay and
because I have the improved version of
it they gain boost dies on all skill
checks
for this next so you just really do
better no no no I look over here at this
mess
and I look over here and look at this
mess and I raise the comlink and I say
I've seen way worse guys you got this
okay we're doing okay yes
are we yeah are we and are we in risks
ship yeah does he have a kind of metal
talent that is holding the steel heart
of our ship and play absolutely does can
we leave absolutely not we have guns or
hyperdrive barely we don't have any of
that you know we have we have each other
all right so you each heal three screen
two sticks and k3 you're reinvigorated
now no it makes sense that I'm not
affected by that I'm just like how does
that help what does that mean do you
want to try to make another mechanics I
do yes check on this on this particular
I'm I'm like hitting it with my gun okay
that would work it's only I'm only doing
two difficulty now because of your last
attempt right it loosened it so to speak
yeah the jars it's ready to open now
pickles inside yeah so remind me of your
mechanics to yellow and one green oh my
god you don't do it but you must Elvis
come on booth come on boost this clamp
does not budge but you have five
advantage so okay it doesn't unlock but
how do you want to
so while I'm hitting it with my gun yeah
it's going off one of these foolish guys
just takes the bolt right in the back of
the head and dies the sticks even oh no
I don't think so okay three guys do they
think it was a trick shot that you go
this guy's amazing
he must have bounced it off like five
different walls like are you kidding me
okay you're welcome looks at the doorway
and sees a dead yeah and he's just
perplexed rhinos though deep down when
an aqua leche dies within five parsecs
yeah we know angel gets its wings and
yeah so I attempt to shoot again this
time at one of their feet okay so
they're they're taking cover I'm gonna
give you a setback die and your yellow
to green yep yep and a boost oh wow this
is incredible and to advantage because
the blaster-bolt that you fired came
from below it destroyed a little bit of
the catwalk yeah and when it went
through that guy so by shooting at the
one guys the catwalk collapses and
all the guys all three I'm gonna give it
to you yeah
the whole thing just crumble and it's
just but where do they fall they're all
getting pale no I mean it's it's a long
drop down to the bottom of this Bay and
so you just hear the sickening crunch as
boom is each one of them hits the bottom
and then and then sort of a sizzle and
you look down you can see that there's
actually a huge blue shimmering
forcefield and beyond that is just a
star field and you can see these smoking
little piles where their bodies must've
connected with the force field
yeah I'm still moral don't tell anyone
the campi know about that one k3 I would
like to I will say now the control room
and this Bay really isn't that dangerous
it'd be more if you wanted to if you
wanted to try different tacks no I was
gonna say rather than beat on the clamp
what I would love to do is use computers
to use a console and you have to
convince the the mechanism yeah that the
the clamps are under some kind of stress
that's what that's what they're
experiencing and that they need to
release wow I like that okay so you're
gonna move to the control room
yeah wait how do I - do I need to get to
the control room because how do I get
there there's no catwalk anymore
I know the the catwalk that connects the
Minot to this control room is good they
they were up above you they they were
not on your oh they were taking a
position above and we're firing down to
the control room that catwalk is
completely destroyed
you can't you still have access to the
control room okay shuffle over there
make me a computer check I'm still
walking we're getting there doesn't do
anything in a hurry it's three green and
one or yellow oh man this is murder
yeah
success you make best friends with this
hitter do this computer swipe right you
you are in deep in the green flame so
not only do you have access to the the
clamps but you also notice that there
was a message recently sent to Gris and
it would be very easy for you to just
pull it up right here and there's a
little hollow projector yeah let me let
me grab it so a shimmering blue figure
appears on the pedestal you can see that
looks like an imperial officer he's very
straight you know he's good posture
he says risk you've done well I would
like you to deliver the crew of the my
NOC to Planet 1-0 for as usual before
bringing me the ship also I need you to
bring me the Droid and then he winks out
do we have another droid on this ship
maybe none that I'm familiar with do you
inform us yeah you guys could hear the
audience yeah okay I say is there it's
something we don't know okay three there
are many things each of us does not is
there anything specifically about your
relationship to the empire that we
should know k3 none that I'm aware of is
it is that true yes yeah you have no
idea why he would want because you're
you're a repurposed but you're not a
rear you're a we were a repurposed like
war droid right
yeah I'm a like I'm a modified war droid
that that now cleaves closer to protocol
drew yeah yeah okay so I think that
that's true yeah
so there's another droid on this ship
how you got there yeah I like I am a
little bit insulted there has to be
another no want me I there's no way no
it's not personal
keeps me what I'm saying is that if this
person is asking Gris to bring them a
droid it may be that this droid is on
this massive ship
I thought the language was that they
want the crew the implication and the
message was that the crew of the my NOC
is to be delivered to this whatever this
planet is you've never heard of it
and the drawer bring the cool useful
droid be brought to you but we do not
know about that's right now by the way
why this is all happening stakes is
still hitting the clam you know what
we're gonna give Styx a win can you
please have it let go of the oh yeah it
falls away whoa I did it so you were
able to release both clamps before
control is seized from you it seems like
somebody else in the ship recognizes
that you've infiltrated and you are shut
out at this point okay so the my NOC is
now free of the clamps right but you are
still trapped inside the Bay of the
green flame so is it can we these ships
can pass through that shield they could
yeah right sure
individual people know candle much winds
dev kills them
yeah and they die yeah this is a
murderer in one of the worst ways
possible I understand that coming in
contact with one of these shields I mean
oh god at this point yeah you that's
right you would at this point you hear
the voice come over the speaker in the
hall in the room here and it's very
obviously Gris he says omen
I knew you had to make it difficult
how's the leg it's fine
it's never better I'm jumping on it it
feels good the fact of the matter Gris
is that I had an injury a war injury and
it was it was frankly therapeutic I'm
not done making it hard for you and I
say I you need to open this shield we
need to get this ship out of here so at
this point you're aware k3 that the only
way you're gonna get direct access to
open up that shield is from a new
another set of the computers which is
going to be up on the crew deck of the
green flame and you can see you can see
that there's a lift just behind this
control room so is that is the ship is
that is that is my not free the my neck
is free yeah it's not clamped in anymore
yeah yeah you still don't have access to
your weapons or anything that's a
separate thing yeah still got you locked
down okay so we need to head back I mean
I'm gonna lock the place up
[Laughter]
so basically we need to get up this lift
yeah and head upstairs okay then we need
to bring this bot with us yeah destroyed
it's not that cool it's not the cool
droid that he's talking about but but
still useful it's still useful okay I
think we have to yeah all right
the doors open and you can see that
there's a long hallway similar to the my
Knock you've got crew quarters there's a
there's a communal room you can see this
probably a cockpit at the end and from
these crew quarters that line the
hallway blaster bolts just start flying
and you guys duck out of the lift rolled
to the sides and let's do initiatives
okay so for initiative here you guys
were probably expecting a fight oh yeah
yeah so we're gonna roll vigilance yeah
so everybody make me a vigilance roll
right and it's for success is right for
successes yeah my villain is a
you what but yes okay tree has two
successes I have not that I have to
success so there aren't even there
aren't even numbers on these dice and
somehow I've still managed to fail to
find the zero okay so you had to I he
had to I had nothing
oh okay how many successes two to one
success one success all right who wants
to take the first initiative slot I
slide out between looking down the
hallway you can see that there's oculus
thugs sort of placement in these
doorways and at the end firing from the
cockpit is Gris himself
I aim for risk okay he's got he's got a
pistol out I want to shoot his pistol
okay alright so I'm gonna give you a
setback die no we can do this again just
like before
yeah difficult shot give me or your role
to yellow to green all right
[Music]
that's no good hey nice
90 is a success with one advantage so
damage I shoot you don't want to hurt
him I should his hand okay and he you
can hear the blaster sort of clatter
onto the ground
who wants to go next
so when I see him do that yeah I'm Chris
backs up into the cockpit at this point
just I gotta make this useful like this
is just not so I'm gonna use my my
scathing tirade okay to to yell at the
of his cronies and say if we're this if
we're this could have a shot obviously
we can take you all out real fast I mean
look at that it's hand you selling it we
selling you want to make a coercion yes
check this is their last stand
they're intent on holding their ship and
protecting their captain it's gonna be
difficult to change their mind can I
just if I use my scathing tirade I can
just keep going and just make them
really tired of me yeah yeah cuz it
straight it basically it's a global
attack but it causes strain is baby wow
you guys are just the worst man you
demoralizing whatever is watching him
what's your role what are you guys oh
this would be for coercion still right
yep okay it is oh yeah one yellow to
green one get rid of the black dice and
then one advantage
oh you automatically have an advance
yeah you do not succeed and you have one
threat they don't like it no I'm gonna
give you one strain for that oh because
you really exerted yourself yelling are
you sweating now go back to my trash
pile and I just don't like this anymore
can I just it takes a third slide
I'd love a lozenge right now yeah
so good really masculine I'm trying to
use that in the character yeah describe
the the hallway yes you've got a whole
way you've got probably at least five of
these oculus thugs firing down the
hallway without honey firing down the
hallway at you you don't seek risk
anymore he's backed up into the the
cockpit at the end mm-hmm you can see
the plastic seat on the ground what I'd
love to do is like find a fine a console
something that I could do to turn the
lights off in here yeah I mean I'll say
that you are in the sort of communal
area and there's absolutely gonna be a
console in there okay yeah talking you
know slice into that yeah let's see how
far I get with that yeah while you're
while you're yelling i total over what
are you trying to do I want to get into
like their their fire suppression or
shut the lights off okay so nothing too
hard this is these are big systems yeah
okay like more of a distraction right
right go ahead and make the computers
yeah that is three green one yellow wow
you succeed with one advantage so I'll
say that you absolutely find the fire
suppression system here and it down a
little bit yeah I mean is it the same
gel yeah so I would imagine that each of
these crew quarters has their own sort
of spigot that would just fill the room
with this foam it's working
every time puts out all kinds of fires
yeah so there there's they're
effectively sprayed okay
they're spayed and neutered yeah as
their rooms fill up with this foam each
of them they're exposed yeah they're
exposed they move out into the hallway
and you can see that there are five of
them easier shots yeah the fire
suppression system is not filling the
cockpit
and so but you do see a hand
the clawed hand reach out you can see
there's a reptilian hand you got him
uh-huh yeah that's it like I just wanna
I'm gonna get set to throw some punches
so they're not behind cover anymore so
they're not gonna you're not gonna have
setback dice or anything like that
shooting at them okay nice so I'm gonna
dish up the disarming smile don't worry
don't worry that was always going to
happen yeah
at length so I can I'm gonna use
congenial to take one strain to lower
the difficulty of it okay but it works
like this I take the disarm I take the
disarming smile action I succeded an
opposed charm check and it lowers all
the defenses of a target by my ranks and
disarming smile was it basically we're
gonna do opposed charm checks okay right
and then if I succeed then I lower all
of the probe all of my targets defenses
by one yeah I mean the oculus thugs have
no charm oh this is this is for Grist
okay so I'm taking a few shots that are
mostly theatrical yeah yeah in nature
and I say Gris I don't know buddy how's
the Empire gonna react when they hear
you lost the ship I haven't lost it yet
and so you make your charm check what's
yours
I do really good yeah to yellow to green
and then minus one black if there isn't
I subtract the difficulty which by one
okay I'm sorry I was figuring out what
risks was what's yours
exactly to yellow to green
three successes out to green Wow
risk is only gonna be two green and one
yellow so you came out of here with
three successes and three advantage the
same isn't it more successes and two
advantage no no risk yeah
he says just for once in your life omen
do that just do the right thing for your
crew for the miner put your guns down
and make this easy there's no reason you
have to die here don't do it what don't
we're gonna die here don't no no we're
gonna die whatever I don't do what he
says keep your guns up in fact just
start screaming all right I've got thugs
that are gonna start firing down this
hallway that's you guys
Zev you're obviously an easy time een
you're the target
you're the best shot clearly I get it
I'm the hero yeah
risk is gonna take a shot at you he's
got a blaster pistol back in his hand
and being had
yeah and he's mad Oh No
one advantage I'll give him a boost died
on his next role and then I've got some
guards they're gonna take a couple shots
at omen
this is all still well within my
parameters it's a plan that I've been
hatching for a long time I knew it would
end up in the story and you didn't yell
we are gonna die here yeah it's part of
the plan yelling it yeah there we go
oh no three advantage put some advantage
yeah I'm gonna say that at this point
the fire suppression system has stopped
and they are all able to retreat back
into their rooms two yellows when
they're in a group interesting so they
do hit they do hit but nothing else
crazy happens yeah
damage to omen is six
okay what's your soak three okay you're
getting low hey listen
never tell me the odds we're gonna go
back to the top of Sam's zev I want you
to kill them
I don't are generally speaking don't
force the issue and it's listen I
respect that you have a thing but they
have a thing also and their thing is
killing us that's true and they and they
are bad and there's a lot of weird stuff
going on in here okay don't touch same
well no I just I'm just saying you got
two of them I mean you should use them
both heard a very specific purpose
Zeb can't hear you over the beautiful
like dramatic music playing in his it's
but my mouth is going like and I'm
spinning along the wall and then I take
a shot again at Griff gun
okay setback one two three
I wish there was a way I could just
nudge his arm just like they're right -
yellow - green
J okay there's one more one more green
no that's a wash but it's went about
with one advantage everyone in the room
all of the thugs are very impressed
[Laughter]
that's dedication
respect we should shoot that guy he's
great
now right he's just trying to shoot our
hands I mean I'm not super concerned
about him it's weird but okay yeah
that's this thing you can always get
more hands oh absolutely
just look at Luke right that's on brand
for Star Wars yeah yeah sticks oh I just
watched this again so upset
yeah there I'm just gonna blast her the
heck out of them okay and I didn't aim
so I don't have I mean I'm any special
things but I'm just gonna blaster them
okay and that's a one yellow and two
green oh and it's not gross I'm gonna
start aiming for the UH the thugs thugs
yes yeah you come away with one
advantage but you do not hit anyone hmm
you want to heal some strain do you want
to give a boost die to somebody else
could one of my bullets ricochet and hit
his hand again risk at the end
now yeah so he drops the blaster again
and retreats back into his his cockpit
great perfect yeah
I meant to do that yeah k3 let's see we
need more in this computer and you
notice now that you actually have access
to what looks like brisk sort of
personal database where he keeps his his
probation his tinder profile want to
find what's his favorite hand hey good
looking out and balance thank you it's
like it's like in the dossier yeah why
would he record you you're gonna need to
slice in here you can see it but you're
gonna just slice into it if you want to
gain access to his okay let's do that
it's personal folder no absolutely
that's three green one yellow okay he's
got he's got his stuff locked down we
got Norton three green wow this is
amazing
jeez you have access to his entire
browser history yeah all of it all of it
there's some Transocean stuff in there I
stole it I keep it but yeah I'm bored
yeah you noticed that he has in here a
set of hyperdrive hyperspace coordinates
to the planet of Mon cow okay and he has
a description here of a Jedi holocron
that has been sealed away in a cave on
Mon cow and this cave is only accessible
once every hundred years when there is
an especially low tide and he has done
the work too real to figure out that
that moment is approaching very quickly
and he's got all of this information in
there very tidy all packaged together so
that it was very clear that whenever
this mission ended that was going to be
his next
his next job okay hmm
next time you're poking around in there
you should try to find out about planet
104 sure
and just hit Fandango see if there's
anything good plan yes you have you have
completely stolen all of his plans from
his personal databank there yeah can I
just got it yeah pour it out delete no I
perform at his drive Wow but there's
like you notice there's a folder that's
pictures and in there there's like some
pictures of some little Transocean I
don't care action out of an egg no I
delete the contents but the folder is
[Music]
this this is evil yeah if this game had
alignment wow wow you're hardcore yeah
okay yeah oh absolutely
he's completely wiped his entire
database they're all his games
everything are gone he had like a high
score oh gone oh man yo I am interested
in starting to take shots take a shot
shots shots shots yeah nobody has
actually hit I know that's why do you
one that's that's why I'm sorry nobody
has done any serious damage to any of
the other combatants in this fight yes
you mentally like yeah it's gonna be in
yeah good idea
just check-in oh no I'm gonna go for it
again I'm gonna go for it again what are
you going for we're gonna go for
congenial again so I'm gonna downgrade
difficulty on this charm check okay with
a little more strain I'm running kind of
hot here yeah you were running very hot
I'll get your strain
yeah and I'm gonna say I'm gonna do the
disarming smile again on risk okay I'm
just gonna try to continually wear him
down okay right yeah I know
so a posing charm check and I'm gonna
say yeah I'm gonna say I'm gonna say
risk some pretty interesting stuff in
these folders a lot of people have
access to this computer
[Applause]
yes communal everybody uses it come on
cow huh maybe when I get done here I'll
go grab that holocron for you what do
you say omen now I gotta kill you all
right here let's roll up some some die
Wow
for advantage but no successes well
let's see how he likes my brand yeah -
yellow - green Wow yeah yeah so now what
does that inflict on risk all of his
defenses r1r lose one so basically
everything is just easier to get at okay
all defenses of a target until the end
of the counter okay yeah he's definitely
rattled okay cool and then from here on
out I'm gonna just keep moving up like
all these rooms are basically here yeah
it's gonna keep going from room to room
getting closer to start blasting okay
he's mad he's super mad yeah he's gonna
take a shot at you at this point he
should try and so he did he's got a
super gun he does have a super gun
shoots lightsabers
bitch dude this is amazing
Wow he gets he's nothing like this that
war this fight started with words yeah
now he's just like shooting down the
hall he's flustered yeah I'm going to
give him I'm gonna give him strain for
that actually exquisite yeah so now now
I'm in there now I got him it's just a
matter of time you've wormed your way in
his guards you can take a couple shots
mhm
they can't I don't think they can see
you I think you're tucked back in the
corner
kidnapping away zev you're out in the
open and looking at very impressed by me
though and they are interested but they
want to be the guy to shoot you they
want to be the one that takes down this
amazing Marx I'm still spinning along
balls and twirling and rolling oh wow
two successes and two threat interesting
so the minions the thugs actually don't
take strain they take strain as though
it were damaged so I'm just gonna have
them take some of direct damage I'll
have them take two of that nice and then
they are gonna shoot you they're gonna
hit you so that is six okay mmm I'm
sorry it's AIT's edgy successes yeah so
it's more it's more than that actually
nowhere it's 100 so you're dead a couple
times you're not gonna like it
yeah that is a success brutal nine
damage well so I use my soaked yes so
subtract your soak first okay so it's my
soak is three okay yeah we got to bring
this to a close
six we can't take that in any more shots
like that that looks down at his at his
mouse courts yeah
very expensive shirt hero shirt yeah and
looks up like they're trying they're
trying to kill me
[Laughter]
this is really dangerous yes yes that's
that's been happening the whole time all
day it's been happening I'd take another
shot at their blasters now I don't know
anything else are you shooting it she a
Gris or their guards the guards who shot
me the garden the garden is shot
specifically you want to take a shot at
him at his blaster do you just think it
looks cool can you envision that their
head resembles we be gray should be over
this has been over you do not succeed
but you two have four advantage so you
can't hurt anyone but you're very good
at it
I want to give the advantage to
Styx's next you want to give a bonus
yeah boo Stein yes yes because you'll
actually do stuff historically that have
been true yeah
sticks what would you like to do I'm
going to just like lug my blaster up
okay I'm just I'm gonna go for this risk
armed yet yeah he does have a blaster
right now in his hand because he just
took a bunch of shots in the moment he's
but he's furious
yeah he's wigged out yeah so he looks
like he's distracted yeah absolutely
okay so I then I will go for the guards
then okay and then again that's oh yeah
one yellow and two green plus whatever
whoa jeez Wow okay so give me what's
your damage and add 3 to it I'm gonna
have two of them die yes yeah so this is
straight through two of them just fall
right out of that you can see just
tumble into them through them makes up
for all of my dilly dallying with my
yelling and my freaking and you come
away with two advantage oh do you want
to pass that on I do want to pass that
on okay I'm gonna pass that on to k3 k3
is next there's still three guards along
the left side of this hallway and risk
in the back okay I want to I want to
move away from the computer and just
basically become like walking cover okay
yeah that's awesome
you can start moving up but as my son
liked the movie voice over guy can you
just say like in the world yeah no no oh
you tried to go deep down and it's not
there I'll do it normal in a world
that's pretty good no so I want to walk
up I want to deck one of them
okay well I'm at it right the first guy
in the first doorway yes walk up to just
with those nuts what's your role green
and one yellow oh no oh you do succeed
oh hey whoa what's your damage and add 2
to it
I think it was 4 yeah so 6 yes ok yeah
this guy this guy reels back he stumbles
back into the room just holding onto his
face and what do you want to do with
your advantage um ken huh
well I guess I'll just pass the savings
pass the savings on peut forward yeah
yeah all right exactly so he's shuffling
down the middle of this thing yeah and I
am just like I'm right behind him the
whole way with my hand on his back I
have the pistol there so he punches this
guy yeah and then I shoot him
immediately immediately as he as he
stumbles back he just BAM and it's just
right in the chest yes
it's like a old tactic yeah it's classic
give you your boost oh wow
I honestly I did not know it had that
although the first could do that yeah so
I think this might be a bug cap we're
looking for three greens oh this poor
guy Wow
all right so what's your damage and add
three yep so it's eight total okay yeah
yeah that guy yeah yep
and then you've got to advantage exactly
and then I'm gonna sort of like guide
him in front of me like this we're gonna
continue going down like it's become
sort of a dance maneuver there's like
there's like a Lamaze aspect to it you
know where I'm just like sort of like I
got in the belly but it's going this way
okay and then I'm gonna start sweeping
the pistol down through the hallway and
I say just like that it's just things
like that are gonna keep app
- you guys all right Chris is going to
pop out now and he's going to take a
shot you're gonna have he's gonna be a
disadvantage though because you're
taking cover behind k3 yeah oh I like
this oh good luck risk yeah really
Wow all right so he does not hit but he
generates one advantage one advantage
dude this is incredible he is going to
heal that strain he centers himself yeah
Olman deep breaths you always gotten you
have a way of getting me flustered you
know how to push my button you know how
to push my button said I'm not gonna let
you do it this time alright so he
researches himself he finds that calm
center of the storm that calm you know
meditative lizard yeah and I'm gonna
give him a boost on his next he's just
thinking about the present you know like
what can I feel how very force yeah
exactly and now there's still two guards
left they can take shots at you omen
setback the best mmm actually I'm sorry
I'm sorry I did that wrong because now
that they're dying they're not doing as
well that's great news is their minions
so step back difficulty
Wow they generate one threat they could
take it as damage yeah there they are
spooked at this oh yeah I mean I'm
behind this because they don't know they
probably seen this model before yeah I
was just coming down the hall like this
it has these mysterious other arms yeah
at this point at this point they backed
into their rooms there they're taking
cover Zev Zev so you imagine the scene
yeah let me paint you in the back six
has this huge ridiculously big gun this
massive blaster the two of you are
walking down this corridor and as the
music swells in the background I'm
rolling and flipping and you come around
the side yeah oh you think you're
shielding me I've just been like
twirling in front of you the entire time
I want to take another shot at Grist
blaster at the blaster itself at the
blaster itself okay to yellow to green
interesting Wow
okay so you have a success yeah you hit
the blaster out of his hand
great stop it just stop it
what a omen it's this guy in your crew I
met him a long time ago it's not time to
discuss him right now listen just let me
take the ship why do you need it it's a
job you know how it is if you don't
fulfill a job you're in trouble if I
don't fulfill this job I'm in big
trouble risk you're in trouble now oh
man I'm in a tight spot does this have
to end with me pushing you out of your
own airlock is there another way not yet
as near as I can see as near as i can
see Chris you're gonna need a head start
to get away from the Empire let me get
my ship you go where you're gonna go
I'll go get the holocron you don't want
to be it you don't want to be in this
system yeah you don't want to be in this
system pal oh man I'm gonna give you one
more chance just go back to your ship
and wait I will drop you off at it at
the spin which is a Space Station you
guys are recognized that name it's on
the outer rim black market traders it's
not a horrible place you know but he's
like listen I swear I will drop you off
at the spin all I need is the ship and
the Droid my droid
what's roid you you can anyone own a
draw I mean draw it's a Droid do you
want k3 yes
[Laughter]
[Applause]
but brisk you're confused
this isn't he's not a battle droid
listen I don't ask why I just deliver
the goods
Ohman we're in the same business how
about a little professional courtesy
use your manoeuvre I mean you're great
yeah this is great so you come into the
next room you can see that there's an
oculus hiding behind his bunk he's got
his blaster over it so I'll give you
setback because he's taking cover but
you have a boost Wow Wow you have the
ultimate boost nice the boost spoken of
in legend the booth spoken of in
Revelations this is a book of boost to
green Wow okay yes
pretty solid nothing there but you don't
need it you succeed but you generate one
threat so I'm gonna give you strain one
string and then he is and what's your
damage plus three Wow just aquasheep
pattern of spray like blood on the back
of this wall Thanks and he's obliterated
all that's left are two tusks oh yeah on
a pillow resting on his bunk to test in
the morning I mean I don't that's what
they say do they say that I don't think
so they do yeah yeah I don't know where
they are but you took your string I did
yeah k3 where's this other guy so he's
in the next room down so
sticks walked in front of you this first
room it's like it's like breach and
clear there's another door further back
that's got another thug in it and then
you've got Gris still back in the phone
I'm gonna defer to you I'll say should
we finish that one off first or yes okay
we're looking for a total clear so what
I want to do is want to march in there
and because it's the same role as my
brawl I want to rip his blaster out of
his hand and then just come down all
right I love this can you imagine the
terror it's like because honestly the
fact that you're nice just makes it
worse yeah that that blank
Threepio face is yeah it's either
brawler athletics oh I think it would be
melee though because you're using a
weapon extreme but it's but it's it's
too good not to do worse why don't we do
why don't we do athletics to see if you
can wrestle this thing away from okay
okay I'm happy with that
um yeah so that one's gonna be two green
one hello you grab it and I'll let you
use the advantage to take another action
to sort of just beat him with this gun
all right then then that's me like yeah
melee okay that one is three green these
are bad times it's gonna be great oh
trying to showboat didn't work out no no
you failed so this thing comes down and
he dodges out of the way and you connect
his bunk and you generate three
advantage though do you want to heal
strain yeah let me do that yeah okay
pull that string off of there it's
starting to pile up I just piling up so
what is it 103 okay well I only have two
at the well okay so does that give me
one advantage to confer oh okay let me
do that
who's next next up is omen okay let me
give it to you and drawn give a boost
died all right I'm gonna hit him with
the I'm gonna hit the team with the
inspiring writer okay
this is the time this is the time see
what I say you know what look pretty
crazy back there we were in a real bad
spot now we have two ships think about
that you know what it's funny how it
happens
yeah funny how it happens we step one
ship and we got twice as many ships yeah
why is that great leadership ship that's
the greatest ship yeah no leadership
that's great ship of all Chris Stroud
everybody oh that was premium that was
premium okay yep so I'm gonna hit him
with the I'm gonna do congenial I'm
gonna lower the difficulty okay so we're
looking at a easy leadership check there
we go yeah easy leadership check so it's
1 yellow 3 green and a boost hey that's
the boost I know about welcome back
booth
yeah you succeed each success one Ally
when Ally recovers one strain so
straight so one strain is recovered does
anybody else need an extra strain
removed I might I'm gonna pass it over
do I fix and then this is the best part
is that each Ally affected by inspiring
rhetoric gets boost dies on their
attacks on their chicks any check on
their checks okay so the guard that's in
the room with uk3 he doesn't have his
gun anymore but he still got his
knuckles and so he's gonna try to drive
its just right into that and throw face
yeah the best part is there's no there's
no articulation at the end so it's just
like grab the my mitt he has success he
does have success all right so you're
gonna take four five six damage okay but
your silk is five right yeah yeah okay
all right what part of my metal body
does he want to hit right into your face
and you are disoriented for three rounds
what does that mean when triggered
target is disoriented a number of rounds
equal to the rating well yeah that makes
sense go to risk I'll figure that out
for you right it's bad though you won't
like it you won't like it you're gonna
hate it doesn't sound great yeah risk is
gonna take a shot at omen so setback
because you're taking cover yep behind
k3
ah all right Chris let's teach a guy big
bag of nothing no no geez you're not the
best know he misses but he's got an
advantage oh wait here to boost I on
this one yeah so he's going to spend
that advantage to take another boost on
his next role sev them sorry rolls up
right in front of risk yeah and stands
face to face with him okay push it put
your blaster on his hand puts his
blaster on this hand is your favorite
hand yeah it's hard it's hard here Chris
surrender is hard so let me give you a
hand like point blank blank
I don't even get excited but there's no
difficulty you're literally holding your
gun against his hands yes morons blaster
though I don't want to blow his hand off
dude I mean don't trend oceans grow them
back yo I shoot his hand off oh yeah all
right you're - yellow - yellow - oh yeah
oh no wow oh no you have a triumph would
you like to use it for a critical injury
role so there's a list here awful things
of awful things
he knew the risks
yeah so I I shoot his hand okay and
because the blasters of his hand still
it fires and it shoots a control panel
that unlocks the slave system of our
ship setting it free setting the my
knock free everything you say you did it
by the book
yeah so he ricochets down hits a control
panel and you see crisco's Oh No
now the my knock is completely free
and not tethered to the green flame in
any way you have access to all your ship
systems including the weapons I believe
this happens okay to me risk okay that's
amazing it's unbelievable to me how that
one shot is completely foiled all of my
plans all this is happening I'm just
aiming at him and I did it myself in the
end I was my own enemy
ready I think this revelation just like
take your name whoa
stare six you're up next yeah standing
in the doorway rubbing his hand and just
shaking shaking his head he's going down
how could this all have gone so wrong
yeah I'm gonna shoot him
now he's the worst now I'm gonna give
you a setback die because Zev is right
in front of him I mean they're crazy so
you assume you're trying not to shoot
him grazes him maybe I'll lose half my
body he'll be fine
okay what's what's your role oh this is
starting to get weird
this is getting weirder and weirder one
boost you take a shot and he's rubbing
his hands he looks up and just dodges to
the side as the blast goes right through
right past his head and we both look at
you like what yeah exactly serious my
hand slipped and I'm gonna use the
threat that you generated to kill Zev no
to let it's like risk-taking maneuver
and he is going to try and kick you out
of his cockpit okay here comes
oh whoa whoa to success
yeah so he just puts a huge Transocean
boot in your chest and knocks you out of
the cockpit and then he reaches his
other hand
yeah with this other hand this one is
just sort of cradling let's see that was
six K three I'm gonna go over there like
to stand in front of him
I like I just want to like lay down on
Grist yeah we gonna do just athletics or
brawl right yeah you want to try to to
tackle him yeah I'm gonna if it's
broblem just gonna try him in the face
okay yeah yes you've been kicked away so
there's no setback he's not engaged with
that anymore right
no doesn't work out oh you love a trend
Ocean City free wait oh I forgot what
about this other guy who does not have a
weapon oh you're so you're sitting there
with him you have a gun in your hand
yeah yeah but I'm not great at it as a
cudgel I'm just gonna give it to you
thank you for your use I say thank you
uh I'm gonna punch him in the face
huhuhuh loser me and he gives you the
gonna say thank you and then you turn
back to the Chi no I know I say it's an
inelegant weapon Wow put my that's much
more elegant yeah what's your what's
your bra it's uh two green one yellow oh
it's happening yeah I don't forget don't
forget that tender boost we all know how
the boosters gonna turn out right it's
gonna be blank
so they show it is a success so damage
this guy's bone okay whatever you deal
to him he is dead all right yeah six
punch right through those tusks they go
flying out in each direction stick you
see the tusks tumbled out into the
hallway and then you have three
advantage what can I do to so much risk
with that yeah
yeah yeah I'm do time yeah you know
everything you can get into this
dialogue game it's a lot of fun teasing
risk okay um I dunno all of it I just
start playing audio room is from yeah
like I have your personal files yes and
then that audio distorts coming out of
my voice box
I must have ever virus yeah I say hang
it up Chris hang it up if you ever do
anything if I ever hear that you are
considering talking to someone about
maybe doing something all of this goes
out on the HoloNet it's still the sound
I told you it's a communal computer
everybody on the crew had access to it
Chris we're leaving now
and we're never going to see you again
he pushes a button and a blast shield
comes down between you guys and seals
off the cockpit yeah we need to get to
the ship right away yeah okay turn
around yes okay so you head back drop
down into the mine och the force field
is gone the clamps are off you have full
access to your ship's computers and
weapon systems right Google Home has
been installed yes
do you want to make me a piloting check
I assume that you're taking the seat
yeah I know exactly how okay I'm gonna
give you a this is we're in space well
you're still in the hole you need to
drop out yeah yeah yeah exactly but
we're not what it is it isn't on the
planet's surface no yeah but you were
out in space absolutely yeah I'm gonna
throw in a yellow green green geez Wow
it's no problem it makes that sound a
lot it makes this sound all the time fix
it so you failed but you have you have a
lot of advantage yeah how would you like
to spend it
what's all it's all messed up yeah and
that's what I'm doing I'm just like
turning in my chair all the different
consoles and it's like this worked fine
that worked fine yeah look out
underneath the cockpit up up at the
upper where I know Gris cos yeah now
sokka risk is busily working away at his
computer system and you can see the blue
force field return now underneath am I
not jump into the gunnery position and
unload on the entire dock okay so
scaffolding is falling these catwalks
are tumbling down use it all I authorize
the use of the concussion missiles I use
the concussion missiles you won't shoot
someone but your ships are not people
there could be a stowaway I have a
bumper sticker on the my knot that says
that yeah yeah so the whole inside of
the green flame is just from
and you can see the forcefield flickers
a couple times and then vanishes exactly
and I don't even I don't even like try
to control the ship I just I just let it
fall out oh okay all right so you drop
down now you have coordinates to mon cow
but you've also heard of this planet
1:04 so at this point
Griss locks on his weaponry to the my
Knock and you can feel the it's starting
to rock is he's taking shots at you what
do you want to input into this computer
gosh we want to go do we want to go to
Montel and get the holocron if somebody
wanted to make a check to try to you
under like to learn about this 104 do
they know anything about this planet it
would be an outer rim knowledge check
okay I'm pretty good on that
that's for green G's bookworm scholar
this is a secret hidden planet so it's a
hard check that I've heard of I'm sorry
you said it was three green three green
isn't it I'm sorry four green for green
you need successes boy that turned
around at the end didn't oh yeah it was
not good times you recognized that this
is absolutely a hidden planet most
people don't know about it
even in the outer rim it's not really
spoken of but you have heard rumors of
it being sort of like a work colony
people are taken there they do hard
labor in these mines and it's all for
the purpose of the Empire okay and you
because of your advantage I'm gonna say
that you were able to pull up the
coordinates for this planet so now
you've got coordinates for launch ow and
coordinates for planet one zero for you
guys want to go to that prison should we
go there so this is where they were
trying to take us right have I noticed
have I lost contact with any other
smugglers recently why don't you make me
an underworld
check you bet you're looking at yellow
green yeah
do you know what the the what's it
called this one here the threat you know
the threat is what the sadness yeah
you're gonna take strain because
thinking now about it you recognize that
you've lost contact with at least a half
a dozen and it happens right I mean
wrong jobs yeah but it's odd now right
you're realizing this at the moment
you're like well I haven't heard from
these from these other smugglers it is
odd smugglers are disappearing okay so
you have sent me the tend me the
coordinates
yeah you got both of them where we want
to go I need you to make me a piloting
check because Grist is taking
laughing yeah yeah you're looking at the
yellow green green listen if I can add
my two cents
Wow there you go so threat I'm gonna
give you strain you are sweating at
these controls yeah yeah my Knock dies
know it all so he's like counted tell me
about this coordinate hahaha actually
it's a planet where the Empire ticking
Roger says I'm just reading the numbers
off to you Jim three do it exactly so
we're dropping out
I've fold the back wings down okay and
try to yeah you amazing shots easily but
you have generated strange yeah do you
want to put it's 13 do you want to put
in some coordinates here look we mod
count and get that whole cron yeah but
that's a lot of water like what if we
were the heroes
and went to this empire planet here's
the problem and save those smugglers
well as I see it it's a it's a prison
world so there would be no guns for you
to shoot there
[Laughter]
[Applause]
instead we they must want me because I
was built by a Jedi I wear his tattered
cloak
that's just so he thinks a rag it's it's
his wrath it's their rag I forgotten we
have to go there and not to the other
one okay so this whole conversation is
taking place in the cockpit we're
arguing take another job yeah yeah
you're too green to yellow yep
yeah yeah you just exactly I say all
right command decision I put in the Mon
Cala coordinates Oh
all right one last message you can see
as you're typing the coordinates your
indicator is beeping that you've got a
message coming in from the green flame I
hit it
say what oh man it's Chris yeah I know
hey listen we're all just trying to make
a living out here in the rim right no
hard feelings
I say case three hours give me something
good you know what I walked by one of my
guys using a terminal Eifert I saw him
he was looking I said go not on my ship
my guy doesn't work here anymore and you
can hear clearly grist boys going that's
it oh yeah I like it yeah loosen omen
I'm sorry
just don't go to Mon Cal okay for you
just one time okay it's the last favor
I'm ever gonna do yet Mon count
push the lever one toward the Stars turn
two lines and you are on your way to
Montel and that is the end of our first
adventure and Star Wars what what about
what a little bit of look yeah there's a
guy still all our ships here's the day
new mom whip here's the day new mom flip
I'm gonna go I'm gonna go down no
hyperspace I'm gonna go down and I'm
gonna open it up flips game
and I'll say I'll say drones game but
I've got an opening I'm gonna reach down
into the hold you work with that you
know pulling back out yeah thank you
guys very much for those are words thank
you guys very much
thank you all very much
[Applause]
cell phone
yeah
he's still going oh my gosh thank you
thank you
he'll make it here eventually