time is the enemy of the past and
threatens the fastest weapon you
wouldn't make it past a second and
that's the question
play it brash and reckless to choose a
card solution you saw it was prudent in
a Sepulchre poker to don't become the
pew tree it's that well-fed I pursue in
no mountain too steep for dungeon too
deep to send expanded their marks up to
the top of the peak of beneath they see
Yugi they come like sharks to it while I
swim in that money burn like Carl Barks
through it so since you're national
parks drew it I'll send him home in a
natural box with the close tie the most
of the parks included save your breath
for a cleric confessor death is a lesson
and life is at any professor but if
you're seeking my official advice sign
on the dotted line and wish of the
choice it's like a vapor part please
don't blow I am Tycho Brahe hey of panic
in packs
I am also Owen drawn CEO of acquisitions
incorporated but today I'm sherry
Hogan's I'm here to play a game of
Dungeons &amp; Dragons with my friends to my
right
Dragonborn narcissist Dennard wit's end
hey whoa so correct title and then also
correct name we're on well this is a
good start I feel good about this bingo
so good about this one the person by
Ryan also here awesome man
right well no I heard I heard they are
my favorite and literally said I was
your favorite masked no you've said this
side of the table was crap anyway hi
I play walnut donger here's my opening
night a seed what grows something later
world walnut done grass when I did this
part we're chef to my left not your
grandma's grandma expected those made
rare cases so where she is your
grandma's grandma no Rosie please singer
and
breaker of staves that's right
staff breaker to the left of my left
returning to the table yet again special
guests dream us beasting exactly right
Rivas our drivi mote dream Oh seems like
a good brand we got this dream boat now
who else anybody else anybody else do
does anybody that was mine no it's
everybody I have four players and so are
you Mike there you go emerging as though
from a mister out meatball fine cuz
wrist Rob all right now make a random
when last we saw our heroes they had not
entered and then very quickly made their
way to the docks of Neverwinter
Neverwinter available on Xbox
Playstation 4th and the P thief there's
a this isn't that you won't see any of
this stuff in there but what we came
what we came to know through various
thresholds of cleverness on the part of
the C team were that the tower that they
seek indeed the trapped individual is
off the coast of Neverwinter and in an
effort to secure passage from the docks
out
they came apostasy they came across a
strange boat strange insofar as it bore
the livery of acquisitions incorporated
clearly a lot of damage to the hull
hastily repaired
and Rosie let leaping Li onto the onto
the deck and was very very quickly
introduced to a flintlock sidearm yeah a
man up in the rigging looking down and I
believe the last line of dialogue was
who the are you at least at least
that's what I wrote down or what the
do you want something in this
there's an F word in there I want to
apologize well I know that my mom does
watch the show and she has said she
suggested that I work faint a little
blue yeah and I mean that she has
suggested that I should do that I mean
that she has identified correctly that I
leverage that type of powerful
terminology you do listen the words have
had power for a while and I'm just
picking it up that is the situation in
which we find ourselves
it's true okay I've thought about this a
little bit I may be for a minute I'm
just just a minute me because we've only
been gone a moment the history that
rosie has led her to this place in her
life I believe that she's probably had
more than one gun pointed at her face oh
yeah probably even on the deck of a ship
yeah so this is not anything that's
gonna rattle her she's had a long life
if this joker wants to smoke her then
absolutely bring it on
so she literally just like looks them
straight up into the rigging and says
why don't she drops the gun okay I go I
pick up the story
where's your God now yeah I pick up the
gun but I don't pointed at him it's like
what are you why did you come down from
there let's have a discussion you know
what that is a great plan and welcome
aboard the Merry Widow something's got
off on the wrong foot and I think on
both sides there was a lot of aggression
and it doesn't have it he's saying this
like looking down to you as he's
climbing down that the the rigging had
shabby
you know tunic open but like a vacation
open all right not just not just like
you know or to read a mile at a time
right sister situation oh yeah
yeah yeah so dad on vacation know
exactly you think he in fact there is
there is sufficient chest hair there is
sufficient chest hair yeah I mean do you
think that if he were to shave it there
would just be like a human head just
rolling around back and forth with the
waves of the dock you think that he is
90 to 95% hair Wow okay is he beardy oh
I'm telling you it's hair a goggle
nothing it is it is you you're not sure
how much is underneath it finally
someone I can possibly we're talking
about a Lycan like in type situation
everywhere that's why I'm using my veto
right now
it's Patrick promises writer he gets you
know top level story he gets the
mountain but he's looking over yeah he's
looking over you can see that the rest
of the party is sort of gathered on the
dock holding the gun like a dead animal
yeah I clearly have no intention to
shoot him with it yeah but I also have a
firm grip he's not getting it back in
fact it's probably gonna be a gift for
one of my friends yeah it's not loaded
no you know I got to it let's just let's
just figure things out right now okay
can I pop it open and see if it's loaded
nice one higher percentage all right
sorry pop it over I'm like oh okay and
then I pop it back close and I keep
holding it like this let's continue the
conversation let's go get my deal I
don't remember yeah I found out it's
Cooper Webb what is going on with this
terrible ship situation
this trip has seen better days well I'm
afraid that's a lot of the issues that
I'm not at liberty to discuss a lot of
the issues you can tell that he's sort
of adopting like a more technical like
mincing certain mansplaining boats to me
no no not boats what are you saying is
like this attack was it is related oh
man Sweeney
he's use the veto on that he is he's
like it's its acquisitions incorporate
oh
perhaps you'd like to speak to our
documents are over there on the shore
she is trying to show off like her
documents are still it has a eye on it
and instead she's just holding up a
hastily scrawled roll that has like a
terrible logo you can see it from a
distance
we're here were the red large Jessamine
Valley branch the CT what is the C stand
for crew courageous we don't know I can
tell you what the B stands for what well
we know that yeah we know the B team you
say anticlimactic oh that's just what
you think the B stands for yeah that's
my that's my guess that's what I mean I
could put in I could have my documents
or put in the official oh sure where are
you
what team are you we're the C team and
those those chuckleheads team Team B he
points out to the town says Neverwinter
right team nine team Nyad okay mascot
yeah I know I know immediately show us
no you guys have that link you're not
like the end team you're just team Nyad
you got a hole name where the Wildcats
okay is it a Wolverine team cougar
it's my there's do you hear a woman's
voice from the crow's nest she's looking
down over at the dock like not directly
down onto the deck she's calling out she
calls out individually she says dragon
man I heard of you yeah I'm Finn
I would probably if I had to kill you
I would probably pierce your acid sack
and boil your organs that's that would
be the ante I play it from ear
I think she likes you never that no
thank you
[Laughter]
she says you seem like somebody who's
into bands I'd probably just I'd
probably learn to play the lute that's
probably all I'd have to really do down
hands out on the edge guess it takes a
good look and says poison dust on an
altar that's I think that's about it
yeah I would do it you want it two
months observation of fen she says okay
and then you can if you want but she's
sort of like leaves the edge just you
see if there's no centerpiece there's
some sort of game she tells us House you
got to say how you'd kill the other
person do you want to I wanted to get a
read on her yeah she she comes back in
them look looks like bends over like
straight down and looks at you for
probably a solid eight seconds and says
I hope I never have to you couldn't if
you tried I agree you got a string bean
neck she says she says that's rude she
just disappears what is some other part
Finn is a her she has gray hair she's
tall has gray hair very gray hair very
very slight build and features and
even up there even in the crow's nest
you can tell that the behavior of her
hair from the physical perspective is
not one-to-one okay like you think that
you think that she might be a Djinn a
sea of sometimes yes Brian doesn't know
what it I don't know their names
yeah I just II step up there and I fly
you out over the water and and just drop
you and then you get work it's very hard
I'm I'm taken with someone right now
it's not gonna happen
I would not don't write any poems taking
vena dead yeah gross captain says I'm
our decision Asst nice to meet you go
Corbin champ
Corbin Rosie beat singer Michelle do you
have an obviate er no what's that
that's a fen for lack of a better term
I'm gonna get one
yeah then he said is it enough they're
excited I would say that that's the
Corbin that's the main thing
okay is that they get excited excited
okay somebody has to know we have a I'm
our cartographer don't have a cool bike
cute name or my car turn the fists or
kurtosis cartographer fix right are
y'all nice our decision astiz the dragon
man didn't I put Sun yeah we call them
the Baconator that's our documentary
you're probably gonna have a lot of
forms to fill out for threatening me
with this weapon
sorry little too so as you as you as you
can make this introduction he says I
have one I mean I can have her do it
okay and then you the boat is continuing
to sort of list on its side and from the
damage in the substructure of the boat
you can see if they
inside looking up at you and you can so
you can see the glint of a documents or
seal she's like thank God thank God
are they keeping you down there no I'm
here on purpose someone has to do it and
no one else will do it does that sound
familiar
yeah and she says where did you get that
bag I'm good at my job I want to see
this bag you got here no because if I if
I'm not here then it's gonna be even
worse for the boat even worse it's bad
you threw the boat she goes I need you
to make yourself a bridge jump that I
can toss you I will not be tossed I will
not be abridged the ground that's so
simple why not do this before oh I'm
sorry I forgot this is a very important
moment for us because we are observing
his flight yeah the first time yeah
friends I have the solution we don't
have to do that if we can go wherever
you want to go the power of flight I
cast a fly and from above somewhere a
great distance you see what looks like a
a black hair descending it is a very
slender tentacle and it makes it all the
way down from the firmament coils around
me and I go limp but have some commanded
features and it begins to drag me short
carelessly in the air and I'm like haha
horrible landing yeah yeah it's and it
gets us pretty close to what and where I
wanted to go on the deck and then you
just you just like flop out on the deck
and roll
I want to geek out with another document
it's happening but as you're trying to
find the way below deck you hear Corbin
shale turn to Rosie and say what has
been your experience these are the the
b-team like how many how many stars out
of five I don't know that any of us have
a super strong opinion about the b-team
5 they're awesome wave of nausea
UMBC's very rashes over him it's very
effective hmm they weren't effective on
this what happens so they have I'd never
heard of it but they have something
called a wild card license oh yeah yeah
don't know what that means I get it I
know what it means it means they can
steal your boat oh well that's
nice with it but well yeah let's just
don't get a boat all I'm saying of any
rate don't get a boat in this you want
them to steal it for happiest two days
and boat owners like
nice deal so we went up and down this
coast trying to find their cartographer
who I guess has been missing for a week
now oh no Cup there's a couple things
yeah
so their cartographer is gone they don't
know where she is
this is a huge problem just at the
outset right and they had to I guess
they had they back filled the position
temporarily sure it's flee bringer
something like that we bring her
beasting or something along these lines
be thicker yeah same name as the kid
same name is the kid we got in the
staggers and Jags there's a kid in the
stairs Joe yeah so he a child well in
the salut he tried to steal my dinghy
because he imagined and you'd be
surprised how many times I hear this he
thought that he would could use it to
impress a girl or something uh-huh can
you describe this be stinger I would say
he's too big too green and I think that
he needs to focus I think he needs to I
think he needs to just sort of get on
the just get on the river and just go
going one direction you have no idea how
right you are
I've been telling him that for a very
long time just picking one thing just
pick one thing and get great at it you
know really really just have that drive
in that motivation we can talk about
this all day yeah absolutely so so this
other do you have any kids who are
wizards uh do I have any kids that are
Wizards it's hard to keep track
it's possible though can you give me
more of a descriptor pendragon basting
er is that dragon beast err Rosie
definitely doesn't remember a Pendragon
B singer but she definitely acts like
she does
dragon dragon the wizard yeah yeah it
was it was I have to be honest with you
it was not a good scene he seemed to be
doing everything that he could to
impress these other two assholes and it
wasn't it wasn't making a good
impression on anyone else hmm okay and
he is back filling their cartographers
yeah currently okay all right well I
didn't know that about ten dragon who
has not written me in some time but then
just a heat and warmth even in this
crisp sea breeze right just emanating
from this chest hair hmm it's real it's
if it's profound it's distracting but
you put your chest hair away please this
yeah this here yeah can you just put
that away
that's a first your loss lady he's
trying but this entity can't be
contained yeah
this entity is like it spoofing it way
out just never been a shirt no like it
contained no no but yeah yeah so which
scene do we want to do next we only do
the scene where you go to the staggers
and Jags we want to do a scene where you
go downstairs all right yeah well I'll
be right back okay so I yeah yeah he
snaps and points over toward that sign
Oh
leaping Li off of the ship and then back
toward and I'm I'm moving with a speed
and purpose so far and I did a lot
easier short stature yeah yeah yeah you
guys have seen this like this set of my
body and my shoulders in West perhaps
yeah you've seen it before so I don't
even you're still on the shore you're
still no your moustache around the deck
yeah I like the idea that like when you
really trying to jump off the ship I'm
like yeah just like triple
next to me I might you should track with
arms and just marched right past dinar I
like I don't need to there's plenty of
room but I brush you insolently anyway
has to go pass every way it's like just
walk-in toward this in throw up in the
door right right this is done the
board's of the docks just yielding yeah
there's this dangerous mother yeah I way
like hold on I have this written down I
think I weigh like 29 pounds ribbon wet
somehow I'm making the board's shake
yeah exactly
with your maternal race just raising out
yeah I don't have my weight but it's
like 20 it's not a lot but I want to say
that like there's a part of my character
I can use vomit RG yeah and I there's
like there's like a hint of it I'm not
doing it on purpose no so mad that every
step I take it sounds like 10 dinars for
the doc mamataji holy on the CT so so
yeah you you push your way through you
look over at the status and Jags and you
can see that the they have an adjunct
sign as I suggested before just like the
sign outside of the drawn and quarter
right right so this is this this is an
operation that is affiliated in some way
as you push your way in this is a dark
room imagine like imagine dislike a
interstellar Cantina level of malevolent
lighting mm-hmm and dark can't imagine
if you will a dark candle literal yes
there's a lack of light and you can see
there is a bar far in the back you can
see that fish fresh fish are being
gutted and
fry out on these these huge stone slabs
situated more or less in the middle of
the place is a circular of a round stone
circle that actually has exposure down
into the water of the dock itself oh and
you can see that there are patrons here
and indeed your sundry Busby stinger
fishing directly in the directly inside
this bar and then just taking their fish
in the back to be cooked earth cool I
wanted to go there someday you can see
but it's like what filthy towel filthy
towel like rough knife down here
trailing some guts so I mean even even
it by Grievous even Budd Rivas beasting
your standards he is less focused than
usual and covered in filthy towels
dreama's pretty stinger there's a lot of
hunch even normally in his baseline
baseline hunch and there's like and then
there's like there's more combined with
sort of a furtive like he kind of tries
to hide a little but there's nothing
around here he's like I was wait all
that get a get the hiding out of your
system it's fine hi mom hi what are you
doing it's lovely to see you
I heard just now that you tried to steal
a man's dinghy is that true
mom I'm not old there was a boat
yeah I feel like I've taught you better
than that if you're gonna steal it folks
I love big rods no small dinghy is my
thing kidding me right now I was not I
was not I would never I I would never
now I would never steal a boat and after
this moment it was I was just good I
need to use it for a little bit aha girl
was it mom you don't understand what I'm
doing here yeah I don't I
I'm on a quest mom really tell me about
your quest I can tell you're already not
taking it seriously like you really got
stuck there he's like you couldn't tell
if he was like really grossed out or
just so random or maybe kind of
impressed it's a holy quest mom
literally fiddling with his rod I've got
a wart here okay all right all jokes
aside what the hell are you doing here
what's your course
there's there's
there is a girl I found like a magic
locket and it's got a picture of her and
she's trapped and now you know know that
I'm a paladin I have to she's trapped
okay
and so I have to you're a what I'm a
paladin mom I and that means if there
are people who need help
I have to help them do really have to
help them okay
it's my whole thing mom yeah Wow some
your pelvic now yeah that's exciting for
forever yeah yeah from yeah you have you
always been I just know I know I like
the things that I've always had it
inside me but then I really realized
them right that is just wonderful what
God do you serve but like but yeah so I
needed the boat to save the girl and
they didn't have a boat sure so I
wouldn't take it because I'm a paladin
now I'm gonna take like not for good I
was just gonna use it for my holy cause
and and then but they caught me and so
now I've got a fish for my holy cause
now or I'll go to jail for just a while
I think like two weeks and then oh yeah
I've got a really big frigid fee
structure here
the C stands for okay listen listen who
said man's waiting so suddenly he's sort
of perks up he's like like mom mom could
you could you lend me just for a little
bit right enough I just because you when
you steal a boat apparently in this city
they you get there's there's fees and
there's there's a fine and then yeah I
broke somebody's cart a little but that
was not my fault because it was they
were coming after me I and but I need
just I'm earning this off but if you
could help me with a little loan
yeah and I would get you back in and
then I could go help this girl sure are
you woman this is this woman are you
confined to this in right now it's just
like a prison fishing situation I'm
under my own reconnaissance right now
that's for sure okay this is not the
first time I've had to bail three pass
out so this is not this is not anything
that I'm not used to I'm just like how
much what's the damage who got hurt
how much am I in for right now they like
having the labor so they have not
established a timeline or a payout price
why'd you have to be so good at fishing
you're invaluable to them now I'm sorry
I can't help you I kind of assumed they
would just tell me when I had fished
enough and then they would let me go
I've been here for four years like and
there's a stand there is there is no
like there is no shortage of fish yeah
like while he has been having this
dialogue with you even as the emotional
texture of it
as you know has it has like the
sine-wave of it has crested and fallen
he's probably caught four fish
Wow he's really good this he is he is
actually good this Joseph but fisherman
is not a class not yet
yeah damn sealed multi fancy class
whatever you want apparently okay
listen let me try to work something out
you keep fishing and I'm gonna see
because you don't have to have this
locket on you right now do you can I see
it please okay
and I it's a ridiculously tiny yeah I
have the same one which looks
ridiculously huge in comparison but it's
an optical illusion they're the same
size and I open it we look at them
together it's exactly the same hmm okay
it's his gold mines gold yeah my Dennett
dinar has yeah okay okay
mom are you a paladin dunno no sweetie
listen we've received this locket after
killing someone I can't remember I got
it
no no that bar in this base no this was
the devil or nothing around okay
um I won this in a bet inside of a
gelatinous cube I don't get into it but
we are on the same quest I am anyway and
and my Dragonborn friend outside you
might remember the big one oh yeah 21
yeah he also has the locket so he's on
the quest to these two haven't found a
locket yet so they're not invited
food is cool if everyone has them same
Locker yeah it's not so I felt the same
way when dinar got the locket I was like
throw it in the water
who needs it now okay I'm gonna go try
to work it out so that you can earn off
your debt coming with us on a mission
we'll split whatever gold she has on her
when we inevitably killer
three ways to the dark I suppose whoever
looks like they're in charge in this
establishment yeah sure explain the
situation I want to waste too much time
on it but sure I want to just borrow my
son we're gonna come back we're gonna
pay off his debt in very nice gold and
you can buy lots of fish with it he says
work it out with Corbin okay no problem
Bernsen curve Corbin oh okay so back
outside back out of sight now I want to
make careful note of something do I get
a perception check from you to our blitz
in 10 which is with average no I don't
have any I got regular old garbage eyes
negative brain your eyes Wow
so you you can you here just sounds of
merriment and revelry in there so and
rosiest sometimes when Rosie goes into a
place the merriment and revelry stops
sometimes it increases yeah
you can't think of a time what I mean in
the in the fullness of time yeah perhaps
such a thing is possible so you so you
have you have brought your son yeah out
yeah walnut on grass you have you have
found your way down you find the portal
to get downstairs Corbin opens it up for
you close it behind you and down two
flights down just in the guts of this
ship you can see even the even in the
dim light down here you can see these
golden scales shimmering on this
document sir now she sort of illuminated
in the in the holes in the upper part of
this hole that she's trying to repair so
she'll run over to a pump mm-hm and then
she will pump it several times sweet and
then once she has pumped it sufficiently
then she goes over and tries to put up
one board
right I immediately have analyzed this
situation I go what we need to do is
streamline this process and here's how
we're gonna do it and I lay out my 10
step plan which amounts to I'm just
gonna keep doing the pump you're gonna
put up the boards she no it's just yes
yes yes dould Roma told Roma yeah she
holds out her hand
walnut grabs her hand and goes it's it's
a pleasure it is an absolute pleasure it
is an absolute pleasure did you know
that team Bellerophon mm-hmm she walks
over and looks outside you're pumping oh
yeah totally gone he walks over she
looks out and just inhales he's your
nostrils flare see air fortifying her
for what she's about to say Oh God
she puts her hand on the edge of this
crack and she looks back and she says
did you know that they don't have a
document sir oh well not at this point
you can see she's used enhance ability
on herself to boost I know I don't know
what kind of hellish contractual wild
card license thing they have going on
there I I tried to fill out form 27b
obviously the nautical requisition form
sure yeah they weren't having it they
weren't having it there they team be and
paperwork doesn't really go hand oh no
no you know what goes hand-in-hand
success and paperwork that's what I'm
saying I'm saying getting the job done
it's a one-to-one ratio Danny she lifts
up a board I just so as you're moving
back toward the boat you can it sound it
sounds like like some kind of like
goblin factory end up in the base of
this thing and you can hear even over
the pounding you can hear shouts from
these two women going back and forth
it's just like they don't respect to our
so she says she says you need to tell me
about this bag you need to tell me how I
can get it back I don't know if I don't
know if it's something I need to fill
out I don't know
does Corbin need to authorize it from
the Home Office and then a woman just
goes she she slows down she's a little
more personal now she goes this bag and
it's like how does not care about
material possessions at all but some
reason she was like she was this bag she
goes head office gave it to me actually
omen specifically I actually have a
letter from him when I got it mouth just
says omen drawn but there's no voice
Shane oh my god
yeah the same they say that he was the
first document sir I believe it that's
what I've heard too have you ever read
his contract with Waterdeep not yet yet
I'm working my way through everything
available to his in listen good all
think that's the cherry on top I read it
but I get it I get it and then she she
she goes shake she pulls out the the
note the sheet that she has for him and
she goes check this out and somehow it's
magically laminated mystical yeah like
she dunks it in the water and then she's
like it's safe
[Music]
she does have issuances have any of you
have any of you leveled up our horts
person also seems to have got a got a an
advancement well no art I know that
Corbin is third rank decision that's do
you really need one well like you do
because when they rank up they can
requisition from the Home Office are
things before your facility are you sure
I'm sure that's not just decision s
propaganda did you see that did you see
the sale yeah level three level three
I want my thanks to all the all the
stuff that they did like trying to get
the carriage house like just by
themselves like something that the home
office did not give them and she's like
huh there's something exactly so she's
in and then as you're as you're working
other crew for the ship not in AI livery
obviously but basically just the rest of
the physicality that's required to
maneuver this craft is coming down
they're picking up mallets they are
trying to put the rest of these repairs
together I don't want to hear I only get
one more perception check from you good
sir just stand around for Steven Fortin
view here you here like distinctly you
hear the sound of dice hitting a table
to move in like back in the bar like
like it imagine imagine the pass of this
sound it's like the dices here it's like
off of a cast-iron pan mm like
reverberating through the wood planks
you know it's just like there's you just
you can hear that face that's what dice
face daredevil okay have they come out
yeah they have come out alright okay in
there Wow legals here hey drew this so I
said we'll be singer isn't everything
good thing cuz I hear it sounds like
there might be trouble I'll go check on
it did you do something did you do
something in there I'll go check on it
everyone else wait here I don't know
yeah should I grab it should you wake
you off your strength yeah in my mind I
went up to talk to them but in this in
that you can talk to Finn oh man exactly
because you're like so set up to fly
yeah
like why not I love your special effect
man that could not be better very funny
basically it's like the it's like the
ignominious like final portion of the
bungee jump yeah where you just sort of
like wow I guess I'm powerless against
the forces of nature
yeah all right well then eyes the screen
coming do you think'll nope
intentionally or is that just an
effective I think I think that the
tentacle is like a numbing effect oh
yeah yourself over completely no I think
if anybody is on the tangle head in the
back no you wouldn't have quite okay
they already take a yeah we take form in
some way
all right yeah you can have all of it
requires that you sort of moist years so
go ahead I'm doing Lee I've done that
like why we're all separate right I'm
gonna I flipped the Crowsnest
yeah and she's right as you fly up here
you tract instantly by a hand crossbow
well it's it's don't worry about the
tentacle you think I want this don't
worry about this the tentacles I'm
asking it to do this it bangs me into
the side of the crow's nest I land on my
on my back in there it's a flop down it
on it uncoils
yeah it goes back up into this guy
just snaps and I whip crack and I and I
say conspiratorial II I don't even know
what God is performing some kind of some
kind of homicidal mathematics on it I'm
just trying to figure out like how it
can be incorporated into her schemes a
friend is there anything I can do to
assist here if she seems it
authentically disturbed by the black
tentacle she says that was not that was
not in the calculation what type of
calculation well it's not hard people
are giving you signs all the time
haven't you found this is the case
people are always sort of like
everything they do every everywhere they
go how they speak there's other always
sort of saying yes I hate to speak for
other people but yes she says no one
else hears this it seems like you hear
it really well and I wish I did I'm
going to make you an offer I would like
to be best friends with you there's no
catch
what I can offer from my side is that I
will not kill you unless it is
absolutely required and from my side I
will not request that you kill me but if
we solve a lot of problems for me right
now the deal is done she extends her
hand I extend my hand the guy he also
coils around to see little God he comes
out a dagger comes out in the hand and
she says don't reach for hence this is
that was a free one don't don't ever
reach for them someone puts it out don't
do it keep your hand back hey someone
it's a sucker's bet I just don't do it
the time yeah on house hmm oh that's
nice nice to know
she continues her circuit it's very very
important to her that she catalog
everything that is coming into and out
of this the space that she observes so
she's like a oh I just ask straight up
like you're not a you you're not a well
you're not a horse person clearly your
what your hoarding is data you're
hoarding information I'm an obligate err
notice no I'm so if this is so quick to
say what is that best friend she says
she's I solve problems living problems
the problems of life yes if some of the
problems of the first that is like she
says what I have found is that certain
junctures there are people with too much
life and things go much much smoother if
I can bring that down a little all of it
who's gonna say we have a lot of overlap
I think I desire that problem worldwide
exactly yeah she says how would you kill
to ogres hmm
did they like each other sort one knows
the name of the other and the other
knows his brother are they aware that
I'm there no not yet mm-hmm not many
time to act
mm-hmm if one let me throw something at
you if one had there's a little chill
it occurs to me that if one of them
speaking maybe that called me out on
being seen
I would perceive the inside of their
mouth perhaps to the back of their
throat misty step she puts her hands
over her mouth then parlayed the shock
of the other knife the first four words
no problems you while away a not
insignificant amount of time choosing
targets combinations of targets figuring
out how precisely to liquefy them I was
just gonna say we're never getting him
out of this crow's nest you come up with
an ID now denied what's in yeah you push
your way into what I have already
described as a scenario we have drawn
from the intergalactic cantinas of stage
and screen I say this is nice this is
nicer than our place you have to live
with opens mom and I'm an addict that's
true this awesome pad it's rough it's
business this is 100% a rough spot but I
mean obviously it's not too rough for
you but being pretty and being
head-to-toe in gleaming steel plates you
are not a good match aesthetically hmm
for this realm but you do here just
bless a dice
he's got the dragon-sickness blessed
dice and their music yeah the music of
their faces upon the mountain table no
either my ears I sniffing no no Melanie
and in fact at the last hit of the dice
one of them stands up and then tries to
flip the table over but the table is
apparently affixed very fluently they're
grounded so he strains it a few times
until he's sustained some injuries lower
back and then he's sort of
in shame creeps away from the table
holding his lumbar region I'm gonna need
your dice I think I think your dice are
maximally your metal ones Oh are we
gonna be maximally visible in here he's
40 now so how many other people are at
the table right now right now this this
is apparently a table given over to this
gentleman to operate the houses
operation in the back of the staggers
and Jags now you are not obligated in
any way to play it yeah but I will if I
will inform the rest of the cast about
it and I'll also establish that this is
a play this is something you are not
unfamiliar with either okay when you saw
a Giants and halflings played you
recognize immediately that it was a
lesser probably human designed game a
lesser game to the one that you had
played engine R and indeed they play as
far north as scholar called vaults so in
vaults you play successive rounds
against the house mm-hmm
on increasingly sized die so Johansson
halflings is a d-10 versus to d6 this
starts with a d8 moves to a d-10 you're
carrying your bets forward with you move
through a d12 and then finally to a d20
the other twist is that you can expend
one of your coins to purchase a dagger
for the final round which is a d4
that'll help you beat the odds against
the d20 now but you know perfectly well
that to purchase the dagger is itself a
little shameful you know that having the
dagger grants a four to one payout but
that defeating the final dragon involved
barehanded that is to say without the
use of a d4 grants a five to one payout
and obviously that's the only true
victory yeah
so just the curiosity you're you it's
one-to-one and they don't stack so like
you don't get a payout of two to one and
then then the next one you're doubled
bet doesn't then yeah you can you can
take your bets scoot them up in as much
as you want but until you have and you
basically choose win to pull out of the
game okay so if you lose the final round
if you get all the way to the d20 the
final vault and you are a and you lose
that role no money has you have not
gained any money
okay all that money is kept by the house
okay do you want to try a round of it
against this brigand back here yeah
all righty ever yeah oh no no I sit down
I say no this is my game what are the
odds are we playing house rules or
minute the Minnesota variant so as you
as you sit down this chair is not this
chair is not dinar size yeah I'm yeah
yeah that's too big exactly here you go
nice but to say these you would just say
these are your gold coins as they say
but yeah that's right was probably worth
doing around back there he opens he
smiles as you sit down you don't know
why you don't know if it's just because
he's been cleaning people out all day
you don't know if it is because your
chair is very small and then you are
very large yeah he might just want to
show you the golden gems that his mouth
is stuffed with it's one of these things
and all I get it's one of these things I
said oh great and add jerky it's brick I
call jerky jerky grandad jerky he's the
guys a bunch of money just walked over
here play you for your teeth yeah well
see if you get there Annie I'm up
alright game is vaults do you know about
it I invented it I'm Johnny bunks
pleased to meet you
the vault family you're gonna curse my
face are you using them arias I'm
telling them yeah oh yeah yeah I'm all
dirty
okay I'd like to have to boil em and
salt up for this right the two DS right
yeah oh yeah use those two together
right whichever ones you like whichever
ones are most legible yeah there you go
now so if you want to play you got to
put a coin by the d8 how are that's how
you play God feed that horse feed your
teeth to my horse dude another thing
yeah you will when you're gumming your
porridge tonight right now we're just
like intensity flings a one on my die is
an instant win that's you getting
whipped by the Dagon's tail yep right
and the double one is a autumn when
devil one basically pushes and pushes
the dice up to the next pushes the dice
in the fed up to the next vault now
the other thing is that if you roll over
that's the MA just like in Giants and
halflings so you want to beat this da on
your to d6 mmhmm right so wait wait the
mall is if you roll nine ten eleven or
twelve on the first hand yeah that is
the MA
okay you can't exceed it gotcha all
right right here go ahead and throw them
in there oh I go first oh yeah I don't
know the number to beat you know all
right six oh that's an otter loose all
right he says Paul this is all right he
says oh my teeth yeah
Hey all right so seventh no way you
could beat it right yeah no no so you
can grab one of those chips move it over
to the next vault you have to pay into
each vault
all right that's the so this is just
letting it ride exactly that is the like
the the fee like - yeah expedition feet
right so like so but I could just take
it in
you could go so I'm sure there's like a
statistical bell curve on this one it's
like mm-hmm not worth it I'm sure that
I'd odds already filled with something
you walked up to the table yeah yeah
someone did the odds on the Giants and
halflings it was awesome I'm sure
they'll do it on this tomb there's even
a narrative version I think the
narrative reason why that why you win on
that but here let's give it a try so you
need to roll on these to d6 you need to
beat this d-10 yeah whoo-hoo 8 &amp; 8 get
it gives him pause that's just cheating
he says you know shiny you can bet more
than one gold at a time that would speed
things up for me a lot you're gonna have
to roll good at some point you can't
really oh goodness
he says yeah can you you know I need you
to roll a little bit faster the bank is
gonna close soon and I want to bring all
your money there three
oh what's that time I went Tywin well
that's two to one I gotta get you I
gotta get a bunch more chips there's
some right here
hey that's right here oh no I might need
even more that's good just yeah yeah
root play that clean you out yeah go go
roto-rooter spoon real money on the
table yeah we're out of chips no money
so now this is deep for the next yeah
yeah
no he owes yo see that stack it's you
doubled and eyes are two to one yeah
yeah no it's it's real money with these
big stacks that's also yours yeah
exactly so he's exactly so yeah I want
his teeth and I want them bad mister you
got some money to front yeah it's not
denying what is right yeah yeah oh Jesus
oh yeah a little roll one borrow like
the odds are uh hey guys we can buy a
boat I don't need them fix this way you
know the chick that's stuck in a tower
we buy that gee people in ya nightmare
why are there so many okay so now you
can now you're at the final vault you
can take this money and leave tour or
you can spend one bet increment to get a
dagger and bring a d4 into this final
fight we gotta go we gotta go whole hog
although I will keep all those winnings
from that other one I won't just yeah no
shame this is do I have to keep these on
the board no no you can you can scream
at future
[Music]
already I wanna I got a lot of your
money already I don't like if I get any
more everybody arms will be able already
know you didn't like you're detecting a
kind of nervous tic yeah on his side of
the table you can sort of hear like his
gums sort of wetly slapping against the
back plate of the gold and gems say stop
that distracting and gross this one do
you want to do you want to purchase a
dagger no legit oh my gosh ten would
have been great so you have you have
left him in a like raft operating
capital yeah in the back of this fish
hole yeah and I stand up and I smile
Jomon my pearly whites
right I flip I McCoy and I say something
pretty dinar emerges from the staggers
and Jags
I said he has in this pile a lot good
Christ Annette no he's having fun he's
having fun
no I don't need it at all that's what
makes it so tragic so he comes out and
he's just gleaming there's more than one
source of this light some of it is some
of it is psychic and spiritually and
invisible from the crew exactly some of
it is glinting and then you and then was
it fences
like him mm-hm he's open she says she
says in what way I don't know how to
convey it I don't have that I remember
the language it might be time spent with
that's tricky it's not as efficient as I
like but yeah oh yeah not that so
everyone is everyone is piling back in
now that the guts repair has been is
well underway now holes are patched tar
pitch it looks better than when it was
built
exactly it's it's looking it's slipping
like a Millie like it's it's it's ready
to gets ready to go the water has been
pumped out we're starting to even back
up now you and dole drama are it's the
yeah absolutely
yeah she's a gold boys a gold in the
scale dragon for that spring and jars
that copper brass copper tarnish
yeah like nasty rusty so now but it's
the pumping is is vestigial at this
point it's just something you're doing
to pass the time yeah things that things
are looking much better we talked about
oak maybe at one point yeah you really
upset about it yeah yeah she's like oak
true strike yeah Oh ever strike tell me
yet tell me that's a real name
that somebody gave another person yeah
making up fake names for yourself stupid
oak true strike and then I go oh I mean
you seem to have like a lot of paperwork
on them do you know the last names than
any of the other ones what about that
what about that gross barred saw the one
that were the one they were looking for
that's what they were looking for yeah
the cartographer the yard yeah yeah I
understand that she's there she's there
cartographer they needed her for
something I guess she'd been gone for a
while yeah I mean I hadn't heard that
yep
yeah
what's her last name lady 8 oh right
thank you while her immediately is now
like so now piecing together that bro
what's the cartographer in that had
never come up at all at any point in
their conversation it's just like
learning things because so she's missing
where'd she go missing if they don't
know they don't know they had heard that
she was on this Coast so we we traveled
north and south along the coast for a
week or so to the towns that they had
gotten reports let me ask you a question
and yes I also dislike team B yeah yeah
she she means and she says documents or
business there was there cartographer I
did know do you know anything about team
B and maybe something with rings
desiring about yeah they were trying to
find her ring why did they want to ring
they were clear about it it just seemed
like a really important thing to them
everything is really important to them
that's the thing that I noticed first
everything that they want has to be done
right away
yeah well even if it's dumb yeah sure
even if it's a dumb well which it most
certainly is I think everything o quants
is pretty stupid um more like O's hmm
well I hope that they find her are you
still trying to help them find her no no
it we were glad to have them off the
ship look right so there goes sir
they're gone do you know where they were
heading they didn't say they don't they
don't have to tell us anything
yeah and that's the only thing they did
tell us is that they didn't have to tell
us anything and they told us that a lot
just everyone in general you know what
though huh oak had a ring just like it
Oh can I ring - yeah they said it was it
was a ruby ring mm-hmm
and it was just like it it was very
similar in any case Phoenix anvil not a
real name not a real name not real and
for a respectable person he did not have
a ring like that hmm all the colors and
readings from the one station she goes
so so only the cartographer and OCAD
those rings they had matching rings yeah
there they were both simple I don't know
if I saw it
yeah I'm sure just inked a nice like
everything that they have so they call
each other on those rings and that's
just like a one-way line between oak and
the bard that's weird stupid I wouldn't
give it to everybody - they'll have them
all right it's that if that's what
they're using them for it seems like it
would be pretty handy to get a hold of
your whole team yeah well not I want to
say her hand isn't the her pocket she's
touching the ring like but not gonna
reveal that she has it and she goes how
does he call her no idea I was trying to
do my due diligence she goes well yeah
listen I want you to know DeeDee I am
filing a full report oh now that oak is
gone
all right expect you what I'm gonna use
all the form I would and triplicate
there are forms I haven't even used yet
that's great think about it aren't I so
dull drama says so what brings you guys
out here C team doesn't operate out this
way yeah we're a bit from the desert
valley yeah
we found uh here's the thing our our
cartographers one a locket in a bet
inside a gelatinous cube like you do um
and inside the locket was a girl in a
tower and she feels like we feel like
maybe we should go help her but funny
thing then our decision is found the
same locket in a bird's nest right by
the docks
oh yeah kids sell those they find him on
the beach and walnut wanna like just buy
five of them for a copper watt laughs
and she just looks at her feet and she
goes don't tell my team just yeah all
right he's super don't let go so you
come out and they run into you two on
the way back to the boat you pass them
sort of on the way yeah so you're
joining that back up so you you are you
and and rivas are out on the ninth
korben korben shale is like hey kid I'm
sorry about your boat mm-hmm sorry I'll
take it
yeah that's good that's a good amount of
sorry you got a good kid he tries to put
his head on her shoulder
keeps going down keep believing farther
and farther down I got a question for
you I got an answer for you we both have
these lockets I take it from you I show
we've got these two pockets mm-hmm and
also our decision that has one do you
know what this is about
have you seen anything like this before
I've seen a couple of these I've been
more common okay maybe more common
sometimes people will find them on the
beach okay yeah we found I found mine
far from here
do you I open it up and I show him do
you know where this person is it seems
like she's here and Neverwinter he taps
on the he taps on us like it's a good
trip trick whoa I never seen anything
like that oh I see
hey that's Rick oh you had me worried
this was some kind of gimmick so we're
trying to find her we we've all got
these lockets it seems like she's in
this town where is she
well I show him the map that I drew yeah
yeah yeah to the tower she is here does
that look okay wait he's like well yeah
okay no it's the coastline we can see
the coastline and that's why I wanted
the boat I wanted to find where it
looked like mom you're super good at
maps yeah he looks at it he looks at it
and he's like yeah I I know how to get
there we have been having and then from
the crow's nest problems we've been
having problems we can't really leave
like a hundred percent go like leave the
we can't a hundred percent leave the
harbor a lot of boats are having
problems
right now but I think that we're having
more problems than other people okay
did you see the hole yeah okay so
there's no there's no show
there's no reef it's it's pronounced
school school it doesn't look like it
but er Deena's this is not a thing that
can happen I'll let you know what it's
okay you don't have a boat you tried to
steal my borrow borrow I'm really sorry
I think we all are ya know I might be
able to get out with your help
something is happening when we leave the
harbor and it happens very quickly hmm
we discovered this with the help of the
of the B team help this is one instance
where it was kind of nice to have them
they were able to scrape all of the
mermen more or less away from the boat
I'm gonna stop you right there
mermen man merfolk okay mermen we're
common
okay continue Dave do not like the boat
I guess it's the best way of putting it
okay so angry they hate it angry merfolk
in the harbor are attacking votes yes
our boat a lot okay but if you help me
manage some of this mer bandage no no
sorry a cast Island Sun creepeth dreams
didn't get to talk from the ages like
six
- eight kid kid you don't know about
this yet because you haven't made
anything of yourself and you never will
listen I can understand why you might be
invested Wow
I'm allowed to talk to my son like no
one else is so back up take it back I
want to apologize for suggesting that
you could never succeed good enough now
when I became a third rank decision
aesthetic to the boat hmm
for people like your son mm-hmm
let's let's let's let's keep the Brig
son free it's a careful application of
parenting when the boat is underway I
need 100% focus I think you'll find that
things like this know I get out there
and it's just but I got to make sure
that it's just boat the whole time all
boat yeah weird that he owns a ship and
he keeps calling it yeah you are all
boat sir okay don't worry we'll keep we
will keep this under control
and all this oh this I think you'll find
in a pan she's going to Italy I'm
looking forward to seeing it okay I love
silence don't talk silence is lifted but
you and I
sound the horn of teamwork how do we get
together you can you can see a you can
see a a dark shape from the crow's nest
huh looking down and then you know up
around the shoulder yeah okay this guy's
this boats righted and now you're
finally all within range yeah hey what's
up whatever we do we got I tell them all
about the mermen folks and we got him we
got to make that stop happening so we
can go save this locket easy you lift
the amount of the water until they
suffocate well that's great easy Thank
You TV I got a better Dragonborn if
anybody's interested
hey buy a boat a friend yeah later ask
fen how she would kill a merman that's a
great question what would you do for
these but these mermen you surely
thought it about it
how many mermen how many did you have to
contend with 20 a big big big Merman
full-grown yeah hmm
yeah it's the math becomes very complex
at that more dense the interdiction
becomes I only have so many limbs it
would require a substantial preparation
and that is not unfortunately the sort
of ship that Corbin children's we we
will add our limbs to yours I have more
than most of my teammates tell me more
with some pride that kind of a limb I
think of them as such
exactly and then you know underneath the
underneath the cloak yeah exactly
way ahead technically I mean he's gonna
be a much use the limbs though okay
technically yeah exactly that's four
more limbs yeah that'd be me yeah okay
so so it sounds like everyone is is
ready to were assembled set sail the
avengers so to speak
we're the the sales drop and billow the
the famous iconography delivery of
acquisitions incorporated its exclusive
this has a brand expression we mas a
magnifique is there like a symbol for it
we could do that's tough a gang sign
yeah yeah trying to alex dirty yeah they
all do still dirty curious it's cutting
you off like right above the hand
samesies profound interactions for Table
Talk
but the the craft hauls up its anchor
and the Merry Widow sets sail out of the
harbour way we don't have a plan into
you're gonna be okay anything goes down
shadow council mayor Labor's please you
this is our commercial break
recall that subscribers only see cool AI
stuff instead something considered don't
go anywhere we'll be right back I'm a
pencil hello I'm here for K Harkins and
this is test C teams when last we saw
our heroes you cool yeah all right good
it seems good all right
it's like this joy but then there's like
a point beyond joy okay so you never
it's like you can go a couple ways
beyond joy these jokers yeah a minute
soap in my eyes now they're Merry Widow
hmm has made its way out you can see
other great vessels approaching the
harbor they don't seem to be bedeviled
in any particular way you're not seeing
a lot of problems from other ships visa
vie on the very back it has like a motif
right yeah yeah it has a cross that
there said there's a somebody's texted
me a term for it and I forgot what it
was
eat a dick her folks just like like this
was facing down I seem to remember it
was like what appeared to be a woman and
two men you mean oh yeah okay but nobody
was Murr no enduring no there was not a
mur mur mur
there was an imminent murmur all right
well and on that if I do
exactly exactly so she's terrified as
it's going out you are win you are with
Corbin shale at the helm yeah and he is
he is dialing in your expert direction
right
he is dialing in the course to whatever
is out there in the distance I want to
say something like cool nautical
shooting but I don't know any sell
Amy cuz we filming can you fill him for
me here kind of stuff when I shout
authoritative Lee would you we're
laughing you idiot porous leeward small
of stature right but on the deck of the
ship just this strong carrying voice
it's just that crisp clap of the sea air
the waves on the side of the boat like
this is you are this is one of the many
lives was on the sea and it is yeah this
is yet another sea words that are not
appropriate for the chili pepper yeah
does Grievous know because like merfolk
come up and while I'm silenced I think
about merfolk like really hard really
hard but like do I do I can try to
manifest in my in my vasty lures that I
have accumulated in all of my years of
undergrad education
do I know anything about merfolk Oh
almost certainly
let's get let us dish up for the shadow
Council that with his dear ol the
under perception no I'm here in spirit
what's your water creature it's like
it's like dude
with your with your two you're just
you're thinking about the creature that
is that has no head at all and it's just
two fish tails against this is what
we're looking for breeding fruitlessly
against to see you you spare a moment of
empathy for this creature beating
fruitlessly against the sea is juices
cover band every minute but it's also
the name of the first album and the
single exactly so you so you you are you
you taken you you taken leave of the
group you were not able to deliver your
mom evidence of your scholarship yet
again can i and roll history checks here
just a show that's done sure this is
great grab that done can do so much more
but grant super old
yeah that's fine I know I am proud of it
but 19 oh yeah tell ya now you imagine
two fish heads gobbling everything yeah
so that that doesn't sound right to you
mirthful like that doesn't sound like
that doesn't seem like the merfolk that
you know from stories are from direct
experience like you don't see them
acting as a sort of like sub aquatic
bulwark deep strike force against ship
holes like that doesn't sound right that
actually sounds more like a marrow to
you a marrow what somewhere Oh
[Music]
thank sexed mom I digress Noah marrow is
a corrupted creature no no I mean that's
like I wanna I want to say that that's
not the case but if if you were
literally to picture a dark merfolk
imagine imagine a Lost Tribe of merfolk
at one point and their histories
diverged from merfolk proper as a result
of their adherence and worship to a dark
God
so like the drow of the merfolk yeah the
deep drought I was gonna ask equation
can be seen yeah see I was gonna ask if
I'm familiar with like in any of our
natural lay no shudders that's stupid
what do they call Mara do they exist in
the Underdark at all as as a as a
delight you know on a alchemical table
to explore there okay you know the
potential of their organs me somebody
knows a guy as a punchline yeah a joke
they walk into a bar and they swim into
a bar but what exactly and your stomach
sinks okay guys this is a vicious they
sound scary Oh vichyssoise I'm scared
all the way to hold a mirror of your
bones cool great okay so this is
chilling and I reported on the party
line chillens chillin mindin my business
that's right
you know it every day and so I tell them
that we've got we got a marrow problem
and we might be up against something
that we
may be unable to contend with however
knowing that it's merfolk can we ask fen
art sorry no no it's not merfolk can we
ask them the same question as before but
how she would kill a marrow I'm not
familiar with them by saying I hear the
marrow that's what my team is telling me
that these might be oh sure how do they
how they different what would we do for
them the best the best way to protect
yourself from a lot of them would be
protection from evil so your broader
your that's your larger-scale
response to something like that again
like I say that the math gets bizarre
yeah we finally have a paladin so
combined they can get the you know
double sure um from what they were
saying about the mirth are these things
like legit evil like like like old dark
yeah like like these are the store
like their stories that people tell
about merfolk the bad ones like the ones
that you scare kids with like the ones
that the ones that would make a sailor
perform some kind of gesticulation you
know at the first sign of bad weather
probably not merfolk probably something
more like a marrow so I go I go oh no
problem I'm I can tell her things like
that are around cuz I'm super holy now
I'll do divine sense yeah divine divine
cent
yeah the new aroma from Yankee Candle
dredge right so so dream is you take you
you you sort of move to the center of
the
of the dock sort of near where you went
down below I thought the boat had
already taken off yeah totally
absolutely yeah but you you sort of
moved to the center and just just try to
you extend your awareness out if you can
see him sort of using his body to expend
you know to extend whatever field this
is and then as he does so you definitely
feel you feel a twinge like the that
that taint don't look at me when you say
hey I just that taint that right fully
extended it's fully extended and you can
see you can see drivas shudder like he
has actually authentically learned this
huh it's it's quite true it's entirely
possible Wow that he may have that he
may have hidden talents so maybe maybe
once he has learned every class in the
flares handbook please don't give him
ideas you do it I mean and then
immediately over like over his head as
he extended you're about to say oh yeah
there's a there's a huge problem like I
am fully aware of this and it's
definitely something that we have to
orient ourselves towards resolving
harpoons and grappling hooks fire up on
each side of the boat arcing over the
middle and then grabbing onto the the
deck and then raking out and you can see
two separate two separate deckhands
seized by these hooks and then just
yanked right over the edge you know
Wilhelm scream obviously is leverage
kind of scene like this historically
that is so much that is precision
yeah that is precisely what's going on
another another thing to indicate is
that we need to roll initiative oh boy
wait
there you go enjoy uh 12 mm-hmm please
you of course dinar Blitzen your servant
has a bird up something promise
something skillful now dinara I assume
that's gonna put you right up at the top
no no does where's that nut I'm a 19
that's very good it's not as good as
tonight well he has a negative to his
initiatives
does he really do you SIL does he does
my dexterity he used to know brevis 3 oh
my god I mean the time okay mom I rolled
for Locati where's Logano yet he's at
9:00
okay so he'll go right before just
wearing dirty dream well I'm gonna write
on here up on my backside here but if
you think if you can get a little
picture of Locati to to ELISA yeah we
can print out a get kula got eat a
hamburger and we can and we can honor
him oh we can honor him to do right in
this way so you can see these these
hooks and harpoons just repurposed
reshape some of them look as though they
you know are like of an alien
manufacture like a radically different
aesthetic some of them are repurposed
human weapons that have maybe fallen out
of ships and that have just been used by
this force okay no I want to ask and I
want to answer cuz I didn't manage to
warn the rest of them you know and and
sure that's her but I did sense that
this was coming yes can I gain advantage
on my initiative
here we go you know what though I think
this I think that this is okay so you so
you should roll out a diet yeah I'll
take that I'll take a seven
okay okay I think the Guddi beats you
yeah but it's like and then it's like
all right yeah there's no question
you're not as flat-footed okay Maxie
would have been you have you have a
moment okay um you know let me deflect
myself you knew you you can do it you
can do it ever you like we used it was
not attacking you're not being attacked
okay that's what's required right um so
I do have a kind of exploded donar
what's that so we're in the middle of
the ship exactly where they think so so
right now I mean it was just it was just
arcs of these are these sharp tools and
ropes coming up over the top I mean you
know to take a moment to do it right now
it looks like all of the ropes and hooks
but no one fight yet exactly so what
you're seeing these hooks come up and
like they're grabbing people and then
they're flinging them right off and you
can see like coming up right behind
their ropes over in the front of the
ship like pulling them pulling up the
rope and then like slithering along the
side of the boat and then just like
pulling off these these poor deckhands
just like flipping them over as they as
they sort of like flatten out and arch
up on the deck now hold on they might
want to just be friends yeah should I
try the tree let me parlay with I'm real
quick I'll use command and then I
command parlay what I was gonna say at
the beginning of thrist having heard
that they worship a dark God just like
how dark a god yeah what is it like an
unknowable like it's not necessarily
dark I wish I had actual literally got a
good no think you undo I'll give you a
little boost II nope do this a white
litter oh no wait I do
probably no you don't worry about don't
worry about me airing the old Christmas
week on the decorate
daddy D there are three that you can see
slurping around with their long fishy
gross tails and their their mouths are
just a mass of hanging tentacles free
floor right around the base of the chin
coming up to it a mess of sharp teeth
coming up from the lower jaw there's no
stats in here for a pistol
we have stats sure should I decide to
use utilize my pistol yeah absolutely
what's your got I'll do I'll handle the
damage yes sir I got you okay okay okay
all right yeah just gonna go right any
get dirty right somebody's day so yeah
this is your first chance to really test
out your level 5 yeah I get to
accomplishments who-who's brow the
ruthless toothbrush and I get to go
first which is super rare so I just yell
out like I go everyone
alpha formation protocol sword and as I
run I I drag it and I try to hit the guy
with an uppercut so on a get to attacks
11 Oh
17 oh listen don't you are bad
oh I was just 20 feet away she can't see
what you're holding up oh it was nothing
like yeah he does
Jurassic life finds away yeah exactly so
yeah yeah 17 absolutely so it just it
just it turns and then its jaw drops and
about a half gallon of just fetid
seawater
you know just falls out just all it down
all down its scales skews you exactly
yeah just an intimidation though yeah my
guess element14 that's attack one is not
dead is that is that how the campaign is
gonna be all right
so you you can you connect with him in
absolute terms like a toothbrush there's
up the spikes along its back edge I just
come up through all the straps of its of
its leather armor plate seashells are
falling down by the seashore
mm-hmm still he still upright though hey
oh yeah yeah well then click clack
number two all at once that's the only
one for eight mm-hmm tack a smile on top
if he's still standing yo he yeah he is
he's standing like on his weird tail
okay well then I'll smite him on top of
it which is mine
nice I know I've got like a buncha
smites it's like which is my do I want
to use
thunderous Mike it's an embarrassment of
smites 2d6 and he gets knocked back 10
feet wait an extra 2d6 thunder damage if
the target is a creature and must exceed
on strength or be pushed back ten feet
seven nice yeah yeah so you fish up so
yeah so I mean he's easily half of his
vigor has been drained away by this
first uppercut the gruesome slash and
then thunder cracks down and it flies
off the front of the ship yeah thanks
nothing tell you Frank
well arresting your fish walnut on grass
representative of the natural world
couple things I can do here so are some
of them still clambering up yeah yeah a
beam you mean like all on the sides I
think they're still climbing up the
ropes right now there are three up on
the deck and there are other ropes that
appear to have sort of like dug in to
the deck on the deck down all right keep
more from getting up okay you know that
I can do I was gonna attack the roads to
okay um so I would like to just grab
just take out for once which I've never
done
you know are people out of reach my
son and I take out for mother and I look
at her I just go I hope you're a very
good sort and I pick it up that leafy
scimitar and then I will just you know
what no actually even though this is a
stupid thing to do um so I can use flame
blade on a wood boat whatever we
discussed it right which for walnut
takes the form of for mother erupting
into flames green flames and then she's
gonna just do a fiery slash on one side
on the the starboard side like right
down the rail yeah like right down the
top of the rail for all those ropes the
most badass way that you can think of it
that is the way that yeah god it's fast
where's it takes a step backward whoa
yeah yeah there's just this heat shimmer
on the green glass of foremothers blade
you're able to you're able to shred two
of the ropes sure they're all over the
boat yeah I got that that keeps two new
combatants out of play that's it that's
a win
alright that's cool is what I'm on tape
but yeah forty ropes
and they turn into licorice yeah no I'm
fine
yeah our scent of the Roses the fire
resistant is the fire persistent yes the
boat burnt down Tbk finally really no it
is not no don't worry I was just saying
it could burn through the ropes then
yeah they're very thick they're very
thick rough justice on just angle the
ropes are made on wet seaweed I mean
like the fire does nothing today but
it's just it's one move from the waist
engulfed in flames straight through to
people continuing to move purposefully
up the deck rosy bee stinger yeah we got
you on deck
indeed wielding the staff of the master
third master how do you contend okay so
my level five skills were largely combat
and I'm about to employ a bunch of them
so sound to work yeah I see the work
that Nora's doing I'm very impressed
with it and I also think that he's
enjoying himself a lot yeah and I but
the form you want to show off yeah
before I'm gonna let him like have a
thing because I think he's got some good
stuff coming but I'm going to go for the
other two because I mean attacking one
is fine but you know attacking twos
better so I have now stunning strike and
extra attack which means exhaustingly I
have something like more attacks per
turn if I use a key point and then also
I can do a studying strike so we can
spend two key points and do five attacks
one of which will stun so we're gonna
see that thing explode my dear fish yeah
it's me like Fist of the North Star like
yeah those headaches whoa oh I remember
how to fight
this is fine you said obviously not
remembering how to do it at all
and I got it okay that's a 22 she
remembers and then I will do this hit no
here no shadow council mayor laborious
please you
indeed in an effort to please you
greater let me confer with my friend
Rosie be stinger very briefly true hey
listen I got a written down I trust me
on this
what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna roll all
these attacks we'll see which one's hit
oh and then you make an awesome story
and they will flavor it I love it yeah
okay I'm gonna do another one
that's an 18 but ahead well it's very it
okay let's tray it and then these are my
tin are unarmed strikes coming at ya
that's 25 yeah ironically did not hit
know that though the unarmed strikes
ever do you leverage your arms
well I had not considered that man work
unless I kick that's true
my legs yep that is only a 12 nah I hit
okay
that's my last arm strike I believe
stunning strike is a feature that mainly
weapon except I can't spend a key point
to try to stun it and it has to succeed
a con save or be stunned to the end of
my next turn
blam bow jeez yeah so um here's what
we're gonna do yep um Rosie's gonna
leave you to your marrow barfing
seawater she will attack the nearest one
move toward it in DTAC with a physical
attack of the staff
she then will use her new stab the
master ability which turns it into a
ranged weapon that she hurls it's
correct toward her enemy and returns to
her bounces off of the enemy yeah so
she's gonna do a slap across the the
fishy part part effects are carefully
selected the finest finishing is right
slap that throw it
it comes back and then she uses her
other hand to punch it right in the fish
I'm reading the entire fish yeah and
then also will use a stunning strike I
definitely get another attack for that
or is it just a I think it's sounds like
you point no it's just a cue point yeah
okay so that means I've spent two key
points this round and con save will save
it from being stunned otherwise it is
stunned that was stunning now I still
rose damn it's all done how much more to
do but I did not work okay great so 1 D
8 + 4 super step attacks love it which
is that one is the 13 G's decided this
is just kidding thank your team still 15
no I'm not doing it again that is a 7
sorry and that is a 10 those are my
staff attacks yeah and then my one arms
is a also 7 and then I've started stunts
yeah I can't move at all till my next
animatics turn yeah it is just it's like
a drum like you just you just unleash a
flurry of lightning fast that attacks on
this fish it's very surprised that's
some daredevil ship yeah exactly like no
surprises it's the little fun it's like
I got a say wow didn't see that coming
heard a lot about the surface world new
info take a good work
I need a process but yeah oh oh this is
gonna turn locally so um that was
explicit and look um the thrust drought
so in how many we still got standing how
do you still have standing on the flight
once done and then one fresh free one
how far are they of all these two yeah
14 feet okay I was gonna I was suing
I just took it faced by like I have a 14
foot Ranger this thing perfect
I'm assuming more will come up so I
don't want to blow my my point area well
who knows who died in stay I don't want
to blow my area guys just okay that oh
no the cameras are on all right I'm
gonna pick which one looks the the
healthiest it's probably the one that
you just it's done
no I think that one there's one fresh
yeah there's one that I can get my range
so it's only got unharmed from our
commencement which is not changed all
right another marker players let's have
the market price to us oh oh listen well
just go for the whole business then
forget it
I was gonna say that oh wait a minute no
I have a perfect thing to adjudicate
this whatever you're ready not my
imaginary friends here but the real ones
in mind I wanted to use elvish blast
because I have two of them now they can
for it yeah but the goal of this is to
knock at least one of them out and I
don't want it like sprinkle damage so I
may as well just just go for the whole
bit so I'm gonna do hex on i'ma bring
hexie back on hex you finally caved to
the tag line I'm sorry about it and it's
I'm sorry mom on the one who had the
worst looks the same how she got there
hex on the on the most frail looking one
what's that save he's gonna know it just
happens and then if they're near each
other that I'm gonna just go
she's an share time okay I'm gonna hurt
him really bad let's have those
Constitution throws from the both of
them okay what is it how do they feel
the first one feels pretty good the
second one less so they've be 215 what's
that maybe the 15 the first one did okay
that's unfortunate
for me but see let's see sue those
delicious Tyson may I use one of these
what other dates thank goodness but not
a bit embarrassing paying attention true
shame it pays off oh yeah oh yes that's
us this is a 701 canteen
I thought it was a wine that's eleven
that's nineteen for that guy by tan for
that freshman yeah okay and the person
who succeeded takes half that hard this
is real real nice yeah so so the first
one then get forget about the tender hex
that guy and the other guy can enjoy
which is a six yeah exactly
so okay so you curl down mystic force on
the deck and the one on the left the one
that you had invested so much care and
attention into mmm-hmm surgically yeah
manifesting your martial capability
breaks into a thousand pieces just and
there's like scattered across the deck
and then each each tip of the ship just
you know some measure of these chunks
just slide out into the ocean the other
one is is grievously injured by the same
by the same thing it's the the the fins
that they have are the like the very
tall like a like a like a sail yeah
almost and they're just they're torn and
shredded like that yeah then you dumb
fins
hey worthless what yes he was like get
your blip like hey like what we gonna do
I turned up and I say hex shattered he's
pretty good and on these guys
she says mmm good she reaches into her
vest and pulls two vials out
he says holy water huh um no thank you
you you are able to elicit a chuckle and
these these rain down on the deck proper
water yeah look at that get that trophy
feeling no it just just hisses just all
along the the sheer scales just like
steaming steam is pouring off of the
flesh now we're talking about these
special friends so that is at this point
that's three more pull themselves up on
the day three more pull themselves up
north
um but one of them one of them looks
substantially different than the others
oh she has pulled herself up on the very
prowl
sort of where the you know where you
would historically find a sculpture of
something like a mermaid yeah she is
Stambaugh ship lady oh I love it so she
is she is standing on the bow of the
boat
she's like a bow sprit ah right
she is looking at literally like looking
away from the group from the party just
looking out at the sea
and then she turns back over her
shoulder and just moves her hand toward
the party and the other two move out now
listen important things are happening
now exactly like that a harpoon flies
over the edge of the ship at Rosie
finally mm-hmm I think euros oh here we
go here we go and things are happening
important things are happening I'm gonna
deflect missile okay that is as a
reaction I can reduce range weapon
attack damage done to me if the damage
is negated a catch and may throw it back
as a monk weapon nice okay so I roll a 1
to 10 plus 5 plus my decks mm-hmm and
try to beat the beat your damage roll
mm-hmm if you throw it back and we board
their ocean that's right okay so 1 to 10
so 10 is an 18 yeah yeah so you'd be so
you you catch it yeah and you can see
that it is base is made of what must
have been like an anchor for a small
ship that's just rusted down to this
sort of jagged prong may I add a little
flavor to zesty kid it's a it's bigger
than I've been a an arrow or a bolt
right right but but because it's so big
you catch it and you drag but you
maintain your balance I mean yeah yeah
and and just just like 3 4 feet didn't I
could not you saying you've got a kungfu
panda at where you go all the way around
yes that's amazing
straight off the side of the ship yeah
okay so I am now holding that do I see a
source is there there a creature in the
water that I can return fire yeah if you
if you were to look down if you were to
look down along the line of there I mean
functionally speaking they're fishing
right sure if you're look down on that
line you can see indeed
you can see someone whose intention is
to not be grabbed okay they want to grab
instead
sir could you redirect it to somebody on
deck certainly okay there they haven't
aggro'd me but wait there is yeah this
person is this this creature a matter of
principle
hey I don't know if you could call my
attack back and the one that attacked to
you I was just curious about that um
yeah I'd like to to throw it back hopper
if I need to hop up and and but before I
do I'm angry and it's like this is a big
harpoon I'm mad my child is on the ship
uni yeah I don't really any mother yeah
I don't really have anything but being
on this ship in the harbor it's brought
it back smell and the fish and the sound
of the gulls and this end it sounded
like the water splashing against it with
all of the ruckus and I look at this
creature in the ocean and I just scream
this like guttural sound that shouldn't
come out of me but there's something
there's something that's that has
completely been awakened in me but it's
not it's not pure anger it's also a
little maybe more than a little pleasure
right I'm very very happy with this
throw that harpoon right at it
as a monk weapon right don't know what
do you want here
what it's all gonna you it's all gonna
all that stuff is gonna be based around
your your decks anyway yeah yeah I would
pretty comfortably use your attachments
that okay you guys I'm good that's any
times what happens yeah yeah 17:18 yeah
absolutely
okay you want me to just roll the stab
with a master mm damn it I know I didn't
have a Democrat so yeah I mean the whole
point of this exercise is that the
harpoon is gonna come up catch a person
and then they'll pull the person down
into the water that's that is the
opposite of what happens they said you
have grabbed it redirected its momentum
expertly and then hurled it with a
barbaric yawp back down imagine if you
were actually fishing imagine
imagine dark fishing and you are you
real you throw the line in and the
hook exactly right in your own
lip no I'm the fish pardon media yes
naturally yes I made in her eye at this
level because it's a casting a third
level that shatter should have been 48
not 3d eight oh so on the person who's
left standing
yes who did careful if I could turn back
then I want to encourage him to know
himself and that is why I will allow it
thank you neither if you have enjoy it
an additional three he detonates
ice-cold Ghouta fish alright he hates it
chief
I tell him look be hurt more exactly off
on the oven affront to the left you can
see Corwin shale is just a brace of
pistols
it's just firing shot after shot into
the interlopers who have just come up to
up his brand Lee his brand new
repaired boat he's able to find purchase
a couple places
chest hair wafting in the movie yeah
exactly
oh yeah yeah III it again water well you
know no it's just like it's just like
when he when he reaches out for the
brace just a couple buttons
there are a little crucifix buttons so
they are at the fact the front of the
boat they are did grabbing people
putting a couple quick loops never been
on the sea proper yeah like have you
ever seen it like when somebody like
that old yeah on the dock
that knows exactly what to do with the
rope yeah maybe that's not like he's
just up there nice to see ya like it
doesn't look like they're doing anything
but they're making this yeah and
every time you do it oh no oh you're
pulling as hard as you can and then
you're your father-in-law is really mad
yeah I mean just like one's father yeah
ah yeah the Royal we you can't
please this guy yeah yeah that's what
evening sorry I always start with
goddamn ropes so they'd say these the
Amero at the prow sure the marrow in
boat town proud marrow keep on rolling
in the forward of the aft but like
quickly expertly tying them up putting
something into their mouths and throwing
them over the side of the boat because
there's one because this is important -
dree beside rebus has got to save people
now this is his whole Spees this is face
have these fees yeah this is my steez
now so it's like a millennial word the
the marrow take a movement action onto
the boat grapple tie people feed them
something and then also throw them off
all in one turn that's right do they
have five actions their 20th level okay
I was just checking it seems like we
have the I dream us me personally
Patrick Rothfuss is being denied the
opportunity to potentially save a
helpless person with my poor
directionless character
rebus I'm not saying that these Merril
should not eat the out of these
sailors but it maybe not all in one turn
previously offended
I'm just curious I'm just I'm gentleman
here already I think you're committing a
dream ethera right now I'm just just fan
like I want it i Pat would feel bad if I
didn't save at least one sailor
well yeah it's like I feel like like
General Grievous but I don't really want
to reference those films at all yeah
like and I feel like I've been I feel
like I've been robbed - basically I'm
trying to say sorry Table Talk you know
Table Talk yes that's exactly what
happened okay so I don't have a chance
there's gonna be lots of people you
could try to save them well I was sweet
on that one of them no you were Locati
mm really what are we peaking out here
so in my mind
um it doesn't change what I've done but
I'm still in the crow's nest or didn't
come down no I think you and anything
you and fin are enjoying yourselves up
there yeah Ariel Gloucester mm-hmm yeah
that makes sense okay but so I can't
stop him but them but that the sea spray
and the smell blood of occur as the
Gottis charm babe grabs his dagger and
he's coils down right down that master
yeah
and no wait not yet and he's gonna he's
gonna erupt ooh the boy he gets it he
gets down and then you can you can see
him rising up into his sort of like
dominance sigil this shape that he
assumes when it's time to go to work
it's not a snake the boat tips and he
just falls over in those roles no it's
for the best
this beasting so there's the one over
where they first came up in deep into
your left he drew a little thing here
these gotta like this well I drew this
but like these these men are these other
crew people have been thrown off with
something horrible in their mouth what I
know so and and you know I would like to
say again so are they are they gone all
that the crew members up here at the
prow they're off yeah they've they've
been yanked off one by one
somebody initial grabs dude that I feel
awful how close honestly it was only
your sloth totally my fault and that was
like replaying all the stuff you did
this morning before times I did four
times his mom his mom close to me cut if
I'm making a movement there can I can I
stop by her enough for a bonus action
yeah sure
okay so I stopped by and I go down and I
put my head on your shoulder I say mom
that was the most amazing thing I ever
saw
you're the best person I've ever known
in my whole life and then I take off you
get one died of Bartok inspiration you
get a d6 you can add to any role hell
yeah it's pretty smooth nice my boy and
I will go up here this is just one there
there's a couple there's one that that
has been pretty badly worked over and
then there are two additional ones up
there and then worked over one and big
mommy not stunned okay a stunned one is
now a million being devoured by by fish
and so I go up and I get up in there
into the mix yep
and I go like hand write down and I
thunder wave right in the middle I want
to blow ball off the frickin but I love
it I let it fly and I don't have to
worry about the sailors cuz
they're not there that's like now if
they hadn't all been you know robbed
different situation provide you an
incredible context I'm daring do I will
find my silver lining so anyways thunder
wave I
it's just damaged but they all get to
safe okay saved to be pushed no tell me
what you're telling about your spell DC
[Music]
I'm absolutely gonna cast it one level
up and yep and this is this is the
maternal guidance hmm that every young
adventurer need one of them was a 20 and
the other two were party looks like yeah
yeah okay yeah exactly so I feel
confident here that a twenty is is a is
a freebie but the other two were we're
low so they're gonna eat the full meal
deal okay do I get luck in do I knock
the boss off well no just let's get the
damage in the middle turn borrow some
you're absolutely we're looking for
eight here's another here's a need for
yam and another eight
there's another tendering Middle's 43 oh
it is three goes up to three because of
the other day and I'm done very
flavorful incredibly zesty the one that
had been here since this first Ben's in
an unhealthy way as a result of the of
the attendant thunder wave you suspect
that the internal damage is substantial
the other two one of them catches like
it is not back but it's caught against
the wall the other one flies out the one
not the one that is on the very proud or
about fish lady mm-hmm is is cast
forward off the front of the boat but
denies physics I love that and turns to
observe the scenario Dennard blitz in
this is very anime that was the most
anime round of combat I've ever seen
from the from the stars it's dragging
the sword then the yeah everything
everyone except the boss now whatever
was there was the one guy the boss the
boss arrived and gave directions yeah
yeah her last thing who's the top of the
list now that's what I'm at the fide yes
you may yeah and that's the only one is
she the only one left others there was
one one who was knocked back and
actually came into contact with the
boats drive misinterpreted back off okay
alright I said this is a joke and we
started under try it I'm gonna try to
come and do it
parlez I'm gonna can parlay today and I
can do it as a little too so I can do it
to both of them are the only two enemies
there yeah talk it out guys let's talk
it out so they have to do wisdom saving
throw okay
and what's this 14 pretty good I
like it
so the just because of the the nature of
they're sort of like fish sent our
bodies horses well no the basically it
would be basically the the marrow that
was on the on the on the deck had sort
of like flopping all around and that's
kind of lay on their tail exactly just
it whips its body around and is able to
bring itself back up right and you can
see that it has two sort of shredding
gauntlets and but in the in front she
steps from midair step slightly back on
the bow of the boat and then says
something to her fellow in some kind of
undersea appropriate tongue merlok yeah
oh right and she says let's just keep
going through yeah she says she says she
says we will speak are a queen seeks an
audience with you the servants of the
eye to discuss the matter of your king
jim dark magics cruel and evil treatment
of our sovereign Queen sorry
that's what's going on no we have two
full minutes left that's enough
annihilate her King now sir mayor
Labour's please you there is a
commercial break
of course subscribers see cool stuff
instead of something to consider helps
us run the show hey we are going to go
take full advantage of the facilities
after which we will return for another
zesty episode of Table Talk don't go
nowhere
you