time is the enemy the past and threatens
the fastest weapon you wouldn't make it
past a second and that's the question
play it brash and reckless to choose a
cost solution you saw it was prudent in
any seppuku poker to don't become the
putrid it's that well-fed I pursue in no
mountain too steep for dungeon too deep
to send expanded the marks up to the top
of the peak of beneath they see me they
come like sharks to it while I swim in
that money build like Carl Barks through
it so send your national parks drew it
I'll send him home in a natural box with
a close tie but most of the parts
included save your breath for a cleric
confessor death is a lesson that life is
attending professor but if you're
seeking my official advice sign on the
dotted line and list of the twice hello
I am Tycho Brahe hey panic attacks
I am also Jared cave Arkham's now see
you Ryan you me up you are doing
this scrambled egg thing yeah it
up right now here let's just do Frasier
come on to see it let's just I'm just
I'm gonna put up this and then I'm gonna
when I when I reveal myself yeah from
this arm bunker yeah probably afraid
crank you'll be pretty Niles Niles crane
Marisol brother of frogs I take a right
pyramid residue thing with these
assholes to my right talking about
narcissists did I would say yeah to the
right of my right reppin The Naturalist
of worlds its walnut on grass Oh gross
listen listen
Cupid listen this is it is to my liking
that you are not able to reproduce this
town don't have any art to it yeah yeah
this ornament this is just some kind of
a condition that you have I don't
believe any of this no to my left but
not your grandma's grandma except for
some rare cases in which she is your
grandma's grandma
OCP stinger that's right no it's some
kind of 4 dimensional rod it's evolving
just in case you think it's dirty then I
break it
no that is not less dirty honestly
that's a little yeah to the left of my
left adventuring lizard folk
entrepreneur battle axe wielder shelter
tonight fighter eldritch night fighter
self-insert Cupid Donner Blitzen
yeah the more you know to the left of my
left of my left emerging is though from
a mist shroud now we call this brow
kethry Stroud from a mister out like
who's this now so could it be now hey
stop it
trumpeter man now when last we saw our
heroes we finally at long last learned
the true secret of the locket that rosy
be stinger won while playing a ghost and
his own scale at me inside of a
gelatinous cube yeah
below a spider that was weaving sweaters
there's a very complex of rich tapestry
yeah you're gonna want to go back some
episodes if you missed that one yeah
that's that one that is from a long time
ago but the main thing is that it turns
out that there is a girl of a sort
inside the locket but not in the classic
sense yeah sort of a darker girl imagine
if you will a dark girl or in any case
or in any case imagine a scenario where
a creature like any
other creature has developed a very
sophisticated methodology for ensnaring
prey yeah
now let's go very briefly over these
scenarios and then we will get right
back into the action because we have
never actually ended the game in the
middle of a combat before very very very
exciting if trust me you'll either
manage this or the party from chaotic
right what can you last episode
obviously hold on to your seats so we
have a situation where the Merry Widow
which is a ship piloted by captain
Corbin sail his crew that consists of
Dole drama and fen as their ship hands
it is now currently in the warm embrace
and this is this is this is for your
benefit
Alyssa tentacles spectacles while I
watch it has everything we're talking
about a massive hug a hug that will
result ultimately in the destruction of
the will cannons are loaded but cannons
have not been fired because on the
island itself an island that has a organ
of some kind that resembles a lighthouse
yeah you know nothing about yeah yeah
yeah rau we have a members of the party
still inside the structure yeah we do
that is the situation so honestly on the
deck of the ship
we have dinar Blitzen mm-hm
we have rosey bee stinger yep and we
have and I believe Keith it is also on
there I don't I think I was still in I
don't think I went down no not not down
certainly I'm still in the penalty
my boss was like that's exactly a dream
Asst of James's yeah also on the deck of
the ship but that is the that is the
situation so it could be that you are it
could be that you are sort of in that
place
coming down the tower a choice I think
ready to go indeed because it was your
turn so I'm going to place you at the
front of this right here
and I would like to get initiative roles
from everybody else to mix it up
that's classroom what do you have walnut
mommy got it Josette how about you Chris
restaurant 14 there's an old fella Gotti
Wow he's an 18 he's a big boy
blow the good rolls early he's a special
boy well I'd say what God he is
something I'm about but it got lost but
right now I just put a little letter for
him on the back of these no cuz it was
so cute it's a little picture of love
love God he was so badass here actually
yeah you want to draw some commercials
no we can tabletop razor exactly
now does this equal to mash keep it yes
you tell me more about the situation so
so you're exactly as a result obviously
no your basically your progenitor he of
the ancient books the books of Blitzen
out on the deck of this ship scales
glinting here in the middle distance
tentacles reaching out from the boat or
from from this island beneath somewhere
in the substructure water full thick
with these lockets that is the situation
you find yourself in I'm still in the
stairwell as far exactly yeah very near
the the exit doorway um from okay so I
could go out the door you can you can
but this is
so you can story with me she sucked at
the last Jack's role so she couldn't get
up the stairs so I think we're just
gonna continually tumble down and she
sees the walnut goes down there and she
was like trying to apologize so I think
she rolls down to the basement area just
sort of yeah well there's our flipping
her office she goes because you would
actually set on fire yeah I got punched
in the gut and then I got set on fire
there's a burn ban I was just
not exactly so the their scene that's
the scene that you see before you is one
of Chris trout Morlock to a mysterious
power he only dimly understands
supporting himself against the wall his
eyes gone a milky white thirsty well not
done grass so did you move down there
yeah I was next to Chris and I saw him
with no eyes exactly exactly so that's
the situation so you see walnut posted
up by her warlock companion there I pay
zero attention and I just start
apologizing I'm doing like weird drow
stuff I'm not familiar when it's like
it's like yeah you have no idea
no you have no cultural references milky
hiding but I'm trying to figure out if
apologizing is a pic of full action
genuflect
please apologize in real-time
okay not rolling for it just actually
doing it I'm so sorry I'm just so so
covering myself I really don't know
what's actually going on I didn't know
that if you put the folks together is
that the right piece I didn't so sorry I
know that you're already going through
puberty so hard but just I just need you
to I just need you to not ever set me on
fire okay sorry about that again I don't
know if you're particularly flammable
again I didn't even know that I had
powers it's all really new at different
miles if you've been slighted yeah like
can you she's like what's what's
happening what are we doing what's
happening outside
what are we just like yeah so I'm kind
of doing the same I was I don't know I
just felt on the stairs and I I don't
think I saw them actually leave it's
like the whole towers they dumps
themselves out of it yeah I think
everyone's outside there might be
cannons I don't know I
what is this plant thing what is this we
don't have this at home the whole thing
is really really could use you up your
buddy I don't want to do anything yeah
no I can't yet it my turn
fancy indeed indeed now Cupid have you
accomplished what you set out to not at
all tell me more about how you
investigate I this space just explore
the space all right I am curious about
this Cather's de roba character uh so I
I especially with his wit I'm gonna
point say dis Joyce look is this what he
always is this normal not so much you
know sometimes you should
I I'm not actually hearing you but I say
yeah sorry buddy
not feeling it she brings out an egg by
the way she's like this tiny little like
egg is like kind of a peace offering you
can eat it here's this egg I I have
apology eggs
I have other types of x2 it's it's it's
a custom or how the sec oh my god I'm
like not even I can't even lay yet all
right she's taking like a whole turn to
talk about that but she's really
interested in what's going on with this
whole thing and I'm gonna bring out my
star okay I'm gonna be lucky to asahi's
are what's going on with your friend
here what you must understand he
communicates with strange powers
perhaps he communes with them even now
perhaps he communes with the Lizard King
ask him hey if he is talking to the
Lizard King and more importantly if the
Lizard King has referenced me in any way
ask him if the Lizard King remembers any
of the great times that we share us are
right that's okay yes you you went by
that desert King have a name but I just
told him the Lizard King
okay we're casually King okay yo I'm
talking about this King thing dude what
go away not like I got a sword that
wants to have a chat with you about
sorry sorry I'm sorry
oh all labor's will soon be at an end
really weird dude I will have all of the
answers okay is he normally like this
that's our he's our buddy
I would say that this is very much on
brand for it is it is no doubt what
people like most about him okay thank
you sir
okay I trust you have you heard about
the Lizard King at all like you gotten
any letters or stuff I know what's up
with that guy because I thought it was
it was dinar of the Blitzen but I mean
tip to me he's the Lizard King I don't
know I'm very busy right now
I respect you hiss are the Lizard King
died I a part in him
Cupid answer turn dumb grass you find
yourself at the top of a stunt of a
stair spiraling down into darkness great
so this again this again um so I'm gonna
take my turn to communicate with cuz
apparently that's something I can do
and so I say no I don't think so much
but I go to him and I am I touch him his
was very okay with touch acute there's
now um it goes and goes what is it well
the yeah I sell the guy onward into the
basement it's not this is the Black Gate
I see it I see it through his eyes
there's so many of them I'm trying to
angle him so that all of the eyes are
pointed but he's got some of the back so
it doesn't work i I need to go down
there you see the gate from before from
the Crypt
yes in this lighthouse yes and at this
point um so wanting to believe get the
rest but maybe just being like are you
sure sure we didn't bonk our heads and
we were doing why she's like okay do you
want me to go with you that's that is
your choice things that you're like
making like dramatic that there's
probably nothing in the basement right
yeah she's like she's like okay well we
can't we can go check the basement
looking we'd really got it it's got a
outside well like you had believed like
as a character you'd think that we just
won't let think that there is given that
this thing is a big creature that there
would be potentially something to chop
up down there I don't maybe maybe yeah I
mean maybe there's something down there
it's not like you go down in the
basement by yourself yeah okay um but no
the idea that the Black Gate itself
would be under this wibbly-wobbly white
house okay I guess I'll do that on my
channel yeah yeah yeah um but so she'll
be like she's like I'm sure it's nothing
let's just do this real fast yes yes
that makes sense
well he can't a male earth yeah okay yes
wait what do you see that do you see a
symbol down there no what no we are the
symbols yeah I know
I love this she's like wow I know we
shared a really special moment in the
forest we were we were we were chosen to
be to be vessels for them yes and and
and you seek her still yes and I seek
something as well yeah I know that when
I crossed through the Black Gate I will
find it maybe you'll also find what
you're looking for
where symbol was was in the crib before
that's where I first saw it never fresh
me too
I'm wearing a new necklace indeed that
ice transformed as silver was the herb
was one of them the symbol of Mahlon
yeah yeah indeed the other one was I was
a bona fide the right word the right
word sigil of Obama right yeah so I do
have the newest sigil on me are they
reacting at all yeah at this distance so
they are they not yet know
not yet he says oh my goes ok let's go
let's go see joint head down yeah sure I
mean I mean given that we're all nicely
bunched up initiative should we just
treat it as yeah we only get initiative
fate right it goes yeah exactly like it
literally goes walnut Locati tooth
wrists like this is pretty auspicious
yeah it's like plump firmed no so so you
you steel yourself against the side of
the wall it is pitch pitch pitch black
we got specialized exactly exactly you
can see the shapes but it's all it's all
grays and you you would get like said
the awesome it isn't like just being
able to like see a cool thing but you
can see you can see this game sucks you
can see symbols that you recognize oh
around in you in concert with other
symbols that don't seem to parse and
seem to change every time you look at
them how does walnut feel about the
symbol of male if now well now it's just
like it's a sad thing she does it she's
not reacting viscerally to it any no no
no no no no we're saying it or talking
about it is that like that was that was
there was a faded experience yeah yeah
okay just checking
I see how upon seeing this she's like
grab scriptor Sisk looking like pulls
him down faster just leads him down yeah
like oh mom I saw candy butter and we
gotta go yeah yeah explore exactly
exactly uh Locati
is the it was already down there right
and you can you can sort of hear the you
can hear just sort of the glass that
makes up his body sort of squeaking
against the stone floor in the cracks
thanks his his tail is anyway his tail
has the you on T dagger raised in
defiance at this what must be perceived
as a kind of earth
Rhett yeah not that her but no but the
ER is one of the symbols on this Kate oh
yeah
does huh I'm trying to figure out how
the Gotti as a I suppose like a remnant
of the god of mouths like of that
tentacular spectacular right
what would he perceive like how would he
feel toward any given symbol it's like
this it's like um my understanding could
be wrong but I think this is correct
so when snakes hatch the biggest concern
is actually that their father will
devour them and so he is looking at this
as though it is a larger in aggregate a
larger version it's me from Assassin's
Creed some YouTube sir I'm just waiting
for my turn
you're not to let's go look up with
Daddy God but any case it's basically
like a larger like out more astute more
dangerous it's treating it as though
it's a creature so he's looking at the
down the mouth of a of a mouth snake god
yes yes yeah yeah okay he would probably
want to surge forward let me say that
he'll he'll he'll wriggle up there he's
had bravery that he's got and I'll
actually take it trying to take a lash
with that dagger at the at the lip of
the of the gate nice yeah nice nice he's
just rated chip away yeah he's like yeah
you want this yeah
this antique it is completely inert
either there's no hint of the of the
energies that you saw mmm unleashed full
unleashed yeah
well just I would describe these
energies as a leashed
at least okay in credit well come back
leash to own solid rates but yes that is
what our young serpent sees yeah that's
it I mean I was gonna say that's
probably good enough for him like he and
I'm he's bearing the way for you to
semester yeah he senses I'm coming
so I mean I suppose an attack as an
action but yeah otherwise he's not
solely know cuz first route stumbling
down are we now at the the you are
indeed indeed I know you stand before it
how far it seems if just a few feet
before maybe five feet it's right at the
base it's right at the base yeah but do
you see it ask woman unbelievably yes
it's here we're supposed to be here
well I kept like kind of closer to it
like is it like is this like s somehow
she somehow he's been like run into your
insanity yeah exactly
Jesus I can't believe that it was just
like it's like when you see someone out
of context a so you get like a co-worker
yeah Airport randomly she's like okay
what do you think what tell me you feel
that same tug that same resistance but
there's something about the lattice
structure of the new focus that keeps it
from being as manipulable by these
forces about no it's nothing like that
is it is able to sort of like distribute
that that pull through itself mmm okay I
am going to I'm in return my site to
myself yeah once more as as that seems
to be a good idea now the question is
like legaia is through his vision like
how does my what I see now differ from
his I'm now able to see well uh any any
thing lighten up no no his vision is
actually much clearer than yours
it hits everything is in everything is
in relief what's almost hypercolor
mmm the the depth of the the depth of
the violets and the purples you can get
a sense that somewhere inside the stone
lights like that live but not like not
like Locati the further gaudiya it's
obvious I look to walnut as if I'm
expecting that you would stop me it's
like did like not even psychotic just
like did we did we make this appear why
is this here and that she looks she
looks that I mean she's just like is it
she says just factually this isn't here
for us why don't we appear and she like
kind of cast like a faithful look up the
stairs like mom's gonna be so mad I just
see it I went down to the black aid and
she looks it cthis and she goes what if
we just think she looks like very sirs
what if we just touch it hmm because my
immediate impulse is get this thing off
stick it in there open this gate up tell
tell her that okay um
no it's like three the gate three
schedules I have three owls I can open
it do you think that yeah yes I'm like
I'm listening that's just like do you
think that do you think that she could
be through here email symbols right here
I think that I think that me more then
her is through there I think that
everything is through there
we have to look we do we uh
I hold the do you hold it together yeah
is that it is that something uh cuz I'm
treating it like back out at any time
this is my thing I gotcha
so I am approaching it yeah and then
almonds gonna put a hand on the mouth
one like just kind of like setting a
good intention for this and just being
like okay yep okay right you can see in
the center of it whereas what happened
in the wandering crypt before a single
symbol lit up and then the absence like
the voids created this cascading effect
mm-hmm in that structure that caused the
acid to rise now you see three symbols
appear inside the center ring of this
gate you see the symbol of the you you
don't know what it represents but you
know it represents some kind of power
you see the symbol of male ahthe lover
goddess of Maliki and you see the symbol
of the earth which has been your
fascination from the first moment yeah
these three spin in place open up and
then the entire gate disappears and
reaching out from this infinite star
field expanse scavenging claws of
amethyst reach out and draw you inside
now Rosi bestow ah it's your turn
Oh hold on I got a lot of notes to take
oh we're dead hmm alright where's the
Basinger no let me let me give you let
me give you I notice a very emotionally
wrenching scenario let me let me tell
you what is happy
let me tell you what is happening to a
rosy bee stinger okay rosy bee stinger
is on the deck of a ship yeah with her
son Grievous yeah she is there with
dinar Blitzen yeah
on the beach out here on the rocky coast
you can see Cupid
so through through the doorway there are
three fleshy tentacles reaching up from
beneath this rock structure okay
reaching out to sees the merry widow in
a dark embrace and there are five would
appear to be rotting versions of the of
the creature you saw in the locket just
bulbous distended versions of that of
that lure that I had used to bring the
party to this island okay try a combo
with you but I think that enemies get
yeah yes unfortunately how bare these
tentacles in terms of their like
diameter earth yeah yeah they're very
thick trunks yeah
there's thick trunks it isn't like an
octopus's tentacle it doesn't have like
suck ease on one side okay they're more
smooth all around except for the vicious
Barb's vascular no any veins no I'm just
asking
sometimes it is a fear of the mind I'm
just trying to paint a mental picture
here with the light front everyone you
crawled into the gates and the balls
where I want to be what what to me okay
so these rotten peach girls yeah are
they've been falling apart
at are the merest touch so I think I'm
more concerned about the danger of these
tentacles you shook it just shook out
you know yeah a supply right then I feel
like you could probably handle that they
weren't doing much damage and pick go
down with one slice yeah um they hurt
when they kick you yeah I mean I hurt it
hurt there's a lot of chips I got no
it's a lot I think I got kicked what can
I do
what's hard is it
it's a mid day excellent one o'clock in
the afternoon and these time 23 nice
weather situation misty yeah exactly
okay wind out of the something okay
obviously that's interesting yeah so
midday technicals are surging out of the
water you need from underneath it
appears that a rock structure so I
assume that they are casting shadows on
the water Oh indeed all right I'm gonna
use some very American and indeed on the
deck okay um I don't I have no idea I've
never used grandma Mansi or something
like this yes so this is a bit of
desperation to try to save our sweet
little boat which I don't think is
possible at this point and I don't know
I have that I am going to use grandma
Mansi to attempt to describe it describe
I put it in my mind
Rosie hops up on the prow of the ship
boat word boat nose thank you thank you
so much
chef's up on the boat nose and she is
going to use guru Nancy to the best of
our ability to control the shadows of
the tentacles that are being cast on the
water ends indeed upon the boat itself
to try to tie the shadows around the
tentacles and drag them back toward the
lighthouse and it it is a it is a beast
of a thing for her to try with this
power that has never been used to this
scale before so that is in credit so as
you reach as you reach out what do you
what what memory are you tapping into
what Grandma memory is it is it is it
something like um is it something like
folding bread and a knot oh god no like
what are we talking about oh you mean
for that for the action yeah it's taking
oh I see I see okay yeah what experience
are you drawing on it's like folding a
boolean or not absolutely folding a
person into a human not yeah you know
actually making uh making something like
a croissant some kind of folded pastry
that has like you roll it you mush the
butter in you roll it again you must the
butter in that's what she's trying to do
is make tentacle crisps on okay good
yeah pigs in a blanket
so yeah in the mist it's even more
strange and eldritch looking but the
equal and opposite versions of these
tentacles peel away from the ocean peel
away from the deck of the ship and then
begin to war with the solid physical
versions and they begin to braid so two
of them begin to braid themselves and in
their efforts to to escape this force
these shredding barbs just begin to
abrade each other so two of them have
actually pulled away ship hands are
backing away from these thrashing
tentacles as much as they can but these
these two tentacles are here it's one
here at the ship ass the two of the two
in the front are actually in the process
of liquefying themselves and then it's
is shrieking and drawing it back into
the soul water wonderful that's the
sea team Cupid you see do you
see these tentacles out there reaching
and trying to triumph as I say trying to
make the Merry Widow something like the
rest of the shells of the boats
it's adorned itself from the Shadow
Realm do I consider those things like
that's a home that's a real one
it's like it's like smelling a fresh
baked loaf of bread ah no human no no no
and you know you know that you know that
the shadow realm is perceived in such a
way you've heard this from us our mm-hmm
the shadow realm is perceived in this
place as a place of treachery it's as a
false place and you see why because I
was staring you see was totally badass
and wicked scary yeah do you see why
they might think that when it's not the
base when it isn't the Assumption when
it's simply simply a tool to be
manipulated one more thing when Rosie
got one more red thing one more I just
know it's not super rad it's just uh
Danny ran when she's watching this she
is impressed that it works first of all
and that it appears to work very well
and then as soon as it pulls the
shrieking pulls the tentacles back away
from the boat she she goes your fin from
the crow's nest from the boat hat yep
okay she says I want to know how not
right now we don't have to discuss it
now but I want you to tell me yeah about
that seems handy I look up I go thank
you all right so what a what a delicious
turn rosy bee stinger now you have not
used your move action why would I need
to UM I will perhaps I can use my move
to get into a position where they might
draw their attacks from you mm-hmm your
big boy you probably handle it yeah take
my move to UM to approach them from
behind and hope to try to get an
advantage of a flank scenario smooth
smooth I love it
it is now their term makers so the let's
see how many of them are there I mean
these new oils there's five five that
have currently been shaken loose yeah
from the organ huh oh
Shadow Realm no no opposite very
different there this morning pool listen
stabilized way to manage this so they
begin to so you're you circling around
the back and you're able to attract a
couple of their attentions just this
it's like this gruesome parody of the of
the sort of like sad bewilderment
but it's just it's completely shifted
around they're all nasty indeed they are
swinging swiping at you I cannot roll
for but they are but they are they
have definitely taken notice of you okay
two of them I'm swiping their little
yeah they're doing they're they're doing
their absolute best three more for you
tune our blitz in twenty twenty twenty
no no something like that it's not the
first attack AC eighteen AC eighteen
yeah I'll hit you with a second one and
I miss you with the third one so they
said they basically had just in their in
their enthusiasm hmm does he asked yeah
indeed for flesh they have basically
just made themselves into a kind of like
surging pile and they're crawling over
each other trying to get you only one
connect nine points so they're all in
one big pile that's handy I kill him are
they going on big pile oh they are very
very near to each other like in deer
they're out of the way no no it's not
like that yeah yeah can I kill one and
get them all upset
[Laughter]
yeah one do they all like the most
[Music]
Letterman's jacket on oh yeah the first
one to go to college yeah that one I
want to group them all together that's
my goal so I want to use like harvest
apples and I want to kind of put them
all I want to just be like Lu
say something clever throw him over
there pretend I said something funny I
hope he just says something there's like
nobody around and got me to here go over
there
I want to like you have two attacks yes
so two hands yes like grab - nice throw
them at one and I grab two more I throw
them at one so you just want to grab I
want to pull on a pile yeah and then I
want to go drink this thunder wave them
off the boat and I want him to go could
I want to put them over towards the
railing oh I see so you're just grabbing
heaps of them and teaching them around
and I'm trying to I'll pretend our sweet
baby NPC boy at the Miss is the fantasy
area so go ahead and give me I'm gonna
give this strength and strong light I
know I'm gonna use strength athletics
checks for these okay got it you got it
no do I directed one free chain or shoes
yeah all right so all right 16:18 Lord
15 so they're not they're not able to
they are not able to resist this is a
they're definitely overmatched in terms
of strength yeah I kissed my bicep easy
for each throw so you just grab you're
just you're just corralling them
basically there's a
there's a swing and then just like no
there's no this thing no you push them
over there and then grievous looks over
you and he says you didn't like it when
I cast it last time I didn't but you're
growing on me kid I smacked him on the
butt the game dream is a singer you cast
that spell right now fine fine
he places his hands together don't you
hit that missing mass yeah whatever it
is as a word right mizzenmast oh yeah
this is nice I think is a coyote no I
think I'll in become Looney Tunes yeah
hit that wily coyote nitroglycerin so he
he he put says he looks over you with a
smirk then puts his hand without even
like looking at the targets he just
smirks at you and this wave of Thunder
crashes on the deck the the the boards
of the deck itself sir flex and warp one
of them is knocked clean off the boat
another one is knocked into the spines
of the of the tentacle itself and it's
just sort of draped and hung there
the other two are knocked below and
there's there's one that was able to
escape this blast oh ok there's one left
there's the well what's below - exactly
- two of them are going in water exactly
yeah one of them straight off the deck -
the deeps
I can't yeah gotcha davy jones's etc mmm
now Davy Jones hope yes yeah exactly
Cupid denied what's in Oh tell me what
you do tell me what adventures you have
in a strange realm that you'll with you
you will relate to your family clutch
when you return honey
I'll have his heart write me a book be
nice change of pace I thought I saw them
talk but I had no idea so I was taking
notes the whole time just going like
what
like my leaky subscription right yeah
like there's some weird stuff here that
I just don't know about some like okay
okay okay so there's some stuff and
there's I mean there okay fine um do I
see them down there right now you do not
so they disappeared they disappeared and
I look up and they're gone and I'm like
ah and then I look out there I'm like ah
because that was cool and bicep kissing
was something that we've never done and
so that was really new Richard super
torn and I don't know which way that I
should go and then I'm like and then I
run out a to to the boat - the boat area
I run out kind of whaling and she's
gonna get rather confused they went down
to my leaky also that was amazing went
down to melee I don't know I heard my
leaky Mei went down to a thing oh she's
very overwhelmed and lady you get on
this boat what's what's around so in
order to get out to the boat there is a
tentacle I'm gonna up Rob the
tackle you just thought there's a
tentacle and there's also you know about
you know 30 or 40 feet of open water
there's like a tentacle bridge there is
a ten to one technical you managed not
to shred whoa that's a bad idea
everything about this is a bad idea I'm
gonna punch a tentacle because I'm
feeling very frustrated and they need to
get my anxiety out exactly listen you
know it's a bit sublimate you know what
I mean sounds negative impulses push
them to the tortoise productive way
bring him in reroute bring it in alright
the first one I'm going to do is I'm
gonna go in for a bite attack she might
be my put you a full time kid
all right bite attack I'm gonna now also
just dive right in this is the only
thing I know yeah it gets it gets wicked
bit I have another one should I roll
again for a hussar the battle ax Oh
but yeah like we both get a chance to
fight let's say that this is true ok so
you know but tell me about the knowing
first alright I grab with one arm around
this Gurfein shall we we've gone with
girthy exactly carefully avoiding the
Rose like thorns yes right yeah thorns
are my people yeah they're cool with it
I've got I got horns these are thorns
were similar I mean it's like cousins
III jump right in there get down and
dirty and just like kind of start just
biting just ah but my one arm is free I
like it umm and I have to do my you
might damage damage you do have to do
your damage or first and then I will
subtract it from this large number 5 + 2
7 piercing damages that's a classic so
you pop imagine a dark squid no no you
just go through the skin it's just like
it's like your teeth go and go and go in
this just pop it wasn't clear fluid
moves into your craw zone is it good
then come down no I would say no oh ok
drink it anyway
smear it down my face like work it's not
good but but huh sour knows when it's
time to get down that he has to be as
rigid as possible oh my god Jerry this
is happening yeah it's like where's Jeff
he's dead
if driving home right now has aneurysm
is it because he can he has various
states if he can beat that's time to go
to work yeah he is a weapon he's at
attention so it was his intention to be
firm it's almost like it's like a whip
you just sort of like his his his open
mouth and skull just sort of slap
against the end and you can see us you
can I action search to give him a second
chance additional action on my turn on
top of my normally allowed actions so
it's I have one per sort rest are we are
can we not well no I listen you're a
creature of the shadow there's much we
have to learn from you yes yes I'm gonna
try and kill this thing and then he's no
Christmas you're the worst
hasar is the worst I was just like this
ancient creature honey get together on
the boat I'm watching this by the way
she just buddy like weights it gnarly
she's screaming she's whipping it with
this and I turn around and are like your
daughter wrong
everything about this like obviously I
know as the dungeon master for the
c-team there's a little bit of Medicare
right but I'm always trying to reach a
new audience I feel like I feel like
actions like this interactions like this
ya know I'm telling you mistress
mistress keep it is gonna be bringing in
alright views like it still do damage oh
yeah it should hasar mean the Water
Tribe weapon bondo so I can just bring
him back together because that's true
walnut done grass it's your turn oh yeah
you have been one one hand reaches
around your left arm and then over it
begins to tug you into the biggest a tug
you into space and the moment that the
moment you try to keep yourself trying
to keep your balance another hand
reaches down to your left leg and just
Yanks you up and pulls you through
you're absolutely unable to breathe
it is ice-cold I can reach her chorus at
all on this no no you're yanked
completely out and you are but you are
told in second so this there's several
terrifying seconds of ice-cold lack of
oxygen you can feel frost starting to
form on your flesh like real space who
knows and then you find yourself drawn
up into a circular platform you are
inside of what appears to be a kind of
Cathedral you are drawn up and deposited
through it these know through Cathedral
drop through through this through an
entrance in the floor of this and then
just sort of like flung out flat in this
place it's cold but it's possible to
breathe
to live oh so and so so so you so you
for your catching your breath you're
looking around you can see getting a
quick stock of the of the area you can
see what looked like almost eight
pillars of darker purple crystal okay
that all reach up toward the sky and
then fan out almost in a kind of
writhing crown and through that crown
you can see the stars again this is the
same this is crystal look familiar does
this look the same the same make that I
saw in our shared vision tell me about
the vision the vision that we had where
Walnut was embodying they got a smiley
key and this was mail it and mail if
these amethyst shards came down yes yes
circle time so there are many purple
there are many ranges of that and from
probably from violet to richer lilac but
that particular color the it's the color
of what appeared to be the prison that
is the exact color of the of the pillars
itself that appear to support this
structure hmm
okay and do I seek your thirst anywhere
you don't see Catherine so you think
that whatever this is the but this room
is is breathing yeah through the top and
bottom of the chamber and I see the
stars do they look at all like something
I've seen you think that well here give
me a perception perception that 1:17
sometimes it was very good bad it's not
you think you don't you have no idea how
this could be possible but you think
that you think that you are looking at
the home word star from one of the
points of it
Oh what oh no I'm gonna I'm gonna call
out first for Chris and then if I don't
hear anything I start calling out for
for male ahthe mmm and I say I'm here so
as you look around you can see that
these pillars themselves have symbols on
them and you can see that this symbol
you can see the symbol of male if on one
of these and you can see something on
what you could see something a shape
stirring inside the column itself
yeah I I'm gonna I'm gonna approach it
and carefully because I understand that
I'm in this like wild and weird place um
but I want to I want to reach out and
just touch the the symbol if it's at my
level absolutely
so you reach out and as you're trying to
touch this symbol the symbol that hated
symbol of MELAS as your hand is about to
contact it you see a emaciated bone
white hand touch the symbol first and
then in a kind of fluid pushing forward
toward you you can see a face that has
been almost completely stripped of flesh
of the pallor things that hair skin and
bone are all more or less the same
unified color it is legate strand
where's ya Maga do is with Catherine
okay the first Rose turn so you find
yourself you find yourself pulled
through and you know this of you nerble
in here you know exactly what this is
you are drawn again through this same
sort of oculus in the base of this
temple but this has a completely
different shape what you saw before
was crystalline in nature it was liquid
and yet at the same time had definition
and edge the facets exactly this is a
much more sophisticated configuration of
that space hmm and so you see you see
what I described to your companion
walnut dawn grass you can see pretty
clear connections both to your new focus
the black gate like this thisa ceased to
be a metaphor this is some kind of
fundamental axiom now like what's my
vantage point like am I in the US but
you have been taken out and basically
just like pulled through and then
basically like brought through by these
claws and then essentially flung into
the space and walnut you seeketh ris
basically sliding on the floor from the
force of this and then as you stop
ligardi gets loose and flies even
further they're both wearing socks yeah
this is the funnest this is the question
if you're gonna be murdered by God get
murdered by this is the one pillar with
their own yeah so yeah I come to a stop
the guys out of my reach now I see are
we on the same platform absolutely okay
okay yeah you're both contained inside
this whatever it is it looks like a
temple this is not like it was before
the symbols yeah oh well it doesn't look
back doesn't look back again but here's
an eye goes someone's in here I look for
one with the earth on it yeah finally
absolutely oh yeah you're shopping
you're shopping for God's mm-hmm I I ask
you if you've you touched it
you did uh it's not clear if you did not
know right before it's just recovering
there and there's like this emaciated
thing and uh woman what's back um looks
back this for just a second and goes I
think she's I think she's I think we
found her um what is my focus doing
right now because what I'd love to do is
take the I want to tape it's in your
hand okay okay um I want to bring the
the maelys component over and see if
there's any reaction see if there's any
identification of the like if we can
actually speak to this yeah yeah so you
you bring it over and you show it you
show it to male ahthe who looks over to
you with something like recognition like
there's a there's a moment where that
where whatever torments is experienced
in here are replaced by kinship for a
moment then the hand comes away from
this symbol and then just starts to claw
and scratch at the inside of this and
that mouth is wide open but it is
completely silent in there and you hear
can you hear a voice that seems to
comment once from the top and bottom of
this structure it says last time you
brought me to morsels now you have
brought me one sacrifice but oh she is a
feast
yeah I look at Walnut what what's she
doing I wanna like give give mail
whatever she wants Michael she needs
this like you know trying to push the
focus towards her mm-hmm but I'm walnut
at this point
like almost cuz she can't this creature
maila it's like what she pursues you me
like it's just scratching at it right
but it's just like oh it's it's like
behind a membrane exhibit yeah it's it's
literally with behind cut glass okay so
um well at this point we'll we'll put
her hand on it as if to try and be like
we're you know trying to say like we're
trying to help you yeah at that point
like try and reach for the focus like
yeah yeah so she places her hand where
your hand is and then immediately with
the other with the other hand is just
trying to find any seam in this
construct so I say I'm now I'm
addressing the voice I say more
sacrifice more sacrifice what above I
know I mean it's not him saying yes yeah
I'm saying like oh you want more
sacrifice then to no one like what what
do you need with these sacrifices are
you a god what I this is what Keturah
says he says he says what is the
sacrifice of a worm to impose what do
you what kind of a God are you that the
death of an insignificant thing would
bring you power that you would even care
about who are you that you think you
know what is significant and what is not
I will show you something
that I learned when I devoured the earth
and you can see that walnuts hand is
against this symbol mmm and you can see
a spire of crystal fired directly
through her palm and then through her
shoulder and he says can you see now
think about everything you you're
feeling you think about everything you
know that is my food that is my meal
can't you see it that's not your meal I
am here he says he says you are my mouth
I have three laws I explained it all to
you quite clearly the universe is not
but meat and mouth even we will devour
every world and star this is my song and
you will hear it and when we are
finished I will devour you that time has
not yet come you have brought me scant
meals scanned meals and now you're
trying to deny me this one can you not
see what the sacrifice is can you saw it
can you not see its purpose and it that
voice sort of fades away and another
voice moves in and it says I'm sorry I
often forget that you are not what you
will become
you are this thing with this things
limitations says come I will let my
little mouth help you I will let my
little mouth help you see mm-hmm and
legaud arrives over and then climbs up
your leg and then out onto your arm then
he looks at you and you can see yourself
reflected in all of his eyes mm-hmm and
when he strikes you you are surprised
it's never happened yeah he strikes you
first in your left eye and then in your
right and then drops away like a leaf or
a husk and you cannot see anything for a
moment hmm and then shortly thereafter
you can see everything where is it bee
sting what yeah this keeps coming to you
and no it's like cold cold glass of
water every time that sounds good it's
good guys my turn to go back to that
please you made me you made me do this I
was gonna suggest something oh sure a in
helping her doing a fastball special oh
hell yeah totally shall we yeah okay so
well I don't what are the rules on like
waiting your I would say the interaction
would tell us there are different yeah
there are different people manipulate
this and there's a lot of house rules
and things like that if you don't want
your initiative yeah you can always take
a lower one if you want okay okay so you
think a lot of you son yeah I'll hold my
auction
watch this that's as easy as it is my
friend now with what it has done is it
has put the creature basically what
Rosie is done is granted the creature
it's turned first so some of them are
laid out flat some of them are stuck up
on this Don this tentacle this sort of
writhing and flexing as it tries to pull
the boat further into Shore you can see
that it is getting closer and closer to
being wrecked Corbin shale is is firing
pistols and then just dropping them on
the deck and firing more pistols and
they're just sort of like you can see
the shot
hitting the tentacle and just like like
a drum head you can just see us sort of
like reverberating out whatever he is
trying to do is not the effective
solution that's on these tentacles
obviously
no shadow magic very handy bare minimum
right but these these creatures are
trying to draw themselves up and take
big swings on you doing art dinar blitz
and crap all right okay
that one will hit eight points so it's
it's swinging and it's connecting with a
surprising amount of strength and then
the hand is just the hand gets caught at
the wrist between the plates of armor
and then it's content just to pull the
rest of the arm way mmm it's a trail of
your friend at really drooling out of
the wound dinar blitz in I am just
unaffected by this oh yeah it's just
like mmm yeah so there's a couple more
of these coils yeah ropes like this out
I got them to Cupid yeah I'm like we
gotta help her you have to help her I
can't help her in this culture and our
culture that I created yeah
parents aren't allowed to help their
kids rule all right so so I look at you
and I go ahead and I go do the thing we
talked about you go fastball special a
small special wait all right thank you
like this and I take running joke hop up
and yeah okay so you give me strength
I'm gonna take advantage - you shouldn't
Thank You chefs
was this her owner I don't I jumped into
his giant dragon hand and he is fast
ball to me back to the White House so
you give me
the acrobatics and you give me a flare
and I'll get to this well two to zero
that's an eighth for me you're done to
choose before probably 20 to 15 I roll
two both times
face-first in a tentacle and there's a
halfling grandmother flying say so you
so the angle as you are coming in like
headfirst yeah to this rocky crag ah
that is this thing's carapace sir you
are at exactly the wrong angle yeah like
this is the one that they test for yeah
you know what I mean like this is the
one you wear the headgear for right um I
need an acrobatics check from you okay
to see how much of this damage you can
avoid got this one perfect now you take
four so basically you're able to catch
it on the shoulder yeah and then you're
just on your feet you're like it doesn't
feel great but you're not dead and your
neck is in one contiguous column and you
feel like that's not what you like after
what happened that's a great wind yeah
wait first try all right now Rosie
beasting yeah you can see Cupid Donner
Blitzen yeah yeah engaged in some sort
of tentacle play interacting with it in
a way that is not from a purely combat
perspective a hundred percent effective
and the impression that I've gotten from
observing captain shells attacks on it
is that it is deflecting physical - it's
deflecting his it's affecting his shot
his crate his crappy shot
yeah okay and then but her bite
seems to have you can still see the
sleeping moon okay so yeah okay so I
think what I'll do then is I think I'll
do the whole suite its is the tentacle
attacking anyone right now the tentacle
is just it's sort of like imagine like a
chainsaw yeah
like it's just sort of like as it's
grant grabbing the boat then pulling it
in just that natural action of these
thorns is just doing gruesome damage to
the back of the ship okay so it's it's a
talking about got it alright it's
attacking the boat and the fact is that
the boat does not have long for this
world if it gets pulled all the way into
this sure then what I'll do is I'll do a
to my normal to attack so my flurry of
blows key point so that I can get to
Marshall attacks on it'd be the best and
I think we'll stop there because I don't
I don't think that's stunning it will do
much detail sunny strike who knows open
wound
okay that is a 21
that's very good a 17 mm-hmm so those
are my two quarter staff attack I love
it and then that's gonna be a nineteen
from my own arm strike and a 25 OC
be sure I know give you some
damage okay give me some damage and then
I want you to tell me in a true a
narrative tour-de-force
you bet you bet of course that's an
eight that's a six and then that's a
seven and that is a nine mm-hmm okay
that's good yeah so you have C so you
have done significant damage now not as
much like like you have you know how to
do this okay you hit things all the time
you know having to do it you know that
you're not getting what you would expect
damage-wise out of this but
that is Dennis not to say that you are
not having a profound effect so you have
sought out you have sought out the soft
places of this tentacle yeah and it is
now you can tell that something inside
the core of it has been damaged severely
because it's sort of story is starting
to get bulbous on two sides okay
something has been damaged in the core
of this oh nice yes yeah Indian this is
this this organ and you can tell you
it's not getting the torque it's not
getting the torn in that time you know
anymore yeah I'm steering absolutely
nice work Cupid Donner Blitzen uh-huh um
so you're seeing some cool oh do
you want me to narrative oh yes yes
please here one moment cubed yeah kind
of um put some yes or Tuesday - six -
its - six minutes I am going to look
down at you I think your mouth is full
of tentacle at the moment I don't think
I'm gonna be seeing any all right I'm
just checking on her she seems alright
um so what I'm gonna do is first quarter
staff attack will be right at the base
at the tentacle where I am that's a very
tender location yeah yeah and I know it
doesn't like that and then for my second
one I'm going to do a ranged attack oh
nice yeah
BAM at the try to aim for the part
that's attached to the boat yeah in the
hopes of shaking it free and as I run to
retrieve my quarter staff I'm running up
the tentacle and smashing it with my
feet from the Marshall attacks I'm going
BAM
like I said as hard as I can with my
little feet and then Statue my core
staff back out of there exactly so you
so you so you are they're just sort of
like against the misty sky yeah you can
see every everywhere this staff is going
you're just cutting through this mist
and creating clear space yes finally
after the final two stomps is just this
burst you can see the blue sky in park
behind you keep in tune our blitz in
welcome to the table
tell us how are you gonna create an
incredible story for the kids back home
I don't know anymore
is getting harder harder I disconnect
from the tentacle yeah feeling that it
has been knowing thoroughly aware that
it has been grievously injured you know
it's good very good weird look
yeah it's like it's I think I did all of
that so it's like man it is so good I'm
the best at this good job oh sorry and
I'm gonna come in again and get my fight
line I'm gonna go yeah we're gonna do a
bite bite back you're like I'm doing so
good is 15 it is good okay and it is a
seven again all right feast yeah
so I I get in that and this time when I
retract my head I spit some of the iCore
into like a little vial and keep it okay
you catch it like on it now I'm like I'm
giving some condolence yeah pep talk to
toughest are it happens to a lot of
swords okay let's see what happens
oh council may our Labor's please
you your servant Cupid Donner Blitzen
has offered unto you a boon did it what
you say - yeah you roll - so how
are you able to how are you able to
encourage this bizarre acts that you
have brought from the Shadow Realm I am
horrified that I have to like wordsmith
critical okay
this is your this is your brand and you
know it okay yeah but I so as I get back
and I get the iCore I you know like a
little bit of a thing extra um and I
kind of bring him out and I go really is
that the best that you can do because
and then I just let him be angry at me
it's like the lady
he's scandalized I saw somebody wearing
that shirt plus once and then will your
attack great where's my d8 let's see oh
that's that's one so I roll it twice yes
image and an eight so Wendy eight plus
two so I would add four at the end no no
just the Plus that goes ones okay yeah
so that's a seven eight nine numbers
good job house are yeah good job Bobby
so he says young Lee I say and then
three then it goes straight through the
tentacle like it cuts half and then
there's just this like stretching and
snapping of the tentacle and then you
can see a good go transparent for a
second before it snaps completely and
I'm just like seeing was that so hard
was that too much it's making a face
that's making me like and so you see you
you see it like wrap immediately around
the entire ship like something is
something about now that it is free
mmm-hmm it is just like it is tightened
up around around the back of the ship
has just begin to vibrate by move action
is backing away slowly time again
nothing
are those by you is sort of like that
slurps down below but the part around
the ship has just begin to become
agitated spit on it it's literally just
like that's full of the iCard you'll
need this yeah Oh walnut on grass to get
that so let me let me let me take us
back into not that so touching the
pillar that has what I perceive to be
may Lilith in it and do I hear the voice
talk to Chris from before it doesn't
sound like a voice oh no but he's what
he sounds like a trumpet
don't put it just it sounds like it just
sounds like tones huh it's like it makes
like a whit like a wind chime underwater
[Music]
he when he responds to it it's the same
tones oh my god and so I also like um I
turn to take a thrist to look at that
that's amazing and then at that point
that goes straight through your palm and
then also through your shoulder and then
farther back damage is it does that give
me okay I got it okay fear not I just
want to know if you wanted to tell me so
excited now oh yeah so I took some
damage before yeah yeah so you're good
what are you at now seventy your
difference at seventeen you're at 70 now
yeah okay okay dang it that's that's 39
that's right you guys split the party
you get in this tackle hole goes through
like it's push it pushes through and
then you feel like it is just stretching
against this you see it here into the
skin raises like this and then it gets
pierced through and then goes back but
there's something else happening like
there's you can sense just that your
wisdom is granting you this it is doing
something that is not it is damaging
something that is not your mundane body
so I'm not feel like physical no you are
feeling physical agony
in addition to that I'm being like
dreams what no no no no you can feel
yourself being partitioned so you can
hit in your mind it's like it's like
ever
have you ever done something at have you
ever done something in a social
situation that you regretted later
sorry that's don't rap just don't know
what you say possible yes imagine that
imagine every partys regrets happening
at the same time did all these warring
versions of yourself every decision is
all Ben it's all being pushed and
partitioned out and as you and you're
basically like hanging off of this this
like Dowell right through your shoulder
and then as you look around you can see
yourself oh and then there's more of
them appearing all the time okay do they
look fine do they don't like me no no in
fact when they look at you they look at
you with the same terror Oh what do you
do so see you so some of them are here
and they're drawing therefore mother oh
and they are starting to fight each
other
oh no I want to dragons maybe you can do
whatever you want no no so I want to
first time look at Mela and tell me what
is she she still she has ceased to
suffer for herself
I was now suffering on your behalf ah
okay great
but there is as you look at her face in
this column yeah you can see a white
pinprick a light reflected over her face
oh okay um wait pinprick of light
reflects to her face do I see like a
break in the scene anyway you don't see
a break in the scene but it is a
reflection oh I think of something
behind you I say um yeah
yeah I mean I miss what survey all of
these versions of myself and it's bedlam
and then and I look at yeah see over my
shoulder to see yes absolutely
it's a longer you look at it so larger
it becomes oh dear okay
like a magic eye puzzle yeah the dolphin
gaze into it yeah
so I I mean what I look for okay so I
look at this and I'm thinking does he do
I still see him yeah I'm wondering if he
still sees sometimes you know you and
you look at cthe wrist you see all down
his face you see blood ah and so I think
you see Lagasse on the ground like
twisting just against anything you see
that the dagger just sort of like
scratching and scraping along the ground
like ligaw Diaz and it's some kind of
intense throws mm-hmm I try to because
this is faces oddly calm okay
in this moment okay so I'm feeling
extremely hopeless and I looking around
I don't know what to do and I seeing him
like feeling that unknowable dread like
is this am I am I going am I gonna lose
before I get to do what I thought I was
here to and I'm going to touch with my
other hand the help of for mother and
when I do that I believe I can start
turning into a tree you can't okay
so I would like to begin to
transformation into a my tree form what
tree form is it it is the nemecio Trant
form which is big and I'm assuming
you'll describe it to me in that it's
gorgeous in some way
but it is large and it is a siege
monster which means that it would deal
double damage to objects and structures
this starts happening and I don't know
if I break the crystal or if it comes
with me but immediately it's like start
transforming and it's like raising me up
and I'm getting bigger bigger and then
finally as soon as I feel my hand like
become that form I want to just like
crack it down on the thing holding
exactly so you reach back you reach back
to the hilt of the pommel of four mother
and it says precious daughter even in
this place she is here and as you grow
this the the spire of crystal just
becomes thinner and thinner and more
brittle and ultimately irrelevant it is
just completely shattered right and your
body discards it like the useless thing
it is shadow council may our labors
please you that is the first half of our
show
obviously subscribers are about to see
some cool see team stuff and not adds
something to consider of course of
course it being subbed ember
subscriptions are half-off semper airy
yeah indeed yes I'm willing to put some
in front of any month some a but it
won't matter in the other one it won't
matter in the other months only matters
this month any case thank you so much
for hanging out with us we'll be back in
a second hello welcome back to the C
team a lots going on right now when last
we saw our heroes camp at dinar Blitzen
Donner Blitzen the patriarch of her
shadow clan and rosy bee stinger we're
kicking ass and some crazy tentacles and
some rotten kids ladies yeah it was
really she it was real weird um while
that is going on cthe wrist drought has
perhaps unwisely entered into the very
heart of his patrons power a mysterious
place subscribed exactly he said yeah
exactly though out you know in a cold
mysterious venue very near the home word
star a a constellation of some power for
the bee stinger clamp the very last
thing that happened was that walnut on
grass cracked out the NEMA's ear tree
form a form that she got from a sword
named for mother that she claimed in the
occur sand city of NEMA's ear it is her
birthright and I'm very excited to see
it finally make its way into the game
the next turn is legate
I want to talk to him right now yeah
exactly you can hear him you can hear
him scraping in what sounds like agony
against the ground do I do I still feel
a connection to him absolutely yeah he
is he is still your familiar but there
was a moment where that connection was
suppressed yeah because they're seated
upon Carthoris trout you now see before
you your friend won't my walnut on grass
what's going on in these orbits do you
had anything in there what you see is
when you go on that Don grass frozen
held in a specific physical
configuration hmm and you can see that
up from her you see what walnut dong
grass represents which is the endpoint
of a immense causal chain and you see
that causal chain rise up like the trunk
of a tree and then explode in limbs and
leaves and then you see what looks like
imagine the imagine the long fingers of
a black widow spider
you can hear the voice say now this is
what the sacrifice is anything I consume
I know absolutely when I consumed the ER
it was this way the ER was the first of
my feasts when I consumed male if it was
this way says now look what can be done
with this knowledge and you see these
long fingers reaching into this immense
nest of causation and just pluck threads
hmm say look here here is her mother
here is her father look how easily it
would be you can see several fingers
sort of connect around her father he
says this is s'lethkk ripped garden this
is but there's no reason but it need me
suddenly the crypt garden look how
easily I can insinuate my follower
Mendes veil and you see the fingers
reach in and just shred that outcome and
you see it spin together from amethyst
threads an image of mendes veil in that
causation but this is this is something
that he says this is a delicious irony
look at this look at this as a meal in
itself but this is the thing you have
seen this iconography before you know
you have you saw it in red larch when
what I've seen it moments before you
emerged from the alley your powers at
that time your research mm-hmm there was
a period of time where you thought
you could do this to yourself you
imagined that you could seek and explore
through your own chain of causation and
there was a moment where trying to
maintain this iconography in your mind
was too great and it snapped in half
from the moment you tried to contact
another plane for answers to a mundane
question mm-hmm an idiotic question why
mortals die that's not a surprising fact
right yeah you had been yet you had
gotten the attention of something and it
had followed you to that place and it is
offering this to you now it says I know
how to do what you attempted to do this
is the exchange this is the other this
is the offer this is what I had agreed
to become this thing's or to make this
thing my patron God and you can see sort
of rustling out of these leaves and
trees you can see these other versions
these other potentialities of walnut'
dong grass mm-hmm
falling out in great heaps wailing with
confusion and terror as they look upon
their own countenance and a growing sea
of identities I so this is what I
perceive in my eyeless 4/1 yeah my
mortal form that's correct
they're normal things that columns and
everything like that those are those are
dim they represent something in this
site but the main thing you see is this
potentiality this causality am i aware
of
am i aware of wallet in the room or am i
consumed by just this well you know that
you know that she exists at the bottom
of this chain of causality you know what
she represents and where she is in this
space right this is where this is where
I want to go with it so let me stumble
through this role play and see if I can
get there the this I want to say to the
little mouths everything everything that
you've shown me I can conceive of
structurally it's a question of scale
and it's a question of being able to
hold it all but I understand it and I
know that when I look into the face of
my god the true God
beneath all of them that I won't be able
to I'm looking for a truth beyond that
of scale you consume other gods you
consume stars but it's still eating even
a mouse is just meat than you and if you
are if it can sense how I feel I fixed
I'm this is what I do every night in my
trance I fix in the air in my mind and I
and I whatever thing is is is giving me
this power that I assume comes with
knowledge I look for that connection
again and so right now my mind is filled
with it and I'm I'm disappointed and
angry that
it's no better than wonderful when I saw
that the the other gods are Petty and
they love and they hate when I get
jealous and they demand worship from the
ants right and I think no it has to be
beyond that we have to be beyond that
that's the truth that I seek and this is
a this is all the same this is these
these are theatrics yeah okay so you you
can sense the something you can sense
something growing like a presence
manifesting itself behind you in this
space so you're talking to a little
mouth this is women kneeled down and
said this Stila gotti this is what I'm
saying yeah
that is incredible so yeah behind you
you can see from the earth you can it is
expressing concepts to you broad
concepts mm-hmm vast concepts the
concepts that the concepts that these
other ideas are for the substrate up to
and including a system and a mechanism
for extra cating itself from this
structure and then as soon as as soon as
it has begun to formulate this idea it
gets closed back in again into its
column it is now the turn of the
tentacle which is now shredding the boat
on the back it is grinding away they're
very railings the rudder on the back
just in its death throes around the back
of ale exactly exactly you can see from
the from the
rocky shore you can see fin has climbed
down the that has climbed down from the
boat hat and has is using a variety of
tools to swiftly sort of like strip
she's making tiny slices and then she is
like tugging at certain parts and she's
like peeling it like a banana she's made
a few choice cuts and then she's tugged
it and she's attached that flesh to a
weight and thrown it overboard so it is
just pulling and stripping it all the
way around on this back so now this is
there's this inner layer that without
the assistance of this external sausage
case is not able to perform its function
dinar blitz in are there any more of the
Goyal's or we have to clear them out are
they no there's there was one more that
was attached to this right here but the
the immediate threat from enemies is
gone right now the threat is that this
boat is listing dangerously close to
this yeah Rob so we have to get the
tentacle off the boat I think tentacle
is mostly dealt with right now it's just
about trying to get well I thought I was
listen to reading that just like the
weight of a tentacle is doing us all
right so I think we're drifting we're
about to like crash into the island okay
I don't know nothing about no boats no
boy everything that's true he would be
the best someone has to ask him you know
what you're doing and then I'm like yeah
of course we're gonna do this yeah what
I'm doing yeah that's my tower I can
bend space-time to just back up whatever
I say there are there are perhaps thirty
deckhands yeah that are just running
around the deck Corbin has lost
everything
roars Corbin yeah we've been saying to
do he has lost control all right
of the boat okay so we're doomed yeah
abandon ship for a dinghy everyone seems
to have some independent individual idea
about what to accomplish on this boat Oh
know what to do i legit don't know what
to do
you can ask Rosie yeah Rosie what should
I do grandmother what should we do
all right I love it that's good
I said yeah you know what I'm gonna
delay my turn back all right I mutter
something under my breath about
landlubbers and I jump up on the same
railing that I was on before at the boat
face and then I yell a commanding boat
thing that someone who knows about boats
might be able to help me vas
avast ye swabbies it's nice
yeah well short turn yeah I get get the
get the south winds anchored in those
those masts you your arms and yeah turn
us turn us starboard but post Department
quick more about your platform oh no I
have command and I have intimidation I
do information yeah totally cuz I
Rosie's not performing this is real yeah
yeah Kate's performing coz she's garbage
she's a filth lady that she coughs I
know you know did the shadow Council has
offered you advent yeah that's do it
yeah yeah nine I got a food do some work
on this it's a nine it's a nine and I do
know about boats so a lot of the words I
said but wearing words I don't know
about both sorry Rosie knows about both
you rate you're able to snare two or
three of them how 30 yeah see
you're able to stare two or three of
them they're just like you're like
they're like starboard okay definitely
both stuff exactly you think you think
that you think that Corbin is not suited
to sea monster battles mm you you feel
like this you feel like I mean that you
might be tempted to be mad but at the
same time this is definitely a unique
challenge this is not an Immanuel sir
you mean this is adaptability excuse me
or what any qualities that a good sea
captain has have anyway exactly so so
two or two or three of two or three of
them have taken a couple deep breaths
yep they are they are pulling ropes in
the way that they should pull them great
and not in the bad way 24 you know like
24/7 horrified by this moisture dinar do
you have any way yeah so to inspire I
will men and women I will try to repeat
what Rosie had said but louder louder
yes with your kana continue I like it
now
do we need to go use a toothbrush or are
you ads oh yeah it's a pencil
all right now dinar blitz in of the
noble house blitz in yes of janar yeah
how do you encourage these lesser beings
so I will have to give impart upon them
some measure of your chronic strength do
you say hey go freaking out hey maybe if
you if you work hard maybe the closest
why I put my arm I say champ everything
all right everything good first I say
everybody come there's a few stuff you
stop tugging ropes in opposite
directions you can see that if you're
the top a couple of them are pulling the
same rope look at the rope and they look
at each other and they look at you and I
say and I go I go what's wrong what's
wrong a little guy you want to go home
is that what you want I start marking
out boat words now you have to try
missing mass I say that missing mass
just over and over
all my side yeah that's the thing and
they make you the new cat and now I'm
gonna do captain and I say stuff I just
repeat what Rosie said trying to get
everything ready I don't even know I
remember the bow starboard yeah I make
one hand walking plank you begin
speaking yes well you see Finn plug your
ears it is just instinctively
immediately mmm just fingers in ears
interesting time to learn and so you
basically what happens is that there is
a point on this deck like that like um
the blast radius like you get one person
on your side and then it spreads almost
like a virus like this interviewed
confidence just jumps from person to
person like a sexually transmitted
infection yeah confidence herpes yeah
okay basically it's a it's a good name
in high school it's a it's a good
version what you do is you confer upon
them a good version of herpes like a
version that they want a regular herpes
Thank You Haley we're gonna do this
right all right
anyway so that is what happens and
immediately is it begins to jump
not unlike herpes for me I hope not
there's a lot I don't know about herpes
so you mean immediately they begin to
tug in earnest um like a Robin you know
at the mornings first earthworm these
ropes are getting tugged over the
shoulder a lot of strength a lot of
leverage that way and they are able to
act in a manner that communicates the
boat in such a way that it is able to be
able to move just out of the edge a few
minor dings and scratches insurance I
mean it's a rental
what's a boat without a few dings it's
it's not a big deal um
kourin shale has come to his senses he
is wheeling the boat left and but there
are still he would he would open up all
the cannons on this island if everybody
were out of it
Cupid Donner Blitzen I'm not even on the
boat yeah I know I'm just standing on
the shore going like nicely done Oh No
and I have waited a long time to have
still no idea what the hell to do um I
think I'm just gonna roll with this she
was fast here at this 18 yeah I I think
she is going to throw hasar woo at the
at the at the tentacle tentacle still
mommy right well on the boat itself yeah
it is but it is just it's sort of
wobbling and gelatinous now you don't
you you think that is long for this
earth alright there's a sort of sad
tentacle here on the on the baby looking
for the rest of it yeah - oh man - get
to the other side of said tentacle yeah
because I'm clearly closer to what would
be the brain slash heart slash whatever
it has a caramel core like a hundred
grand
I collect more of it
put somewhere in there the solution I'm
sure should I it's all for the diary
should I ain't investigate yeah you want
to end you wanna investigate what lets
you investigate this thingy yes whatever
no damn team plus 518 that's very good
and the very poor of this tentacle is a
is a dark purple fluid that diamond have
you ever seen like when like after honey
has been heated up and then it starts to
get very sort of crystal and grand it's
like as soon as this stuff is flowing
out it's beginning to harden and then
form crystal bunches on interesting on
the stone shadowy no shadow it it feels
there it has a familiar tone to you okay
so hmm
so I get some of that stuff do um no
well I'm not gonna eat it don't fight it
don't you usually use my plate listen
you have a problem right fighting biting
is not a solution sometimes it is
sometimes everybody will take care of if
all you have is a ma every problem let's
get tentacle you know I'm gonna I'm
gonna get this are all up in that beast
actually wait wait wait oh yeah I'm
going to use which bolts more about
these bullets which bitch bolt uh it is
range of 30 feet a beam of crackling
blue energy that's is out towards a
creature within range forming a
sustained arc of lightning between you
and the target so a ranged spell attack
against the creature we prefer create a
creep reaches the key and it's worked
where's my where's my magic do I have a
magic thing i dude I'd yours
that's a different is it
just plus wisdom here you roll sorry I
don't seem to have anything for that 11
plug maybe like one no it's a little bit
width no it is a massive tentacle with
with the pluses that I think an enormous
level okay yeah yeah I think I think
that you're okay so mean absolutely so
tell me more about this which pull
alright it does a 1d 12 lightning damage
obviously and I it's a consist of stone
so I sustained it and it'll keep doing
that damage so I don't have to roll
again next this is very interim you
saying burn this thing to the ground
yeah I'm gonna get right up in that
crystal hole and just like pound it so
like I am there should be like a good
like arm listen we need to vet these
guests right now she's pounding crystal
holes mean what's next looking at me
like she's proud and horrified and
that's all I've ever wanted
okay a galvanic catheter is really bad
yeah so I like this fancy like and I
shoot lightning out of my hand and I can
press it digitate and looks like Shh
like a little fireworks yeah okay b12
basically that's all I got it's gonna
roll the second one okay that's my role
before I do the disco I say absolutely
not because if it's terrible you lightly
exfoliate revealing skins freshest layer
at least this turn yeah it's a spa
treatment so this for this tentacle
inert it's like ooh no it's not a rough
day exactly you're super cool and I'm
like like doing this stuff and I think
I'm doing super good what level do you
cast it at
oh I only have a first-level yeah okay
no yeah walnut dung grass how much per
year of the Enclave panax anima
apparently you are now a tree and you
are standing amidst all these selves
failed despondent terrified angry
violent versions of yourself you stand
before a crystalline chamber that seems
to hold male a--the are and behind you
that white light has grown into a
massive orb that has pushed its way
directly into the heart of this chamber
mm-hmm and is expanding behind you with
warmth and support and affection
historically that's been h+ like these
are a few of my favorite things it
doesn't seem like that is this thing's
aesthetic it's the only way when let me
ask you a couple things one when she was
having her causalities mocked with did
she like feel that in any significant
way yeah that's the partition I was she
was experiencing I think basically well
you're just a good writer I got it
cavalcade no it's not like that if you
didn't know exactly than I feel now I
got it um but I want to make sure that
we're on this but yes we are absolutely
on the same page and then did anything
I'm assuming it just bounced off but
when she was smashing on the crystal did
that do anything was I give any purchase
with you mean in your current form as
the name is your form yeah yeah yes this
is happening you have damage for all
this stuff
oh I can do this yeah okay so a cool
thing about trees its massive I mean
there's none attack role that's work
where this is literally like if if you
were a column in front of you and also
it doesn't always the slam it's a slam
and it always does it twice
and it does exactly extra to objects
because it's a siege oh yeah yeah we're
on the same page here
let's see some damages okay great see
which one's the 10 you know this one
it's awful this one in this one okay so
it's a 2d ten plus three but I got to do
it twice so it's 40-ton when that first
one is 13 plus 3 is 16 and then the next
one is a 4 and then 9 which is 13 plus
13 is 16 again 16 16 which I know is 32
so you so you're your vows you just you
ball up these massive pummeling fists
and just unleash the strength of your
ancient order on this prison and each
hit I mean from the first hit their
cracks nice bike and fourth fret and
then you just drive your fist into that
crack and the crack gets even greater
you can see that there's there's a like
a film starting to form around the
cracks that is beginning to collect into
drips and rivulets that are starting to
flow down the front of the face of it
Godfather so that was before um that was
from before the commercial break so and
then I look down at Catherine I'm I'm
gonna do secret you seeketh ris kneeling
down and speaking in the soft voice Tula
daddy I'm gonna I'm not sure what to do
about that but you might have to deal
with him later but awesome
we can't you see some shrugs though it
seems it's oddly conversational
windchime even so one thing I want to do
is well it's it's crack it's cracking so
first I want to look down at all of
these selves that are fighting there are
only a few letters
if you left and dave they have
annihilated each other they have
absolutely they can't be with each other
does did they look the deep cut today do
they all look like as I do now like not
as a tree but like no no some have for
mother some have a for mother that is of
a different shape do I see any that
looked like me as a young child still
left no I mean you saved me that one
well then I want to I want to reached I
want to reach down and I want to take
one I want to grab one I want to
separate it and I assume it should be
one that has for mother and I want to
lift it up and separate it from the
others because I'm I'm feeling like if
there's enough I want to choose the one
that's left yeah and so she looks and
she finds the one that looks most her
like yeah and lifts it up in the air
yeah it's what is it she's struggling
mightily and cursing in elven that's
great
well I'm gonna continue to hold on to
that one for a second and then I want to
look back to this this structure with me
within it and I want to see if I can
find any purchase trying to like take
off like now that it's cracking like and
if I can take anything out if I can like
make a hole
yeah yeah well that this this orb has
actually passed through you oh I'm sorry
I thought it was like about to get us no
no no no no no you were there you were
punching on this thing all the things if
all the things that you know have
occurred okay it is fast and it is
growing I think so it's supposed to be
surprising okay so and it is now envelop
you with this warmth and you can smell
like a like rain and a forest and as it
passes through you see mail earth
like where this orb is the other thing
is not oh and it's just pushed
completely out and so you are here and
you're holding this small version of
yourself and Maliki is following along
with this orb okay and she reaches over
in places a hand on your sturdy trunk
and she says you have found her and then
can I like convey to her however however
I can just try to talk to her I'm
assuming she can hear me and I say I say
I found her
I fear at the cost of my own life I need
your help to get her out because I I
don't know if I can do it alone I said
and I'm just trying to and then and then
I was reminded I say I say like I can
take care of the rest if you can take
her from here mm-hmm right she goes over
she brushes her hand along the side of
the trunk to sew along the bark and she
goes over it kneels down over the
exhausted sobbing male ahthe who is
rendered here in this place as perfect
as her eternal self the eternal self
that you saw embodied by Catherine Ralph
and she raises her up with joy and tears
and kisses her and a black wall vivisect
the orb it actually cuts it straight in
half and draws the two draws the two of
them together or draws the two of them
apart and then you see Maliki move her
hand like this and expand the orb back
out to its full weight
and she kneels down over male ahthe and
kisses her hair and kisses her forehead
and her mouth and when that happens
something in this place is punctured and
you feel yourself drawn very near to
cthe wrists robbed and pulled back
through this central hole in the floor
and then as you are yanked out you can
see there you can see forces beyond that
which you have seen up to this point you
can see that this place has enacted
itself to war with them on us on a level
that is not a mortal level at an
existential level at a philosophical at
a folk that philosophy made real level
and as you are as you are pulled through
this you are deposited in the base of
this door but your massive frame has
crashed through the stone and structures
that support this tower so you were
actually pushed halfway up the stairs
there is just this void down in this
hole where with a gate was yeah yeah
where they did where the gate was now
you can only dimly see you have no
authentic vision at all you will need
help to get where you need to go do I
enjoy sense Locati at all yeah he's he
is here with you oh all right
[Music]
come here boy in the old ways see he's
hurt or is he is he shrugged that off
now no he's he can some he can he can
come he can be with you if you'd like it
yeah for you to get him there bring him
to me trade site with him you can I can
see that you can bring it you can bring
him up and hold him yeah um Oh bring his
head near to my violin yeah exactly
hold him up here mm-hmm
just borrow his site right to make my
way I've had around yeah right like a
miner's helmet yeah no it's like that
it's like the Kindle reading light yeah
okay exactly and then from the from the
rock outside
hasar begins to sniff through the
through his bone nostrils he needs to
sniff the air suddenly while maintaining
my special enema spell i am very curious
as to with what's going on what's going
on isn't the king yeah he's he's up
there on the boat no he's no he has
returned no yeah he's up no he hasn't
read the letter King the artifact you
seek say why I stopped but the spell
ends very anticlimax okay so what how
okay what bring him up
I've got more than enough time what is
happening this is it pick me into the
tower why just take me into the tower an
officee she goes in ancient prophecy so
you see you see you see Chris Brown face
absolutely streaked with dark blood
reaching out but the face is oddly
serene halt and he's climbing he's
climbing his way up I said halt no I
need to get up these stairs first a
second Lizard King recently no not not
recently
I was I was somewhere much more
important than that
sure whatever dude he's not here sorry
are you looking for him yes I can smell
him I know he's near I have so much to
tell you
my beloved King did I just rode the
accident am I'm
like go down on the ground hasar - are
his two halves of his head he bends at
me says my king he doesn't have full
mobility but he sort of like inches at
least one of us would we'll have what he
seeks today right and I disrobe dude you
look that best here the King you here
that's missing the Lizard King size a
sigh of relief Luther King oh you were
with me the whole time I and I will I
will be in the future I sleep a lot now
and very old weight of them think the
Cape is too hot it's too hot it's my
heavy cloak it's too hot it's high and
hussa hussar says my king my lord and
make laser King says so no you know I'm
dead again says no my king no I heard
you
oh the fire of your voices no I'm dead
oh I died again I died again
Oh dead I'll never live I can't be dead
all oh sorry
it's it maybe it will have to be enough
that you got to hear his that that sweet
melody its death worth one front of
final time Cupid
if something happens as a realization
strikes Cupid as she's looking at this
and she goes Lizard King Lizard King she
just goes up and gets it like she's this
is this is mine now
you you you reach up and you you grab
the part that is standing out the
furthest yeah that's the head and then
it just comes up
I guess friendship friends I cast
friends yes it's on dad
I'm cool with it yeah it doesn't say it
doesn't say it doesn't - one creature of
your choice that isn't hostile towards
you it doesn't do anything I did like
advantage versus charisma sure I just
want it to be my friend
yeah so friends it's just you just
whenever you pick up an object actually
I would suggest not because I when the
spelling is a creature realizes you use
magic to influence its mood and becomes
hostile Oh up to a minute okay gasps
gonna pop off in a minute head the head
the top of the jaw that the bottom can't
move much and I was like oh the death
curse so it is upon me mmm cool so are
you dead or not yes sweet and I put like
some kind of satchel and I have this is
mine now you're supposed to be dead
without talking like that we
must transfer him to a Royal bag soon
sure sure about that um yeah let's it
these things are still happening in her
mind it's just like this is the lizard
king this is the king this is this is
your king
this visit guess obviously of course
he's an uber splendens okay it's just
like crazy I'm gonna be a hero I know
what to do I'm gonna bring him home with
me I'm gonna go home and I'm gonna I'm
gonna bring him there and I said that I
that I found the Litton yes yeah we
don't
I mean we've we definitely she's still
trying to fit in are we need we need he
is he's the grandfather but this is dish
is pretty cool and it also it talks and
she's like tapping the side of her bag
what right Ned yes great and she pulls
him back up she's like good
hasar I'm gonna bring it home yes let us
both bring him home we will write a new
book yes yeah that's right books this is
great she takes him and then she looks
over it could dress the body what street
is she's not sure if he can properly see
her no but she just kind of backs away I
guess I'm very happy for you thank you
for delivering I think you're so weird
you know the pleasure is all mine is it
good she takes a little the young the
day is dispatched to this strange little
rock as the party moves out here walnut
you are down in the base of this thing
you can't get out in this form oh sure
but you can probably make a way out I
think that absolutely 100% I want to
bury this place in the sea which we are
so I'm gonna just slam my way out
exactly this is the only multi slammer
exactly so so you are you go there's no
attack role brand you can find it and it
is not attacking you so you tunnel your
way out of the guts of this and then
just beyond the stone there is a sort of
a weeping mass just beyond the the
carved parts of this body then as you're
getting out the of the door it's like
the kool-aid man but like a cool version
can I
so please grab this is a dragon so yeah
I want to push past everybody and like
you like like tunneling up the ground in
that way where it's like now they go
with it some chewing the inside up and
y'all who have not seen what's gonna
happen is um you see this like the tree
this is a resplendent like automata tree
who's like Oh leaves look like they're
on perfect moment like Sun sir no matter
where she is
it's like she is in that moment of
evening when the Sun is through the
leaves and you just see a tree growing
really fast and then you realize your
horde that it has limbs and it just
busts out yeah exactly
and there's like this flurry of leaves
and stone and all that and then after
that it all like just falls out falls
away in the way that her transformation
is and she just looks like she's in like
this pile of dried leaves your yard
remnants and bags and wigs yeah
basically and then Frank Lippe she just
she falls to her knees and then looks
like she's going facedown but this just
goes sound like this and it's just like
heaving and having him in it if she on
that deck what about no she's just
telling you guys me Eileen yeah yeah if
it takes a couple of the leaves and
things and it's just like this is this
is good I've kind of stared my way over
there definitely scared yes absolutely
you you needed to be there you did have
to be there I was missing a part of it
the gods are flawed there they're weak
and they are jealous and petty but they
have all of our other qualities too and
I think that that God was afraid I think
that
it knew there would be a day when there
was no more to consume and well it just
looks at him and she goes she goes
that's true she goes that's why I didn't
need people like us see team turned a
camera Rosie goes um she's at I should
not a new particular hurry because she's
she's still kind of think very stunned
by the tree thing so she's looking up
and looking down as she walks towards
you and then she reaches a hand out to
help you to your feet and then
well not like tries to do it herself and
she's clearly very exhausted them
courteously like it takes a hand uses it
to get up but it's like she leans over
and it's like comical how she just needs
to like she needs the support so it's
like on Rosie like yeah like Rosie's
head covered in walnut yeah yeah yeah
she's wearing that's your new equipment
yes clip it in your triceps alot
and in yeah in the style of Rosie and
walnuts relationship Rosie just goes
okay guys I don't know yeah and I said
you're sort of draped on her right yeah
yeah yeah faces are like like no friends
oh let me help share the load and I get
your ankles up so it's essentially like
a wheelbarrow but you're the wheel
because you're carrying her front like
she's draped on the wheel barrel yeah
you're the body we were like a cape yes
like I'm can I help all right
exactly you are loaded back onto the
Merry Widow the merry widow is not
completely destroyed you take say you'd
you head back to town you are unmolested
by maro this or salmon right or salmon
in this case
Cupid you think that it would not be
difficult to charter a boat from here
south along the coast to the to the gate
to the shadow realm that you used to get
here to begin with
yeah because I'm totally rich I can just
do that yeah exactly
swimming in it listen you know any mean
that work is not below you I mean it's
gonna be good for you it's gonna be good
for your memoir that's true that's gonna
be your face it's one more thing and
yeah I I decide I'm like I'm just gonna
pop out for a little bit I'm gonna go
say hi that I did meet you I will be
back though and soul you at some point
it was great seeing you yeah I totally
am this will sound wrong but you're a
reminder of one of the worst parts of
things that were happening me sending
yeah so I could do sorry guitar I've
never had that before
so all of a sudden you just go so heads
up I'm you're like fifth-generation
grandfather ah way beyond that like way
way way way way more I've been gone like
a month from when this happened so I
don't know what you're going back to yes
keep that light yeah a bit of a time
shift I don't know if they told you that
when they sent you everyone you know is
probably dead yeah yeah yeah it happens
it does but I think she just was great
seeing you
[Laughter]
well you feel you feel a hand on your
shoulder his wrists mmm and you hear
Finn's voice and she says I've got just
the thing it is of course no surprise to
you that I know precisely what to do in
a situation just like this mmm and she
takes a bandage like a bandana and then
wraps it around your eyes and then ties
it in the back and then tightened up and
then from a little bottle paints little
eyes on the front of it like black star
but she paints like the happy little
anime friendly friendly welcoming having
Corbin jo says come back after we've had
an opportunity to repair all the damage
that's occurred since you've been here
dold roma shows you with the light her
documents her level 2 bag and she's
she's like she puts up to docq buddies
and then they do a um they they get out
their quills and later practicing this
handshake when they were trying to do
this and they do a thing where they like
link arms they're both holding the
quills and then they sign like yeah like
I bet they make that like exactly yeah
it's like it's like it's a document of
mutual mutual team appreciation is
signed this day you get back to your
cart ready for your trip north to scala
there is another there is another horse
that is looking at coriander in her
locked down form with some interest
you're not sure percent how long that's
been there how long it's been going on
there's anything about
so rewarding I'm not some courting
scenario may go on shadow council may
our Labor's please you that is the end
of our game for today I want to think
Nicky Harper at cupid do not listen
don't go anywhere we're gonna sample the
facilities and then we're going to come
back for Table Talk so we'll see you
soon
you