time is the enemy the past and threatens
the fastest weapon you wouldn't make it
past a second and land the question play
it flash and records to choose a car
solution you thought was prudent in any
sepulchre polka tune will become the
future it's that well said I'm pursuing
no mountain too steep but dungeon too
deep to send expendable marks up to the
top of the peak of beneath be they come
like sharks to win while I swim in that
money bill by Carl Barks through its
suspension national parks through it
I'll send them home in a natural box the
closed top of most of the parks included
save your breath for a cleric confessor
that there's a lesson in life isn't any
profession but if you speak in my
official advice sign on the dotted line
and wrists of the twice yeah
hello I am Tycho Brahe haeth Penny
Arcade in packs I am also a minute
affair were drawn CEO of acquisitions
incorporated but today I am Jerry
Hawkins and I am running a game of
Dungeons and Dragons for my friends to
my right Dragonborn narcissist Orion
Hardman button oh you're gonna feel hard
he called you Ryan Hartman becoming real
oh yeah wait this is my Braille our
names in our Blitzen it's hard to tell
it if they've already look to their
right of my right talking giving you
break yep rubbing the natural world
walnut on grass and walnut on grass but
to my left not your grandma's grandma it
can accept for in rare cases where she
is your grandma's grandma Rosa V singer
recipe are we on global finally selling
it is it this the staff of the matter
that yeah yes the Reverend is our
grapefruit I'll tell you it the twist
the scientists to bend but that's that's
where I get a little you gotta get the
fan I could no you don't put handle on
the top and it would be easier to
process what I don't know and take
places yeah you know what I mean guys
yeah very exciting
you're the left of my left occupying a
far left position whoa
whatever work at pool emerging is though
from a mist shroud Corinth route yeah
this crowd
see there all right noise no I know what
happened last me Oh God Jesus I'd only
instigate yeah the crucible of this game
was just a detailed discussion of
different animals dicks and then that's
a substrate of this like let's see where
it goes from here I'm into it
I guess no one said anything about that
I mean all in your heads rising everyone
ages into it I'm getting on the train to
write at night
so when last we saw our heroes a strange
occurrence terrifying
specifically lock it related you may
recall Rosie be singer to that
the locket that you had won in a game of
giants and halflings with a ghost that
ghosts own skeleton and a gelatinous
cube a game that you would play inside
of a reclaimed hotel full of different
kinds of monsters we don't wait we ante
a thousand dollars here in that exact
ecstasy team you had secured to lock it
and at that time you had looked inside
and seeing a young woman there your last
experience in this locket was that it
achieved intense heat and then upon
opening it you saw the same young woman
retrieving the locket from a fire and
then showing you a view outside the
window of a coastal sea indeed what city
was it the city of skilled hands jewel
of the north
never what
was the daytime or was it night the data
now you determined you determined
because you are cartographer and a half
yeah you know exactly how to get that
way right and do that stuff profit has
come back after what was but all you
know by any standard a successful if
very exciting at one point last stones
day feast indeed the famous food critic
of Waterdeep min song and his emaciated
scribe came away with a great review it
was opposite when generally speaking you
want stars in a review like this you
came away with no strikes against you
it's awesome he said he would find a six
star to add on to this what that might
mean for the the drowning courier I
guess will remains to be seen profit
didn't seem super excited about it he
maybe didn't want it the extra ten
gentrified it but but yeah but who knows
who knows and we'll see you know a lot
of people come up and they start
checking out this stuff who knows she
might just be modest as well okay she
said she's a sophisticated character now
she's a well written exactly rich
backstory a literature L robust oh so
well plan on you have a cart oh yeah we
do and a roboticle horse clad in copper
or bronze mystically rejuvenated
but hungry for gold oh yeah and as we
had closed out the last game it sounded
like you guys were planning on feeding
it
another one of these medals that you had
won in Wizard cart without her one one
three more that's right boremont
this is a long track she's welcome to
none of us really cared for that that
round thing I mean some people are with
their current champions I mean like it
would be ashamed to separate it from the
trophy but those are Expedia that row
that's a good point
no wow let's meet at the truck hey take
a wallet yeah yeah just pay for the
trophy like I wouldn't loser bunny yeah
when will it not stop refilling right if
we didn't really just need to Bouldin
angles right yeah good question let's
find out we got we got two hours yeah
all right not well how will you contend
with the incredible challenges that lie
before the c-team we unlocked level one
upgrade of carriage house that's right
and that has increased our current speed
can you give us some details about what
that means absolutely so I sort of when
I look at the map Nermin how far how
long it takes for you to get to a place
this is just like the sort of upgrade
one might include in it in a video game
basically you'll be able to go about
one-and-a-half times just for just in
just for like the napkin math that we do
for the travel time back here
okay just fewer resources that you have
to expend on coriander brother love it
so here's where we're at
you guys can tell me what you think we
need to go north to Westbridge in order
to start our voyage we have some history
in Westbridge so we might want to steer
clear or not I don't know there's some
but maybe reek and your cold button but
I like to see what's going on there yeah
look it smooth over what happened yeah
we do have a like we've received a
statue as tribute from this person so
maybe we'll be welcomed and Westbridge
always worth checking out once we get
past there we go past West bridge to
tribe or where we have our base
your friend grellus we can check in on
see what she's up to get some snacks and
then we are going to head west and the
north of Neverwinter and then pops out
of Scala which is a place where right on
the way he could yeah I mean we may as
well we're gonna be practically there
sorry there yeah to make new that yeah
what the knock what it was eggie hatched
what if she's on there she hates that
other Dragonborn what a shades of
garbage princess she's a mean garbage
princess that's true because you can do
anything you want you decide yeah what
if she were going right well I'm freaked
out I'm going to be murdered yeah let's
you can forget everything which is go
right there oh my god where she's in
trouble
I don't even think of that we grab later
suddenly Denari ganea and says in the
Shadow Realm and about exactly I'm her
nephew brings a mess eternity eternity a
lot of any type things you know that's
right it's all going through this mind
right can i before we get on the road
can I just do like a survival check on
your lizard king vest oh yeah oh my god
what I want I'm so the cabin seeing you
card around this lake zone boy for a
while and yet you've been talking to him
a lot and he hasn't been chuckling too
much though but notice how much before
13 Wow it's hard to sum accumulative
2000 K right so you basically just want
to try to assess the living this yeah
like the live attune like between like
functional is it like wearable searching
is easy let's say that one this is as
near as you can as near as you can tell
as someone who's profession and training
you know are deeply intertwined with you
know living things or not worries as
well they are they're always living at
first so maybe they all start out living
I'm ready to go weapons free on this
just yeah yeah you think that this is
you think that this creatures torso and
bones are primarily just clothing now
for for Chris wrist route but you know
you don't think that it you don't need
whatever was clinging to it whatever
life was clinging to the lizard king has
been released
no I look at the dead body and I leave
there alive
I know your friends dead like I'm even
more doubt I know that okay I don't know
if he knows that so I'm still talking to
him don't worry about it buddy
so disturb she doesn't know she's
talking about this is like giving a kid
like captures and grasshopper and tries
to keep it alive
yeah later on right keep swirling in
ticker like my goldfish is just sleepin
yeah okay yeah I can't just playing
sweet lioness and go invisible and the
balls cleaned out and recognized and I'm
just a little upset that you're wearing
it like a dead thing but like you
haven't like can decide or like process
it yeah it's just like yeah good you
know what's going on is cloak
could be all kinds of smokes and spices
you know there are holy smell doesn't
stink yeah can you know the snot he's
pretty desiccated yeah I don't care what
he was baby was ready
mine is ready to be hauled into a
sarcophagus everything extra high I'm
riding in the cart with them yeah check
in the back with him a menagerie of
death hiding bunny it was pretty good
I'm so good so whatever find it where
did you get your leather goods from like
a store and I guess like pop them yeah I
like the idea that this was my friend
I know connections are these things that
you're wearing
wow I knew this
orange what yeah what sort of a seat
idiot now
oh I like this yes I like where you are
going with this we will cover this when
AC has required time uh yeah buddy I
think moans inside like frangible food
it's like being said by ten thousand
sharp knives reah
but then then you're the litter King
like the Santa Claus has another way to
do their sack of like this man come on
the year and we made surprisingly
violent what is the lizard sovereign
version of its enclosure now we've all
seen it I mean we're talking about stuff
we all know I joked on Twitter that
we're going to spend two hours trying to
figure out how to get in the cart and go
I think that's probably free acumen
we've documented by well well here so so
G is there any is there any other
objects you'd like to assess for oh um I
took some I took the oceans to the
potions you already know if you're a
comic connive you a little chef um
because I mean I know about I don't know
can I dress a rival check on that what I
know in Madison I got a course for
medicine no I don't think so you might
want to hand those off to your man's
over here I think take a look at it out
that corner and just hope oh I got
garbage for medicine II know what's on
medicine I have the medicine check I
need your Archon of these Oh tell me
what an adequate my slop drought I'm
going to trust I'm gonna try to small
dice you see them because I need us yeah
sure to try we have multiple decoys here
it's Arcana yeah this is what happens
this is for one dark it's in routine my
god what how did it happened twenty four
your duns going honey it's you and if
you had rolled just a little bit more
you would have served the shadow council
sir and then to confine our yeah where's
your song message identity ID one
absolutely so you think that you think
that when this potion is consumed that
the user will feel an almost like an
overwhelming urge to uh belch flame
whoa firing ok ok I have a query what
about the other one
these are both potions of fire beating
oh all right I used to do stit they're
the same identify one because you follow
all questions are exactly exactly from
there also if I wanted to change the
content to that you know like dump it
out and it would reset it back up and it
would refill two hours of what's this
one
yeah whatever issue would oh yeah
totally but there's going to be like a
little chart you guys make up and put it
by the thing it's like this color is
this
there's no headphones are they red yeah
these are they look like them a big red
type soda it's sort of fulminating thick
sweet yeah I'm not an evil I have a darn
imagine dark alphabet soup and then the
litter spell fire breath they're
floating around on question okay okay
let's get in the car maybe anyone else
got anything I think we should start
filling up jars and potions and just
leave them hanging around yeah vines
yeah
thanks a lot Mike Rahul ik wait the
opportunities for like the business
opportunities that preserve themselves
when you have a to show I guess more
about it retail yeah let's do it we give
it up inside money yeah I know what
we're going to do they offer me all
right I get as many mason jars as she's
got in the place she is a grandmother
ah there's probably going to be a jar or
two if there's anything in the jars dump
it out yes
yeah we know they don't know this
venture dump that we should probably go
get do we have enough financing all we
need or have to the rest of you sugar
water
yeah that's true it can be snake oil I
got a perfectly good snake you gonna
actually in it put the gelatine I'd quit
I rested
Rosa Parks of the cart back in the
carriage house and close with the Darwin
and just Lenny more
it's a bargain we're great I won't
settle down with our goats and our
turkey that we had it all yeah I got
their second son Jack was where we
ballistically run dreams oh let's get in
the cart because we can have a
conversation just riding all right
because we are right up our business
place do you we never left the cart yeah
there's a no-no as you as you are
getting out there you can smell the the
wart you can see that after the last
stones day profit is in there trying to
set up another barrel of the house ale
not the siren out there no no this is
she is not a fan of the of those Agron
Israel okay
some are if I recall correctly cut wrist
grab you had decanted I am trying to use
mall a few crops yeah flask I could
probably get you really fucked up pulled
on yeah yeah you think you're real
fucked up in the back got the plan was
like you were just going to like slowly
get turnt up on the ride
yeah well I aren't I'm mulling it over
yeah like it seems like time is as far
as I know is paused in that in that
realm uh-huh so yeah I'm going to feel
it out pace myself
mm-hm just explore that mushrooms is to
thank you happen exactly now so you pull
the card out classic configuration
I would assume oh yeah we want augmented
with any of our shit or are we good
augmented yeah we have like we undergo
genital lop out do we know what it all
does yeah yeah at this point okay yes
you have it all we have the animal
contestable all akatsiya crystal ball so
we know that there's displacer be some
along yeah did we tried stealth in that
last time they did not have a I weren't
into it I mean they probably grown up by
now and I have no problem telling
full-grown displace to be sure there's a
kid so why we have this
no kids until they're leavin it's a
blurry line humans but yeah I'm kind of
like I'm kind of hungry for blood so I
kind of I'd like to maybe just God
playing okay you want to the samurais
huh
yeah sure bring on the dancing later
Auto right identify the ground effects
yeah what's the oh the crystal ball is
to see everywhere right Rex yeah from
inside it is more but I fail to do it
what was the a like on owl let's see
from it and it tethers to the cart oh
that's right fly doesn't okay let's hook
that up down here let's get the owl so
we can get an aerial view of those of
those displays are you okay yeah I'm out
the owl yep I'll mount er yeah okay cool
fix to the front yeah yeah be on top but
I want to have the elbows like at the
edge secondly look down and talk to so
this is a game image yeah like crouch
for it a little bit yeah yeah a little
bit closer
well available right but it's not like
the pressure is not there ready no no no
but the availability is there and you're
aware of that a man inside of course we
have Chris drought the desiccated ass
Lizard King yes and donor placenta it
doesn't bother you that I got because
you ran into a bunch of these guys and
sired many lizards children yeah just
troubling to you that I'm wearing this I
know that desk is there some people who
look this is closed now
it's weird if I cut the head off so it's
just a vest is that I just pop that off
what the while we're in the back that's
probably better
yeah does it have a little crown of any
kind
Heather accoutrement never had any
changing in name now none of the spirit
weasels winery no not anymore
bearings yeah this is something like
make his memory a wasteland
I'd go thank you can't remember that
even more badly right now after the beer
now
like she's got the bad Mary over my hat
your sensual hat you're incredibly
handsome yeah loving has and we all saw
the fan art and it would be little
vinegar a little fast listen a warlock I
never won is a big city I personally
never traveled that far north because I
only does cold as that but I could
hopefully find a place that sells like
spells for me to purchase and consume me
once we're there let's see if I can find
something that will remove a part of
your mind
you don't like frontal lobe but mess
with everything from here at something
will we get yeah got a railroad spike
huh yeah I'm medicine can be I read
about it just in Torrance yeah in today
like yeah alright well we'll see what
you got because it's not I do it I just
I just banging on the roof I know we're
going to keep dip it in those potions
till we get some sort of memory wife
raisins oh yeah I just feel pain dormant
usually what I do is I guys guys yeah
it's the the the carriages to me for
lack of a better term rocking I mean
it's yeah
don't bother knocking bother exactly is
it tie on the knob on the range exactly
what s boys get up to you and go to
sleep
you take a nap and yep I just try to
identify things and then yeah what nope
so you what sauce cold thank you so you
guys you start rolling north on the long
road you have you have made this trip a
few times once to Westbridge and then
taking a right to head out on the
to manage the goblin raids that were
occurring out there under the auspices
of Lord visited carton wheel they'll
remember him oh boy do we ever do right
obviously Westbridge is itself a town of
novel character many people do stay
there and then farther north from that
you know there's another town called
tribe or has a lot of fields it's a lot
of livestock so with a Wild West sort of
like rural type town okay
what's world wild west world oh well
well West Loop and wilder than west
imagine a dark once world bush
I want you to leave okay so not see we
need we need we need jokes of this kind
for the for the inevitable live shows Oh
save it you know what I mean maybe I'll
contact you exactly like Capet well it's
still fresh okay so I'm just going to
unless you guys have a super compelling
reason we should stop in West bridge I'm
just going to keep on trucking through
well um here's the thing is that I have
about the good work that we did with
Trevor at the doone-gate in yeah and
that is just I really feel like we
merged the good name of acquisitions
incorporated I would really like to just
stop by maybe just try and kind of
things over a little bit and as I recall
a lot of that was because someone
relation by blood maybe like blew out
all the windows an entire city street
huh naming any names but that happens
and seems like people were pretty upset
about that is not my blood relations but
fine
the town's not there anymore well then
we roll past and it took some jobs
injured or not and we're going to clear
this bridge is that I guess not there
it's gone it's like western memorial
hold oh yeah
so there are ghost towns but then there
are towns that are ghost
yes oh this is to separate I got chills
just now from that stupid thing you do
John Kerry well I do Rosen I go when I
said blood religion I meant a lot of the
heart of course I know what you meant
there so would you like to would you
like to stop by private left or a hair
of and Dark Dragon oh this is the sort
of player that a dungeon master and I'm
telling you all this
just to imply where you all exist in my
player hierarchy it's lower okay then
this it's lower I always my real bad you
know what I mean
it's down here okay so other things that
you do not encounter the displacer
beasts at any tier of at any age of
execution oh okay I was lying
you had them oopsie yeah exactly
pumps yeah matriarchs nothing biss yeah
exactly
just place your keys there's nothing if
there's nothing in there you don't you
don't see it I mean obviously the same
places they were running these sort of
like ditches along the side like you're
waiting for this you're waiting for this
assault it doesn't arrive
you can't uneventful II continue your
trip in your newly juice cart experience
the skull of fixed inside humming softly
you have exactly right as you head into
West bridge you can see you can see
groups of people moving through town
this is it this is obviously there's
some event there's some something
something as drew as drawing them into
the town square which is where you know
that the ancient rivalry of pragma cleft
and heroines are dragon resides now of
course to obviously the shadow council
has many matters that
are you know forefront in its find its
managing issues all throughout the
realms but so it makes it may be worth a
brief reminder turbaned our dragon loves
asses that are sculpted out of marble
and for some reason pragmatic left is
about the potty and he likes he like
statues energy like he like statues that
pee constantly you collect nice pieces
no now there was it such I haven't in my
notes that when we left they had erected
a new statue of Hera van der dragon with
no pants no no that's the one we
received that's what we got there how
are you - here yeah I we I don't know
that okay - these - okay there are no
statues I don't even get eyes on them
and I want to make sure that everything
is just like well with our brand no no
you can you can actually see them they
are both in the town square
together together they fighting no they
are holding hands maybe in front of Ann
Arbor when behind them there is a way
you assume is a statuary of some kind
underneath underneath a wrap oh my gosh
oh my god I tend to wonder and you can
see that that the signage for their
different venues because I mean
basically between the two of them they
control the the most bustling area of
town and they have come to a different
some different arrangement here pragma
clefts facility if facility it may be
called inside a kind of like a mission
impossible matrix of interwoven urine
streams of incredible mathematical
sophistication
it says cleft and dar dragons
and then the opposite side of the street
it says da dragon and cleft I bet no she
I knew it they really have a yes to
thank for breaking down those loves it's
right thanks to something brilliant son
just like I know like just tore down Lud
related lovely old tore down the walls
and like yeah we should talk to them and
like see how they're doing
there was blood it was yeah I like
necessary it's like you know like
bloodletting a wound like lentil each
yeah yeah you guys know when you're
covered in leeches yeah right sure we
also turn one of them to metal
temporally degree mess so yeah saved our
dragons life notes he had an opportunity
very briefly become the statues a statue
of this sort he crepes right yeah right
exactly so I think I interrupted again
so the card is is coming in you can tell
around the seat that the seats are sort
of set up in what looks for like pie
wedges around the front and it looks
like they're each sort of associated
with one or the other members of the
wedding party you can see there's a
little diets behind each and one is a
naked person and then one is just an ass
and then it sort of goes back but
there's like four of these pie wedges
back here but there is a path that the
cart can wheel around okay and helping
to the right you can see inside near the
statue near an exquisite cake bulbous aw
round making taking full advantage of
the libations that are available you can
see Briella
predator with her with her small cart in
the back tribe or is just north of here
so it looks like she might have been
called down to lay down some baked goods
but the the sheet comes down as the as
the card is moving around this half
circle the sheet comes down and it is a
commingling here in the very center of a
vicar in the very center of the
courtyard it's got an incredible ass but
it pees as well from the end I love ya
know the total package you know it
doesn't it doesn't pee from the ass you
guys but there's so you go to the front
yeah I'm out of there yeah that's yeah
so then what were the statues before did
they not have masses on them before even
not like this not like this not like it
was like like as an actress a functor e
yeah yeah exactly yeah sure it was some
vestigial you know what I mean not the
important not the focus of the element
it wasn't exclusive but but but this
town any rate in the localized way has
absolutely been modified on this on this
fateful night that acquisitions
incorporated came into town I didn't
realize that the wedding woman didn't
realize it was a wedding and now she's
upset that somebody else gets to find
happiness just like the farther around
you did it at the faces to it she just
looks very disapproving in the whole
thing Shauna was very intoxicated right
I am a little bit for loner I I'm a
little bit upset as well because I had
an experience with dard Dragon where I
started to appreciate art like it was a
very it was a formative moment and then
when the two of them clashed I thought
all of the hold works is nonsense and a
little bit of youth and beauty died that
day in the older wood but now I'm like
maybe it's maybe it can be worked out
but that makes me mad because I wanted
to believe this garbage like all things
in this room I believe I'll make nothing
and why don't you mean words to me than
does that I'm a little bit upset about
this yeah it just looks like two obvious
outsiders who like
but the best should invest is that if
you're looking at the cart like from the
left side it's like you can see him down
you're looking out the window and
there's no top you're just like ever
were these just like Rosie Rosie of
Syria de roda credit every way and so
she she left him wedding immediately
just like a waterworks start she's so
happy
usually old loud inappropriate snoring a
treble of drowning of music this is
basic arts like okay so this side all
mean but if the camera were to wheel
over on this side obviously the Eiffel
Rosie but the camera wheel on this side
you can just see dinar blossoms just
mouth open against the glass yeah face
press up that you have a given up on
Rosi yeah all of the interior structures
of his mouth you're able to pull around
clean the center of paneling and commit
yourself to a northward trek towards
tribe or okay so we're not even sides
made what we rewrite what we're going to
talk to grill about all right the
realist finger Berlin will be in a
center I guess they were just going to
say hey cement that yeah I think we're
essentially like what's up along our yes
in that work yeah build that roll of
dice yeah Deb is omitted do we have any
good wedding gift
oh well let's see what I got those
eyeballs Gabby's I mean I'm not give
another way that's we can bring fire you
transform into a seat weapon if we had
gone I have the name of your seed pod
[Music]
for your gardening yeah yeah we like you
just rented this wonderful town garbage
can with it see publish it like it
patterns on the one on what's around it
and so it becomes a huge shiet
it's just like you you know we hate it
mostly I've seen from space
yeah I know I want to I want to believe
that see jess is a term that was coined
right here on the CV proposes I hope so
yeah actually worth it but I write down
a later laughs so do we we don't have
any good wedding gifts for people who
appreciate blessing T so yeah running
late you can get what you can There is
obviously a gift table available for you
so maybe somebody went to gym if
somebody wanted to if you may want to
drop out or you park the card if you
wanted to and you can definitely show
them our but I lived urinate how long
did it take to get here yeah what was a
clown X minutes I know couple day all
right
okay we can't double back and give them
a statue I was going to say the statue
back it's like once you bested do not of
hate and now this could be like a sex
thing I guess yes I liked our potion of
fire breathing or they liked our potion
of making your new spouse metal maybe
don't like a person of fire I was
thinking that too I how can you like
they want to push in a fire breathing
but I'm not sure how that figures into
appreciation of butts but who cares arms
are right yeah yeah yeah yeah maybe he
could like breathe on the butt and it
turns red it's a guy I don't know yeah
yeah yeah I mean it's there's all kinds
of applications we just need them to
know that we were here and then we're
going to leave a very tasteful note yeah
unresisting court the company letter has
it good right let's just go do that yeah
okay well we can do that and then also
there's just already like a perfectly
sealed envelope and it just says like
congratulations care of acquisition or
is it busted out quick
documenter package case split open like
you're like yeah a little too yes I know
how does it work okay I feel better at
it great
Briella give them a push well I'm going
to top a compliment it grow on because
obviously this beautiful cake is her
handiwork and be like yo I see you I see
that cake I see that beautiful mound I
see a glistening cheek action you've got
there that's not easy now
in say room like you already where you
getting that kind of shimmer
he knows it's edible amazing yeah you
know miss mrs. suitum that's right this
is another different story she makes she
makes note of you but then she's clearly
like all biz she is she's looking back
over all the the small the smaller rumps
you're the cupcake style right you know
what I mean
and she says gotta go ah it went
extraordinarily well she said you this
there's still a drawing courrier haha
I'll say they're looking for a six star
my friends you know what I mean she yeah
she knows most okay okay six star yeah
man in song ringabel
yeah agreed yeah not a fan
he wouldn't prophesy when she got back
she seemed nervous right I have I had
that in my notes she she returned
nervous she was looking for fault where
there was not that's true
and oh she did find a chair that was
that place oh that's probably for the
best
yeah if she had felt if she'd felt like
the place could run without her that
might have been unpleasant for her and
you well lesson learned but thank you
again for all of your help but as we're
we're heading north
we're going to try to make it to
nevermore direction in a self and tribe
where and see you so ok doesn't stop uh
if you're going there right now you
might miss me here hi may I may stay on
here a couple days okay all right well
maybe we'll see you when we come back
there
nope I'll be there okay wonderful right
right now and then she turns her she
turns herself to a assigning cakes the
young people in don't take so much of
this good fortune looking at this for
the person notice yeah great have your
wedding hesitant ring over and over in
my pocket yeah yeah exactly
alright
Doug's tonight yeah there's a dead bird
baby they go about a foot and then just
fall down
thank you wait how many I got and they
puke spiders they're all incontinent and
then they bug them love it they're like
oh what a joyous day you split the
difference
yeah you found that substance that
they're both into so as you as you leave
through the north end on the long road
through West bridge just about a day of
travel and as soon as you start to get
close to tribe or we can sort of see if
this is not not a large place very very
rural very cow oriented yeah you would
say it dude so cow oriented but you're
actually not sure how you're going to
get your cart into this town with cow it
is it is basically like a cow roll that
stretches out the long road hundreds and
hundreds of feet cardboard call it try
cap turned into like aw I face it is
that does I want to I'll try me on Davis
let's go more yet kind enough I like it
there I'm like time low line we have
over an area so we are block by block by
industries it is just like the eccentric
an album but it's true you are blocked
by cows let's both speaker dial all I'm
going to use my normal voice
well hop down and just trying to like
reason with the cows and has dived no
special powers this was just business
just something I'm going to try to do
what I want to be sensible and I want
her to feel like she's doing it so I
want to you you know let it happen so I
want her to let it happen but I'm going
to speak to animals
to a neighboring County was a new
adjacent counties and cow and I'm going
to say and that I'll do it be like um
hey friends sir madam we need to get
into your your town um do you think you
could think y'all could just move one
second there's really great rats right
over there same if not better
maybe greener over there we just get
everybody that that it takes your
estimate is that it takes a hundred
years for the cow's head to raise and
then look over at the grass and this is
Brad and I know that I know that walnut
is probably gonna talk to him was but I
want her to think that it's working so I
released legate just give a snake on the
ground scare the share of these cows
they're so stupid ruminants out of our
way walking dead edge there's a pile of
potential friends risk potential not I
need a smarter friends okay
so so the Gotti beggars can be choosers
peggotty legate hits the ground I think
that that call a grass is the grass call
just gets taken up by cow after cow but
when they turn it's like it's like a
aircraft carrier like the whole thing is
just sort of like this infinity clock
just all sort of turning over toward
this way but they're turning in ways
that make it difficult for them to turn
the correct way when the gaud hits the
ground
instantly legate gets up on two on two
loops and the knife is in the air like a
rattlesnake and it just it just
immediately asserts itself over these
much larger creatures and they start to
run
fast then I go I'm banging on the side
of thing I'm like drought they're creepy
noodles on the ground going crazy again
what is eating all the cows you did it
you did
they're out of our wedding we go with
those I want to come town I want to look
at what got a standing go
wouldn't you creepy I don't yeah you
know everything to got that nice even so
high and mighty
walk like I'm watching you okay I met I
get it I know your number
you're not animal I know animals yeah
you're on natural head like this
Thanks toes its head turns its head over
this way and it's all new eyes yeah yeah
yeah I'm in a chick chirps and shatters
at you in what you think is probably the
response to what you have said and it's
just a but it goes on for two minutes
biting as I said real quick I wanna just
reach in my reach my bags I have my
little snake friends that's been with me
this whole time
but I'm very neglectful of and I go you
don't understand that thing do you are
just listening only writing oh yeah
service is it's not made of meat nah I
mean it's made of something I'm me a
call total guy Gotti change the record
already you all heard of lectures with
the second thing you understand
everything really sorry
I'm sick of it too so the guy needs all
your scenes until you're seeing you guys
right yes literature yes you know it's
always a good way
yeah thank you okay the preamble area oh
it's the same story every single time
there's like I did it you get him to go
back I didn't send them out there to
like you know going to be the mid of the
town just scare them away you're saying
that when you make name Stampede and
then the DM is sitting right there
sometimes it's all fake
I'm not even before I stuff this snake
back in my factory I was going to go hi
I'm sorry I've never really been
properly introduced what's what's your
name we've ever known as snake to give
its name first I go and I look at and
look at it breath like I'm like this guy
and then I go I'm called walnuts on
grass The Enclave connect anima excuse
the tail seizes the tail and your little
nip yeah that's good you know so
straight and knit them back yeah McHale
just know how wait it snakes smell words
it's like yeah just like not smell like
sour but like it really oh yeah yeah
yes it don't speak smell yeah ghosts
this one really touch makes any touch
with use my hands make diffic smells
weird fix it nobody recall I think it's
no sneaky like whoa I put now I get it
I put seas of the tail on mine I don't
know his name finally I know that's
great Mike pat pat and i would personal
my snake yes what's that I don't know
Silva Gotti the Gotti is the guy things
summon the backwater me oh my god he is
summoned back to his master but then
every couple feet he sees these uses
slithering every couple of feet he rises
- alright I am sickened eccentric ever
would be like he's over it like
basically at the leg of your trouser
make sure we got dog again basis please
so got nothing here but still Hill
splitter up your bizarre internal
structure yeah
rabbits wrap itself around the neck
again and then sort of like clamp on to
its midsection and be worn down exactly
like your polo type you can adjust this
low crawl yeah for a great look every
time you're going to love it so so we've
solved your category except well it's
just cows it's not really possible to
just wake up I go over there Nick I saw
this other always summer so you can see
you can see they're different you can
see that there are obviously different
ranches here that people and people take
their responsibility to the cows more or
less seriously and people do come up
here but they go here they come through
tribe or to go somewhere else
yeah generally speaking it we shall be
among them yeah I mean read read large
minute as I understand it from my own
readings read larch is pretty sparse
internally we're talking about farms and
cows okay this is comparable size down
dr. Radler yeah Oh settlement yeah it's
only absolute it's a little it has it's
very specialized okay we're heard in
town yeah yeah there's more head of
cattle than people but you can see as
you as you move sort of into the central
square I'm being polite you can you can
actually see gorillas baked goods how
long because you can see that it has a
sign in the window that says that it's
not currently open but it might be that
it's available when you're on your way
back under any anti stars but it's
mostly supply shops it's mostly feed-in
um road supplies everything where that
grain you feeling pretty good yeah okay
plowing through yeah yeah okay perfect
so you know a cartographer yeah that I
left out from here to jaunt over to the
high road to the coast indeed and
continue north right
you see the right place there's still a
few days travel left up here to get to
Neverwinter as you take that left
through there is a forest that a bus the
town directly on the left side put it
above the temple old-growth forest not
Universal no it's it's and you you can
tell you can tell right away if you want
more historical information I think I
can totally your folk library if I can
put that yeah sure let's do it
Penza yeah that's a good one that's
exclude the hot role which is that you
know that there is a you know that
there's this forest that you're passing
on your left
out of town is Gawain slumber grain
slumber indeed the god of tracking oh
and this would for followers of Maliki
and go away in the are this is this is a
recognized place to rest okay and it
said that occasionally prophetic dreams
dreams of contact and communion with
those gods are whole to be had Mac and
rosy sounds down can we please stop here
yeah here are you mailing is where that
was murdered yeah yeah yeah you know you
know without the without the PowerPoint
presentation and you know that you know
that you are and Jason to a holy play
you're drawn to it okay yeah let's stop
here that's fine I'm just like asking
your mom please
it is really like well all right yes but
this is the last time yeah anyone a
prophetic dream dream I feel about it
like you would like the Mystery Spot or
one of the yeah roadside yeah like I'm
good autumn in for this kooky God what
are you serious yeah yes like tourist
trap yeah the glans brothers to put
gravity tricks but like fun the only
time walnuts look happy huh actually
maybe ever it is a place to rest like
through through fear or our care this is
pristine this forest is a pristine place
alright so I will drive us take a left
yeah that's for us exactly yes it's
cooling the air is starting to cool out
as a cool as evening as evening arrives
so you use your view basically taking
the cart off the main road yeah and I
started driving it where you know where
are you going to place the cart um let's
find an opening where we can kind of
settle coriander into a spot where she's
not in her way and that you can feel
happy I I literally did making this pit
stops on you ask why I've already jumped
off and her boots off and she is like
running through the undergrowth like
giggling do you knock you line but just
like yes very quietly I'm like fucking
seven types of trees this isn't really
right now tell me how we tell me what
happens to a dinar bliss and in this in
this mystical magical context so we're
in a little Glade holy glades do I are
we're starting to get up towards the
NARS stomping grounds do I recognize
this area this
is this totally Cowtown is literally
everything you hate about non dragon
porn
yeah like this is this is like a museum
yeah to what sucks about them yeah no
that seems accurate all right yeah I
mean I guess ever since I understand
this this journey is going to take a
while but ever since the thrist reframed
the argument now I'm just like getting
impatient and now it's like I've done a
complete 180 and I don't care about
never wandering there let's just go I
want to make sure he is okay like this
so I'm a little pissed off that we're
here really ha ha this seems like we
said I am wake up son of McNabb go sleep
account will be up Chavanel yeah I mean
all wait down to sleep nom use your most
of your horizontal got to say sleeping
yo so you're you're you're ready to do
it as you are contending with like just
the information the legacy of this place
it ceases to be time ceases to be
entirely linear great so you're placing
your hand on a tree and then the next
time you are conscious enough to think
about it your hand is on a different
tree like time is like skipping like
like a lily pad your started moving from
moment to moment how do you contend with
this space I probably take a meditative
rest I'm very content that my good
friend walnut appears to be out of her
mind with joy and this feels like a safe
place to me if I know about it as grants
lumber and a forest for these gods who
are beneficent enough then I'm not super
worried about our our safety um so I'm
probably just chillin
yes allowing yourself to relax yeah yeah
mr. Stroud tell me tell me another item
tell me about the moment that you enter
this probe
am i but am i experiencing that same
sort of loss of moment-to-moment
or now you see you start and then I'll
finish say at the same time on three
yeah you know I see when I see wallet
take off I am less dismissive of the
place and begin to realize well this is
an important place for a god I'm not
sure what that God's feelings would be
about me and I don't know that the elf
connection was sufficient to stay some
mighty hand right so I kind of them like
okay maybe just cue to myself I'll have
some prophetic dream if it's given to me
but I don't want to I'm not going to
start marking the place up with my runes
yes how are you sir described don't you
get into that area as so as you you have
sort of placed this this mythical grove
within a set of parentheses that you
feel comfortable with and you can
understand yeah you're able to catalogue
it and then the deeper you try to press
into this the harder this place presses
back hmm do I feel like is it is it a
physical pressure you you feel as though
the air itself is becoming physical hmm
like where are we right now did we
manage to make camp yeah I mean my
suspicion is that right now everyone is
resting and relaxing I haven't heard
anything about camp being made okay um
but there's definitely a moment here to
to catch your breath but you don't seem
to be fully able to enter this place I
you're all out about you probably
further down I yeah I don't feel I don't
feel very good
I think this
this doesn't like me very much I get
besides no of course it likes you much
and I feel it well is right it sucks
here though yeah you have no context as
to why either yeah yet so as you're
talking to as you were talking to Rosie
your throat closes the necklace the
necklace flows down when you look at
your hands you have the device I was
given to you and you have two cinched it
I'm can i unpinch can I guess okay I am
clinched it oh wow I said I don't know
dad you know you're rejecting me did I
did you see me do that or did it do it
by itself I don't know I saw it or not
it was a show yeah I know no no no no
yet not consciously okay okay okay
well um why don't we install you maybe
on the outskirts of this forest like we
were already there way to fail
I want to do I would love to do in our
cat check on the nature of this zone and
see what I get a sense of that's going
to be trash that's a little tiny three
also can be a tease so you are trying to
understand a place that as near as you
can tell doesn't want you to live and
the awareness of it I mean our Canada
isn't going to be the right approach
this is a type of magic that this is the
type of magic that you are not familiar
with and frankly you would probably find
revolting without and you if you
approach it in a completely different
way there's no there's no study without
any further knowledge of what that the
nature of that is I think it's as my
focus it's the it's the mainland the
sigils I have a bit absorbed those
daggers it's tainted of course this
place is going to reject my I'm carrying
that so you have you touch it I I
haven't but I'll maybe I
I'm going to pull it out and see whether
or not it's reacting the day when you as
you pull it out you know
in an instant that it's not your body
anymore you are you you are looking at
what was your body but you are parallel
to it you have been yanked out of it
so like riding shotgun is you're riding
shotgun in your own body
okay Annie you are after I'm really
annoyed me Welman you are drawn to the
edge you walk through a tree mm-hmm and
then walk out of another tree at the
edge what it's cool to the and you are
parallel to your own body
this is afraid as well and you are
pulled completely out like this is this
is absolute release from from this coil
that you've struggled against that's
great and you know that you serve Maliki
and right now the way that you serve
Maliki is by granting her a physical
body time I mean that's one does one way
for a true daughter that's tied at hello
okay you can see before you a you can
see before you a woman and dressed like
fall and winter and you can see that
these two women in immense pain are
looking at each other across a on so the
lines are numbered and they start with
walnut who is not Alona but it is in
fact Maliki you who are the heart of my
heart why did you cast me away finds me
would that I could die of this pain you
are my own blood I have scoured the
every trunk and leaf being itself all in
vain you left to find me okay the two of
them the two of them your friends
collapse on each side of this but in a
moment before in the womb before this
you can see in your guys adjacent to
maliki you can see what starts as a
single amethyst shard land right between
the two women oh and then more come
around until she is completely
surrounded and the entire prison is
hurled into space merely his problems
are male a list of males is homelessness
did we hear that the half like when he
was million now the body did we hear
that if you know if you know elven okay
so he was just I do yeah yeah okay then
you would have heard it but you have
heard it spoken by these two okay and
then their bodies collapsed yeah yeah
when they sell down it's a these are
your friends but he is on the other side
of whatever this is he cannot enter him
to this holy place
what I'm saying so like we were standing
next to him right and she was off in the
woods so we only really heard half of it
right we just heard him go out of body
and start talking in elvish saying fine
I think i teleported through and I
backed over so yeah we heard both
conversations right pick a elvish nope I
do you probably do right oh yeah yeah
after nice I'm just like blah yeah
they're together where you're wearing
your weird I don't like this magically
stand up I don't how it feels
am i an't words close enough now where
i'm aware that you are also on the
ground are we out are we
you can you can wake up but you're
groggy it's like a like unconsciousness
I am at walnuts head in an instant right
trying to figure out it happens you'd
feel sick like you do you feel confident
that you
going to vomit vomit yeah put that thing
away
I get ahead of it particularly on away
so with cons problem play with the vomit
you like this my thing yeah I've got a
brand I got a thing and I maintain a
nail
I've got a throws be like how great it's
acidic oh yeah you're an asshole
let's be done there yeah yeah yeah
little strips yeah this is nothing
nothing I'm sure the best choice for
Canada's vomiting this so that Vetta see
that is the scenario that you want to
throw up
yeah and you might I'm tracking away I'm
stay away from this way that wasn't it
for you that is not a vomit scenario
that is that is an ecstatic experience
oh that is what that is what a priestess
that is the sort of thing a priestess
sounds like a trance was said to have
done yeah I get that tears shit yeah so
I'm on the ground and really came over
to me and it's just like crab crabby
brother cloak and I just please a little
bit and I go I saw something and I think
I think I had it all wrong I think I had
it all wrong before
she's just like I don't know I don't
know oh I heard what was being said I
heard everything
don't ever didn't make any sense to me
those are the two goddesses of my Grove
my own toys well my leekie is associated
with his forest to the other goddess
that that's that's who she is GOG the
other one the other one after those
issues she's the other I keep that at
like face value and you're cool it's no
leak and the other cool and um one that
goes I was always told that she was a
betrayer but I saw her she was taken by
something and now maybe he has to find
the other based on this conversation but
she's up there just points up the sky
she's like that's where she went
okay you need to help me wiki I feel
like she's showed this to me for
something okay
are you still barfing I tried to put as
much distance as I can with everything
from the yes I just like blocking out
like past the cart like again just the
nidus is fast approaching you sort of
find yourself stumbling toward the road
that leads west from yeah tribal or like
a look at you trying to find a non
forest lamb scenario thinking that you
can be a part of like to lean against
the tree no no no this is where things
look you started what can I lean against
I'm going to play to your feet but
you're probably it seems like you're
fine you're great you're like super
ecstatic no way oh my god does she look
different to me can I perceive a change
like has she been initiated somehow as a
free session radiant okay like literally
emanating light yeah Wow oh okay
can you tell can she tell us she was
radiating no she's just doing she's just
walnut see this walnut that is you
scrublord okay I'm going I'm staring at
you super hard but I'm not going to tell
you why yeah it's amazing yeah then who
if that mammoth went there up this up
away there did you get to thick nail it
well she does you know actually no way
don't you think I'd know she does she
does yeah it's Mila she's up there who's
here who's here who's presence is here
whose cultists are here who who's in
who's in the drew house rock that's a
good question but I'm still looking at
you like I'm really concerned about this
religion I do
but I'm also like fascinated by whatever
has a real I told me with a religious
night looking ya know wide-eyed it was
incredible
yeah but looks like Rose is going to
think right all about this later
so she's she's but she's just got it
like she's fascinated academically by
whatever happens mission just you didn't
have to feel coriander him yeah chlorine
ourselves out there and she can miss
pequeos Rosie's penchant for gossiping
and she grabs her her hand hurt him her
puts her hands on her face and she
grandmother don't tell the boys about
this I think one of they might know but
I won't tell them any more than they
already do did you sure you're okay
I feel great never better so do you saw
the other I'm very careful about this
you saw the other go up yeah
where's nameless now here distant yeah
no I don't know I don't know I thought I
thought she was I thought maybe we would
find her embodied in Emma's ear and we
saw those cultists with her hated symbol
but I don't I don't know um sorry I went
I'm going to say Miki I'm asking my name
here sorry I'm getting them confused but
I because I rosie has this what she can
perceive is that maybe he is inside of
you yeah and so don't why did you see
her go anywhere
okay here okay yeah I don't think she
left
yes now her she's like I can feel her
like presence in this forest uh-huh yeah
it's like all around me - yeah I can
definitely feel her cousin let them let
this shit on the drow because I can hear
some real unpleasant sounds back there
and you seem ok I'm going to go check on
you let's
yeah you're just here like Nyonya here
stop Tommy no no no our think well I'm
glad look below and you're like no
amateur I like that doing it from each
time yeah it's like they're gonna do it
do it right yeah god ah so gross there's
way more you know bad huh okay I know I
know
there are stupid see you good very
loaded up - yes can you make some for
the drow get sour stomach nervous oh
c'mon oh I just come on like basically
like floating over I'm like here you go
friend
yeah ep's please eat the goodness okay
nothing read your back sorry
fix your barking worse so I'm yeah what
I've pieced together is or what I'm
imagining is that it has to do with the
focus that's been tainted by five MELAS
and I mean I've had the complete
opposite of the experience we've seemed
to add is this isn't a betrayer or not I
gotta get these out of my beautiful
focus got clean it all I thought she was
at the Trier but it seems like that
wasn't her fault why why am i strong and
when I feel good so good down here
so you're maybe we can start a miracle
because this is the only one that knows
about the shard bling no that's a
conversation that he had with what
everyone had the other from the outer or
the writer business I don't know what
the big amethyst rocks are gotcha no I
guess I actually know I will avoid cut
wrists now what can you identify that
she would identify he would if he if you
were to discuss
areally launched spires of amethyst
crystal I have every faith that even
Chris Stroud would be able to determine
the source yeah there's one one type of
charge excusing worlds yeah what did I
share with them or what it could first
share I don't think he didn't come back
with anything they have to reveal your
secret dark purpose
that's a meta game yeah I'm trying to
figure out barely following this I'm
like where's the wash like okay time get
some ready and he's not going to
unkilled yourself you're done I'm not
going at all I feel a lot of weird stuff
son but you got it okay looks like
bothering me I know I don't like magic
stuff more than any more of this more of
a cell I am trying I'm trying right now
Chris is trying to figure out how much
mistress would share in order to
determine this absolutely that's an
important question I agree so I don't
believe having been contacted by drawn
enterprises and having received another
focus would he share that without the
rest of it god that's a tough one
I agree and how would you have found it
like how'd you find out when were you
sure it was a group right and that's
where that's where we are
well anyway but I thought in but so
here's well here's how this is how could
this would do it okay we don't know what
happens now when you say is done I want
to I want cleanse my focus of this
symbol and when I was um refreshed me on
how I was contacted I tell the story of
like in that transit I was taken to that
place that restaurant a restaurant that
would that contact and gay a woman Diana
prices never imagine if you will a dark
Applebee
I don't have to Mexican I lived it yes
every day and I see it back to my
eyelids angle appetizers smog there's an
intimate end of the breadsticks
what kind of world is this from the
level parking always occupied no spaces
for me 15 Mary no I say I tell you the
whole thing I say that I this much I was
being swayed by drawn enterprises they
contacted me to make use of my services
which they did not specify and they gave
me this I produced the other focus with
the source or the half miles of the
Obama lawyer yeah they gave me a missus
okay how it would be intentional for me
to lose in some way and now I'm
concerned that you need to be aware
before I go too far down one of these
paths my interest isn't purging my focus
not in doing work for them
maybe we can maybe we can fix both of
our problems at the same time maybe we
can clean your rock out and then she
should stop supposed to purge your focus
I'm learning baffle by determining what
exactly happens writing this ancient
wrong
I can't think of another reason why this
vision whatever this was would choose me
as a vessel other than that I'd carry
this symbol with me as here you guys are
deeply focused on this conversation
right now
focus we got it okay they're ready
yeah on this one yes sir you are looking
at her she is looking at you you are
watching because she is standing still
and having a conversation with you you
can see branches and bushes sort of
rising around her feet you can see the
trees moving their limbs to shield or I
would say what is your honey do I notice
us or am I just like it's cool it's all
sort of happening it's all peripheral
teas yeah like as it should be like yeah
probably subconsciously yeah no why not
just respiration
I know what I don't want to be the
embody my daughter cuz you don't have to
do we don't think that that that middle
earth is actually physically here oh no
she got running on got sent to the right
as I'm so excited about this the only
time I've like really been into cabarrus
on restricted is it you had to come here
you had to bring that symbol here so we
could both have that vision and now you
can help me find her here the keeper of
the key I go yeah I go this is what
you're good for I like this is point to
get it out you start trying to do what
you're doing like I'm reading the
situation
my goodness I don't know oh shit we're
doing the table flowers and trees and
yes I got a cut me off right out of you
know some like no I'm like yes let's
what is required how we discover more
without this place murdering me
I had no allegiance to this betrayer I
go maybe showing us everything that it
needs to show us and I look E and I
remember and I go you remember that we
saw that symbol in the wandering crypt
that's right I think that's I think
that's where some of our answers will
leave I see they told me actually I
should have done it before Chris forgot
but let's have a hesitant reveal yeah
like that's that the reason why drawn
Enterprise has contacted me was because
they knew we were seeking the wandering
crypt what their goal is with it they
did not tell me but they are also
looking for it and they identified these
shards as instances of it like like
larval that's well put yeah like like I
look like a version of this thing that
they refer to the shard wing but what
omen calls the wandering crypt all these
are I connect imagine the different
citruses shit imagine these are old
tentacles the only analogy you know like
this that would be bad little tight
together yeah like this and then
branches just kind of like song hell
yeah that that's long as you think you
could never - as you're putting your
hands together just like the branches
and leaves just like an ant
yeah exactly it's your hammer yes you're
drifting winds behind you the thing is
doing exactly my god I think this place
is reveals all it will
I think that our next step is to wait
until we need the Wonder encrypt the
shard line as you called it well that's
a see yeah there's another thing I can
do what I'm maybe not here maybe it's
not the best thing to do here
Catania enjoy display
no anyway journeys it could incur
camin roads right now yeah these these
two foes I are attracted to each other
they want to be together I'm keeping
them apart because I didn't want to mess
with anything I don't fully understand
things they should be together should be
together but now you turn for certain
animals wait but maybe putting them
together will dilute this symbol as
opposed to introduce an element I don't
understand yeah but they want to be
together well we really know but that's
how much I'm seeing apart I know and I
know but it's just like confidence just
like at some level like philosophically
it's just like fecundity like like it's
a richness and grow and together nesic
right and I'm like holy unknown as of
what we need to do so first I got grabby
like vines and branches right like start
growing like over his arm look yeah dad
have a commercial break yeah special
friends remember such a French of course
I mean the shadow council who we always
endeavor to please with our labors we
have a commercial break
subscribers see cool AI steps and not
commercial something consider don't go
anywhere
well right back hello
when last we saw our heroes walnut that
is to say the avatar of Maliki was
trying to push together and join in on
holy matrimony two chunks anything right
here yes
gross with no new to Miss shapen lumps
revolting shit oh no no to test back
yeah lunch particular length of that
have the focus yeah this is a black
altar and indeed other other altars as
well you know that um and so Chris is
saying that maybe this Chris has
commitment phobia he does not know
everything I'm just saying maybe that's
possible that it would dilute it and
thus help us out or add I mean I know
I'm not sure if it's the right thing to
do percent so close to this is the whole
place I want to go together they should
be together we should take a vote let's
take a vote these didn't actually see my
vote before and it's already grabbed all
his hands and yeah three two two at best
one one two people yeah alright together
then they go together and they form a
solid wedge around your hands with a
wedge yeah they basically form a wedge
that retreats down into two shackles
around both of their football around
around his hand first
for the bracelets are they related
shackles you know they are it's a single
piece Oh like this like this okay what
do they resemble at all what they need
to be no what do they look like now
right now they look like to join rings
in the center and it's anything okay get
you like a leather harness I know
transformation is complete
all right yeah oh the green all right
again
oh yeah cut his hands off okay yeah I
touch it if you want to um cuz it was
when I school being glowy nothing little
thing okay
no no no but but seeing the symbol of
mail it in this heightened state is
there's no anger and rage is not there
it's just it's just sadness is there
just an ancient just an ancient
despondency their symbol visible on this
thing yeah it's the symbols that you
have you have a symbol of mail if you
have the symbol of the holier right and
then you also have this third symbol
right over ma the thirteen nice Obama
Osten words or apostrophe at least I
know anyway we're gonna get em a crack
we're going to end a Cappy and a shit
you're you're like visibly sad and I'm
like I'm upset too
I don't like this either things that are
apart should be together
good hands also will become holding your
hands honestly yeah that's better
does accept okay guys your fault drop on
my hands I could cut your hands off hear
me out
right on now so it is it is now dark and
the winds in these Guinness Grover
getting pretty cool
it's probably time to help you
yeah yeah I'll just figure easy to sleep
snapped off
focus all itself I'm convinced that
there's a a misty step solution to this
but the constraints have to be right I
guess technically these are the color
this would be like clothing and I don't
ever miss you step nude to the other
place no no listen all goes with I feel
I feel like there's another business
model there yeah I was promised a new
drought whoa in our sternum annihilation
I'm not sure and you got you got pretty
nude fire call yeah but I took those
things off I don't think I can take this
out seems like it's dope for me to them
are you open to me trying a sacred flame
to try to break it I know that hurts
your cutters powder and walnut feel
about it
oh yeah after I want nothing on you seem
to be okay with this do I want I don't
want anything bad to happen to some more
it's just like a sad thing well no it
was that would that would be sacrilege
absolutely yeah so do you say anything
well good so um my feeling is that it is
not necessarily in the interest of maily
maily key to have a involuntary prisoner
even if it is because of her passion and
her love yet that doesn't seem like the
kind of thing that she'd be into so I'm
still holding on to him as you're
talking about this I'm like okay so I am
proposing that I use a power of line to
try to separate the hands no no no no no
no and that can I make more vines and
stuff that is happening yeah so we're
becoming like woven together in this
Wicker Man yeah okay um bench here like
resolve up a little clamp like you're
like looking at your sight your cheek
and awesome it'll shine like new growth
yeah yeah things are budding and I'm
like I don't know everything must be
together it's not even getting weird
yeah I feel like partially responsive
like
in a small way to this so nice cut your
hands off it
this is one hand it will do it with me
watching both and I can really that kind
of hands off I see once good
hi I'm a guy your head short your left
but I can't scale them back on probably
I'm not kind of percent sure how it all
works
I don't like the idea we keep it as our
last resort if one is I guess being
overtaken by a kind of madness right now
I'm estimated like everything carries
everything's am like one of my hearings
right now in line between purity and
from atmosphere okay good question
your hands are bound how are your feet
doing they're fine very anaemic a
reminder I'm going to coil and buy this
to buy these roots on all this yeah I'm
playing for one fall no they're not have
to grow from the ground that's how they
work and so yeah we're good place here
in the glades or like spending I will
fuck off stay together forever feels
just like the wondering clips all over
again with a different crazy theme paint
now I'm going to try some grandmotherly
intimidation on you but I don't know if
it's going to work out try to intimidate
I got it yeah I will tonight as the kind
of thing Rosie do singer does like I'm
aware of your power but I'm going to try
and I'm going to take advantage on it
because we got it we got to get this
this is not an acceptable situation do
you want to leave we can't they're glued
to the ground and also know it also
absolutely not this way we're like okay
laughs and my intimidation is plus six
so pretty really 12 - okay so I've got
15 intimidation what you want
what's your answer hey one more let
loose that's that before she did what
matters regardless you'll have that it's
probably yeah I would do I would respond
to that with
in sight Oh Oh hmm
11 beat it so the other one was an 18
shit okay alright I just look at you for
a second when I look back to the task at
hand now so this is their immediate
danger fidget a 50 split we could just
yeah yeah I'm like a very cool meanwhile
squeezin Anna
there's an irony here I hope you
appreciate it what I don't know is it
what is it that would be I was hoping
you were doing it yes and feel bad
starting to get a little tight there it
is yeah waiting for it are the not
divine the vine so they are done your
stay here hey why do I already take out
you don't need this you need this doing
shall we kick it out gotten together
that's okay okay plan together
stay on happy yeah I said does anybody
does anybody have a scenario you may
want to execute a camping scenario also
legitimate just pitch up tension at all
and you can't I'm too tense for you and
then tensile bill device size right off
I just lay my a little deal and I'm
gonna let them work it out see misty
step out of this prison I don't think so
I think we'll go with me I can miss you
two out of the plant
yeah yeah but yeah I just started like
ferngully a tree together with a bunch
of little trees but just so you guys are
going to be locked into a tree to get it
forever well you also need there you
can't live in the tree we you can't do
that either I can be a tree why are you
angry
I do not want a human-sized you at all
see I set this plant like the king Dyer
alright if you step a mixie step just
going to man yawn
yeah I'm not going to get out of the oh
yeah I think I am getting there guys
dead what does that make me feel like if
you'll need
so I are for me so I - from in front of
you then there's a wrist shape hole and
the vines but now are like nothing there
and now I'm just five feet behind you
know where I saw where I could see at
this I'm assuming is what still with me
yeah yeah absolutely yeah and I'm like
she is fine
but I won't have to suffocate to death
this is the she can already do that if
you need it
sure she's very able to do that so I'm
gonna tell you what perceives this
severe you can tell me if that's too
much because now I'm just going to roll
it now he's trying that now he's trying
to take it away now he's trying to go
away with it I just it is together it's
together you were right and I would
point that out if anything I went
towards the glade a tiny bit does that
count
yes I'm okay if I'm hoping that fives
are just like locked locked on you then
the vines are very slowly like so slow
and not threatening Lee but they're just
slowly like trying to find my way back
towards you mm-hmm just like dancing
around like the creeping like my age is
not following it like a ticket whistle
like entitlement to trial
I don't know it's very long mated um
option sure don't kill me
I will stay near you but do not will
plant no in my lungs of course part the
part the vines that were around me and
stuff and I come close to again I might
now I need you hate you to find out the
truth I also want that but I'm very i
don't at this way
I don't like this I think there's a
better way and the round horse on this
one this by the one Hank you all feel
really good about what's going on and
that we just make camp figure our
business out we should sleep here yeah
we charge because that's about
everybody's going to sleep actually
we'll do the same shift for our for our
and you both wake up and I will not help
you make sure I don't go anywhere
that's not all right quick not great cuz
I don't want to anger anybody felt nice
for it it's a it's a given what it's
great it's a great fun I love it too
it's one of my favorites
performance absolutely no tell me how
the camp scenario goes well are we I got
I feel like we got to take it an aside
and be like am I gonna camp here yeah I
don't think this is very good for my
dear walnut are we gonna have to like
wait are we expecting her to sleep this
off for this existent I don't know she's
going to say that you see she's glowing
right yeah I thought well no no Chloe
wasn't good I was trying to I thought it
back in the round you know listen but
consider is that as the night has fallen
oh boy he has only gotten more radiant
right right it's it's like a friggin sun
moon down here so the vines while you
guys are talking the vines have grown up
and they made like a bench and I laid
down to like sleep among them adjusted
parties all of them soon they're just
like the minds are wrapping us up very
gently you mean
a sort of hammock in the meantime I'm
justifying to myself like I don't need
my hands
I have a guy Adelbert to do things for
me
I have more hands than most people I
could actually afford to lose more these
should didn't occur right now being
established
yeah but I am yeah mr. silver lining
yeah look at you know it all right
sounds good okay okay she's a goddess
I know I know if there a way that we
could um while they are in their slumber
can me and one back in the cart and
leave good idea you know enjoy whatever
pretending to sleep because there else
until say no we trance I'll bet you
notice that we tied our I have a
marketing analyst asleep doesn't work
darkness and I have silence which is
basically good we also ER you can't
charm elves you can't put a Cicely food
don't ever put a stamp
yeah I want it I want to use awakened
mind so you know it's telepath to you
you can see it's not walnut in years our
technology I reach walnut rather than
talking to this version you all no no no
no exactly no no it's like it it you
give me a brain it's like if you'd call
somebody's house when their mom answers
but you know that they're there and you
could ask right but it just feels like
it feels like it feels rude somehow yeah
well looks like I'm fine yeah hello
could first travel abuser guard
lieutenant what are you
you're right I'm right here right next
to you this is very minor I'm right here
cozy cluster pleasure not smile
well hello Joe
oh my god hmm tsunami I really want to
wait for them to sleep and tomorrow we
gonna do guys I ain't going to sleep hey
guys yeah what okay give us something
what can we do we gotta get you guys out
of here I'm trying to figure out what I
got that might help not gonna sell
clothes oh gentle I have an idea um
poison I have a big sword yeah well that
still doesn't get me out of there she
did
no no he's so nice to Walnut as opposed
to the last time we had to get Carissa
to somewhere interesting knock it off
that's really the room was filling with
acid that there's no immediate danger
and we're like well if I was like
studying a wall of rooms and there was
no problem how did you train told me to
get out be in there yeah sorry I can so
one of the things I took as mask of many
faces would that permit me to change my
shape to a slighter thing that could
take the thing off Wow could I decrease
my wrist dimensions yeah what's your
can you like a change mini I can change
into it let me adopt a humanoid
oh you're a blender man you can use one
yeah I would take on that a half an
appearance I'll be kind of I'm going to
do Rosie because you're the okay but
it's it's fact it is adjusting to the
new size fast yeah you want to do that
yeah no no look it like I am no disco
but it's like a spider or something like
and you walk through like that doorway
and there's the web act right it's like
yes yeah do we wake her up that well no
it basically he right here he just
you're holding someone to smaller very
briefly but you'd not just like that
around feeling that smart paint no I
mean I'm a method RP look I'm like an
idiot as I knock it off him like the
Gotti
he just surges out of my club grab thing
by this one by the center yeah
Biggs it brings it back but he is try is
like he's been it and he's like trying
to pull it back
but tula gotti it's heavier than it
should be
oh I see how heavy but he's tribal he is
grabbing it and he is moving it an inch
at a time but with incredible effort
like a mule near Tamiya Tamiya roll with
it
no no you can you can you can pull it
you can pull it but you want to pull the
Gotti oh I see it's totally got inches
exactly yeah
yeah you can just lean back back yeah
absolutely
are you happy you have returned back to
cut through here with us now and then
momentarily and like we did you who is
it good to look good next time your
boots got the hair wrong but I was fine
Marvin that's my first one I found that
I'm going to bounce in grab the stuff
try to pick up the diffused focus can I
do it yeah you can grab a bouncing black
bounce out return with ligado dangling
from it well I don't know before you
give it back to me I'm actually headed
and I don't want you to have it now oh
okay I'm offering it you hold on a
second I don't know if it's just going
to move back on okay Oh bag yeah and
then they get it back at this that's
true you're at the end of it Oh have you
ever seen river like a and I'm overjoyed
to reveal hmmm that you know people
still make these they're a fortune
teller
oh yeah yeah does you have it and you're
approaching Chris it's going like that
like it's folding and slopping you know
yourself in geometric shapes like it's
trying to find the right shape that will
catch that will catch the thread oh boy
alright you know what I've had enough of
this I'm just going to walk out of the
forest holding this thing and hope that
it put in a birdcage I'm just like you
know what Denard you're with me we're
going to walk out of here hopefully this
little release its grip on walnut let's
just get it to the edge of the forest
should do we just look a buck I like to
in this day and age yeah the cart get
out faster yeah well we have McKinley
walnut here oh no I'm already up and
sprinters very calmly just like walk
towards you like no no
everybody together together we can
definitely stay together but luck if
along that's um no sure yes and it's
good closer you get to the cart every
third or fourth step your woman oh oh
thank god what okay what is wrong I'm
overseas in those moments just some just
that oh oh I think she would just be I
mean I think she's just like
determinedly just walking okay exactly
but it's like it's almost like am like a
Firefly Oh light blinks lashing got it
got it okay yeah so I'm actually being
trying to lure you even closer and
continue to try to get that far flying
side of George yeah like you know you
101 one of four steps is Maliki so I'm
going to pause wait as well not for a
second long solely stuttering or
whatever and then just take a little
inward moment and be like be like I'll
find her for you thank you
ah nice okay okay I do
y'all just missing my girl may leave him
oh that's the best directly all right
I've lured her to the point where she's
no longer radiant exactly okay what's
this what's this now otherwise it's just
continuing to flip through some
catalogue of a cult
geography cult geometry okay Table Talk
this time it's submission listen I do I
have reason to think that it wants to
bind me or can I just wear it I wear it
on one wrist do you think that it wants
to bind you but you but but that doesn't
have to be how it goes you don't know I
mean the focus you've never had three
symbols in it before what does it
represent to have three in there you're
struggling
well you're a box put in a box
orientation yeah certainly breakage okay
you're you're now I said towards the
cart enough to be yeah yeah and you can
you can start steady yourself like you
have you need rest on that okay yeah
I'll just breathe it up against that and
I have vague memories of big spoon
anchor thread it's like there's a lot
there's so many issues like hey you're
back happy not at all like like you see
her looking uncomfortable you're like oh
thank god the time you're agitated yeah
that fun can't make me go crazy on it
sounds like trying to like very weakly
like climb the cart like she could just
go to sleep like a bag of bones alright
can I can you just not let this take him
and I'm going to drive us the eff out of
this forest all right yeah yeah yeah
pretend it's eggy
I mean hop up in the front and exactly
it is it's like kinda crazy yeah yeah
exactly it's like a um like a Rubik's
Cube like made all out of like Bezier
curves yeah that is a four-dimensional
and constantly trying to confound itself
I'm trying to solve some puzzle correct
imagine if you will absorb swoop you
know what I was it was actually true
this is actually true I never even known
then it just conceivably opened a way to
like mix your finger oh wait I got it I
got a good result it hold can you hold
that thing
my name is Bernard cute name yeah I like
you too thank you
well that's good sauce or build it so
yeah velvet can really can hold it but
it constantly doesn't want to be held so
it appears to simply it's moving shit up
in the debate
okay Michael you're going on buddy yeah
yeah we're gonna have to like find a box
murders boy yeah open no listen Nicole
focus is a big responsibility and we had
a box aaaand Hispanic Garza wine to come
to our eyeballs friends you one chest
much for me I'll return this is a
blender doesn't every time this jar vive
all given roses like protective now I
don't have to know whispers my jar of
eyeballs um I bought you in the in the
back with my staff can I know i yeah I'm
in okay so it's now us in the cart yeah
we're just sitting across reach other
thing is floating on the waiting room
struggling against the bell they have uh
uh and then up there yeah I guess the
hell out of this forest yeah fast as
possible trying to see ya so you can use
I to do some night traveling there's no
rest for us tonight finish the game no
no okay okay so you just continue west
and then after significant travel you
hit the high road right which is a
coastal road and it has a yellow
substantial amount of travel north now
on the next part of the road and in your
mind you're sort of calculating the
distance from here to scala and you
think that if you're able to solve this
if you're able to solve this with a
minimum of hassle mhm
you should be able to get to Scala at or
you know very close to the date the
princess requested oh okay so and does
that take into account the girl in the
locket or is that I can be like okay
okay okay so you can imagine quick we
can manage it you should be able to do
it okay okay I see this trip is a good
night what's our specialty get things
done right yeah right away anyway that's
why we're still getting in the cart now
it's all don't want I get fucked again
exactly but it's oh it's a it's a lot
it's a lot of travel I mean every now
and then that focus kiss risk just able
to get away right from build it
necessary hits the ground and mix it and
then velvet scoops it back up and
continues to do this sort of eldritch
juggling procedure that would seems like
it could make a coin or two at a local
fair that's pretty neat that's a good
that's a good idea okay yeah this is the
episode of the money-making idea so it
is no longer Henson Thurman so it lasts
it lasts for an hour although I can take
time to instantiate a new velvet to take
over for the other one okay so that is
the method I'm constantly I'm going to
do this ritual now that same yet to
change all of it and yes this thing but
what I wanted to look what I want to
look at the duration was longer if I
can't cast it a higher level but I do
have a wild wishes going on
I've been like trying to experiment with
it by like Chris trout I could not love
you more
you're almost K level like not there and
not even close but like like an
invitation but compared to these two
Wow yeah mister watch it 200 spinning it
boom cranes ever yeah yeah okay so um
one of the things we try we gotta high
yeah should have tried it with his knife
do you see anything happening yeah
anything there probably not what I want
to do is see if it can be like clamped
into a certain state pressed between two
sheets perhaps but the other thing that
I have is I'm one of those silver chains
the maelys with the symbol on it from
one of the assassin
and I want to dangle that in front of
this of the wriggling focus is that the
reactor that it helps marvelous this is
great I mean I have to be like I can't I
have to be like a neutral drivers sucks
who cares that's a very very interesting
technique throughout the eldritch
eldritch world are the winds are strange
tonight no that's my parody of myself so
imagine if you will a dark wind so far
you are so light unlikely Cap'n you can
gain points when instead wastrels dish
so so you you and you with you endeavour
to have lagari interact with his you on
t dagger yeah
called so recently from a tomb in
Chilton and invariably he just tries to
fight it but he can't really get it
stuck and so every time when he's trying
to stick it it's like parrying it'll
just create a little shape that's good
for parrying that oh I say in an instant
so it is responding to these attacks
absolutely absolutely but the god is
getting too into it but you he don't
even the point you might have sucked the
karna face my fears boy yeah yeah you
didn't yeah we are fun exactly so I
think I'm the only one who likes Pagani
yeah exactly
so you proud of em 50 yeah he just
flipping around but he's mad he does not
want to be called off of this task well
it's like whether it was like a dog or a
like good job no you did that's what I
wanted you know perfect great go back
here no so he so he crawled he's crawled
up onto one of the velvet couches he's
crawled up and he sort of wrapped
himself around the handrail and he just
has an eye on this thing yeah does not
like it and he want you to know that he
doesn't like it exactly and he doesn't
want a situation where there's like a
pecking order and
body is lower no no no you know what I
mean it's not able to dominate it right
so you get you get the the silver chain
of the mail if Colt out and as you bring
it close it folds itself up around the
chain in links so that at the very
bottom is the sign of the earth then the
sign of mail it then this third symbol
here and then five extra blank symbols
around the silver edge 58 those eight
nice so do at that is it still
struggling
no no it's found purpose it need to be
it's a different alloy right and at that
at that temperature at that occult
temperature yeah it wasn't stable Ally
not enemy okay thank you
huh really big thing everybody exactly
don't give them good to know college is
no game good again if you guys get hit
oh now take a little bit it's real good
hang on I'm glad we're on yeah yeah
humidity lay it down underneath and it
goes up this way and then the cloak
comes over and it forms a second red
ring in the same pattern with the stars
on the cloak of stars Oh another like
your level five garb like sitting across
you the whole time like
such a champion exactly you can listen
you know again yeah yeah you know what
uh I just look online alright it's like
but it's like this you look like you're
like in a whiskey commercial you look at
um realtor burns just like perfectly a
family of course I'm just like silently
like your I see you messing with it and
I'm just like anyone gels onto the
necklace I'm like oh and you start
putting on I like do it this isn't yeah
this is what he is this is what he's
about so uh but this is this has taken a
while of experimentation what have you
filled coriander in on older guys long
right what of the horse so mama should I
believe any of it he's hungry his help
so she's going to need oh yeah
she's going to need at least another
medallion and we got some toys Bernard
mm-hmm bang on the couch a horse horse I
just like keeping my Italian let's hear
a good thing all right I'm going to top
of it one more day unless you need to
keep your so that was going to go home
with the terrarium other coiling but if
you wrap it around it's just like a it's
like a Klondike bar like it's just like
bite yeah out of this lozenge of gold
yeah yeah I've told all about
Melisande Maliki but whenever I see me
like whisper because I don't want to let
that walnut oh serious yeah it's very
much within your shell Sears yeah you
know I mean so here everything your elf
ears here they say say yes everybody
says everybody says that um so and then
I talk I tell coriander all about how
much walnut was glowing when she was
possessed by the spirit of a leaky which
one I may not have realized and maybe
has always overhearing but I tell her I
was like glowing and I think she was
possessed by a forest goddess so I got
research that when we hit the next
library
yeah exactly exactly maybe gonna do any
and then I don't even know what's going
on back inside this cart and I don't
want to look so hopefully they're
figuring it out and when they come out
there'll be two different organisms in
there and that's all I got okay well we
good
it was a huge problem but now I kind of
thank you very much so it so this takes
the better part of this zone yeah to
resolve your issues obviously corianders
getting the full data feed subscribe to
the RSS okay really doubt RSS or they
maybe are in RSS stands for Rosie right
right it's a rosy syndication system
that's right or the Rosie Simple
Syndication so you are you pull up to
the great city of Neverwinter in recent
decades it has there has been some
turmoil and suffering but as I suggested
last time do you're excluded history
skills they've definitely put that
they've definitely been able to put the
town back together it still bears the
marks of some historical influences on a
you know global epic scale okay but this
it's fine
what is the so there is the thing that I
remember from what we saw in the locket
well does the river out the river of the
river in the center of the city that
runs to an ocean and that is where we
need to find the vantage point where
that view is visible there's a crown in
the day right yeah okay exactly right at
night currently well no right right now
York you're pulling in a whole morning
nice you're pulling into town with the
rest of the other carts and your guess
is that you'll need to you know head out
to the docks probably okay all right
let's do it
trying to try to find the perspective
that's opposite right
because we know the tower yeah there was
yeah she looked like she's in a tower
three small windows circular stairs you
can see the coast and the city out the
window at the same time okay which
implies that it's probably far away from
the coast like if you can see the coast
and the city then it's probably on the
opposite side of the coast where the
river is visible so let's head there
okay she's going through around it I
like it you're hearing so this is this
is the largest town that the sea team
has ever entered they are very small
fish in this pond as you but you were
able to drive your way out you're you do
try to do try your best to navigate
through this brand-new town just using
what you know about you know city
manufacture doing your planning exactly
doing you're doing your best to try to
figure it out but this this large river
that cuts straight through is giving you
some help you're able to get out to the
incredibly busy dock area this is you
can't you can't see something out there
that you would it isn't obvious from
here the place that you saw looking in
but you do notice a large ship
three-masted ship whose main sail
where's the livery of acquisitions
incorporated coming through this ship I
mean so seeing that we all see that
oh yeah it's huge you I recognize this
crew you don't you don't
it is you know you are familiar with you
are familiar with the airship right
acquisitions incorporated by ownership
which I have canonically named the
wyvern
think that was the man maybe there's
another name I've been on that show in
any case we wear the Webber right I mean
I don't know we're in the time line are
probably okay but the this is not that
ship that was a that was like a
mystically engineered airship type
contraption right this is not that this
is a sailing vessel it's listing pretty
substantially to one side and you can
see yeah you can see along the the back
serving like that the captains quarters
type area you can see that there's sort
of like a wooden cutout and on the left
across the window and this sort of
design you can see a woman reaching her
hand out across this window and on the
right the wooden cut is and the wooden
cutout there are two men reaching this
way hmm and on the back it says
acquisitions incorporated the Merry
Widow
very like yeah definitely want March
right down there check it out and fix
that boat um well so are both of you
know I mean I want to network with the
other dish incorporated I mean like what
if it's I mean what if it who knows it
could be it could be anyone we could
meet new people it could be omen it
could be anybody who knows there could
be any persons true now I grew up as a
sailor and a Fisher and so it's true let
me I don't know how much you guys have
been exposed to this kind of duffel
before but when it is listing this
severely that means that it is in some
amount of distress and we probably need
to fix it well then let's go okay I go
fix your boat all right I'm going to tie
up the cart indicator and ER yeah
exactly they say just just it's starting
to bustle around here you're able to
find a you're able to find a place for
your cart in front of a dockside in
called the staggers and Jags but below
this below staggers and Jags there is a
sign very much like the
one at the drowning courtier there's a
sub sign that also has a kink livery and
you can see the small mailbox that's
similar the one you have please
I can click set up bars blood alcohol
yeah
staggered in Jags I got a Titan we
looked at the locket lately since we got
the tail no enough since it got here
I was going to say like my first thought
upon getting here wasn't hey it's a boat
I thought who's reaching - yeah well I'm
trying I'm trying to like things it is
matter to like not see what well I mean
yes on you oh and there was just again I
forget that's it three we have I got it
can I get perception roles from the sea
team that's very good mmm Evan I think
as well this is be very delicious so at
the same exact moment I mean if it's a
full on it's a full on nautical knows
assault out here all fish guts it's real
real intense and they're just baking in
the Sun don't we thank you you're
looking and then it's like just the
breeze comes in and the two of you sort
of turn your head at the same time and
you know a little nest a little birds
nest that has been constructed sort of
up on a lamppost around the crown of it
you can see a little gold glinting out
of the edge of the lamppost nest
I like the idea we both see it like the
tallest and the shortest characters okay
like blue exact same angle
yep activities life you want to go check
that out
while I open I'm going to check out the
walk and real quick how high up is it
well you could reach up and get it okay
dad you're high you can just you can
chip in okay all right plug it out yeah
where as well sure there's a golden
locket Oh on a golden chain yeah I got
one too that's not cool now what happen
yeah open up now you open it up and
inside this locket you see a young woman
stay
and she seems incredibly distressed at
the same and she immediately upon seeing
your face takes the locket and looks out
one of the three portal windows of her
Tower
and one is exactly the same family to be
close right within the general direction
of error yeah yeah like a life it's like
a live feed yeah can you hear us
can you hear us there's there's not
there's no okay she she nods like okay
um can I show her the boat why'd you do
it
show her the boat and then look back at
her so she knows we're here yeah exactly
so you you show her the boat and she be
sure the voting to show her back and she
just she nods and smiles okay child a
boat a boat go by let's think it wanna
do I'm especially attend to yeah exactly
so close the best part is if if you
retain all of that connection and then
Walnut assisters Walnut London you know
but it's like it's it's still there like
the entire tank so it was just you know
barely stoic angry but she's like always
standing next to cook first now touches
herself doing it is a little bit is like
I know something she needs to very weird
they're showing the locket like if she's
looking out and we're seeing like the
live feed I was going to do produce
flame and just throw one up in the air
Oh flare like hell yeah sometimes drop a
little hurry into a I'm uh and I just
goes up in here and see if I can see
push it in can I be by the shame playing
the rocket from the oh I see it's like
looking out from here
yeah here we lost your life yeah exactly
it's incredibly slight but you think
that you might see it but immediately is
you start throwing fire around on these
docks by these ships sure you get mobbed
well like this what do you think you're
doing
no time for autographs sir I have a
child to find you like one time I'll be
back to sign anything you want or
they're kind of they're kind of like
boxing like they don't know how much
more fire you're going to throw out I
guess that's it
oh right here it's been a while since
I've seen some like good like classic
walnut no good like a couple a couple of
them they walk a bit away but the Nate
turn around and keep an eye with the
rest summer out pulling ropes and you
know like all in Bolton's I like being
next to Denard is just like this huge
like leaves I guess that makes me as I
keep going I just didn't like are you
put off by being around water and all
her no oh I mean it's a lot interesting
um you know about land land land I
wouldn't say the one I would get maybe
this far away from the edge of the dock
and never any closer no reason she died
him I was being on the wood yeah very
pro would like it to be like try to come
for you they say oceans are the forests
of the sea I know it does that comes
over some children to every person I've
ever met
who said that to me it's very great each
other at least in my town like this now
this is yeah I like that
everyone says it I'm going to add it to
the rosie repertory pass and we'll do
say that ok we'll support Susie uh she's
not a prisoner that we could entertain
right like we didn't see any kind of
locking mechanism didn't it's not a
parent ok yeah so I'm sorry
well why is good I was going to try and
do something safer than the flame I want
to send glow man up and then I believe
him toward and you see it's larger or
smaller in the in the image it all
starts cinnamon
well the coarser the how far I can cast
him yeah in the range the range is not
it's not gonna making you just grab this
throw in here there did exist anywhere
yeah
yeah we can use the hot springs using so
many birds as Scouts or something don't
you tell me how to use my baby where did
your kind entitlement or swim out here
okay yeah sure so I noticed that these
are the dock folk not into my flames no
they're not if they're not pro fire
that's fine but I see that there's some
nest-building thing and so I will call
upon my forest friends and I want four
strings my first friends I want your
nastiest your most slimy ax stock bird
get rate up he goes Pelican yeah I want
elegance right I want like cormorants
that like they they're like oh yeah I
got to do something they're like rip
away from their handlers you know like
the fish and cormorants yeah check it
out and so I want them to go you know
figure out where it is and I want to
watch their path I look like I could go
so team walnut takes to the sky dan you
heard him here w walnut walnut fest to
share a locket with me not a director
bird yeah exactly that's a good idea
yes Yeah right good idea I never I work
with her and I go okay I've got this one
goldang goes by oh and when I think I
get so happy I'm going to give it and
then just my rest of the time yeah yeah
it's just in a little bathroom it's a
lot of honkin I mean again this is this
is the reality will notice that these
birds have you know in the course of a
normal day these are not birds that work
together
no these birds do not support one
another but today at walnut fest
1482 Oh Jonathan Livingston Seagull
right and I reiterate if life they are
they are wing to wing and they have they
have left and you're sort of like trying
to reverse engineer this location from
this
um actually it takes them it takes them
a fair bit of time but they get close to
the to the tower that she's in okay and
so you think you think that you could
chart on a map great how to get there
wonderful from the dot okay and then is
land on the roof and then they just
start going sick house with the bird
coos okay every way for the shittiest
tower and white large he's in toilet
towers I love it
well I think she did it like that was
the thing that did it and it was like it
was okay right in de yeah in the locket
yeah you can see that one of the birds
has sort of landed like in the crook of
the window right and you can see that
she has put the locket on she is wearing
it and you can see this she reaches out
with two hands and grabs the bird whoa
very quickly okay and then starts to
tear it apart and eat it what's Lieber
there maybe she's starving though maybe
she's hungry
oh she's hungry or she ate well yeah
slimy goal bird yeah okay either she's
crazy or she's hungry so she's gonna
have to find her is not so bird I don't
know I'm not gonna show many of em so
yeah I'm Pro bird it's Probert oh okay
you'll kill it for me yes okay like
what's a lot of good this can wear the
hair around nearly there listening to
the blocker right we know where that is
I mean the birds are there we'll we'll
find it can we just just just wanna say
hi at the ship walnut
we'll come back to the ship yeah she's
not going anywhere
she's not even doing for being
stationary this thing strongly the left
but that's okay she got a snack okay la
mode
be here it's not about what if I'm not
well not we don't know who's on that
ship to be anyone when I split the party
walnut yeah
anybody could be on it alright beautiful
blonde oh yeah it could be be seems like
it's about right and a potent party on a
boat yeah they don't have heard
murdering honey well they have a very
nice mahogany bow that is respectful hey
I can go get that let's go get the girl
and sorry out I am we go yeah we got it
you need a boat I see them like tune
across that water
oh it's across the block yeah I was in
time another frozen pack yeah I thought
I was in town yeah I do start swimmin
Hank so if we could do that
or I could just lie there finally yeah
shall we
please lass honor you should know I can
only fly with a friend I go oh there we
go
no I'm not ready to get you I can only I
can I can touch our willing target
including my sister that excludes myself
and they can fly
a horse yeah I get such a horse yeah
it's touching my dealings are whores all
I know willing target I mean that's so
I'm going to speed and you can make it
fly let it fly across well I'm going to
do that per diem adjudicate that joy it
doesn't agree you do have a carry to
pass if I'm remembering fly right there
is a carrying capacity yeah I don't
think I can carry three people no but
somebody else use a big boy or he carry
could fly us there and you haven't even
able to find a seed yet yeah I would we
chance you to a kink boat lettuce
lettuce festival guide review by the
worst case there is a method for what
line up another couple of to get there
by boat in our own
I like I do this it's a boat and instead
of a huge balloon it's just tethered to
very small denial just the clamps in my
mouth a boy there's always enough
solution everything you don't have to
whip me I'm going to do it anyway you're
like gosh you do a balloon like we're
all going to go in the same direction
the winter is not necessary so you you
walk out the dock and the boat the merry
widow specifically so hey listening so
bad the gangplank is sliding pretty
substantially across this thing I'm glad
I can fly yes um can I is it
lievable distance first we'll Rosie of
course okay I'd like to leap and take
control of the ship because I have I
have main controller for commentary yeah
yeah yeah I'm going to come and do this
ship I just I don't want to take out
like I said going to be like I'm your
captain now I okay I just want to like I
just want to UM take take control the
sails so it's not listing quite so badly
well because I have a background command
sailing
okay yeah you know my way around your a
salient row yeah so as you as you jump
from the dock up to the edge of the ship
and get in you can see the side of the
hull because it's tipped over like this
you can see that side of the hull has
substantial damage below the waterline
okay even you'd have to you'd have to
look closer to see you're just surprised
to see it as you you jump over but we're
talking about like huge scrapes the
occasional occasional actual hole that's
been repaired hado Haseley from the
inside but you can tell that there has
been like attempts at entry or something
below the waterline this okay like that
so I think my first priority is to try
to get the boat to stay still so my
friends can board it and then we will go
below decks and investigate okay so you
you jump up onto the ship and you can
see you can see a man up in the rigging
with a pistol pointed at you on the dock
vomit on the deck of the ship right and
he says who the fuck are you and that is
our game for this week shadow council
may our labors pleasing
hey we got a commercial break between
between now and table talks consider
subscription deftly helps us make the
show but in any event
don't go nowheres come back and hang out
this just a little bit yeah
you