time is the enemy the past it threatens
the fastest weapon you wouldn't make it
past a second and last a question play a
brash and reckless to choose a car
solution you saw was prudent in any
soccer poker to don't become the putrid
it's that well-fed I pursue in no
mountain too steep for dungeon too deep
to send expanded remarks up to the top
of the peak of beneath they see Yugi
they come like sharks to it while I swim
in that money bill by Carl Barks through
it so send your National Parks drew it
I'll send him home in a natural box with
the clothes tie the most of the parts
included save your breath for a cleric
confessor that there's a lesson and life
is attending professor but if you're
seeking my official advice sign on the
dotted line and wish of the choice it is
a better show
hello I am Tycho Brahe have panic in
pass I am also a manifest Hera would
draw and CEO of acquisitions
incorporated but today he run a game of
Dungeons and or dragons with my friends
to my ride Dragonborn are persistent
noblets in there well we did it they did
it there's several more hours of this so
I want you to conserve your energy it
was the end no that's a victory lap no
no no to the right of my right wrapping
the natural world wala dumb grass I said
it like a baguette cuz it's the birds
breaking its wings in depth yeah so very
long item at respect to my left not your
grandma's grandma except for those rare
cases where she is your grandma's
grandma Rossi beasting to the meter
level of my left a top-secret character
will be revealed shortly yeah
to the left of my left of my left
emerging is though from a mist trout
Chris Brown
now do you want to say no you who is
playing our mr. Kurtz oh absolutely
okay no because it because we found her
on the street it was really weird yeah
this is like a fuse every time I've used
somebody's real name at this table you
guys are like it's like this no that's
too bad she's niihka Harvard
she's a writer she's written the hell
the real names of the table it's already
happening um
you're a monster well anyway I should I
should emphasize before we get started
dad I think I think I speak for all of
us when I say that we missed doing the
show very much last week and I spent
Thursday all the time I was not playing
the game all the time I was doing labor
that did not please you on pleasing
Labor's
we talked like constantly about it we
had a cool meet up did in the bar
everyone yelled hi DM daddy and yet made
a me and I screamed daddy at the top of
our lungs everyone else started
screaming down Jerry was there too in a
public place now but there something
that is sad is that Kate by which I mean
Rosie feasting her she says that she
doesn't remember what is going on in the
game under the boathouse no I don't need
it off-camera talk here foam here what
do you have behind the curtain
yeah a lot where do you want me to start
this is this is my novel I
remember I remember
there's a there's an angry narrow queen
on a boat who is lousy with Jim eggs
she's on a slide it by one jim dark
that's that's one word anyway so
sleight-of-hand know when last he feels
here
when last we saw our heroes they had
made an alliance with team Nyad a branch
of acquisitions incorporated that
operates out of Neverwinter now there
were issues with the vote I mean let's
be let's be honest the boat is staffed
crewed by novel individuals there is
their decision estaphan Corbin shale
then the main thing that we know about
this gentlemen is that he's mostly warm
hair I suggested previously and I'm
gonna maintain this concept that were he
to shave completely it would just be a
human head rolling around on the deck
with the waves right hmm
is it a metaphor I think so what I we
don't know for sure it's a theater the
mic we're doing hair forged hair Forge
it's his hair for in addition there
obviate er a new role you have not heard
of this this task an obviate er Fenn
made best friends with Kath risk drought
so she says of all people well the offer
was accepted certainly she specializes
in adjusting people's levels of life
creating maximum convenience for her
party they are backed up vitally an
important task their documents are
dulled Roma also down in the basement of
the ship I'm just using all the wrong
words for the boat trying to get a rise
out of you
down in the lowest basement part of the
ship favorite old down in the bottom of
the ship belly yeah
yes this is perfect in addition to
filing and filling out the most
important documents she was also before
the rest of the deckhands came on trying
to make repairs to the ship they've been
having some problems
they've been having problems getting in
and out of the harbour recently they'd
had their entire boat and crew
requisitioned by the bay team
assholes all I think we can all agree
every member of the B team every current
member of the cosmos that they have
accounted is an asshole
exactly now and cor Michelle had
suggested that boats plural were having
problems you saw no evidence of that as
soon as the boat that you were on
escaped the harbor immediately terrors
from the deep made themselves manifest
rusty you know provisional harpoons at
best flung up on to the deck people
pulled off down into the deep some of
them said something strange and hurled
overboard that was the situation we
found ourselves in Intel Dragonborn
narcissist DeMarre Blitzen leveraged
divine power and created a scenario with
the command spell that enabled the
conflict to cease and someone of rank in
Merrow society to enter into a
conversation and what she said was that
they're clean sought an audience to
discuss the matter of your kings
gruesome treatment of our sovereign
Queen and she said something else she
also suggested that your king was in
fact Jim dark magic in addition she also
referred to you as servants of the eye
and seemed pretty confident in that
assessment mmm so that is the scene that
we open ourselves up to we allow the
narrative to penetrate our course we're
entering a shared you know sort of
narrative space Wow
yeah got any more nice
Falls of Medicine ellipsis yeah yeah
it's going right a little sinuses woody
um
when history check help me understand
what servants of the eye means certainly
I know the job dark magic is you have
heard of this fellow
yeah you uh I can recall a time inside
the test market yeah when you invoked a
mr. dark magic well we also met him yeah
indeed we have met him and killed him so
but not in that order
he's birth two men killed Lisa
transfigured him back from three chicks
yes sure
we in life we gave him death yeah Mike
we shall make him a king with this queen
with cheese speak to one such as myself
are we all on level terms alright are
you are you are you addressing I would
because I wanna blend n't marrow
priestess looking person I where I want
to know is is she mean the servants of
the of the eye or servants of the
acquisitions incorporated logo the I
he's a little bit like an eye does it
with a hey in it
she literally hey I at the letter do you
want to keep garden magic of the of the
vestigial I'm shadow council mayor
Labor's please you by alyssum please
apportion the riches true our precious
council BAM 24 from your care of Kate
holy cow
so you want to know the term servants of
the I yeah it's it's like um it's like
gelatin or something like that I guess
one of these terms like there are so
many different servants of the I like
everybody always thinks that they have
come up with this yeah you can you can
think if like six different sure six
different groups of a-holes now listen I
reeled it I don't know if you saw that
that's a tuna and no yeah yeah I'm I
hate today I should be able to know
which servants of the I out of the six
with a role like a twenty oh yeah
assuming that assuming that that's the
case
yeah I mean you know I mean nothing that
you can think of directly relating to
your group this ship
none of those pieces of information line
up mmm but you had it you had another
you had another concern mr. drab oh just
that like maybe she thinks that that gym
is is the the king of this of this
entire operation and we are like her his
knights
which is not the case but how do you
phrase questions like this friend
important friend there has to be some
further deference she's not friends yes
sir are you coming down oh yes
are you yelling this from the crow's
nest I realize I have a question then I
say to fan yeah excuse me one moment
and and I invoke the power of flight
from and I just and I said my apologies
in just a moment and the thing is
already encircling us yeah around me and
I just go limp and it drags me uneasily
out of the crow's nest and then sort of
like a like somebody has missed their
cue you know this is very this is very
theatrical
yeah pardon me for a ways yeah there's a
there's a period of time where you are
come just completely just crucified in
reading so you can you can you're
welcome to make your entreaty however
you want to but it's absolutely vital
that your human body conform to the body
that is in the narrative yes so please
please continue but I but if I want to
see that hunch that twist oh well I
wouldn't ask it in flight that seems
rude I did the opportunity to get down
there and genuflect I'm not gonna do it
while I'm talking
that's not that's it you could though I
could I come from a matriarchal society
I'm gonna do that so I'm going what I
mentioned if I might speak dragon and
then the tentacle releases me near her
feet or her fin yeah it's right at mine
about and then and I do not get up the
place is where your metallic objects
have sparks no you have small fires on
the ship Rosie's a little too fast
splayed out face down do you
queen of the of the Seas I am no Queen
Oh what are you I'm sorry speak dear for
when you say the servants of the I do
you believe us to be servants of of this
sort of a of a symbol or this one and I
have a the acquisitions incorporated
logo on my first set right and I display
that perhaps you think me an idiot I am
perfectly capable of reading your
letters I can pronounce
I enjoy she actually tree points that
the symbol she points it walnuts
documents her seal mm-hmm she's like
your your letters are not unknown to me
they're not relevant
I know poetry could possibly be rendered
in them but I can make your sounds well
I didn't know that I can read all I turn
to you guys I can read all letters it
didn't occur to me for a long time that
some people cannot read all letters all
written language
you found something new about yourself
yeah optimal times we don't let it was
so wounded right now so I want to look
at the reason I go so as you were as you
were looking at her Chris's here and
just sort of like a like a pilot like
when you like take one sock and like
just like put into their sock so they
don't get separated and just leave it on
the floor like that's his body at the
base base of this were splendid them and
the tentacle starts to come down to fly
me back up and and she's like I'm not
done with you yet so but as is happening
as you as you're approaching you can see
the ship just rocking on each side as
its surface is growing even it's growing
gents with Merrill okay well that looks
super green I yeah from the from this so
she's just trying to look very composed
it's just a cold sweat she's like we
could help you we've actually dealt with
Jim dark magic in the past successfully
and then she goes one two times to be
happy to be of service please call off
your and looks at Sarang goes what's a
nicer word for goons water dogs water
does water friends likes dogs
kin she reaches it she porpoise here she
reaches into a pouch and then pulls out
a pearl and hands it to you okay eat it
we have a designated person for eating
weird yeah
fear not I have many okay great we have
a designated person for eating weird
stuff I don't mind
I've already on the deck I've done drop
it in I feel like you're not gonna okay
you want me to eat this yeah yeah she
takes me one just drives like a marble
just look drops it on the deck just is
it it's by your mouth all right well if
you push it into your mouth and I don't
see anything happening here yeah okay
well mine exactly this so you can hear
this happening you can you can hear that
what was a pitched battle has now sort
of been tamped down into something
approaching diplomacy but you can tell
that it's balanced on the edge of a
knife and it's the sort of thing that
boldness and wherewithal you know you
know it says it's a sort of thing that a
person of destiny would intervene in
that's that's all I'm saying is is there
a door that I may enter from right now
the best way you may able the best way
you're able to make your way on was into
a into a crate by the main missed oh so
I'm like I am in a pot going I am I am
okay fantastic
do I have to strength check to just bust
out of that beast
absolutely vital electronic thank you to
my dandy group for buying sturdy so this
conversation from a crate on the deck
I'm starting to rock it back and forth
now to just feel like something's
product if it's begun to shimmy but you
shimmy it to the point where no you're
against the mast and you can't go here
or in that direction I'm just concerned
okay Rosie walks over to it and kind of
watches it as you guys you're moving
over like the marrow on the deck just
are like there's no reaction yet but
they are making sure that they are
containing everything about this yeah I
make eye contact with them too yes as I
walk toward the box like yeah we're both
watching each other didn't you watching
me watch some Jewish guys yep and I'm
gonna study this box I'm gonna toss the
look back to walnut all right Oh weird
yeah I'd like to try to pry the lid off
the crate with a semi master without
doing a strike on ya at the monastery
you know they had this crate so they
couldn't get open they're like I need
some kind of rod or something
like that God's pickle truck exactly
fifteen thirteen thirteen is okay you
you you whack the side of the you whack
the side of the crate and you're able to
pop up one corner of the lid of the land
indeed okay in my confusion I hear
something attacking the other side of
the box and it flips backwards right
because I'm just like oh my god so it's
spilling out i'm ceremoniously is a what
you would consider tall but currently in
its prone form it is long
a golden scaled lizard folk and wearing
these strange vaporous robes and
traveling finery and next to her is a a
battle ax which looks brittle and made
of ancient bones and she stubbles to her
feet and then very proudly takes her
time brandishes her weapon looks around
at everyone says halt in the ship in the
name of the blintzes an accord
[Music]
and she looks around she kind of
reserves all eyes turn on dinar she
freezes she checks her bucks for a
minute I'm famous
alright do you mean assign that
grandfather she gets down into a praying
position next to no just just utterly at
your complete service and and shocked
she says it would be an incredible honor
for you to know my name I am the chosen
one
Cupid and then she gives herself a self
high five
impressive digitation sparks come out
like these people were queens you fish
monsters who do work things are very
different in this realm aren't they
marrow are moving across the deck
writhing on the fishy ass tails and they
have got pearls for everybody let's
drink this with us that's a great
question it was to be said yes i'm i
planed rebus no land really end up who
knows should I
no no it's um you're welcome to look
around Ford Revis in the same way that
you would see in a box to start hitting
boxes I see what you're doing I hit the
boxes - is it not I'll take two pearls
intending to hand one to my to my son
and I thought it was right behind me but
he's not
Jurgis loves drugs this is weird yeah
this has already taken ten of them no no
you can you can see you here decision is
Corbin salesy damn it okay he says you
can see him looking out past the front
of the past the front of the boat past
the priestess oh boy because you can see
him in the distance growing the thief I
get that dinging yeah thanks like that's
twice that's the same dinging oh yeah
this enough he's gonna marry this tui
like boy and his Danny you need to keep
an eye on this kid yeah he'll be back
it's like he's on this paladin holy
quest thing I think he thinks stealing
is wrong but I don't know how long he'll
feel that way so um do you know what it
could just be the business we'll take
care of it but uh if he doesn't return
it it's on is that how it works yeah for
sure
all right though man so good my friend
walnut no let me go way back so it's
good well we'll figure it out no one
looks like yeah totally so there there
are marrow so you have taken one you
have taken you have eaten the pearl yeah
I'm waiting for this pearl trip because
Pearl Jam's on it so after after a
minute or so passes you were beginning
to find it difficult to breathe hmm
it's gillyweed
Rosie what do you do like should have
asked first so that the priestess is
looking at this bizarre family reunion
isn't shaking her head she's like it's
no matter this will all come out fish
men are definitely trying to give you
this yeah very each they are each taking
in arm not not gently but not you know
not taking it for their own it's not
like WWE you know what I mean but they
definitely are they gonna push us in the
water it's time for you to come so with
my last breath I swing off my dock and
then oh look at all of my sweet sweet
not waterproof paper and I look at this
and I just enter your personal space
open up your whole horse person bag and
just show my donkey dancey bag in it and
I close it and I grab you and I go yeah
so it's like it'll end I think it starts
with the corner it's like it's able to
slurp up a couple of scraps like like
pasta and then it has to work much
harder for the bulk of the bag but
you're helping it along oh like yes
she's got her foot in it
see the motion foot I'm wearing the bag
I'm like well as like punished it takes
that for mother and uses the hills of
Italy - right
it's ventually able to get around it and
then twist itself closed a little bit
and we're thinking about cheek for two
weeks all of my papers getting turn to
mush so yeah yeah Rosie as we're getting
pulled off the ship is trying
desperately to give you tips on swimming
because she knows that you don't know
how
and so like it'll be fine because we can
breathe underwater it's gonna be alright
but she's she's like just do a lot of
kicking kick with your legs don't worry
so much she's hearing so the the marrow
are able to cut straight through the
water and you can out in front of them
is this this leader figure that was up
on the on the bow of the boat the front
the bow front if you no no I got it the
boat tip the nose
yeah the tip yeah it's one of the two
same four different art it's one of the
tube and then the deeper you get down
there is a it's almost like and you can
look at a glass and that the water and
oil separate it sits like that here but
for light it's there's you pass through
a period of darkness where your senses
aren't able to perceive anything and
then once you once you penetrate that
the lowest part of that it's nothing
like that
it's perfectly you you're in a place of
perfect visibility beautiful clear water
and you can see all manner of a radical
reconfiguration of how a city would work
mm-hmm
you can see you can see platforms
suspended and tied from trunks of kelp
you can see in the distance as you're
passing through small
you assume that their houses crafted in
concert with coral and in the distance
you can see what looks like the the
superstructure of it appears to be made
of massive boat holes that's a good boat
word right but they're all held in place
and then filled all around the rest of
it we again in concert with this shaped
coral but it's it is not it isn't it
isn't just like cement or something it
isn't just like a different type of
joinery this is live this is a living
reef that these marrow also dwell in as
well I'm trying to tabletalk him trying
to give you the best starwars experience
I can picture it's like dark little
mermaid that's right we've been over
this you know I made this note original
loop yeah exactly so you are you are
taken down into the great doors of this
hall and you can see that there's not
stairs of the classic sense they don't
require that but there are tunnels that
they travel through so their tunnels
don't need to be as tall right they just
pass it as you're being drawn through
here you can see various types of armor
tridents like you're moving into a place
that is heavily policed and you are
taken not to a not to a a royal chamber
but to something adjacent to it and the
the priestess brings you in and says you
could never you could never enter the
Royal chamber of our queen garb like
this makeover this what is it he looks
great late armor I'm just like
like a stone bedraggled yeah absolutely
I did what ever it is about this pearl
is allowing you to okay to conceive of
language here but you also of course
have your your mental capacity to
communicate as well that's true so you
can see you can see just in this in this
space
there's garb of various kinds for bipeds
hmm this is this is if this is not the
first time they've had visitors
apparently that's nice what's this
what's it look like when the
understanding that Christmas is probably
already disrobed
oh yes 100%
yeah 100% they have all kinds of
stitched it's almost like the kelp is
used in place of a textile so there are
pouches and bags to keep your things and
there's also food here there's some
something that looks like an apple but
they're sort of suspended from sheets of
seaweed mmm there's also fish all the
classic water foods a cute kid lets out
a long breath and say see I told you it
was 15 minutes even longer she
definitely is so wait I have a question
before we get started at the first
please put on some clothes so she starts
drawing like blah
so so are you part
lizard folk no because I mean like the
resemblance is uncanny
yeah she creams doing did we now
remember the shadow yeah plain like he
came out with was not there our friends
here sold me to the Shadow Realm house
Walter Robert yeah he went willingly I'm
sorry wait oh oh you know I seen her
Rosie saying something like in passing
yeah yeah wipe my memory that's why yeah
yeah yeah do endure or enjoy no indeed
or 60 years of shadow creation and
rebuilding I guess is the term here wow
yeah yeah you had to wipe your memory of
us oh because you could not exist in
such grandeur other line coming that I
mean have you seen this place being here
I was like on a boat and I'm underwater
this place is proud it's like so much
better
plus I'm like way famous there so I can
like totally get you into all the cool
places that famous bear no you're
totally famous but like it's gonna you
know I mean like this really needed you
said I'm your grandfather so who's your
I didn't think about through
hierarchy give me a second I need some
it's not Walter it's no longer you know
you mentioned Walter he's my great great
great great
no it's like seven or eight past okay
but he was so cool he was the one I
hated the movies she's already kind of
like why it's like this is not what I
was expecting at all so she's like yeah
we're from the realm of shadow are we
gonna box hold for a minute and then I
hold my acts in a kind of like cradling
way and I start whispering a little bit
hmm what's going on there little friends
hmm it's your it's your it's your jam oh
absolutely
oh absolutely yeah how do you want that
how you want this to go I wanna I want
to ask something I was like was he was
he always like this
I am I sure that this is the right guy
he was he was not my friend friends I
have one friend no I had two friends we
were okay it's easy
yeah we talked about this yes yeah it's
part of therapy honey
okay well maybe we can find your other
friend and I just kind of like pop it
back over my shoulder and I'm like okay
whatever
hmm-hmm just does it I mean yes he says
you must give him the button
Chris Brown the button the button that
fell from his clothes so long ago isn't
the naked guy yes I need really guys
she's super not sold on this
sucks he is my friend and I'm his okay
he says she walks up and she's like dude
I'm supposed to keep this button or
something I see
gets like suppose you're not even where
I don't know and she kind of like
positions it more or less or see his
crotch don't worry it's like right over
the glans no I don't worry I've already
taken the incorrectly like the smallest
possible there's probably not one of the
intended pieces of clothing it is a
strip of kelp I'm supposed to give this
to you I think it's from him and I just
like give that I just kind of like show
the ax sorry you indeed ah indeed she
wields us our house our is the agent
Onaga I remember indeed my friend and
now a battle ax
yeah but sort of but almost like
decrepit even more decrepit than usual
and transformed into this sewing ritual
acts he doesn't he doesn't seem mad how
have you been
well you've been through a lot oh you
know how fares my king oh boy Oh
he had many an adventure and I he was so
virile who certainly probably was before
I met him the king that different
different different man we don't have a
talk about your it's a before therapy
service apparently okay I would love to
let you know that even now he lives on
within me
I feel like it's better to not show him
the best King what yeah no it's fine the
cloak and now I'm gonna put it in the
bag first and I'm gonna put my cloak
back on ideally one day oh that's a good
question will they permit us to wear in
other words RAC is at the mercy of
whatever this kelp provides yeah I can't
go in there with my cloak it's not great
I see I gave you a nice with you okay
so that stuff isn't like my design steel
kelp also I just realized
mushrooms breathe underwater what's
Cathy situation look good like you said
him approach I fed him a pearl it's more
wine time my favorite yeah its moist
it's fine well not looks at all the
company goes
so there'll a separate changing areas no
it is a single massive as a single room
no one was just like okay you all can
you all do it and I won't watch and then
and then everyone leaves and then me
[Laughter]
Rosie's modest she's changing into the
halflings sized the most half-length
eyes garbs yet it's fine but it's it's
like um it's a almost a parody of what
you'd expect it's like a tiny like later
hosen it's like they don't they don't
have like the best yeah I mean like here
they don't have a lot it's a favor not
even they read a book it's like someone
they knew read a book and told them
about it when they were drunk yeah okay
well that happens to be
Rosie's fashion sense she she's thrilled
it's like it's like it goes down to just
above the knee ya know beautiful straps
yeah a little straps and she she doesn't
like she's not she's not good this level
of like de robing disrobing you know she
um she is just facing toward a walls to
it so as to be genteel and not to climb
on it yeah but she's jacked as hell
she's got this like roped corded old
lady muscle and like just a thoroughfare
and gnarly-looking
and then she she covers it up well it's
just a clone back tattoo yeah yeah
no she's got some cement a twisted
yeah this is a great don't play lower
yes I mean it's it is real labor yeah
that damn nail there's gotta be a pain
in the ass do I help ya I can help you I
am very good at this all right I got all
the buckles and I what what armor is
this the best everything I have it's
about everywhere it doesn't need to be
there's like no gears and stuff is a
steampunk pieces this is her dick okay
fine
she's gonna take some kelp yeah and
we'll my kind of start tucking it under
her robe there we go and then when she
takes off the robe there's just like a
halter top bikini that she's made she's
like the dress just yeah I want to find
like a bathrobe of kelp just like a
bathrobe tied and the in the middle
yeah just like barely open is it it's
not her baby the garbage all the way
from magazine-style um when in reef
business I wall that's where I had at
least five pieces of clothes she is
still covered from yeah let me also add
that because we're underwater like this
loincloth might I mean it'll work where
there's gravity
yeah and air is that the practice too
much but here it is not doing it's very
much just like a limbic depending on the
angle it's the same as not having it
exactly exactly it looks like it could
be like a cummerbund or the loincloth
torso decor napkin right so really make
sure to always stand in your interview
we're ready so stream three marrow
materialized in this in this place and
then lead you back through this tunnel
you're able to hold onto various points
of their Trident and you're sort of
pulled through this space and when you
enter into the the throne chamber mhm
as I said I said before you could tell
from the outside but in here is it's not
it's not decor it isn't like a like an
interior design choice this is a
completely functional reef mmm that so
fish schools of fish are moving on
harried there's curious eels poking out
to see what new what new sites Bugatti
is very curious about brethren there's
lots there are lots there's no shortage
of strange undersea friends for the
ngati down here but you are brought up
to up to an empty throne chamber behind
which there is a curtain of six scales
and kelp iridescent scales and then
there's a much something happens that
you can't sense whatever it is you don't
have the organ required to know when you
should be operating at maximum deference
down here they perceive some signal and
they immediately bow toward this empty
throne mm-hmm as soon as I noticed I do
but I can't yeah I bow does yeah look
around like oh yeah I'm watching him
yeah waiting for him to go
then I get taller
I think it'll hit you're trying you're
trying to lay down but you're a couple
inches up and you just kind of doing
your best there's some strange current
in here and then you can see that these
these gleaming scales and the kelp sort
of like rise up with the entrance of
this queen but they have called Sundra
frill you have overheard this oh my god
you have overheard this many times as
you were as you were preparing yourself
and then you can see that the the kelp
and the scales just sort of like they
rise up and they drape themselves over
what looks to be a maybe 15 foot long
salmon that fully salmon that's no ace
salmon it's just a fish just a fish it's
a to half mermaid not two tails you know
like a fish head and also a fish tail
like a fish it's just a fish it's just a
massive a massive fish and as soon as
she assertion she comes out and just
sort of comes to rest over this over you
know whatever the it's like um like sea
anemones and there's just soft just like
just drew lays down and then as soon as
as soon as she comes into contact out
from these out from this this mesh this
undersea Warren of the coral fish come
out and immediately begin to cleanse
every scale on her body and you can tell
is as you're watching this the
transformation it's like it's like the
Disney movie where it's like the glasses
come off and then the hair but like the
fish version she was a fish the whole
time wait so they become cleanser and
we're like oh now she
so mean and she's nuta fool she's a
clean fish yeah she's fat but still with
fish okay she's a very shiny fish and
now she's coming I'm gonna whisper to
hasard hungry I Marilyn snaps his head
just stare at him like that Sundra frill
addresses the group says uh servants of
the eye and remember it's like a salmon
mouth so the hi is real like too high on
the bottom and she says yes the last
time the I visited us is all smiles ah
smells of deceit well that's on my mouth
yeah yeah then I could see that look at
it he's not great lies lots of lies well
we're not with him yeah it's just a
quick sorry if she said he's not great
well what he I'm interested in what you
through speak of my husband
I thought we were talking about someone
else who is your husband save me guys
I'm tired
tell me is your husband Jim dark magic
yes King and I am his wife Jim dark
magic of the surface world
when were you Wed two years ago down
here where else I mean there's the
surface world is another place that
could gouge it or the mention of the
surface world she looks over at the
court the court note just just as the
guess the curious eels had begun this
place is now rapidly filling with every
tear of marrow society there's a lot of
curiosity about this and the mention of
this surface world as a place one could
possibly be married she turns her chin
over to over to one of the factions you
know that is a materialized here and she
doesn't have to say anything like that's
just ridiculous on the face of it you
can tell that whatever a salmon accounts
as a smile is now occurring I do the
same well it sounds like you've got
yourself a pretty good situation you're
a queen he's a king things are good yeah
what could we had an arrangement what
was it we would protect his vessels okay
mm-hmm as he maintained our pact which
was seven nights each year oh that's not
for you to know okay yeah I think so are
we gonna be at dinar again no I'm gonna
be here for it very gonna be like
dissociation all over the place so when
was the last time you saw King dark
magic a year ago and he's due quite for
his week hmm well so you will
communicate this to him
in any way I see fit
hmm and in exchange your people will
stop attacking our boats this depends
upon the actions of the king of course
there are many ways to communicate this
to him mm-hmm from our perspective my
feeling and I suspect the court will
agree is that when your bodies wash up
into the harbor of Neverwinter our
communicate course though it may be will
arrive hmm well we actually have a
direct line to your husband's um is that
so that is so great great Queen our
murders and subsequent beaching would
indeed be an effective method and as I
pause a little too long for anybody's
facing your eyes wander yeah you're
thinking like should I continue you but
there is another way in fact it may even
return response for you right now
I have there you hear a few Morden
chuckles from the court and they don't
sound like maro
you've heard that hmm if this crowd is
very large now it could hide any manner
of of participant in this court we would
give an air-breathing
we're air breathing why no but I know
we're here
I cannot my quest for 15 minutes is just
water this day I can I can attend to to
raise him via the spell of sending and
send a message you have not been able to
contact him any other way no do you
think we haven't tried as my husband I
just wanted to understand the to
ascertain the directness the nature of
these attempts to better understand why
he I cannot believe that you are still
talking I go so I will never I've never
used this spell before sending which I
may send a message of 25 words to a
person I'm familiar with indeed tweets
that's right magic DMS out there hashtag
that's nice
no it's okay god I I can receive a
message back I provided that they wish
to send it I said I assume yeah so what
how would you how do you want to
construct hold on did you draw a picture
of Queen Sondra frill yeah I'm just
trying to draw the dice be sure to draw
some of the pilot fish oh we gonna just
like framing her yeah he doesn't share a
little person like for scale yeah
just somebody that you're holding Europe
oh sorry the question was what's your
message what's my message yeah gosh do I
want to maximize these 25 words on it he
can't really write you can't reply to me
okay when I asked him he also he made
nice new phone who this and that's it
I'll see he's somebody got to be from
ago he right yo your fishwife gonna kill
us and come down sleep with yous no no
no never
I don't think you've met him before I
had met him I've met him to it and I
thought it was horrible
I wasn't I mean he's okay yeah I like
him I mean yeah okay um do you think
that there's something that we could say
to get him down here that's not what's
currently happening Oh deception that's
a good idea
are we doing this by listless
communities at um I'm not saying in
front of the fish no I think this chance
of mr. dark magic coming down here for
what's actually happening is probably
zero um maybe we could tell him what
does he like
he likes spells he likes he likes being
adored I think he also likes not dying
of the direction sickness he's dying
others until there's a cure down yeah
for your sickness and your fan club this
year
can you don't send more than that oh but
a message like the header of the
messages he knows who sends it it's not
anonymous
exactly okay the intimacy is fun and you
gotta include the location from the mind
of yeah yeah let's start with that would
that information I'm a cartographer so I
can tell you that okay yeah we parcel
that out into our many words required
and then like a bit like we hello
friends Queen frill your wife has found
the cure yeah it's done mm-hmm
you must return don't mention the Queen
just who cares onesome just food
shopping fine go away is his problem
that I'm right or I'll work shopping
this right before I shut the door no
you're right let's just do it but he
might have an idea this is where we are
that's fine I'm gonna explain
I'm gonna say that's a cure to your
condition it's racism
I can grab a that yeah
the cure underneath a cure is is here
beneath the waves here is here beneath
ways and you're in water deep know the
name of where we are and what you call
manage it and a bunch of cool magic
yeah yeah yeah yeah team same team same
team see you send that one off I do send
it off and then how do you how do you
let me see the sending card real quick
to get take a look you get a tweet back
yeah yeah hope so yes but this is this
requires verbal somatic and material
components oh no no I'm not worried
about the material component remise
saying you have to speak the Perl will
you will you speak but I'm saying it is
very obvious that you were casting a
spell in the middle of this in this
place and so these these tridents are
leveled and you are you maintain your
concentration and send it and then about
30 seconds pass and you receive a
sending back it says miss afraid of the
from Jim dark magic it says just cried
you you're with all those fish no
way
[Laughter]
Queensland right Queensland referral
says yes we have had more entertaining
wizards in our court have we not she
says she says child keep cupid is
immediately on the so we're totally
chill here she's like so like I'm also
royalty it's super cool to meet you and
everything also know a lot about like
people who don't come back like when
maybe when it's part of a prophecy or
like they're supposed to or like stuff
is happening and shits going down and
you're just you know weirdly alone
I totally get you on this like who who
is who is this King that we're supposed
to get i bet for us it's gonna be like
super easy it's a shame that you won't
live long enough to learn to speak well
she filled cheese casts a great gaze
from a giant fishy i hmm
left and right there's some twitch that
she is able that she was able to commit
and immediately try dance our level ah
and there's a voice a voice that you
recognize
walnut you can see us you can see a
shape sort of emerge from a group and
sort of it comes out into the center of
this area into the audience chamber
itself
flanked by two young women in black
robes you see mendes veil who spoke to
you he spoke to you atop the cart after
NEMA's air and the queen says world
right veiled
what do you have what do you have to say
on this matter
it's a is it's like she doesn't want to
assume that all surfaced Villiers know
each other you know what i mean but she
really want to be that person he says he
says i cannot abide the insult that
these people have committed to you and i
cannot abide the insult of jim dark
magic against your royalty he says but
they are my prey and i would kill them
myself and you have my you have my
guarantee in this matter I am aggrieved
by their behavior but there is no reason
to muddled the water of this court with
their blood
yeah we're the worst I look at
Catherine's real quick because he
doesn't know who they're and I I went to
one of the the women I go sisters of may
Lilith so you can you can tell right
away you can you can feel underneath the
underneath the waves you can feel the
natural forces that bind these chunks of
the altars together you can feel a sort
of rising and reaching behind you but
this is occurring behind you so it's
actually pulling it against your throat
mmm
here in the deep if you turn to see him
you can see that he wears on a chain a
chunk of black altar and his his focus
has two symbols on it one of May 8th and
another one of these another one of
these icons that has brought you such
torment mmm because it's not language
just like the ER it can't be translated
it can be understood it can only be
consumed - am I able to see it at this
distance where I can just tell that I
can't you used you just know you just
you know that it's something that you
need to have mmm
and the Queen says how will you do this
tell me how you will do it and he says
when they least expect it my lady I will
kill each of them in a place that they
believe is a place of safety I'll save
one for whom I have reserved a fate
worse than death
hmm baby dying right now
take it grandpa what if you've gotten
yourself into
it's like it she says like what Tuesday
kid um so so so she nods she nods from
her perch this is onions dragons you can
tell you want no yes this is too much
now you've lost me everything until a
fish not again
so I look at manners doesn't as well and
I see that he has a focus on he does and
he does that symbol that you know was a
symbol of terror and hatred but has now
been completely reconfigured in your
eyes now that I know that the myth was
taken away and not of the traitor not
her fault I look at him and I go I say
you wear me a little mark I say that did
we serve her and I say and we'll just
tries real hard and it's very difficult
cuz she goes she goes she goes in a way
I served me with two he his head
and I go I saw her in a vision I say I
saw them both he does not like that
that's fine and I said I say I saw what
truly happened to her I go and I say and
I I kind of look at this I I convey to
him I invade his mind and I say she
chose me as her vessel yes and I say I
say and I say I say help us we're here
we're here to to help mail it we're here
to find her and set her free
yeah he says we could not possibly serve
the same maelys is it a common name and
then I go I go it's possible that what
you know is not mail it and I say but um
I say well I don't know they got the
same symbol yeah oh my god well no well
yeah I don't I don't know who you think
you're serving but if you don't think
it's the same person then
you shouldn't be wearing that symbol and
you shouldn't be saying her name because
you don't know about her whole thing I
[Music]
say to him it's a lazy solution to the
problem you now have he's he says name
three mailers albums yeah exactly it's
like we were first
what's your mail with them he says he
says as I suggested we'll be seeing each
other soon enough we may have a moment
to discuss it then
real quick before you go who was the one
you're gonna kill last death but not
death right was it my death
yeah death death right is it me
it's okay we can just go home one does a
hand gesture could just go you've never
seen before but is like a hundred
percent no flippin the bird but it her
gross version yes exactly it's it's the
it's the EPA version that's so like
anger yes so the Queen seems satisfied
with this solution great all right you
you are gripped just as before something
like a fishnet woven out of kill that
includes any of the pieces that you
might have removed any of the naked cthe
wrists clothes are sequestered in there
they don't what they kind of trashed
down here mm-hmm
and they they drag you up and you can
sort of see like their sky is completely
dark it's just this dark layer of water
above their City and the club once you
once you pierce that you get back up all
the way to the top and you can see dull
troma fell
fan and Corbin shale just like looking
worriedly over the edge of the ship so
just to be very clear queen Sundra
thrill said we have to contact Jim and
she was gonna kill us to do it and then
Mendes fails showed up and said I will
contact Jim and also these are mine to
kill exactly mine okay I will do your
quest and don't kill these fools right
okay yeah but they're pals again so we
got off pretty easy cuz I got the vibe
he was gonna kill us anyway so like net
positive it's a win it's a win chalk
that up as Owen it's your relentless
optimist everyone here so they're
immediately like dull drama sees you
competent oh she's there they're
throwing ropes over the side and they're
reaching out and trying to help you guys
trying to pull you back you vomit yeah
do we get like pulled up we're still in
the kelp and then like somehow like our
clothes just get like thrown up I'm
pushing on dinar my take him first taken
for exactly you can't see you can't see
him anywhere you can't see Grievous
anywhere on the water all the digging
made very good time he's he's going he's
her body strength yes it's just that
yeah yeah it's alright it's for the best
I'm always sad to see him arrive and I'm
always a little sad so Corbin she'll
says are they but he coming back
not for us your boat your ship it's not
gonna be protected anymore apparently
mr. Jim dark magic had a pact with the
fish Queen to protect he said that he
handled this well and then he didn't
because he's apparently dying of some
great robbing disease I don't know he
said that he had negotiated an
incredible deal well he didn't he did
well he did but he is not fulfilling his
side of the deal side of it it's just
supposed to do bang a fish okay
I mean 790 years with the fish Queen oh
well that's I mean that's that certainly
has to be considered a win
see that's what I was thinking I
absolutely have like if you if you said
that you're gonna come back you know you
should worry what you weren't ever books
that you're supposed to you know like
come back that's that's a that's a
difference of the deal where we show
says I thought I understood the
conversation we were having but then it
seems like there's a different there's a
lot going on okay wait but I think that
I don't know wallet illicit older I'm I
guess I think we can solve this problem
with documents a filling out forms like
like lanes
and they like have it pulls out and it's
just like it's like red ink
it's like Xing stuff out and then it's
like a fender and it's like gym dark
magic and ratting him out Rosie there's
like Rosie bringing you fresh ink pots
and like wiping your Braille they're
like catching squid yeah it's like
removing the ink squeezing it out can
actually make a little quill out of the
bone inside of squid talk about on Table
Talk anyway yeah so yeah a it's a team
and files documents saying that there's
trucks and that with the gym dark magic
the whole thing and then Team C does the
whole thing and then we can deliver a
mail by just shoving them in purses bag
sounds true I walk over to him and told
arm I should have like a whole armful
them too I go to confession I go okay
ready I'm stressing that mouth oh well
that's a monster just like tomato juice
where I'm like put things in the mailbox
best part is that cuz Chris doesn't care
at all he's like yes that's the right
way to do it each one I go I go you can
put one in this documents why is nobody
why don't we have this this is a new
this is a new art form and so don't
drama is like right there with you
you're sick twice M be 27 C and right
she's just counting them all out and
they're just like hold her I'm doing it
sideways it's like a yep okay that
should be right and then she serves like
like the subheadings all the
categorizations some white wax Caelius
right there oh yeah she's right there
it's like she's heating the wax it's a
quickly vamping BAM
yeah yeah yeah this there's there's a
few moments of this that are like
Showtime
like first 11 o'clock it was playing the
whole very specific sub channel of
Showtime
meanwhile Rosie be navigating us
absolutely going back she should you
have to have to only have to go there no
no you're going to cost us all right you
weird dreams cross across to the right
pretty we continue we continue our way
while you guys are doing this Rosie
saying cool ship stuff like Oh trim the
main that's one thing that she says and
it's not one of many yeah person Rosie
still uses the word lar bird deep cut
large bird also she caught enough crows
nests the main top yep that's for you
guys yeah both boys out there yeah we've
been doing this we've been doing that
history yeah yeah yeah for cartography
and that's what we use it for we do we
do oh that's an eighth though she didn't
do so good on that
oh good time that's a ten no it's not
good history right so like this is a new
ship exactly it's not your face but it's
not it's not it's odd I mean you had to
sort of reverse engineer this right this
scenario you're trying to navigate to
something that is not on a map right you
found with the help of birds and with a
boat that it's kind of a piece of crap
let's say beyond this hey hey hey it's
seen better days
well after lingerie to Victoria's Secret
Merry Widow you know what tables that's
where all of her points are and like
before
it's all so boring this is a great
adventure gonna white house can we not
see a white house say goin okay the
daytime Rosie's definitely the kind of
person know who when she gets her bad
history check on her cartography Zeng
she will blame the boat oh yeah but only
the boats fault actually well yeah
because it's sort of like nose listing
or something listings
then listing since we saw it every time
I'm like it's listing again and lazily
to the left that's right exactly
and listen yeah it's
not really pop this word I bring the
battle-ax over to him he just really
wants to catch up and I just like kind
of push it into like his chest and walk
away I'm like looking second ice
ordinarily this is the top part of the
head and the lower part of the head sort
of form that ax shape but then just
snaps closed and he's just he's just
he's ready he's ready to interact with
you III I say I didn't get a chance to
tell you down there but if it weren't
for those pearls that they fed us you
think it's a smile you don't know I mean
you don't know what is happening with
this for so long
are you hungry thirsty what is this
emotion I can't I can't read it
yeah so I says well how have you been
I've been busy but not as much time as
passed here in in this realm I still
don't quite understand the the nature of
the shadow realm time the incredibly
curious well let me tell you what's
what's happened to me the entire
dragon's hoard was dismantled by
usurpers hmm
I was killed several times I'm knowing
nod yes that he took the central column
where the King lived and its shadow
portal and built a kind of temple around
it hmm and I found once I regained life
that I could crawl into the shadow
portal and for some reason they believed
everything I said about everything I
don't I have a trusting face I don't
know what it is
I can see that is that I I told them all
kinds of stories and they started
writing them down and for whatever
reason they oriented their entire
society around it hmm
but long story short I'm back we can
hang out this is great I meant to come
back for you
instead yes oh I have I have every faith
that you intended to I've never I've
never impugn that desire I always knew
that to be true
what are you why are your what are your
equipment stats no I say no I say not
having done it before I say Oh would you
indulge me may I wield you it says oh
absolutely get that get that half-turn
yeah exactly I might not be able to yeah
yeah it's just this massive it's this
massive spinal column right with a sharp
set of teeth and a weird head at the top
of it um wait hold on a second you're in
yeah there's no way I could lift it yeah
I'm not picking him up twice move in
touch Billy yeah exactly yeah I could
pet him yeah may I do it in that way of
drag him around with your lug yeah you
know I leaned him against the wall when
I realize I realize it's not I won't
drop yeah this is fine just yours guys
this is fine this is great if you need
me think this I'll be right here where
you left me this business happened a
couple times oh no problem
uh I'll talk Cupid where you are thank
you in case she needs the use of you
over there okay great good to have you
back and you can just see this like eyes
just like wherever you go on the boat
it's like those portraits know you
always think SR might be interested in
your location and I'm kind of cool with
being free of it for a while yeah like
just rest it's tearing his small net
listicle silence when I was looking at
dinner going
so again 60 years in the shadow yeah
that reel
why didn't I file paperwork on that I
don't know why didn't you it was very
traumatic
well I guess I could do some in oh yeah
well Jesus well night gets out of note
ya know oh god geez Wow because so 60
years and she goes okay so damn one walk
me through that you get there and they
made me their king okay hey one day one
yeah right from the word go
I was kind of crazy and then they showed
me a room full of eggs and then I had to
inseminate the eggs mmm oh my god okay
well I got it from here yeah copy/paste
ctrl-c ctrl-v like I heard you got yeah
it was a lot like that also and she
brings out like a stack of a couple
books and she's like it's all in here as
well if you want to you know borrow them
you did a really good job earlier I
thought it was really great fire work
that's great oh yeah now she's like not
entirely she's still wondering if like
maybe this is like part of the maybe
this is part of the charade like maybe
this is because he knew he was gonna
like assassinate that she's like yeah
okay and now we're ever keep it as well
that's like keeping an eye on her but
very much like what she's reading these
the books in the corner yeah whatever
book you're reading I'm reading the next
one oh yeah cuz I know it's got two
boilers got some filth in it it's a
little dirty this is like way way way
down the line like the message you're
reading
not directly about him they're like
stories that might have been
mythological tales of what might happen
sure like this is some like Bible
looking for the driving so it's like you
have the book here and then you're
steering the ship he couldn't breathe
fire there's like a little manual
there's a tiny little manual of like
manners and things that you do it's like
okay so on your first dinner with new
friends or acquaintances you have the
ceremonial eggy which you cook and split
among the group nothing to do with
anything but like there is an idea and
it's like kind of like this ritual like
a gesture of friendship where it's like
if you meet a new friend or if you find
an egg on the way then like part of it
is you keep the eggs you get rid of them
in some like beautiful kind of fashion
like giving it away to someone else or
eating it when you greet each other yeah
yes three you keep it for a while but
then it is eventually just lost in the
world
break up with something to say you're no
eggy yeah yeah and that is deep it's to
meet you and also to you are the
characters having table talk I'm like
can I just when you give someone an egg
you regret it
about three months later yeah I keep
touching your foot and I want to
apologize it's okay I was like yeah I
was like I used to be able to put my
foot here without touching Kate's foot
sorry I know I'm doing so this is
everybody basically the entire deck is
full of people reading different volumes
of this stuff so you you hear a sound
from your belt Karissa no it's like just
like a little tongue lolling out of its
radula what out of the pouch and then
and then I'll call yeah exactly so you
you tip it up and you sort of help it a
little bit
Tom all right no no and birthing a calf
gotta get the second level documents or
bag hits the deck is it wet you just dry
his bone it's wet okay it's wet but dole
drama does not care she does not care
shaking like I do you get that she's
just down just like a like a newborn
baby just like just brushing off this
slime she opens him inside just like
sniffs pulls out this incredible this
incredible book gold leaf or she's just
crying a little bit in the middle of the
deck now Rosie be stinger if he would be
so kind as to guide the ship and wood to
this island this island home that you
have discovered so justly just gangster
lean yeah way back absolutely these
gangs really but also she's very small
it's real low goes right ship goes right
the ship she'll council Merrill areas
please you hey we have reached the first
commercial break thanks so much for
coming up and hanging out with us we
will be back momentarily to see you my
mom
hello I'm Cherokee or Kim's your friend
behind the game screen today I'd like to
not wonder you good
so when last we saw our heroes rosy be
senior not your grandma's grandma had
begun to steer the ship
Corbin shale closed at the ready in case
anything is required if they don't need
to kid a little bit of a hover but no
contact all right you know what I mean
calm down like he's not gonna touch it
unless he touches it which might happen
but he's not gonna know my videos to
think no my first bow do like I'm using
that term no it's good it's good
but you can you can notice something so
it's it's the midday sale yeah you feel
like a million bucks yeah it's I mean by
noon yeah had already gone down out
here it was a big day yes it was a big
day now you can see the sparkle on the
sea just that extra glint up on the caps
of the waves I need some perception
rules you got it that's a real show
there walnut my classical I got a tooth
so I might see water I'm very distracted
number the bees totally isn't a real
beast I don't know the number of a beast
yeah okay
now the number of a beast I will accept
this now from the from atop the crow's
nest because the MainTop house was
actually called crows nests are actually
only on whaling ships so if this is a
whaling ship then yes it's crow's nest
yes in his whale tango anyway she she
seized you
approaching the edge and looking over
and she fences I don't like it I don't
like it and you know exactly what she
means because this is not the glint of
ordinary this is not just like the Sun
dappled glint you can see floating in
the water
hundreds of lockets oh geez that's cool
huh huh oh boy that's pretty cool I kid
that's that's some spooky I can't knock
it till you throw a pop it and lock it
hit smash that lock button like like
this there's thick with it but you think
do you think that if you had a super it
was a really long arm and you could
actually reach down to the water from
the deck you think you could catch six
of them in one hand over the edge with
with with my yeah with hasar and there
just like it gets up yeah it's like a
crane toy this is amazing look she's
there's like six of them like like she's
just you you put it down there and he
has a few in his in his craw but there's
a few other ones just hanging off a
little horns you know like it's just a
mess you bring him up and then just just
like you shake him out on the deck
waters do 14 and every one of them shows
exactly the same girl do we think it's
the same girl all along yeah let's get
them all Dinaric it is I think it's the
same girl we have to reach 16 girls
that's okay father I know you can do
this are the lockets invading our shared
momentum at all I think of shucking the
water no it's nothing like that
okay so the ship is cutting right
through them okay Scrooge McDuck
like let's change the sound of the boat
in the water okay it's just a sort of
clatter as the front of the boat is just
cutting through this layer of lockets
that are sort of floating on top and
then even the farther down you see like
you can just see the sunlight shining
down through and there's lockets below
that as well ahead of the Merry Widow
you can see the lighthouse atop a small
rocky island and around this you can see
the bones of ships of varying sizes mmm
you can see a small D freshly placed in
a little crook he has not secured it he
is not to be seen he is not to be seen
in the boat or indeed even on them
ah geez on the surface all right so
someone needs to go get the Dean then go
get us yeah I want us to run aground
here
can we pull up throw anchor safe
distance so that we are not running
aground on this island
do we have another method of getting to
these yeah yeah I mean you know well
you're know how long this take my fly
back your sense is that it's quite we
and we can hear senses that it's quite
deep okay around that this is it is
literally out here in the middle of
nowhere
okay well even so generally speaking a
bunch of crash ships around an island is
not a great thing they didn't run
aground I mean it's it's like it's it's
just like they're heaped up okay around
it just like a snap ribs kind of sort of
lected over rocks like a nest yeah that
that seems fair okay so is there a safe
place to I mean you wouldn't tie them is
that is it does it look like there's a
spot for that it doesn't seem yeah it
doesn't seem like it's okay weighted
towards us far away
then you I mean I I can I can Park us
what are your 70 feet away from the
shore and then - out there
35 times - right that's how - works you
can move very quick on her yeah why not
I'm a monk I can do that I probably
bounced on to like a broken hull of a
piece of a ship and then bounced back in
yeah
so just right but again like slapping up
on its on its stone you can see lock it
after lock it just thick clumps of them
also the chains sort of bound up close
you have a wild shape that could
traverse oh yeah and one that just cuz
she goes and she's like she's like oh
yeah I could do that hmm I goes well
does that'll get me across
I suppose I could get Rosie across if
you will permit me to ride on your back
absolutely
grandmother of course and then I go so I
don't know you three wait here or figure
it out yeah yeah if it's taken long
enough that I've that I've gotta back
then I would how long does it take um
enough for a long rest we took is it no
I've seen that's a bit if you took a
short rest and burnt some air yeah stuff
I considered talking to Sarah very short
and very restorative rest enjoyable
sorry short um but I would imbue you
with flight because you have the biggest
Harry Caray capacity maybe you do either
one of you that is a better choice than
me who's stronger arm wrestle yeah it's
mine even on that list no where did you
carry really like an on the carry weight
just right I don't have the normal
she is stronger what's your strength 17
so get out here I could've had extra
points but instead I decided that I was
going to take feats and everything so
I'm good like I have proficiency and
like a half of the skills I was actually
going to do a lot more of this but Gigi
Durham North I can't have really really
good animal handling I have good
survival obviously because I'm out on my
own
why just keeps going I gently pick up
rose I go excuse me grandmother and then
I just jump us before we hit the water
gracefully wild shape ya know and then I
turn into a crocodile this is like this
is like the story of like the monk in
the crocodile yeah I'm not gonna
crocodile yeah cupid immediately thinks
that she is so much cooler than you at
this point because she's like just she
turned to talk are you seeing that she's
like she's like she's like she can turn
it to us she's like she can turn it to
like there's a lizard thing just any
time she wants to what kind of skill is
that I haven't read anything about this
this is totally different was something
so fast leans down she goes thank you so
you look up you you look up atop your
crocodile conveyance and you see that
you see drivas head in one of the
windows so this is is there's a
lighthouse top yeah but it has multiple
floors and windows on each of the floors
and you see you see drivas looking out
of one of the windows you sort of push
it open like a portal and his hands are
inside there he says mom
you don't want to be in here and then
and his face disappears from the window
oh sweet baby boy so you guys get up on
land
[Laughter]
alright so we gotta take the Diggy back
retrieve these flown and that and that
is basically okay but this is probably
I'm gonna be way more than 500 pounds
the other oh yeah two sixty two thirty I
don't have anything to that cursor is
negative okay cuz I was like right next
to you the entire time I guess is 85
dripping wet son being like close to you
doing this yes you're doing a special
time holding all of us and like it's
gonna be like a so when you when you
find yourself crawling up on this rocky
outcropping you can feel that it is
shifting in the water it's not it is not
stable when you when you approach the
tower itself on here it has a sort of it
has there's no door in the base it isn't
simply an opening at the base of this
tower structure and you saw you saw
grievous on the second floor sir
can I do a perception check to determine
if this is some kind of mimic sure
so I know lighthouse now that's a
lighthouse sniffing 18 yeah this gets
quite good you think that you think that
we see a mimic would have either be more
flesh you would see at some point you
it's you'd be aware because you see
mimics before by now they're very sticky
as you saw with the door oh yes but you
would have seen he is as soon as you had
gotten on the mimic would have made its
play okay that was your experience
previously okay it doesn't wait you know
what it means sir tonight defines divine
sense yeah tell me more about it
as an action or the location of any a
celestial fiend or Undead sure until the
end of your next turn and detect the
presence of any place or object that has
been consecrated or desecrated as with
the hollow spell like that like button
you don't even need the desecrate that
divine sense
well no no what this would allow you to
do would be to determine if a like
button had been despierto but we know it
has oh yeah yeah so that my alarm is
just being the in spider sense is
tingling
all right exactly but what whatever is
happening here does not match up with
the categories that divine senses
designed to assess June cool
damn it you tried I didn't gold stock
run detect a shadow full can we can I
approach the I'll turn back in the woman
cargo is gonna be super useful here um
kind of walk up to the plate is there is
there a door
yeah I've so yeah there's there is a
various infected doorway there's no
physical doors no physical but there is
an entrance Rosie I'm gonna warn you
like be careful there's something weird
going on here and yeah I'm gonna get to
the bottom it and I want to use detect
magic to know the presence of magic
within 30 feet and I can see auras in
determining the school
that is what it says cool I might have a
card that has one I think I have just do
our thing there's over old for what it
is mm-hmm that's got it well it doesn't
say that I'm right
sheet oh yeah the sheen the sheen is
awesome as long as you know was like
certain again as I know it is yeah oh it
just says if you sense magic this way
you can use your action to see a faint
or around any visible creature object in
the area that bears named magic and I
learn in school of magic penetrate most
barriers but is blocked by one foot of
stone one inch of common metal a thin
sheet of lead or three feet I'm
detecting I don't enroll okay yeah you
don't see anything magical right really
well I can concentrate so up to ten
minutes so if anything magical does
happen yeah I love Rosie and I go yeah
if anything weird happens I'll be the
first to know about it and then you'll
be the second from the weird tapping and
then and I look back and I see these
guys and you just want to describe to me
your your landing we haven't landed all
right oh no you tell me well we have to
be like pinwheeling
yeah just shoots out my land
as the crux of the wheel and you to go
twirling into the sand mightily just
like head first thing I would do yeah
yeah like there's there's parts of me
that is emerging and you can't quite
tell where the actual lizard is I also
land violently in the sand and I mean
again friend so the the party has found
itself in keepin Aidid on the Isle and
you hear you're looking up at this tower
you hear a Corbin shale say cannons well
if you look out you can see that a
tentacle has reached up from the
direction of the island and is reaching
up over the ship over the top of it
entirely and is trying to guess just
trying to grip it and pull it in that's
my sweet there's a tentacle tentacle
Union how far I mean from the ship right
now right now you are so far away from
the ship that you should roll initiative
[Music]
I have 1623 okay willed me out her when
she first drove by that is not high it's
not great how are you doing cubed all
right but where is the gaudy yeah I
wrote for him as one yeah but you didn't
give me my my things keeper yes
so where is he thank you he's very rash
when he rolled even worse that's easy I
can I can make that happen
yeah relive my glory excuses all right
that was Mike Wallace on grass that you
stand at the entrance of a strange tower
atop an island that exists on no map
what do you do do i okay I'm on an
island all right okay uh and there is a
stereo structure before you yeah
am i concerned about I don't do I really
care about the boat do I care about
what's happening on the boat you tell me
Gil drama in New York on buzz yeah yeah
okay all right I can move really fast
all right so I look at the tentacle and
I look at Rosie and I go I go I'm gonna
go get the girl we gotta we gotta do
what we gotta we gotta do all this at
once so I'm gonna I can run pretty
pretty good and so I can do 35 feet so
if I - I could do 70 all right yeah you
can bring your ass off so I wanna go
exactly so you run directly in so you've
never been here before
and so you are you're contending with
this completely new environment while
running as fast as you possibly can you
see I'm trying to go up yeah exactly but
you use pairs
you walk in there is a set of stairs
that goes down not that and there's a
set of stairs that goes up a hobbit a
split level so you say you if you come
in immediately cut left and run up you
can see that in the in the stone that is
that has been heaped up and transferred
into this tower the mortar itself seems
to pulse and throb but it's not uniform
it isn't like between everything it's
like there is a path that's traced it's
almost like it's traveling a maze up
through the structure so as you come up
to this first floor you are immediately
kicked as soon as you come up this floor
you can see the stairs that would take
you up to the floor where drivas was
seen you can see the girl from the
locket I see her yes and she kicks you
hmm
not as hard as she can oh yeah I know
what the hell yeah exactly
ac 15 AC 14 mm-hmm okay that's a quick
one
feast on six straight just straight in
the middle of your right on your right
on your diaphragm but this is this is
the this is launched exactly your face
is haunch so this is the thing that is
this is the thing that is disturbing
about it the entire time she is visiting
this upon you her ostensible Savior yeah
her face has never lost this sort of
despondency like the same terrified
person is it's like she looks like she
is just as disturbed as she ever was she
is still completely 100% in this wave
dear I can take it laughing face is the
same thing as the red hourglass on a
black widow it's just that's it
it's your turn but you're - you took a -
as an action right I didn't know if I
used it you did yes yeah it's cool well
I promise action wild shape I kill her
walnut rosy bee stinger uh your son is
currently on the second floor of this
and you can hear a muffled version of
your son's voice yeah red downing from
the window between drivas and walnut all
your kids are in this so yeah F that
boat um and I'm just gonna run up after
walnut I'm not gonna I'm not gonna - and
let's it's required though I'm gonna try
to you were right here in the doorway
like you could very easily use your move
and get to where walnut okay okay I'd
like to do that so I see what
so as you you jump in you see what she
saw there is a set of stairs that goes
down you can see plainly this is a rock
outcropping okay you have no idea what
down would even mean right right to your
left set of stairs go up and at the top
of those stairs
you see walnut on grass doubled over and
in front of her you can see the girl
from the locket and she looks at you
with so much pain and longing and
loneliness hmm and I look at walnut and
I look at her and I see I say I can tell
you're in pain but you're about to be in
a lot more okay um so I'm going to I'm
gonna attack the hell out of her I'm
ready I will do some good the whole the
whole tamale this time oh you mean like
with the key points and like yeah I mean
yeah I mean I think what I would like to
do is is disable her to the point where
she's no longer attacking us yeah I
would not like to kill her but I will if
I have to oh okay so I'm gonna do would
you like me to just do all of my attacks
Oh last time it works pretty good for us
to know which attacks hit and missed
okay and then come up with a cool store
okay sounds good so um I am seven timid
so that's a nine that's another nine and
that's a 17 and that is my oh I got two
okay those are those are my it's my
quarterstaff strikes both miss I assume
and then my unarmed strikes are coming
which is a 19 so those I think probably
both hits so yours that sort of staff is
all misses but then when you start to
connect with your your physical body
correct they all land yeah and I'm gonna
chalk that up to a berserker rage that I
entered that it jeopardizes my
monastic focus and as soon as I realized
that my staff's wings were flying wildly
out of control I took a deep breath
before entering my unarmed strikes which
are going to be plump 9 - and a that's a
I'm at the one I'm lucky so I roll that
that is another 9 so 18 damage on her Oh
healthy Jesus Christ
Rosie be stinger so there's a piece of
the puzzle that I'm missing and I'm
hoping you can help me with it
okay her sort of crumpled form of long a
dong grass was at the very top of the
stairs where she had received a savage
tip cracks can you tell me how you
navigate that space with your monk
techniques because this could also this
could also help us understand why the
first couple quarters strife to the
quarter staff strikes missed right right
so she's right there how do you get
around her to engage with this entity is
she blocking the entire mean she's but
she's like hunched over she's like down
okay so tell me how it happens you know
I'm gonna yeah yeah I think so
you're I would normally just like
perhaps give you some kind of warning
and then
you as a jumping point but I'm a little
worried I don't know how bad you've been
hurt so I don't I don't want to
jeopardize you but I will do the same
thing only using the wall so I will jump
to the right of walnut with my feet on
the wall and then use my staff to push
off swing wildly miss both times land
and then reach back for two punches this
is a thing though have you ever seen
that those rear those rearward strikes
that's right now you're saying it in my
mind yeah yeah this but it's so two of
these punches land right and it's like
punching like the texture to be like
punching a ripe nectarine you know okay
goosh goosh okay
how does she react to being attacked her
face has that same tormented youth you
don't like it
yeah okay Dennard blitz in of the house
blitz in Genoa royalty what a pleasure
hey glad I can be here everyone how do
you can you hear this heap not one to
split the party right yes I run in
slower behind everyone mm-hmm and then
lumber my way in exactly silly so yeah
so as you're moving in you can hear
concussive blows you know hear the sound
of the quarter staff straight you know
is striking through the air hitting the
rock walls right at the top of this
stairs you can see walnut just doubled
over in pain and that's the predicament
you see yourself with this this this is
a young woman from the locket that you
had seen is is basically between walnut
and grandmother so I get up the stairs
I see walnut her double down down I see
Rosie attacking this girl who looks
troubled and scared yeah and getting
beat up and then I go
we're here to save right I would be like
I don't know who got hurt I don't know
why I see this is a very complicated all
right yeah so thank you can can I say
yeah absolutely but I want to give you
an extra piece of information whoa
she has just been struck twice mm-hmm
and you can see like she should have
been tugged much farther over but you
can see there's almost like a stem there
is a that is ripping from her hair okay
and is extending up almost into the
darkness of the ceiling above it so
she's like a real like a marionette kind
of thing so it's like weird little uvula
or maybe it's like a mimic i mimic maybe
it's academically like mimics mimic oh
yes well observing that this situation
becomes a little more clear okay I guess
I would yell first before I did anything
yes like what's going on yeah everybody
cool out there but I would say a roll
call me like hey everybody cool out I
have a good girl cool furious look on my
face because I'm acting irrationally I
was like she kicked walnut
yeah but haven't we all wanted to kick
walnut nice do a little kick just a
little tap like see it's fine it's more
fun than it looks see I mean in all
science I get it I get it
[Laughter]
watching yes I will join in the fight
the fray yeah show me what you do I
don't know I mean you got so many get so
many calls here like this I know maybe
some rich zone what do I see beyond I
see Jesus in trouble you yeah you hear
muffled you hear muffled cries oh you
know it sounds like a
young multik last half work under
control oh yeah I just give one last
little tap and then I run up run past
what stem no you guys thing went ahead
punch ahead look at me right she is not
taking a neck she's no spring
I'll run time you're too shiny my past I
want to check on our our sweet baby boy
during the day so as you as you because
you reach the top of these stairs and
look in at this scenario you can see
that there are two two girls hmm
similar to the locket girls with the
same faces but they're like distended
and puffy
mm-hmm like them like overripe like see
blood no no no like like they've been
like they've been on the counter too
long okay so I'm up on the second level
nail this fight blow down on level one I
think I see Jesus he's he's contending
he's competing with him because he does
not he does not he has his he has a wand
and he has a sword and you can tell that
he like doesn't know which one he wants
to use at that exact time but he's like
I'm really really confused you guys okay
still more I feel like I've done all the
things I can do tell me what you want to
do I'll jump in there and start helping
I'll give you one of your two attacks
all right it's got all my so many yeah I
say everyone should offer ten minutes
something around my speed yeah I'm good
toothbrush room I'll toothbrush
something let's see it I just run past
him and just go after the first one
mm-hmm that's a ten plus six mm-hmm
exactly
already roll 2d six plus three yeah
Jesus yeah you you slice straight
through what it's not there's no bone
hmm of any kind
they just cut straight through and the
two halves just heap themselves up on
the floor it comes off like the the stem
comes off like like a imagine like an
apple at the overripe Apple it just
gonna close out okay
indeed indeed now it is the turn for the
opponents and so everyone who is inside
the tower I need to have dexterity
checks no we're cool for this day okay
we rolled lower good Baker's 15 no
that's a 2-1 just want you to know thank
you Mars but dinar takes four and you
take one so the entire structure shifts
beneath you and the tower itself begins
to tilt in the air so you are able to
you are able to position yourself in
such a way that you are able to
withstand this shift and of course the
the face of your assailant is just
continuously surprised by everything but
you can see outside is you can see more
tentacles rising up reaching for the
boat grabbing it and trying to pull it
in but the top of the tower
is tilting itself over the boat as it
brings it in and it's shaking itself
like a like a salt shaker over the deck
of the boat and you can see five or six
like wave lights yes five five or six of
these of these creatures that I have you
know previously described just falling
out of the windows and drawing
themselves up on the deck of the ship
you pit now we got the same problem I
have no idea which is you now
I mean you dropped a bomb on me there um
well food yes squishy overripe fruit so
I just do my Cupid would do yeah is into
I'm gonna that's one option
no I'm gonna run in what my other option
is to go towards the boat where there's
all these other goodies indeed indeed so
there are there are thick rich tendrils
know as I said reaching out and grabbing
the boat
so there's mechanism denying isn't the
tango oh yeah you both are and I'm just
like I'm gonna run right after him keeps
obviously cuz obviously so I'm ready
bikini how far do I get let's see from
where you are you can get up to I'm you
can get to where Rosie is but the
interior structure of this is deeply
unlike a tower now it's it's pretty
cockeyed in there okay and so you're
basically just trying to walk up this
sort of halfway tilted side so I need
some decks just to get in there okay
okay
7 plus 0 is 7 you are trying your best
you're not injured but it's like a
funhouse in here you're trying your best
to maneuver yourself up these stairs as
you can see you can see Denard blitzen's
servant Rosie yeah one who's just a
smallish grandma a lot so I'm kind of
Terry you don't know this is grandfather
you don't grandma there's a lot of
information there and you can interpret
it any way you want to emphasis as the
scribes have done there is there is an
entry might not and do I get an action
or I mean you can see you can see up at
the top of these stairs it would be very
challenging to do so but it's not
impossible if you have arranged
mechanism she is down at the bottom
being jostled around as is apparently
currently her way she's jostled and she
goes stop in the Blitz an accord halt
and instead of her just saying no
suddenly fire erupts from her hands and
it's burning hands oh no this is gonna
be action taxes yep each creature in the
15 foot cone which will also be you take
half as much damage anyway yeah she's
bringing Dex you back yeah yeah I'm not
hearing this mixes we mean yeah I mean
oh no cuz I didn't even make it that oh
my god I am killing so dish up the
damage alright that's a Porsche and then
how much data did did that squish me
that's a wine mm-hmm that's a four mmm
and a 6 ok so that's 1111 so yeah so
I'll do a save for bad speech and squish
does not succeed take that squish and
then that she's terrified she's like ah
the surprise and terror is maintained
throughout sir hurt burning death she
collapses and it becomes unplucked from
the stem that's right bran cath wrists
Rob I emerging as though from a mystery
oh I'm out there on the on the the beach
there you're the only one who can make
good choices and I I see these other
tentacles and now this tower shaking its
its goods evil dandruff onto the boat
and I want to I want to signal the
awakened mind
whoever's over I can spy so let me at
least run up to the entrance then yeah
and I say I'm gonna eat this thing's
brain what is downstairs you said there
was a path up that's where everybody's
messing around or to see what's the
other way I find out I wanna go to the
core yeah I'm gonna go down these stairs
of course that's great not want to split
the party I'm going to the base yeah no
I don't have to split pretty look I can
come with me I'll let you know that
that's where I'll you that's where
you'll find me if the real party ok some
right yeah you're gonna tap in and say
well creepy it's fun in the basement no
but I actually do like so yeah describe
for me this so it's a it's a spiral
stairs yeah exactly expose their case
there goes another you want it that way
that's right and then there's a nurse or
stair Kate there's also stairway that
goes down and is there darkness oh how
far can I see a deep darkness hmm okay
you got your vision you got that dark
vision well I know but that's thing that
helped me see here in the corner but
lagari will ya
my young friend please Grammy Grammy
outside he asked as soon as you cross
the threshold and enter into the lower
portion of this you can feel sort of you
can feel Locati flexing and twisting on
you mmm like he is he's sort of like
snapping and chirping at the at the dark
oh yeah
guaranteed I'm gonna so I'm going to
send him with some speed with some
caution doesn't matter that's just for
flavor I want him to go down yeah I'm
gonna switch sight with him exactly
there the mouths of these so you you
situate yourself get yourself supported
right and then convey yourself via your
crystal serpent hmm
your crystal serpent slides like a dark
slinky thank you imagine if you will and
he finds his way down to the base and
you see something that titillates you
Wow on every level hmm but he retaliated
from the hair from your incredibly
quaffed hair all the way to your amazing
as toe I do anything is cool for the
feet you see a black gate I didn't want
to split the party by will you see eight
symbols no surrounding a group of three
empty spaces in the middle three empty
spaces so exact same configuration is
the time yes the acid the correct acid
room that is correct the Crypt
the wandering crib hells bells that
sounds called the shard link that's
right
might I have any reason to think that
this gate occurs only in the wandering
crypt are we you know part of it now
you don't have any idea what that might
represent but I have every confidence
that you will destroy the party this
time hey let's see what happens
oh my god so you can make you use your
turn so I've got a monitor Shelton to
Loogootee yeah and now he's down there
and now he's down there yes okay and
it's his turn - what would he do what
I'm if I were my do when he's starting
to see the symbols and it was through he
was inexplicably drawn to it and my
weasel self had to get him in the mouth
and drag him and that oh and do that he
wasn't very go into it yeah it's a good
thing that we didn't do reverse turn
order because I would have sent him down
and then upon seeing that I would have
misty step down mm-hmm exactly on there
exactly Legault teas instinct yeah is
that of a creature against a predator
right then I mean yeah what I would have
to say to him it doesn't matter at this
point
so he yeah he's gonna oh he's got his
he's got his dagger William Tate it's
whittling there so he approaches the as
near as he can get to that to that gate
and he's searching for something to put
a dagger and to assert himself yeah yeah
he was this object he knows he that he
has to have dominance over what is it
what does he see that it's couldn't have
a dagger put into it it's a it is a it
is a clean face just as it was before
but as I suggested and when you when
you'd used it previously you know there
was except one symbol but then the other
two regions had nothing they had no
input not and that's what that's what
created the negative impact previously
so there is there is it is featureless
except for these symbols it is not a it
doesn't have anything like a keyhole in
the classic sense I do have three
symbols now
that's interesting the one that it was I
have three now that's an interesting
coincidence Oh weird
well the guy he's done so he's got down
there and one on grass well I haven't
I'm not I'm not like I didn't know about
what you're doing I see you looking at a
wall well I say that when I say told you
I'm going downstairs a minute because I
what I would like to convey in that
message yeah is I'm going downstairs
because that's where the the heart of
this living being this non lighthouse is
I'm gonna kill this yeah huge object
does that that's inserted that have no
more message after that that's gonna say
[Applause]
hey I'm having a moment where I'm like
do I just want to go down there or is
well not like Oh stairs sucks you're
trying to figure it out I'm trying to
figure out what wasn't in her defense
her introduction to the first floor was
not a positive one she would leave a
negative review of that floor okay yeah
I thought we don't fire she looks it
Cupid and then she gives her in the same
gesture Kia Peters like melting down a
little bit she's like and then she's
like almost like you did fine
and so then she looks like it's like the
whole tower is listing and stuff so
she's gonna like just kind of like just
so along the side just like liquify
yourself down like
she's getting really seasick and go up
to Catherine and then she goes okay you
took care of the boat right the boats
fine and then I think she would use uh
issues you'd be like just like I guess
take a couple steps towards the Amish I
gotta do anything sure nothing to do on
this turn she and will look down in the
basement yeah I haven't conveyed to you
what's in the basement I'm going down
there cuz there's the coroner oh yeah
but you all you find is me and my my
vision traded right oh I forgot a
holding action okay so I'm gonna hold
actually if he walks down there I'll
walk with him okay yeah sounds good
Rosie be stinger um I'm gonna continue
upward or I guess we're gonna have some
cars word yeah yeah I need to go to wear
dresses
indeed so once one floor up yeah
wherever up is exactly team definition
so I think that this is much easier for
you than it would be for someone else
right I don't think Rosie cares about
the shape of the battlefield
no never hasn't it what I mean okay so
just just like foot by foot just like
stairs wall stairs wall stairs wall
right up to this other thing about over
to this other tier right this other deck
of imagine a dark cake oh well and this
this over this upper slice you can see
that the the shift of this brevis is now
just beneath these two creatures you
know you haven't seen them yet
but as I described them their versions
age adverse uns like the color of a
bruise yeah well I killed one yeah one
right oh don't know exactly
you cut one in half at rate this
services beneath yeah fresh um okay then
it's a sweet smell like it's like um mmm
fall leaves Oh like a pumpkin spice
latte yeah say it's bad yes
we want to thank Starbucks Starbucks
okay I'll just do to my regular tag
extra tack and I ever strike and just
try to take this thing down because I
don't know that this is a squishier one
so I'm a little bit on it yeah just get
crazy yeah okay that's not gonna do it
that will do it 19 mm-hmm and that's a
27 nice so my staff a master will be uh
and I will I'll actually do this attack
ranged all right at the intro yeah yeah
I'll stand I'll stand
super close to the door like as soon as
I can get eyes on it yeah and that's
gonna be a 10-ton damage and then if
that doesn't do it then I will bounce
over and execute another 11 damage with
a foot well-placed foot exactly so
anyone said that you hurl the staff and
it connects and just like bends the
shape just makes the shape even more
wrong than it is and then a final kick
just bends it in half
these are no laws e's are no these are
not pieces and in dream dream and dream
it says they're not they're not girls
mom mommy no they never are drew this is
his sword his sword his is just on the
ground he's just a sort of like she just
won is shaking in his hand okay and all
Emmys are taking her after you in this
room yes okay I'm going to go help him
to his feet mm-hmm and give him an
extremely stern look mm-hmm and say
encourage him to encourage him and say
this is what you get for stealing a
dinghy twice twice twice
yeah you think you think that at this
moment you think that your words of
maternal guidance are penetrating the
scalp
not unlike selsun blue you know what I
mean but you if you feel like you feel
like you are getting through to him in a
way that you have not previously so it's
upsetting I'm alarmed I feel like I feel
like I'm actually parenting liked it why
don't you want to tuck a bunch more in
here no not at all I want to see if he's
a mimic that was a joke but I
think it was it was you know what it's
the 22 shadow council house context we
pay our debts no do not what sin well no
there's no saving so I'm visualizing
this theatre of the arm shaking level to
hear bait over here boat here yeah I was
good I like I was gonna there's a for
something even but throw him on the
tentacle sorry yeah I'm just gonna be
like I'm glad you're safe buddy what I
know you get hurt the next time the
tower tips so you're looking out the
window and you can see you can see
Corbin shale he sees you know music on
the boat the boat yeah flat you just
have to just flat on his stomach he goes
through the boat it sinks that's our
arrange a range weapon he gets he
attacks me actually you're hanging
around even hanging around with Rothfuss
honor of paralysis character with this
sure he does would do some damage just
roll two dice all right fine you take
for dinner
myself so you're pitching him out yeah
you try are you trying to make your way
through - I want to get to the base get
out well if we're gonna kill this thing
if he said oh the hearts in the basement
yeah you see an expert on this kind of
stuff I don't I don't know yes you never
know it this one you never know it this
one oh no don't want us to come down
before this are they so quiet oh it's
yeah excuse it's table talk to you yeah
you need to go down there you don't you
want to go down there yeah yeah like top
of mind so I would slow him out there
and then I would jump on to him write
him down like a ya know yeah go down
with him and then land on him so he I'll
save your boy watch your like he's my
least aerodynamic child doing all the
math right so these these these plump
delicious creatures yeah on the on the
deck are very excited about all this new
prey that has just been flung on there
from the window and maybe they begin to
take swings take bites okay you and
dirty dreams right they re being fought
there's look at the holes these are team
were their fruit these are the worst
fruit villains they're not confirmed
fruit villains yeah they're not
delivering the goods here Wow I don't
need this little roller exactly
referred no yeah so they come up and
they're just like slamming their limbs
against your plate and none of that it's
like it's just like a buff say I'm here
to save you yeah I got you lock it it's
true it's a it's a terrible night and so
I don't take any damage night
then you can't I think I did every
goddamn did everything massage me I go
up three points it works out that it
works out that Creek yeah you had neck
finally after that last fight Rose abuse
singer yeah that's our cave for this
week damn it Cheryl I know I know it to
me well no no listen it's gonna be okay
it's gonna be okay we're gonna come back
next week we're gonna have Cupid yeah
absolutely I've been with this take this
game we're just gonna put it straight
forward okay lots of adventure
alright it's gonna be very cool I'm
gonna be right here it still happens I
had an idea plan you read that down cuz
you're gonna have a whole week to think
about it oh yeah
show Council Myrlie Evers please you
this is our second commercial break
Chris subscribers just sequel a a I the
c-team stuff desecrate that button if
you would like to we will be back
shortly after we've used the facilities
for some tabletop don't go anyway
you