the enemies the past have dresses the
fat whether you would have make it past
a second and land the claim play a brash
and reckless to choose Akasha solution
you saw was prudent in endemic ripple
curtain will become a putrid is that
well said are pursuing
no mountain to Steven go to do deeds
appendix bed and embarks up to the top
of the peak of beneath this video my
sharpton to it while I swim in that
money good luck Carl Barks period
suspension National Park screw it I'll
stand on all in a natural box the first
time a most of the parks included they
regret for a cleric confessor this is a
lesson would like to continue professor
but just keep in my official advice sign
on the dotted line English in the twice
[Music]
there look it's like this I am Tycho
Brahe of panicking impacts
I'm also omen if it's Hera withdrawn CEO
of acquisitions corporated but today I'm
Jerry Hogan and I run game of Dungeons
and Dragons for my friend specifically
acquisitions incorporated the C team to
my right Dragonborn narcissist
Ryan Hartman I mean dinar Blitzen Amy
Falcone Amy the Falcons back at it
walnut on grass prepping the natural
world the croc across rosy bee stingers
not your grandma's grandma on crack
again on track again obviously this is a
fandom happen over here sure Chris trout
emerging from a mister out more like a
piss cloud oh oh oh hey Maya
Kerrigan today I got it no I'm spaghetti
no that wasn't Lissa
that was ice ask dad linguini no just to
catch everybody back up
catch up our stream friends and the and
you aka the shadow council the friends
who come by and hang out with us each
week and watch the game it's like this
are when last we saw our heroes they had
taken a job specifically
party security at the doone-gate in
under the auspices of one sambar blood
drinker that nice a nice chunk of coin
to babysit what as near as you can tell
is some kind of vampire coven you are
able to dissuade vampire hunters indeed
paladins other holy warriors you are
also able initially wait to push away
when I say this wait of course I mean
shopping yes a dis way their souls from
their box yeah exactly
but you were also you also at least
initially held a werewolf at bay Trevor
the very same the very same but a rat
annoyed walnut was able to sort of calm
him down to provide a life lesson at a
crucial juncture in this young werewolf
life and you were able to encourage him
to help you defeat a pretty savvy crew
of vampire hunters who were very very
enthusiastic about getting up into this
party and murdering all the people that
you have been paid to protect now at the
end of the adventure you emerged into
the room here at the last parts of the
dregs of this soiree after holding off
all manner of unwelcome guests the band
that was in the corner just entertaining
the gathered throng for the evening
announced that they had a song that they
play at events like these they
introduced themselves as acquisitions
incorporated and then said death to all
vampires and you can only imagine at
this point you can only imagine how I
mean if you were going to match a piece
of music to an audience
if you're thinking about it from a
demographics perspective always this is
not going to be the context you deliver
a song called death to all vampires this
is not the venue it's a mismatch it's a
mismatch it's a demographic Nidre engine
really good yeah exactly you gotta Lisa
get police involved if you have to know
your audience it could be a fight
irony like a like a hilarious comment on
like I interpret this yes yeah exactly
yeah you didn't get it yeah yeah it was
Joe it wasn't for today exactly yeah
that's like classic so we don't Weird Al
yeah exactly but so you can you can tell
already that the tenor of the room has
been altered slightly for two reasons
one this bizarre admission and you can
also see that sambar blood drinker has
noticed that slinking in the door to the
event space is none other than his
cousin Trevor who you know who perhaps
feels as though he because he has
defended their lives that he might get
entree or at least an hors d'oeuvre
there bare minimum bare minimum but you
only have a moment to process this
before the song begins in the corner go
on Amy ah you said that you wanted some
stuff so I'm going to give you some
stuff I'm ready
[Laughter]
yeah no no all right are we ready Kat
earlier stream all right here we go
you're trying to do a bite almost every
night but it isn't right and you know
where hand its wound you trying to sound
a brood and you're biting dudes just to
grow it well you're a winner I'm talking
steak dinner
well you're aware now
steak dinner I'm calling all your sin is
cuz you'll win a steak dinner tonight
[Music]
[Laughter]
if you mama
there's more dough [ __ ] trying
to take the town paint the town red than
the matrons down y'all [ __ ]
trying to hate me now wait till I get my
[ __ ] steak the plow come on
take a peek inside my trove of tricks
garlic cloves stowed never slow with the
sticks that got the point at a 10 best
button your lip sore auto because y'all
know my crossbow grip all right now are
you have you been pleased that was are
you not playing so somebody [ __ ] earn
it so you know all the disadvantages to
correcting things it obviously assault
area that yeah that's how jumped over
the cat even many times in a fella yeah
I want to talk aside table talk I don't
want to derail yeah yeah incredible even
it was for you oh yeah now on this
auspicious day I needed that yeah it was
for you now and indeed indeed at the
very moment what is standing in in a
lead singer Ian context you can tell
caught Elvin ears just beneath me only
the hint of a performance a tire you can
tell instantly you recognize the plates
the overlapping leather underneath
things get bad very quickly great inside
you can see this lead singer pulling out
hand crossbows making individual shots
and then instead of reloading he just
drops it who finds another hand crossbow
somewhere within the infinite folds of
his garb Reaper yes
flying out and just there piling up at
the base the hand drum the hasty
membrane is torn away beneath it you can
see the symbol of Joaquin coin God flips
it this this individual flips it over
from the back comes a hammer right the
loonie er reaches her hand up into a
tight tasteful bun pulls the pins out
and then holds the strings back of the
lute a handful of darts fly out into the
room every one of them finds their mark
I'm in love with her Josiah very order
so you can see just if that's important
absolutely the blonde tight topaz all
know how tight-ass firmness of the bun
and as soon as the darts come out oh
yeah I like right exactly pulls it out
BAM
four targets dead good people you're
meant to protect ostensively sure it's
but it's very cool you can see the the
de Klerk with the shield use this hammer
reach he reaches back throws it forward
you see sambar blood drinker yeah take
it in the chest dead center of the chest
and two things happen one sambar is
driven back through the air through the
glass doors that go out to the porch and
at the moment the hammer hits it
reappears in the hand it's the work this
is bad news the lead singer is now
moving target to target to small claw
like knives it's essentially like a
blender elemental I mean imagine imagine
the power of a Vitamix turned loose oh
yeah the shape of a man that's right I
don't let you do whatever whatever more
weathera does that have to say whenever
I can react notice which is line it's
time this
instantaneous middle thinks that it's
the surprise round we're like oh man
socks fantastic I don't think we're
going to get teeth is cute
I haven't yet they can perform a
reaction but we know that when that our
patron flew out on the stage that velvet
my on camera immediately said about
cleaning the blood what a missed one no
no it's just really become and then it's
just like it goes the whole trail all
the way to the quad I'm imagining that
little cleaning bot from Wally
oh no maybe I was exactly that I had
exactly the same image that is the that
is the scene and then as the last person
falls and he turns to you and says
you're welcome but this is something
very very strange happens but I need to
emphasize one other thing any time I
roll a natural 20 or any of the members
of the C team roll and natural 20
constantly constantly 24/7 has been the
historical data in combat are always
anytime you roll it anytime you write
crit then there it is 7/8 what I'm Evan
get a 10 to the 20 we are going to do a
giveaway in the channel anybody who has
been chattin basically the bot is going
to go back through the last 15 minutes
we're going to grab somebody we've got
some different kinds of stuff got some
coop all got all kinds of stuff we're
gonna we're gonna we're going to dish up
but but but that is it so as he turns
and says derisively do basically you're
welcome you're not like a vampire
ologist sure right but I have questions
about how fast everybody went down yeah
you're not a vampire ologist
in the classic saying or what I claim
you have exactly exactly
you followed some of the hashtags right
but yeah you'd have your expectation
would be that this scene would look very
different if this had been an authentic
vampire scenario so are they all
hello yes sir just Anacapa yeah I want
I've come to a conclusion but I'm just
gonna go up onto it so Trevor hmm is who
I very much like a very real werewolf
right
yeah there's you can tell he definitely
a bipedal yes Manuel right but he is he
is he is actually kneeled down okay at
his cousin and he said you weren't never
no vampire I'm gonna just ask this very
quietly swole nika's my god
they were LARPing no hawk I said it when
the guys first came in when they were
like oh you're defending vampires are
gonna remember are they just called it
are they yeah so am I looking around
he's like the like as The Clash of the
Vale pullback I'm like that's just like
Clamato juice they're drinking it's not
actual what we think I was just wine
with some blood in it oh yeah like a
fancy vampire I think for there he was
it was weird tasting but it could have
been her motto
it's weird drink there's a weird drink
it's not a good like only I would rather
drink human blood than Clamato I do your
prayer for what if you just if you have
to want it like this if you offer me to
it's going to be like not the one with
the clam yeah
please and the auto yeah be positive so
hang on so just to recap there were what
I'm going to believe were very real
vampire hunters because they sucked to
murder and if they were just LARPers
maybe not because we weren't going easy
on them right so also thought these
people were vampires
right so here we not yes I can you feel
our take away from this is that these
LARPers great marketing because word got
out that's true there was a there PR
little too good at their jobs again I'm
campaign but also it's this new badass
elven guy the bands that killed all
these vampires is like you're welcome
they're not real vampires dude you just
kill a bunch of innocent people
yeah and also we call it a little sex
yeah and it'll John Brant okay well we
probably should say these things to him
yeah I think they all don't character
yes what specifically do you sell i
these creatures he's a human is so as
you say now the ruse is completely
shredded right lead singer yours you
suspect I mean just your instant read is
that this is a person you would have
seen this is a man obviously it would
not it would not have he would he
wouldn't have at a place in your Enclave
sure but you can tell that this is
definitely a person who ostensibly
Revere's the same natural world that you
do he's backed up of course by what you
assume from the holy symbol and the
accoutrement is a priest of walking and
then that most hated of classes the Bard
with this war loot in the back hair
seeming to still slightly sway in an
invisible breathe clown your water
almost so conflicted it was very
challenging for me quite this is IP
theft but yeah come back here it did the
elf lead singer does he seem small game
proud of himself
Oh deeply okay I want to survey the room
and pointedly look very high up in him
because I seem taller than me and go you
realize these were definitely not
vampires
they were one by the way from vampirism
but the y'all aren't we all there's no
vampires here I could very easily just
kill you for the same reason you'd have
a hard time Brittany
which one was the vampire what were you
protecting these people from I mean
that's the change that was it that was
imminent yeah they were one bite away
but where is the vampire right who's got
the bike yeah classify baby
hey now I was like thanks guys say some
like real like puff up her chest yeah
and be like also the legal ramification
of impersonating acquisitions
incorporated it's just and if she sucks
all the documentary okay guys slacking
and if you're going to search a nerve
bag like like she has so many documents
for this purpose it's like yes they have
tab it's clearly outlined in our
11-second yeah exactly and she looks
anyway listen yeah he says yeah
eventually we realized that our
documenter was just getting in the way I
feel you bro Wow I want yeah I want to
literally punch him in my overhead I do
it okay hang on I'm gonna do it they say
don't do it while I did it this is kind
of a wallet so was it like a bird team
on a good day 14 it's a very good day
can I punch him not now with a 14 but
you used to bring you swing real and
then he catches it then he just sort of
analyzes you just assesses assess every
ring every plate every fold of your
armor aces sorry about your Grove oh
snap maybe if there'd been a man there
things might have turned out differently
okay oh my god I want o to journalist
he's like just are you I'm gonna put a
soothing hand on what and try to calm
her down cuz she's about to wild tape
all over this book I don't want to say
everything on the stream but just wants
to start like screaming and swearing
yeah saying how dare you you don't know
anything about it right
trying to hold you back but I'm like a
third your size so it's not working it's
really like yeah yeah I'm just like
trying I was like petting petting you
I've melt down and I'm tasting some of
the lovely guys this is a regular blood
is a boys blood as humans a lot eat boy
black this is this is horrible there's a
guy say something else so he said
because I don't think they didn't say
one more thing he makes fun of me now
yeah yeah he's he's putting it he's
putting his knives away you can tell
that that you can tell that that line
assessing his his entourage you can tell
that that line landed with the cleric
but did not land with the bard hmm
brands bow in the material way right you
can you can tell that she's
works okay and for the for their bar
that's not a material yeah she's
displeased with this automatic it didn't
Lance ah it didn't it didn't win okay
all right yeah I didn't land and so it
is it is at about this time that you
hear even down the stairs and into the
main the the cavernous main volume of
the doone-gate in you can hear heavy
pounding on the door where's Trevor at
the police rod yeah Trevor Trevor Trevor
is still with some bar this is this is a
big big thing like the one supernatural
creature that was actually in this room
just managed to not kill you still alive
yeah wow they're light at this but at
that the pounding of that door sure yeah
they say they say you're welcome to
right into the head office document sir
ask them about team Bellerophon and ask
them about our wild card license that
allows us to do whatever we want
wherever we want just be sure to put all
that information in there in your
notebook it's a little too real right
now let me actually write this down uh
Amy to human what the what else uh yeah
wild card like that sounds cool uh so
I'm so there v freedom yeah and I go
hang on so you're telling me that you
are actually from Ecuador incorporated
that's what you're telling me right now
you piece of [ __ ] elf person in front of
me a scone and run it should happen well
switch teams
can I sing for you guys yeah man no
there you have it open and they have no
yeah they got an opening do you guys
need a decision
okay babe do you guys need a bacon eater
because you need to see how it yes you
do all right yeah I'm hired Rosie are
you I'm going to look up this year when
he says the wealth card license and be
like it seems like you would know of any
beware wild card let's do I know about
this has been a my dog you have never
heard of it yeah if if it if there is
such a thing it's something you would
have to it's something you have to
investigate cool but like I say somebody
buddy but each each time there's another
fresh pound at that front door Tom each
each time they look and then with
slightly increased tension and then you
see the declare taps the Ranger on the
shoulder she borrowed our Ranger this is
the Ranger oh the man 3 yeah I got taps
taps him on the shoulder and then just
gestures away with his head right you
see reach down into a satchel Ana's on
his belt and they all reach into
separate satchels and pull out the same
object which is a small vial and I say
and the Ranger says oak by the way
listen when you write back make sure Oh
ay que it's a long one listen if you
guys could clean all this up that would
be great and he pushes it will do he
crushes the ampule disappears that
cleric crushes his and disappears and
the bard approaches you walnut and says
baby we don't kill each other we're
gonna [ __ ] so it wasn't coffin back but
and I'm assuming that she immediately
like just like a like a slowly yeah
exactly
exactly just like this slow long and
this is totally weird but I'm gonna go
to close I'm so mad but and then lift
brush and she's gone yeah oh my god okay
so I'm bring the heat alright so and I
want to just lovely real quick the
expression here wants like very
wide-eyed like clutching you're
clutching her pearls as it were but then
like oh so fuming about oak and like
it's a very good holiday treat a teacher
seriously what I see and I'm just like
writing all this down and like someone
needs to get the door yeah just holds it
out I'm in Amador's I'm gonna go get the
door
okay I'm March over there I got a glass
The Velveteen Rabbit isidori I'm going
to loot some corpses yeah good idea
yeah there's a whole mess of dead bodies
yeah I must say Trevor excuse me there's
your mightiness like a ludus cousin
there's a lot of crossbows that were
discarded yeah yeah each cross there a
six hand crossbows they don't there's no
extra ammunition for them at all I don't
want to add on one cross you do have a
crossbow bolt you can see honor that's
great yeah they didn't go well and check
out crossbow bolt oh yeah I was like it
was insanity was literally on the mint
or what a first adventure I'm gonna save
it my nemesis okay
absolutely await and so and so while you
are while you are harvesting I mean
these it you know LARP you know it takes
it takes some coin how do you are
officialy LARPers as near as you can
tell I mean it takes some coin to
manifest that machine there's a nothing
about you know would it cost to maintain
this dungeon environment that they have
here but you do find 30 gold spread out
two gems each worth twenty gold
okay the Minnesota goblets and things
like that if you want to grab a couple
of them they're not like they're the
best from gulp of goblet worldcom like
they're not yeah I think I have an
aesthetic that I like that [ __ ] all
right word is much and goblets what else
what are the nonsense is there here so I
know these guys are think either so when
you went down and wife exactly so you go
down the velvetine ghost that is in your
employ right has since the the front
this way a area is looking pretty good
as things went to hell you can see the
last couple of their sort of shambling
servants wiping makeup off their face
and basically beating feet out the back
through what you know to be the lower
part of the kitchen right through there
sort of lounge area that has that bar on
the right if you'll recall we got wash
more people spaces before starting
that's right there's a lot of good
lessons we got out of this yeah yeah you
know pile it all the way
yeah I'm hanging up so so when you get
when you get to the when you get to the
dorka tris yeah you open it wait I saw
that tonight can I see out before I kind
of dig round one they had their they
have a little peaky sure to think you
can you slide it to the left and you see
three what looked to be guards guards of
the road maybe some kind of a watch that
operates on the long road and you can
see their cart just outside okay
what's the car look like it look it
looks much more like the prison cart
that you had before it's not premium oh
of course of course that's your I
remember now
I was not trying to tantalize you with
this carton so all right well go ahead
and open the door and I say I say guards
I'd like to report an incredible crime
wait we're off duty we came to stay
sambar here well I wish you were still
on duty
yeah there's been a lot of murders 17
that's right yeah how make all of them
the entirety all murder every murder
each murder that could have happened
here
well my favor yeah yeah and Trevor yeah
yeah still understand that that actually
does yeah I know they think about it
yeah I might do it what's to like the
body count like how many were up there
if I hit the floor yeah I'm sorry I can
hear it I can think about as a parent
now is the parent there is 16 people
okay
including the vampire hunters okay so
for their 12 guests did we lose Sam yeah
we yes it early looted excellent ok we
can keep the bodies heap yeah if you
have the refrigerator cards rounded by
death like a lot of lessons learned
yeah got it and good stuff yeah chalk
this one up as a growing experience what
is it is all
yeah you were we're gonna file this one
well not everyone's going to be a hit
you know home office they're not even
here we don't even need to file the
documents on this we you know we could
just tell me what mine they don't know
they're not here the three of you friend
you frequent this this end yeah we'd we
are in need of rooms for the night I
think you could take whichever one you
want you may want to stay somewhere else
is an active crime scene
yeah are you here alone no no I'm not
I'm here with that party we just
witnessed an extreme act of that his
face crow is very taut night or the rad
party but like a extra like an advantage
heart he's not impressed by any of this
weather and assembling the subtle você
attempts at irony none of this is
working for him
cuz that crazy person yeah yeah he he
push us open the second door and you see
now that there are guards that you could
not see through the pinhole okay there
are there are five guards that are now
filing directly into I don't know this
boy a pretend to be a proprietor okay
you're just telling them a beaming that
it recruits like online agent for your
ass whatever is this the ancient is of
whispers I might so like anything he
says where's the staff I I'm right now I
am communicating to each of your doing
like
guys are one where the staff is and in
front of him I'm going ha like I've got
something to say like a parched cover
you can open the doors and tell a bunch
of cops go through the pile of dead
bodies in here you can sleep here if you
whine of murder that's right life died
last I heard they were preparing for
tonight's murder
through dinner that's it you go that's
what I'm talking about
Rosie's all about if you're here to
participate we ask that your way down
here and so we're ready and then there
are no murders
oh no friend it's going to be a murder
solving night of fun join us you won't
believe what this hand has prepared for
you if you could get done good their
cuts ready
come here Jesus Christ all right sorry
that that role that role is going to
make your life a lot easier
we just reckon so no no no no talking um
I can go with this either way we're
gonna die we're actual murderer no no no
no because it's just like we'll get to
it in table talk if you want to but the
shadow council was actually involved in
whether or not they would be LARPers or
amazing for them right little my god no
no and I have to mean I have I have to
bind entities oh yeah I had like I had
the combat one where they're authentic
vampires and then you have a different
relationship with teen Bellerophon y'all
are frickin immersion right now sorry I
don't know I'm sorry guys come back I'm
ready to go I have it all going under
anyway anyway that I don't I'm going to
start I'm going to collect a few items
of clothing and I'm going to join you
immediately and pass out their disguises
for the evening I know the four of you
take notes take my cloak and I'm sort of
going like move the category the cat to
the captain the captain softens a bit
three of his contingent are still well
they're they're still they're still
examining things surfaces looking behind
the counter as things like that one of
the guards he's pretty excited I bring a
hat and a blindfold and a walking stick
and a bandanna I passed them a house go
Samia
genic who's got a little character so
you still you've leaves you can laid
them out and the captain of the guard
if looking at his contingent and they're
looking at him to see if it's okay with
him if they play along with this and
then he is looking at the bandana and
the walking stick and he takes the
walking stick from the person you have
given it to and then gives them the top
hat okay it's a fine choice I'm also
trying to be really spooky with you
I've got my favorite bullet on oh yeah I
think so he saw where you are and he as
he s his you can see his spine arc a bit
yes as he leans into the stick and he
says and you all all right I want to
come in the room I just be like sorry we
learned this from the last group uh it's
20 bucks a head up for Tony gold Pizza
hat at front sorry sorry guys
genius we recoup our feet yeah while I'm
doing this I'm upstairs and I want to
get I want to assure Trevor away so he
doesn't look like he done did all of the
bite when the noise you can see him
because you're still up in the room you
can see him sniffing the air and looking
around the door a bit just of just a bit
trying to keep his snout in it's not
possible he's having a hard time um and
he turns back and he says the cold and
foggy Oh Trevor you gotta go you gotta
go you goddamn right I gonna go you
gotta go
we'll cover for you call Damon I know
you did what you could and I'm sorry I'm
glad you could be here to witness your
cousin cam it's over
who's gonna who go who go around it
could go around the doone-gate in I
think it's going to be you I think this
is why you're here tonight this was your
charge in life I'm gonna go get some of
my rags from the case yeah you get I
mean it's probably racks here but get
your best ones and bring them here and
no one else is going to do it so he goes
oh oh ah keep at it
yeah okay
hammer you're a good boy giggles eek
scrappy gives us a little scratch behind
the ear and then he jumps out the the
broken glass of the veranda door and you
see him just bound straight off the edge
and out into the moonlit field I'm just
like whisper and I say to the wind but
like you know should firstly flail Oh
buddy just yes yes just let this one
that's just one blow man whoops she's
trying to go a safe place yes and I blow
over
and at that the notion that he'll be
charged additionally from the room music
he he loses his old man voice and he
says we were not I assume this isn't
this is the room the room fee I will
include the entertainment absolutely I'm
being told
two things and it includes so much more
if we just charge them too much to leave
a better country yeah yeah use this one
yet when it's like okay use your mind
just play along but I'm pretending this
is like a group call along if we just
raise the price so much they'll just be
like that's too much trouble and they'll
go away all right well it's calling it
is instead of going this family matters
like weird sitcom solution my name is
make them go away give me a second
better day my [ __ ] I want to go back
to the Catholic thing yeah I really want
to have a moment like ah
baron von Winkle stuff please follow me
I have a tapestry I'd like to show you
and I want to lead him away from his
guard okay and it's still okay but first
though uh perhaps libations for our
forget and and I've instructed velvet to
bring a tray oh it's floating myself
from the from the kitchen since it's all
freeze in everything they want don't you
take wonderful we've unit attached
please is it wine or blood
hahaha just sweating yeah I'm never to
do such active no it looks like this is
this is the polar opposite of your
upbringing is now what I would want to
do this like facade on top of facade
luckily that like plays perfectly with a
murder mystery dinners yeah yeah it's
like some somehow conceptually you have
like drilled into the ultimate
manifestations yeah yeah II love this
sweaty proprietor yeah the idea that
like people do this like an additional
layer of lies on top of reality
responded I miss exactly that's okay
great
so you've instructed the the velvetine
spirit to secure spirits where ever you
got back there
from the yet there they're plentiful
there's also as I suggested a small bar
actually out in the open area okay so it
was something to consider but we'll see
we'll see where that goes but but he he
is he is ready he is he is weary from
the road you suspect that their task
involves a lot of driving and nothing
happening most of the time but he he
seems very familiar with the
surroundings I mean you think he might
have been to the doone-gate in yeah a
couple times it's only open late at
night as you know from the gate right
and there's nowhere that can like all of
the rooms are upstairs or where the
bodies are we have to go past there in
order to see so remember main set of
stairs up front
venue right there are two more sets of
stairs that come from the front that go
around and have room access on the sides
of the lycée so they can avoid that that
there there's two there's two dining or
there's two routes that go up there and
then of course the lobby lounge zone is
down there in that central area via the
morgue
guys are we doing a murder mystery or
not they really want us doing this is
this a bit I don't know we really like
gonna improv an entire murder mystery to
distract some cops
I just want to get drunk to the point
where they can go to their rooms I'm
going to be in league whose murder are
they solving no Whoopi Karen fun bites a
lot or whatever the name was no so you
can see so the day of they have been to
they've begun to try to figure out who
they are in this context yeah you know
it means yeah you got you got a right
certainty you got mister you got mr.
top-hat right you've got a scarf sir
right the the one that had been at the
end of the column who appears to have
the greatest enthusiasm for this
construct you've generated it's
constantly he has a monocle he places it
in his eye and he says who I say Oh
keeps doing it who is all my friends
right no no no matter they all did yeah
no matter what is it he sees like a set
he or a Shazz lounge book okay he's just
he's maximizing it I am I couldn't agree
more person yeah hey I I want to I'm
going to take the guards or their
captain a guard over and I'm going to
start explaining to him mostly to like
what the party at this point for yeah
not at this point
at this point the the rest of the guards
are having been given the okay to dress
in funny costumes they are now orbiting
the velvetine spirit like mods yeah
getting that beverages around it around
this bottle and there is there is a
point very near to the their initial
beverage activations that they forego
the glasses altogether
yeah and it's purely it's just bottle
yeah it's just bottle it's just bottle
they set the empty bottle down on the
edge and then it teeters and then the
velvetine spirit adjust and then toddles
back floats back sails back
whatever yeah you can't see them either
it's friction-free what are you doing
it's all fiction free so this they're
going to work now we have Lord Baron
Winkle stuff but he's lost his character
a little bit okay um he there was a
mercenary aspect that sort of crept in
when dinar came and tried to turn the
screws
yeah um quiet shallow my [ __ ] on my
friend can be a little coarse around the
edges but I've brought you into this
room for a reason and I look around make
sure nobody can listen I think that you
should play the relative murderer now
this is a secret role and it is a lot of
responsibility I think you might enjoy
it
I've seen men like you do very very well
in these roles what do you say
it's like generally speaking you know if
you were to say something that increased
a person's confidence their posture
would improve right right but because
this specifically requires that he
hundred you will in Italy he wilts in a
practiced careful way and anything he
says what do you require for he yeah you
ever the only requirements of this rule
I'm sorry gonna terms Duma creepy voice
is that you never reveal that you want
to murder her but you know in your heart
that you are do you accept me return to
party right so he he turns his back and
it takes him a long time because he's
[ __ ] doing it right he's getting over
there
I mean he's barely any you know the
mobility factors has been substantially
diminished and at this point a
developing spirit has returned in the
interim I've said you may want to check
this front area more thoroughly
it could be clues anywhere
whoa John I had to be startled by like a
crucifix Oh he-he'll hehe look he looks
up the grand stair and he says other
clues everywhere
oh yes friend we're still preparing the
illusion did you'll be impressed do you
want a baby close the door yeah so
here's what I want to do is I want all
these corpses I mean that was part of it
I turned to what can I eat all of them
okay good gonna eat the whole stash no
no that you turn into some kind of a
reticulated python yeah exactly finish
it all the meal scream like that scene
in Super Troopers whether they have to
yes yeah I like that you get the concert
so you're able to eat for probable if
you're going to eat all of these
murdered pseudo vampires at Yugi sure
so here's what I am doing while they're
doing this is that I want to close the
area off and then I want to just put
like a chair or something like I was
want to pile some stuff together so that
there would be some resistance if they
tried to do it yeah you want to make you
want to take this room off the menu I
want to take it off the menu and then if
I have any extra time I would also like
to maybe a rink because they're like in
the venue area is near where the
fountain is right only out is exactly
right it's in the hallway just outside
the doors interesting okay well then I
want to just kind of like arrange these
people so that maybe it kind of looks
like ritualistic or something like that
like this is some like wow I was just
going to lead them into the really good
people but yeah I was just going to let
them feel like they were just like
makeup like safe dead people
oh that's fine too I decide for later
when people find these oh well that's
like yeah and so there's like and they
feel like everybody that could have a
cup has a cup and then like
so it looks like the urine but
elaborately I string them up like you
know we can refer knees kind of thing I
believe right the killer wouldn't do
that killer would arrange them in a semi
yeah because I wouldn't what does Jen
are doing besides trying to extract gold
for everyone yeah I was just trying to
get the cops to go away now the new plan
is to get them blitz
to the FL yeah yeah well I guess I got
to play along are you down here with us
yeah I'm with you guys
yeah I didn't know about this amazing
plant dead body puppetry who invited
something like and better that's a
surprise to us like a real-life doll oh
yeah yeah anyway so we're not let some
clues originating something like what
well thank you yeah I got to be one step
ahead of them
yeah exactly I'm trying to think like so
there are six of them by five okay
including it includes the guy the chain
the captain um yeah I mean I would guess
I would I'm just trying to try to plant
some clues I guess that's a good idea
that's about that okay tell me the
nature and location of these clues
well I grabbed a couple of the cross
bolts per song that I'll hide them
behind like a curtain look at Easter and
I'll try to want yeah like an Easter egg
hunt like I'll try to put one like under
like a little dish see we use not like
nice and if anybody's looking away I go
mom okay they start looking at me yeah
you just like turn their head because
something that dinar would like I have
fun with secretly I think I begrudge
idli gold that's what I'm not even
secretly yeah maybe one please lumbering
around like this egg with you yeah I
know it's probably just just dark
fantasies about what could be happening
with this egg yeah oh no I'm like I want
to get help me get to the egg yes is the
plan I just like at a point like I get
behind a cop and I like pull a knife out
especially when you're like nah my
success a lot faster guy you acting yeah
yeah yeah as soon as they start
investigating up
there's I say we [ __ ] it in a piece out
yeah yeah so so they so they have begun
to toddle about you know a half a bottle
of hard liquor Patino a piece Oh about a
well-versed bottle yeah yeah throw that
in the mix that was some hard get up
yeah I got it the black stuff vision
maker on that that you don't yeah yeah
you don't want to you want to remember
you know what I mean but this but at
this point they are it's it's like the
mob if I stayed up station they are
flipping like they're flipping this
place over my god yeah we're going to
bring them up first what's up we're
going to bring them up gotcha but then
we're all going to we're going to shut
the door and lock it
magic it's a puzzle room I'm gonna leave
I'm already on my way out make my way
out yeah they're downstairs sound like
you jail Frank yeah okay so your unit
you're going to continue your rear role
as this sort of I think mad provider I
think we're ready to proceed to a room
which you might find very murder filled
I read let's come the rest among the
bodies is too dark and going to dirty
yeah but fine sweet recipe say that
black blanket epic dad dad mmm so good
but you go right over over by one of the
over by one of the curtains you can see
it's being parted and there's a bolt
behind it and you see the monocle pop
out he says wah wah hoo you found a clue
tonight so so there so this they're on
rails now like they they are ready to go
it takes them the the guard captain gets
about halfway up the stairs the proper
way with the cane and then he sort of
fudged as if the readout of it it would
have taken a long time in the meanwhile
we're like you found all the clues you
thought you found all the clues
yeah so he so tell me about the reveal
you tell us what we see but I'm going to
say Joan are you ready
throw that door open he gets his monocle
fixed just right here anywhere roll it
very well what you may see may disturb
you deeply so from outside you can hear
wallah is not imitating the sound of a
wolf just for ambiance oh yeah whoo whoo
and the door fly open and then there are
the bodies and they're all arranged in
this weird almost a circle like she
almost got all of them like right with
their heads going and like they're kind
of maybe holding hands a little bit yeah
so just looks very nice and then on the
wall like maybe she kind of went too far
uh-uh but she wrote trust no-one in
their blood that's final good and I
don't actually entrails like that
angling like party favors I don't really
like Guler fest I'm ready to put I'm
really like whoa but I go oh yeah what
this would be
oh very different ha ha good luck
gentlemen
all right so yeah they're they're
definitely impressed by what's been
presented here well ice outside
that's real fungus is holy [ __ ] I'm
ready for the cookin it's me outside
we're going I'm reading with a Halloween
in here ready for the Halloween episode
imagine a team but anyway so so bids if
the plan here that is to lock this door
yeah we're going to create you to
recreate your door scenario on the other
side and it as the as you're closing the
door the guard captain just stops dead
in his tracks then you see him look back
through the crack of the door and then
you shut it and lock it yeah like who
did it no no no good question okay run
okay let's grab we get back to a car
yeah yeah yeah
good all right I run over to their cart
and I smash the wheel all very nice
a little official strength disease I
think drinks know it under strong boy
Lex hey that's a 1 that's a 1 I do got
my philosophy can you go over and it's
like you have the plan in your head and
then you go over and you just kick it as
hard as you can and you hit it wrong so
there's like on the top of the toe and
just oh so you see the nurse for the hop
around on one foot
how when you roll a real one the viewers
have to give us something yeah exactly
you don't give them something yeah yeah
yeah yeah what a pity well you become
icy Denar fail miserably at picking I
run up and I kick the wheel too just so
you don't feel bad good I think that's
what mean it's getting away we can
attach this cart without great text I
guess right let's just go fast
no is it horse can I kill the horse Wow
what oh not anymore it doesn't it was
all ours I was good so you you you see
it now I didn't use a horse so kind of
let the horse run away it's late it's
too late it's you're inspired by walnut
yeah I'm trying to make friends watch it
this is what you like right little bit
did I do good
did I did mommy so no what happens is
that is it Hebrew he brings the sword
down yeah and you think for a second
that he's trying just to like make two
or stews as Christ that's a real hunger
games are trying to make two horses but
it comes down right on the strap and the
rest of the the mechanism that is
holding the horse oh you mean it's fine
no no the mechanism finally on a special
exact dates rather the lesser the lesser
horse part and it did is off like a bull
yeah like imagine imagine imagine an
alternate version of this universe where
they had invented something like a horse
cannon then fiery it's like that like
the horse of just yeah that's a good
horse out into the night yeah we could
have used that horse probably better
than the wheel couldn't
chorionic spit this is what occurs to
you and as you see it you know first
sort of dappled in silver yeah and then
I get our shitty horses and I was like
yeah yeah coriander sort of absently
chewing is there anything cool in their
cart shoeing resentfully their cart no
this is this is means you you think that
they may come across things on occasion
and carpenters um but no no this their
school in the car no there's nothing to
nothing back there in the cart it's I
mean it's a pretty like I say it's a
pretty rough it's a pretty rebel vehicle
but yeah he is I couldn't got my sword
like it feels just for a fact crystals
hanging from the back anyway I'm on top
of our car and I won't have used enhance
ability again to make coriander really
fast I hold her back I'm going to let's
go yeah get in the look get it rip no
coriander and in the width exactly
I also enter is a quick quick
I guess standard position yet core and
coriander remembers any business to get
that ancient bigger yes um that you know
that good very exactly the best berry
right this is like level five good
mission right it's um it's Odwalla yeah
right woo
let's get the protein that is exactly
what happens yeah back the cart down the
trail head down to the long road and
beat then start your way north the
Thunder is scaring the [ __ ] out of ya
it's very spooky in here or the Mike's
picking it up though yeah right now it's
physics if they are hungry oh there it's
basically striking the building a shake
on with with the weight anyway yeah yes
it yeah whatever I'll talk about that no
okay um if they start to pursue it
they're probably going to pursue it on
the long road are there any like little
side roads that we see that I can
cartographers our way through I love
everything about this ready let's yeah
but let's see what you got okay what
would you like me to roll in that I a
market offer guys don't worry about it
I told of it well that doesn't a great
Victor I believe I'm saying no but still
there you get for though for now for now
I'm going to say that
that star for Rosie's if you have time
for Rosie
geography is in a historical all right
context sir 20q all right that's real
good put on yeah you know you know for
about 20 to 30 days yeah yeah NAT 20
that's if it's on delayed reaction it's
only his eighth game Dungeons and
Dragons now yeah you know that you know
that in this in this part of the long
road to the east of it you know that
there are some older trails in the
summer hills that were once like mines
that didn't pan out
lots of old work trails I mean they're
somewhat overgrown now but you think
that you should be able to obviously
take longer getting home but you think
that you'll be able to probably work
that since were the only people at the
scene of a massacre yeah exactly so
these all this the situation is
basically just this sort of tangled knot
of trails that surround these mounds
similar the ones that you saw to the
north when you were on the Stone Road
okay when you stopped the rates right
okay so I climb on top and I sit from -
you like that even oh look this bump yes
like get those reins from you and I
start at solicit Vera's off the roads
and we start to wind through the woods
surrounding these like it's that like
scene for me Center when he's walking in
the car yeah how come here yeah yeah
keep it coming keep it coming
yeah so so as you as you pull off the
the beaten path and onto these more
ancient roads you often that often the
distance just in the dark surrounding
the the trail you see tiny wisps of
green flame so you know to be this is
just that this is this is how creatures
communicate okay I think it's very I
don't think it Muriel you think I
probably
like fire fire yeah okay pretty though
no no it's tasteful because on fire
because this is because this is this is
this is vitally important
you have forgone the long road for
protection right and have instead taken
these ancient roads that are literally
artifacts of humankind's failure to
derive any value from these places it is
incredibly dark okay
um so you guys all have dark vision
right yeah oh you're not you're not too
bothered
that's why trust me I'm the only one I'm
like what's going on out there I also
have a fire it's just yeah black figure
I mean I'm snapping them and it looks
painted over I could we could we could
possible ice and ground effect than what
I thought that's truly been to are you
go so grounded Patrick's element okay I
can say yeah go get ready it's so do you
castes in life or is it just part of our
car notes are the cards it's an
aftermarket if you want regards easily
usable light weather can we see with the
ground effects is it casting any weight
it's it's not a suit it isn't an
incredible distance but it's a little
bit more comforting yeah so you guys all
have dark vision I can cast our vision
but do you want to take a peek around
maybe and see what you see yeah why not
yeah boy one timer I'd love to do that
yeah you got the good awesome
no I go to sleep before you you're like
I'm gonna go you fall asleep on Bernard
yeah it's just like cordwood spoon yeah
we argue over who is a little spoon for
a minute right but I'm like I'm the
division it I'm a little fun um I got in
nine but I'm wondering if I don't know
let's have it
Oh actually I don't want to just read on
top I'd actually also like I'd like to
turn into my wolf form and run along
behind the cart because I am concerned
about our tracks and I want to make it
look like maybe we went down here cuz we
were being pursued by something and then
also just in case there's anything out
here because you're kind of setting up
we didn't just get all the way home yeah
yeah yeah we have the silent running
we do we also have the one need oh hi
drive then we have the one that let me
see the all around the car yeah I could
have all those things going that's cool
on the raise up and I also want to just
run behind the curtain okay also in the
mobile thing although I guys well just
don't chain meows whoa whoa no no okay I
lower my wall for no it's wolf nut will
snap up nut both note down grass so yeah
you know we installed one of those
modules at a time of course so you can
have that you can either have the
observation owl but you can have the
silent running cat so let's not even up
to you observation I don't think we're
going to see anything additional through
it so to dark Sally right yeah I mean if
we're worried about being pursued
silence sounds pretty good on silence
like we can do that and ground effects
and dancing like the dancing lights on
one of these a pompous at the comic
exactly where this thing only it does
sound yeah we'll see if anybody sees
I'll see a soundless yeah light sound of
Marty got ya on wheel we have to make
ghost noises I'm looking here you have
to run behind outside of the field of
silent that's fine yeah it goes wolfson
yeah ghosty Wolfie home yeah yeah okay
you're doing this yeah we'll do the
soundless okay attachment the cat yeah
yeah yeah so even even to your it's a
little uncanny as a Dino
virtually perfected pack predator
walking right along syntax exactly but
the it's okay but the pain in the
padding of your paw on the ground is
louder than the cart good nice they want
to mess with us I can go get it but it
also I would love to get a perception
role from a good I really worry Betty
calm uh yeah yeah eighteen you feel
dressed like straight through your your
paws as the every time they connect with
the ground you feel you feel a vibration
no it's
honestly it reminds you good good good
vibrations um but like Brian Wilson it
reminds you it reminds you of onyx oh
yeah okay that that's sort of like
all-encompassing but the earth is moving
okay basically but it right right now
it's like if it does require a conscious
effort to keep track of it okay well I'm
just gonna keep to myself because I
can't say anything yes my friend how I
kept conscious effort um Rosie
your understanding of this of this
environment back here
there should be a fork north okay I'm
very very soon I would like to get some
more history from you just to maintain
this that's not eleven trajectory you
think you might have missed it oh you
might have missed the the North Fork and
are now sort of seeking the next path in
that direction to maintain the time but
you think you may have you think you may
have lost
what's your time right now well right
now it's sort of in a northeasterly
direction it's through this it's
basically you're so you're going on
these paths that are around these
ancient mounds okay that as you're going
north do I know anything about the each
amount people have a lot of theories
about what they are that tends to be
culturally informed okay Giants think
something specific some people just
believe what the Giants believe when I
explain which is that badly that they
are really really big nice they're just
really really big yeah there's not
there's not much here like here where
the Giants believe that sounded like
that they think that that their kin
they're right they think that their
ancient kin are buried here so there was
a period there's a period of time where
they were even greater that the giant
kind today
is smaller than their ancient kin but
there was a period of time where you
know this this whole this whole land was
their ritual grave okay so this could be
a giant graveyard and you are starting
to feel vibrations that you can't
communicate to us okay all right but we
don't worry about that yeah yeah that's
fine
the priest is a huge plus I'm recharging
Rosie Rosie knows this about the giant I
think it yeah these are these are not
weird story okay all right
there's nothing crazy about this okay
well I don't feel what what what's doing
but just seeing those mounds and and
remembering those tales yeah you can you
know you missed it I know I missed it
I'm a little bit so I'm gonna pass about
trace now I'm actually going to make us
like even more difficult to see or find
because I don't know where the [ __ ] we
are and I don't trust that we are in
good space at the moment okay so we papa
trace which means the old shadows
silence radiates from you masking you go
in Danian you you you each have a 10
plus 10 bonus to dexterity self checks
and you can't be tracked except by
magical means and we leave behind their
tracks around the trees super engaging
demon initially I adjudicated that dress
not at a high percent accuracy but my
reading of it sort of implied that you
were the cloak of shadows and made you
impossibly difficult to see right there
it's really about being trapped right it
isn't about being to be able to hide
like in plain sight right so I think
that I edited judicata that incorrectly
so just a lot to keep that exactly at
the very beginning just so just keep
that in mind
so wolf not hmm
I need more perception from you know
closed 24 oh it was almost yeah timing
already give away wings all right you
hear in the distance it's almost at a
similar resonance to to feeling of the
ground the vibration seems to increase
as you hear it almost sounds like Horn
you're not sure that it is a horn but it
has it has a most like tonal musical
quality put that like an Alpine horn
like I see use like like yeah yeah this
episode's sponsored by recollection
that's right
environment um ok great so at this point
I want to pull up like run alongside and
I can't communicate anything slope to
Rosie but I want to like give like a
little bark and then just like lock it
up I'm walking eyes are you okay yeah it
came in the will yes obviously you don't
always bark at me so I I understand
something's wrong yeah and then I'm do I
think it's coming from joy no work
coming home at all yeah yeah I mean
you'd a quality role like that of course
uh yeah you you think that you could
find it okay I think I could find it
okay can I just turn are we going in the
direction of it we are okay so I want to
like lead out in front and then I guess
we just keep going yeah I've gone ahead
I love that you are showing like UK
Canada but you're showing the same
concerns and one more for a dogwood yeah
you are like a halo oh yeah so you tell
concern and then you go in front so
clear you're not scared friend yeah we
follow you go I'm gonna I'm gonna let
you leave like I'm pretty lost right now
okay cool cool okay so yeah I want to UM
like I want to get as far ahead I mean I
know they're going fast but I can you're
pretty tough so I just want to get like
look ahead of them you can see okay
whenever I can look for more absolutely
you the night air is activating
everything that you like about Wolf hood
this is something like this is this is
it like this is this is what you were
meant to do and as you as you sort of
lope out ahead of the cart you can see
in the distance the moonlight is casting
along the edge of one of these one of
the hills in the summer hills you see
like a burst of earth okay great
that puffs out and as it as it erupts
the sounds that you heard increases in
volume oh oh okay all right I'm with you
I'm with you um okay
this I think we should just keep go I
don't want to go up to them at all Wow
like let's just keep going are we
heading toward that verse that you
thought is it like directly yeah but I'm
a straight ahead into the left yeah okay
do I see it as well yeah yeah this at
this point you see it authentically you
don't see but you don't see creatures or
anything like that like nothing nothing
except for the earth and this sound
strange sound and then as that happens
the vibration ceases
well not I'm gonna keep going I'm at
like I keep driving but I'm like walnut
all right mmm that's the scent you can't
place then I'm gonna peel off from them
okay
and I'm gonna go check it out all right
so I'm just did you just look lo pup the
cake now make damn banana in Rome I'm
going to pull around to the left I must
slow down okay I'm just going to keep an
eye on you okay I want to go inspect
what the party's mouth that's good yeah
yeah this is a dive into the pit weight
in the head yeah it is it's challenging
to it's challenging to place it it is an
ancient but notice ancient earth it is
the it is the old stone it is no prey oh
okay
yeah um and then as you get closer to
the door you see that this floor so as
you guys you get closer to what is
clearly the entrance of something
subterranean almost just dis gorged from
it in front of it may be as a result of
the burst
is our bones clothes and a staff okay
all right telling us that this is
normally it is a training staff that's
very similar to Rosie's okay okay so if
I can get closer to the the door and
just do a perception check on like
what's immediately here is really kind
here beyond it or yeah yeah absolutely
do things yeah wah wah wah wah my second
jalisa if you'd be so kind to add to
beat the treasure device for the shadow
council thank you yeah I've unlocked it
yeah you unlock some treasure I don't
like to give away that's what was in the
ancient earth exactly yes
so you here free Mountain Dew with your
yeah with your scooter oh yeah yeah yeah
with your with your senses you can hear
running water and you can hear it
bouncing around in a large space you can
you can hear the sound of this bouncing
around in a excited and expensive yeah I
didn't do it but like okay so at this
point I'm gonna what I'm gonna howl
right here it okay whatever
whoo whoo but then how will they I'm
assuming I can't get in with these dog
paws right you could I mean that's just
the entrance so I can just going okay
then I want to go hey it isn't in the
doorway in the classic sense like that
it's just that passage under it isn't
like a like a knocker okay as soon as I
hear you how I use my staff I just smack
the door to wake these two up and then
I'm like yeah yeah I'm not going to even
like you're adults you'll do what you
want but I'm gonna whack it so you guys
know I'm leaving and then I'm off after
you okay
yeah same oh yeah I wasn't really
staying I'm good so it was like I was
very much leaving
that they're that smelly great stink
yeah heard that sound of other by about
casket bursting open yeah caustic stay
exactly there you know and I'm waking up
it's like Darwin ah yes I mean it gives
you wings so say say so you so you've
helped your compatriots a groggy dinar
Blitzen is sort of half-heartedly yeah
there's no look like home
where'd y'all take us like I say jump
talk at your at your feet at your paws
hmm
you can see like I say it's just like
the it's the rags that are clinging to
these skeletons and I guess a so they
have various various types of equipment
with them you can see that like swords
that are corroded down to the hilt you
can see you can see just like down to
the wood handles but all but the blades
of these weapons are all pocked and
savaged okay by rust and corrosion but
it's been a minute but this yet but this
this staff is pristine
okay well I mean obviously is it a wood
staff it is some first time like threw
the stick and I was carrying yeah yeah
oh yeah yeah you know it knows it up no
is it up yeah Brendon is writing the
bite yeah you're doing a bite on the
standard but I'll ask you like lay down
yeah exactly one of these um okay so is
that like is it does the passageway
continue on I mean I wait for everyone
to yeah we go playing with the station
yeah you can you guys shop and I looking
Perry I know our documenter like the one
who does all our legal stuff is that
care just like God that beating was
small yeah you're like oh look see
laughing like jockey man learn tonight
classes yes
there's a lot of like really affirming
commercials featuring dinar but no no
you see it you see it as a as a stair
that goes down their alcove with sort of
emerald almost green flame in alcoves
that go down into this context okay all
right continue on can I take a look at
that staff yeah you can visit better
than mine can you guys fight a little
bit yeah we're talking I'm gonna do it
like yes good girl good but then you
actually want yeah yeah okay yeah no
yeah it's it's very fine okay balance
there are three black bands around the
top and each of them is in a script that
you can recognize it is it's a
bookkeeping script like a monastic
bookkeeping script okay so it would be
used for poetry or anything like that
it's really it's meant to be as didactic
as possible right for accounting
purposes basically it records the first
ring says two six star on her ascension
to master um and then each of these
rings goes to goes through another
masters Ascension and then presumably
it's passed down you're not sure if the
top is the most recent or the bottom is
the most recent but it's clearly it's an
important act this staff is passed from
from masters to students who then ascend
and this is a tradition that I'm not
familiar with it wasn't a part of it
wasn't a part of your way of the shadow
rituals but it's not unheard of
okay like a Stanley Cup of sticks yeah
exactly justifications all over second I
up I think
her two tickets wrist athlete Mike
that's my vote so named vote in the
channel for the better no yes I went
dick yeah check this out if you keep
some mouth let me get detection field I
mean it's woman up I can it looks alive
a color yeah it does all have good okay
nobody years a better can of but not a
prize role it's a 22 yeah it's very good
I mean this is this appears yeah as you
as you begin to investigate it just sort
of turning it this way in that in the
Emerald light that is emanating from the
tunnel it's sort of the faster it moves
the less coherent it becomes so but
there's no magic oh if you detect its
magical as it s alright great it's magic
it's magic AF could be more than half I
recommend you you will do stuff and you
move it very fast and stop it inside a
person I'm probably take this average I
was like no dude it's negative n note it
event it's like it's like the arcane
Roadshow yeah right it's just like
becomes a result will remember yeah and
also this could go hi Reza have money go
yes listen along exactly you think you
need to spend a short rest with it okay
to truly master it right nice in your
ass yeah in your hand in your hand right
now right it's plus one damage plus one
attack okay but if you as I said if you
can spend a short rest
mastering the quarter staff as you have
mastered yourself then you can there's
there's even more very sexy still second
we put that stamp okay I would like to
take the stuff I start and dump my
garbage staff on the ground
go for it might throw it actually I make
my old staff doing make oh yeah well and
I follow it down the corridor yeah it's
very flattering um so if you have
trip in your on your equipment it's
called the staff of domestic cars I just
also cyber I'm just really living my
furry dreams right now I never go back
exactly no I just like an Animorph thing
or if you stay along as I know by
attorney exactly Joe by reference in my
life today you see a red tail you're
apparently transformers alright anyway
yeah no no no thank you for Table Talk
where I talk about my people over there
no I I did here listen I'm gonna go into
my I'm gonna go into my [ __ ] later no
yeah my druid I had a drew it as well we
can compare druid notes for World of
Alex Mack fiction for me
right and then you be like come on man
why are you pushing that pendulum to my
eyeballs like 160 sponge oh that's right
you'd be chemical anyway so I'm going
down me down the corridor all right all
right so the quarter staff is clattered
down the stairs has rolled to a stop
here in the base you can tell even as
you go down the stairs are slightly
slippery mm-hmm
liquid yeah what it's cool it's not done
it's not cold
I'm sorry sure they're not not cold it's
not cold Oh get it isn't it doesn't like
it isn't planning from hot ok it's warm
you would say Fahmy
yeah it's like it's like a winter fresh
mouth gotcha
yes is it yeah I made that noise oh yeah
exactly but but that's that's the
situation rabbit but as you are going
down you can this is this this stairway
it has some what you might describe as
aftermarket features okay
such as so as you are as you're going
about halfway down you can see that the
stone the work stone parts at two
thresholds to separate thresholds on the
way down and you can see a series of
regular holes
okay and then as you not fancy holes
just regular holy what regular in terms
of how they are related in and gotcha
gotcha they're not actual they don't
come from they're not from rodents okay
right
this is birds don't live in here got
your like this is it isn't purposeful
and intentional yeah yeah your classical
you go you're alone you get it all you
get whole like this but as you are
approaching as you approach them stones
revolve and cover them up and then you
can see that there's another row of
these farther down and as you approach
stones cover those up as well
and you continue down okay shy and the
holes increase in quality yeah exactly
we start to see finer and finer grades
of all oh yeah go ahead of us a real
larger date I'm all the way the bottom a
necessary Randa larger gauges of hole
yeah no I'm with everybody but okay I
didn't know if we were all seamless just
innocence yeah so are the behind us is
this happening is revealing themselves
no no no exactly no no and in fact in
fact as you go down as soon as a person
as soon as there is a space between you
they reveal themselves and then as soon
as one of you comes by they actually
close back I try to do a self approach
all of these holes so that maybe it
wouldn't close up here if it's dry and I
know you still have passive uh face
attractive no that's on the cart it's
just a card does it good one a lot 23 I
was good
absolutely so you you you maximize your
stealthiness yeah every absolutely every
capacity you have to not be noticed
learned over a hundred and fifty years
and it doesn't work is leveraged
definitive rocks yeah it's not it's not
connect you far as you can tell because
you you killed it you know you killed it
I did okay right it's not connected to
the sound yeah okay Mission Impossible
link up and down there's my wire it's
like nothing I suppose what's up oh my
god yeah alright let's continue then he
has anything expensive they want to try
on the tail or what's her what's her
like like our pullback scenario like are
we just kind of like I love going into
the earth I feel good
I like these holes but we were just
going to go back to there our office
yeah what's the draw hand and really we
have to you're a cool staff out of this
yeah you're you know your excursions
below the earth's crust you are
generally speaking cool and damp these
are for you these are great these are
positives yeah yeah right I can actually
see how this would be a draw for you
exactly a lot yeah I mean I would be the
one who going but I feel myself like I'm
used to that pole and I've gotten I've
gone too deep at times so I'm like
before we go crazy
exactly but this is not but this is not
like that it is not cool oh I see and it
is not dark I don't like honestly and it
is slick but not damp this this
environment is unlike your homeland if
you're just damp not slick exactly now
in the base as you as you enter the
large area in the bottom it's a are you
are you already cartography yes this
kicks ass I know I was so pleased I was
also pleased I was going to chastise you
but you're kicking ass now so this is
important information for you yeah this
stairway goes down and then opens out
into a vast realm chamber okay
sister look at inside of a tandoor or
something like it's bulbous interior
section you can see that down at the
bottom to the left is an exit to the
right is another exit I feel like I'm
telling people how to get off of a plane
um in the event of an emergency we're
going to need to know so in the very
center there may be an emergency in the
very center of this room like the event
is a gigantic fountain but the fluid the
the water that you heard is not water in
the classic
since of course never I would've never
is right why would it be Clamato
yeah it's cool motto no no it is warm
when you can field even feel the warmth
of it from out here know about this yeah
and it has a greenish it has a greenish
green hint that's lame
no he doesn't it heartily yeah green
cream to your personality
listen you're talking with the brand
yeah survival so I can like smell it
yeah yeah smells experice yes ah it
smells good it's 16 yeah this is this is
not safe no this is this is something
you would see in a in a deep cavern acid
like a yeah by a bank a sulfuric acid
like like like like this is not the sort
of hot spring you would sit in so
unfortunately like all dogs I got to get
into the trash and this is like all dogs
I go to heaven like here we get the
ipecac ready I go in on that ya know I
been back from it like half no so the
opposite so central fountain exits for
and ass and in the back of the room is
you know so basically these are all sort
of equi distant from each other around
this orb this sort of round area that
you guys are in the ceilings is doesn't
seem worked seems almost like a natural
formation and then the opposite wall
where the other eggs that would be in
this classic thing is a black gate that
has in its center but it's round it
isn't in the classic sort of portal type
shape it is a round sort of almost
oculus type shape the outer ring is
broken into eight equally sized pieces
seven of the symbols you do not
recognize and one symbol you do
recognize because it is the symbol that
is on your focus and then enter yeah so
we have you have the eight around the
edge and then in the center it is
equally divided into three parts three
in the center okay but this is this is a
crease see symbols and I'll give them to
you after the game
sure yeah um course the pour-over jota
for him did i don't know ever so alright
i want to start yelling now I recognize
my symbol but all that I can't read it
I just know the shape yeah you know you
know you know the shape but this is the
thing right by this like you've always
known it
it gives me context you have Mekons
angle because you can see the rest of
this dark alphabet that it is a part I
don't know
it is not concern it is the earth that's
the name of your th e you are that's the
name of your that is the name of that
symbol I see oh so hungry for that you
should see I'm transfixed it's like yes
she is lugg that there and I'll get [ __ ]
one thing about it any other part of my
life and I just turn it I'm like don't
worry about the cops following us I was
asleep for part of it I was expecting to
wake up by the egg you got a second
fuzzy on if you say that I say shut my
egg hey you're a where's my egg
I look can we leave them here let's put
it up to a vote under sniff the gate and
I'm like vote yes leave here what so can
i I can only discern that one
that's right through but I'm not right
not the others do the other the other
and I'm going to write the the others
don't mean anything directly even you
know what your symbol is called
um it's also how coming how close are
you to this thing I think so right now
you have what's the diameter of this
room
right now standing at the like closer to
the steps I'm looking at it exactly so
so the the fountain is in the center of
this circle right and the radius is 30
feet okay okay so 60 K over so um yeah
let me let me kind of split the
difference as I go around it so I'm not
walking to the fountain yeah but yeah
you can safely avoid this yeah I get I
get halfway up yeah if right and if I
feel like can I do perception for for
traps and a touch just down the terrace
yeah
no no can I ever that because I'm
staying it's a double punch I'm flanked
by the family identifier hockey uh well
since we're in like a weird room
I just want to divine sense so undead
fiend or celestial presence I can detect
because there's about to unleash Sun
yeah oh god I do that you are you and
Rebecca yeah until end of turn
I can sense undead fiend or celestial
presence nineteen sixty feet which I I
would like you to make a constitution of
a constitution row yes that did it hmm
and your thirst yeah yeah that's nice
good wondering eighteen eighteen okay
plus toots want to get you feel like you
are as of as a paladin as the as
basically the fist of your face you have
seen castle see do you know how it works
you know what's to be done right there
there are policies and you know
processes for this sort of thing you
feel like you have been struck by a
battering ram like you on the floor ooh
so you you you have attempted to sense
other worldly entities diabolical in
Tana and you are in it from the gate I'm
getting the sense or just from the room
you are you are surrounded by
nefarious intent okay so you see him hit
the ground yeah
and that's what that's what that's what
the good role yeah yeah so so you said
you sniff they playing they're gone bad
bad role or a better okay the bad room
role like really old obviously a really
bad room like bad bad room okay no I
yes never after you see me out and I'm
just like in here I know you know even
in your woven guys wolf nut Don grass
that a documentary task before the first
before you pass the first junction of a
dungeon you know that the documents are
there is a form that documentaries fill
out all right fair enough
I hear yes there's various paperwork
even even at the beginning so sick
catalog it feeling that yeah I'm dying
to hug that human talking also because
we just came face-to-face with team
villain or whatever it is yeah and
they're Colleran excuse me
telephone and I want to make sure that
you know that's the only way I know I
can one-up them is with documents or
ship that's right yeah they don't have
one yeah Chris said how valuable the
role really exactly um so in apply for
job security I turn back into my own elf
itself uh and just start documenting
what happened to your like interviewing
me like buckled over so honest a little
one it pancake probably Jenna know how
much in your face also ten so done but
this is so you you you file a brief yes
informational bit there's a specific
document it's it's called like the
initial dungeon assessment template oh
yeah of course
I know about that yeah I dad yeah yeah
yeah it's like you you slip to it
and then the first question is
yeah briefly describe the entrance oh
yeah to the cavern mm-hmm but really
basically describe the entrance to the
subterranean entity and it's and it's a
multiple choice one of them is warm it's
warm yeah boys
don't ask that about all this stuff all
that stuff is true except that first
parts multiple choice mm-hmm one of them
sort of looks like a keyhole one of them
looks like a more traditional stone
right
one of them has like branches and
bramble that go around the top right I
want it's the first of the three it sort
of opens up and then this is slightly
wider around the top yeah like a
standardized test you put it back in
again Tron exactly then you get your
answer you're like home exactly describe
describe the temperature and environment
hmm which dungeon I kind this one doing
okay you wanna know what I plan on doing
or what we are done are you I need I
need my team with me Fitz
Dre asking me how I still have before me
um you're the document okay so there's
an important time looking at this form
is asking me about the temperature
yeah yeah yeah environment different so
I'm describing a warm balmy
and I say that it is unnaturally so and
then I also just say that it has a
generic ancient stink about it okay the
next question is describe the features
of the first chamber hmm okay
interesting so I say I describe the
entrance the to access the acidic
fountain maybe the gate and I make a
special note like maybe there maybe
there wasn't enough room for this but I
still do it and I note that because
there seems unusually like the full
title yeah course person I'm actually
interested in it I'm in one of the the
icons on it and then I go in this also
to note are pelleted mysterious left
stricken and saying his faith is shaken
right so you're filling this out right
now
what everyone else - I'm walking slowly
and purposely toward this gate and I'm
grasping my relic my piece of the altar
would the symbol on what can it was kind
of cool checks can I do so I want what's
good ok I already did our Ken on I did
our count on your staff that's right you
can get listen you can get a zarkanians
you one you can crank the archanan yeah
well let's see if it way neat man I'm
going to dumb so I'm gonna do it on the
on the gate itself mmm
and then what are you trying to find out
nothing at all I'm just going to enjoy
the mystery yeah I was there
I was going to try to assess like in the
same way that he's trying to determine
the nature of whatever entity may exist
in this space that's what I wanted to
know right I don't know what you are so
the closer you get to it so you you have
produced your focus the closer you get
to this door the more faces the focus
has what so it shifts geometrically in
your hand the closer you get to this
gate and what's more I mean it's a the
nearer you get to this portal you are
dumbfounded let's say that's why you got
a 1 and not because you wrote so poorly
at a crucial juncture took in my
campaign it's our food yeah our labor
not because I'm bad know so it's like a
raspberry like imagine it's just
unfolding right it's like a yeah it's
like a full dimensional object and this
is the 3 fish right well this exactly
and as I said it of course the thunder
and lightning right um now these other
facets as I put it any other glyphs on
the other you know they flippin with the
others look the stones were flipping no
I think it's like seem like a pyramid
shape becomes a cube want to do is
develop a sophistication yeah but like I
said are their volume whether we let
on the other side yes but they are not
as edged your edge for the ER is deep
and purposeful right it is what you cut
out of that altar right in the Underdark
these other faces the the symbols on
them are not as strong they sort of pass
in and out yeah
from of definition from our distance do
we see these changes or is the only
seeing them as he gets closer like the
only affecting and closest person sort
of thing I think maybe I'm holding it
out like this and you're seeing my focus
just changing I don't interpret any of
the rest of it it's it is it wants to be
here it is drawn to this home I have to
proceed so as I said my job eight around
new symbols I mean it's literally a
multiplication of your consciousness to
see this you had seen this one symbol
that represented your cosmological
understanding and there are seven more
oh I stride all the way up there's no
other like it's slow but it's purposeful
it's not slow out of hesitation but of
reverence
so in the middle of this of this
Stargate yeah it's not starting
it's a guy the ball game yeah hey family
honey it's me guys we just come to
anyone else's bananas's like I said you
can live in Stargate with us come on I
want to oh listen up the you can see
that there's imagine a pie cut into
three equal wedges in the in the center
of this and then it's sort of it's spin
slightly almost like a imagine imagine
taking a compass and setting it on a
table and you can see imagine that it's
sort of like dialing and tuning like
it's reacting to you in a way to
depending yeah okay yeah the five-dollar
words keep coming up oh I keep all
walking yeah and I'm assuming if this
thing is going to become a sphere yes so
point
as you arrived your you can see drawn in
broad strokes the symbol of the ER fills
one of the three pieces and then you
hear a low sound that is the sound of
that horn oh right so by the way roadies
I see you rotate four or five and I'm
tired and you can stop him you are you
like tuck a punch to the gut and yeah
and you're taking your doing
documentation like in your implants
again and I'm just like hell no and so
I'm going to run up to you and be like
we should probably we should probably
check us out later the same streaks on
the ground panará this seems like maybe
the wrong place for us to be right now
no you're very excited why don't we come
back later after we were group not
possible okay
oh yeah it's like leaving range yes
happens on the bottom of the document so
you had on tell me about it so you have
got so you have answered these questions
yeah these are all standard parts of
this form I'm very familiar exactly yeah
I like it's obvious like it would be
boring if it weren't so exciting rightly
boring if it weren't so unborn the next
part of the document says the space
there begins to be filled with text and
it is not text of the standard printed
form okay it is being written as you
read it okay and it says have you
interacted with the Gateway and then
there's and then there's a question mark
and a period and a period I hesitantly
right no idiot
which is true below that well actually
it's a liar I don't know as soon as as
soon as you as soon as you write the
note the
autumn of the paper curls up from
underneath your quill okay and tears
itself off the top and folds itself into
a bird cool that flaps out of the
chamber and up the composer there we're
just normal for my dog no no you have
never seen this before you know you knew
that you knew that the document sir
sheath is not paper in the classic sense
but generally speaking this is not a
normal thing the next piece of paper
says this is the secretary in' of
acquisitions incorporated and then below
that it says run oh and then they
underline it three times
ah okay and then I say hey we uh what
was really close you I don't know if
that standard filing procedures okay and
we have our orders from head office we
are to run okay so said the horn the
horn with my stomach here and then over
the sound of the two other parts of this
become red-hot okay and you hear and
written on
no no just okay so basically and you see
sort of the symbols around it flashing
independently and you hear dissonant
notes from the upper left and upper
right thirds of this symbol I see the
fountain in the middle of the room
becomes a just a gout of acid in seconds
it overflows its Basin and begins to
spill and splash out over the floor
gotta go in fact and the room itself
begins to dance and sort of sway
you're seeing it it's the Mambo yeah
it's a dark Mambo do we know we didn't
know from a dark mama so you you had the
right idea to check of the whole time
grandma a right idea
yeah get a [ __ ] out exactly the question
is how are you going to get me out of
this room right if only someone had a
really compelling way of convincing
someone to do something yeah oh well I
got a pill Vanara
I'm gonna tear connick entitlement our
party member he's with him I know he's a
liability
I've been saying it from the start he's
obsessed with destiny this is all in
character although I'm going get him we
got to go
he is an asset to the company all right
there's a very organization the very
first interaction we get really coins it
in yeah all right I'm saying this old
beef all right okay how is your chronic
entitlement my boy okay so I gotta get
up it does my cell phone guys can hold
yourself up I say I just notice an award
my god
I knew God and I go okay like I just go
lean Jean and then I pull out I'm
knocking you down I pull out pricipal
I guess christmas-related we're allowed
to have cross right pull out first of
all okay all right chrome to the actual
function toothbrush for an aside
CrossFit is no way an escape it's in a
family project with my daughter if you
can't tell with the egg yes so you reach
down for you reach down for Percival
yeah to get it out and to you're looking
down to grab it you can see that acid is
starting to sort of wash over your boot
I'm immune so I'm like whatever
yeah I drink this I breathe it and drink
it yeah it's fine all right he's with it
yeah your boots are not immune
yeah
from oh yeah I know I got to do a promo
ready I go Mean Gene you see these shoes
make sure their shoes $600 leather shoes
like now I need you to focus up I need
you to follow dinar cart dryden dragon
flying cursor is stealing wheeling
dealing Dragonborn you need to come with
me right now spin them around whoa and
when you put hands on me I mean you're
like bending me around a grass shoulder
just like spin the shoulder so your
attention is while you're like while
you're finishing that and before you
spin me on muttering to all of you but
inaudibly I say keep this asset away
from you a minute longer like I'm not
paying I know the act of strength cool
you lay your hands on me and I'm enraged
top tenth activate jealous like that
we're not wanting it take my attention
away from the thing for a moment what's
that roads are counter it's our
campanilla all right like you don't know
oh you got it that's wrong that's 13 13
is not enough it's not enough it's
correct what to do so he gave me the
athlete falling down on us right now
yeah did this very good cellular
Christmas so I know no but I've seen
that do you see us that was great I was
really creepy that was the real country
at that what's coming out yeah so he is
holding it you're over here you have put
your hand on his shoulder and effort to
spin him around and without he doesn't
move at all
and you see from the Gateway you see
ruby tendrils shoot out all around Chris
yeah none of them hit Chris
Catherine to the trip but they all did
basically like an almost an outline
around him they go out and then they
just begin to rise around him almost
almost protecting him
almost so the draconian settlement did
nothing
well he used his dafuq they leave him
here I don't give a [ __ ] [ __ ] stay
here I really don't care you're going to
swing at me as dinar I don't give a [ __ ]
I don't like where's my eggs I gave it
my best shot you're gone here's Percival
sorry
enjoy your and would was that bad it's a
toothbrush was gonna swing nice invited
my god didn't work it was the promo no
ice and Raisa no mood you tears really
yeah I could thrist doesn't want you to
succeed but like well you got some other
bag of tricks to to to swing yeah that
was my best move Wow no I know someone
some squirrels oh yeah that's their
friend
what me yeah oh yeah I did take my nap
so I recharged my kid sweet nap hairy
effects I feel bad using effects on like
you're part of your party yeah everyone
we I didn't know works out it worked out
it worked out but I do want to say that
in the second episode you actually did
roll again I know me your table sides me
I know
yeah I like the crystal I know and I was
lectured afterward that people were like
email me like an army thorn with me I
forget you think those for discuss farm
I volley aqua review again party gave
each other alright alright I command I
try command you can all you could
potentially beat this though
tit tit exit alright I use the command
exit okay well I got a yeah what's he go
you have to succeed a wisdom savings
route or follow the command okay I'm
pretty good at that but let's find out
nothing thank you I don't have advanced
uchi guy okay I couldn't even apply
élisa élisa do you think next week we'll
have the rolling trace do you think love
rolling trace next week woo well should
you be there with us right yeah sure
what's your spell safe so I don't think
it mattered oh that's just a wizard you
just I don't get them safe
oh okay gosh maybe I don't know how
those work all right here we go
oh gosh you're all high rise to the
channel Alisa Prince died it
yeah please let the shadow council know
they will be richly rewarded by cut
wrist Rob's critical role accrued
critical role may be rounds in any
critical role may be a trademark term
critical dice result dice notate all
right this is like just lug it off
Carmen yeah we can do it right arm first
understand so this act this assay my
favorite and I will exist so far so far
the leather of the boots is keeping you
okay okay great um so I want to yeah I'm
gonna use charm person on person he has
to try and do just try it again just do
another with some saving through see if
you can get you guys yeah how many 22
gotta give me on a strength you got a
pick me up or something I know well
that'll be next all right roll I look at
her and I go which are my dry yeah we
all try one thing I've one thing I can
do we're going I'm happy Linda I can
cast darkness on the gate and his dark
vision won't work so he is just going to
be completely anything to look darkness
yeah yeah yeah yeah so I'm going to do
that and you can't do [ __ ] to save
against it so it's just happening just
happens okay so I'm holding this thing
up there yeah I'm trying to do whatever
bargain I yeah and it just vanishes
likeness and I'm in it to it yeah I'm
there yeah you you don't see anything 15
foot radius sphere so you so dinar dinar
and walnut but she whispers in a way you
have never heard her whisper before and
then you know it yeah and then but a
wrap around around cthe risk drought
forms this just impenetrable black
marble of darkness wonderful
ordinarily I'd be thrilled yeah if I
said anyone hit in there it's like a
sensory deprivation chamber himself is
in crack the dark night yeah that's it
on the gate so it's not going to follow
him no and you any but you can see
projecting out of the back of this are
these writhing tentacles
I think it's the gates work for a moment
yeah you know I realize it's not I
shrink and I I move about in it briefly
to see if I can correct it and then I I
roll and head back away from you gay he
leaves the tentacles inside the sphere
they're dope they don't follow him
correct they're planted in the ground
oh no they're there they're reaching out
directly from the gate okay
Oh from the gate okay okay I thought
they're underground but he's moving away
from the jail yes he is moving away from
the tentacles but they actually don't
like that try thinking about the game
trying to get better signal yeah I
assumed trying to get in more harm and
trying to get more better you're trying
to get more j-bars that's right take 14
points i damaged holy [ __ ] they were
a trap yesterday they don't want it in
you but you you know how much it will
get they don't eat that no no what if
this is you if you have felt this before
this cold heat you felt it in the in the
darkness between rooms in the test
market in the shattered place that
you're a wimp an yin walnut dawn grass
sewed together with spider silk oh right
yeah and when I encountered that that
the entity that I apparently made a deal
with I'm unbloodied I don't feel good
I'm I'm lashed by these by these
tentacles
that's right thing but you can even
Boosh yeah you've yeah you have you have
but you have been drawn back you can
still see them reaching out trying to
draw you back in but now from the back
of it you can see this dark sphere and
you can again see your companions right
and you're you are it's almost you know
it's reaching up almost to the top of
your boot this acid you I assume have
ascetic sandals yeah I'm like basically
exactly yeah yeah two points of damage
so there are three escapes here three
got escape yeah there's a
up there yeah can you just grab him now
is every time I do something to murder
you're so strong this is dissing me the
pin cushion did actually drugs I am
really strong all right
actually you know what that is true I'm
better too I am very strong and great
right I'm great really great
okay all right handsome yeah all right
uh all right I'll try to grab him by the
scruff yeah and bring him with us yeah
yeah pick him up he lashes out I am not
paying attention to you you're not
fighting anymore I don't have guy I'm
done time screaming as a gate I'm sorry
I was too weak on two weeks then I say
yeah yep you sure are right agreed come
on so sweep up Rosie yeah and I'll see
ya and then I just like in one motion
like I grabbed her and I just like put
her on back so I can see that she's got
those a little soggy yeah I could feel
sucks yeah no party penises um and then
I want to make way do guys yeah the
stairs
I'm just being carried exactly I use so
pointing so you remember you remember on
your way in that the stairs and indeed
the stones were slick yeah I do um you
can see that same dark moisture
it's almost running down the stairs now
god we got to go another way it's a
hotel boy I know we're in like naught
times with flipping slides but Walnut
somehow knows what this looks like is
okay okay of course she doesn't
all right all right I mean someone to
make a quick decision what I could are
we taking but there it is left last kick
left so you you are you are now running
splashing through this
increasing volume of the acid it's not
good you get to you get to the exit on
the left and you see that this is
actually a staircase exactly like the
other one all three of them you could
look back you see that these are all
identical staircases that
go up and you see just rivulet of mucus
okay at this point just because we're
chilling an acid and he's out of the
acid because you're holding him and I
want to imagine this yeah this and it's
like very tender it's not the body
garden co-innovation what we're talking
about what we're talking about here is a
a slash fanfic boundary thank you I love
it
I'm Kevin Costner anyway I cast a park
skin on myself just to boost my AC while
we love it doing this zone um okay so
anyway now I'm all crusty yeah yeah
waiting through the a so let's go try
the other door well they're all there
was one more no he's I played it there
all the C's are all thing it's another
stair with okay well then let's go in
the gate everyone figure hop in
so you are so you are you are walking
carefully pushing your way up not just
things through that through the stairs
you can stand they will flow through but
it has it's very it's very careful
particular work climbing these stairs is
that like really viscous yes okay yes
yes and you can you can see that at the
top the path is actually closed you can
see that you can see that there is
almost stone like you would select you
would brick up or stone up a door you
can see that it's that it's closed at
the very end but you can see that a
small portal at the top you can see that
there is a way to look through let's go
look through there a paper bird was
right yes yeah we got to go go up if I
have again getting it far away from the
gate as we can yeah so you can see and
you can you can feel the place shifting
as you're going up these stairs and so
through that portal you can see earth
piling up against the islands no oh no
oh and you can see that acid has now
begun to fill up and it's now
going to rise up into this passage I
actual nightmare okay can we bust
through the Scimitar to bus to the
stones try absolutely kind over we're
very good time I can't turn in anything
today ah ah to be on a half-wit I
anyways yeah well I'm resigned to my
fate I jump in you know what know where
I throw Chris person and I jump in
behind right and I go oh I'm [ __ ] out
um you know I said do we see anything to
that so we take it worth piling in does
it seem like if it busts through the
stone that we're even gonna be able to
get out like well you'll have you'll
have it you'll have a different you'll
have a different challenge okay that is
better than the current challenge okay
if you have no I have negative one
strength so I got i got nothing i got
alright like uh throw you off the
signing channeling the acid but also
sorry I know nerd I'm gonna get out to
crush make a heavy swing at this dog
okay well you got smite and all your
fists what though I love loving the
sword I'm gonna try to cross I might my
ass through the wall who so uh five
eight is what am i sorry if I type to
swing a hat hit though I guess there's I
don't it's in there go ahead and roll
again
I'm just keep rolling not forever before
yeah okay you are now how you are now
it's nice what I mean
I mean you can't dodge right it's an Taj
it's true but listen there are there are
rules to this stuff okay so you are and
it doesn't honestly it doesn't hurt the
dramatic arc for you to be slamming your
sword against this a couple times it's
here it's a lesson
it wasn't eight yeah yeah keep going
yeah oh my god no no we're good go get
it so it did a gasps oh you are so hot
over here I so you basically you use you
shrug drifts off and he slips down a
couple steps yeah and then you see
Denard Blitzen at the top of this
passage
just with all of his draconic might just
slamming toothbrush against this rock
and then the third and final hit it
connects clean and then you can feel the
shock wave off of this thunderous smite
and you lose a couple steps okay in it
I mean you you're kicking yourself up
against this rising wave of acid
these rocks are shattered and they start
to fall past you
along with earth and rubble pushing down
so right now you're right now you are
essentially buried you need to find a
way through can I do any kind of decks
to dodge around and jump on top to be to
be safe
yeah yeah you can be if you can be as
safe as you can but the reality is that
you're still interred okay so we can't
be interred I poop okay so we got a dig
mentality still coming any farce friends
come in like moles to dig if we don't
turn on I cannot turn into an animal nor
can I come I had the mold in my mind so
what you got
save me groundhogs Oh bugs
it's the party what were the check we'll
just why's that we deserve to die okay
hug yeah yeah it's like weird yeah what
kind so can someone snap him out of this
yeah this is not a fourth player would
help good okay well I'll be the force
clear I jump off of your back and I just
I just started whaling on you because I
I have not officially grandma man see
but I've had some difficult children in
my life and I should have come up and
I'm like wake up right no please me nude
us dig us hell and I I am clearly awake
like I'm not I'm just that annoying yeah
that's the abuse again alright one point
of what if I want her um I'm trying to
figure out a way that we could that we
could get out but it's a there's an
important moment for cuts risk
interrogate I'm also going to intimidate
you
so I'm going to date you this is Mike
our chair yeah yeah we're doing a real
you borrow you can't borrow I was going
to say the reason why it's an important
moment for me is because I'm I know I'm
too weak to survive the answers that
await me I also know that that this God
is not the one I wanted but it could
lead me to somewhere something closer
God you deserve it but I also know that
if I act to help us leave that that is
essentially me telling this this god of
teeth that I reject it or and I can no
longer pretend that I'm in its service
yes or is it you proving to the god of
teeth that you're strong enough to
survive this trial that he's putting you
through right now oh I know better than
that that's very good but I know that
it's not your son
well let's see if you continue let's see
if you can convince me of that
I'm intimidate the [ __ ] out of you okay
your any will see that's actual one one
you talk to yourself into siding with
Hamid yeah you're like actually it's
alright your [ __ ] sounds pretty cool
yeah I reject my face it's like you guys
physically work yeah so it didn't one is
oh is it if it on dinar blitzen again I
got I have insight I'm like I already
know why it's dirt
this is choice to a three-word
everybody's all in hand yeah to honest
with the end all right okay see if we
can you can try to persuade him yeah do
i how many of my how many of my
abilities am I going to use all Thurston
and I take a nap Becker's it's already K
material yeah no I know no it's it's
it's it is now halfway up these stairs
yeah just use all your skill do I know
do I get the sense that like do I know
how much dirt is beyond you can get so
you don't know how much of that rumbling
you don't know how much shift has been
there and you know and you can't gauge
it past that okay all I know is that
dirt is now pouring yeah okay I'm just
trying to figure out if something that I
could cast what if I could blow a hole
out yeah just experimentation sorry we
got to displace the dirt - yeah
experiment you can take land I get a
dick Terry safe from you
oh yeah you slipped down yeah and are up
to your waist in acid come on yeah for
can I send my horse off to chart if
absolutely okay I'll do that absolutely
okay what do I need to roll for that but
to put your core staff down you
accidentally push it uh no um yes it's
this this is slavering now yes I'm
miserable I'm looking like I'm
incredibly late I don't want to do this
all right
first lady I'm protecting the stars off
my clothes and I and I and I throw it up
into the end of the dirt pointing down
whatever is the first yeah yeah exactly
that so give me 3d for texture inside
and you walk dirt and for an organism we
not keep swinging on this just keep
shopping at it yeah I know I
so that's Gumby I can smite one more
time then that's going to be eight eight
yeah yeah so again you throw the seat
out it pauses in midair three separate
red arcs emerge from it strike the dirt
and then once they've all collected you
can see a hole yeah nothing through it
you can see a few stars so you feel a
lot better I do how do you want to start
yeah yeah yeah but so [ __ ] up somehow
everything's upside down yeah [ __ ]
create a constellation just hit back
same just kind of people it's a puffy
nightmare people got socks on their feet
through it so what's what's this uh I
didn't it's right how big is the hole
let's go it's smallish is it small
enough for a little hassling center you
can you can try to burrow through here
sheriff ER oh yeah yeah
alright go there will be a total carcass
perfectly yes yeah okay
oh yeah I got decks all day 15 yep
so you're you're able to sort of do you
can project your way through just to
wriggle out and now
by the time exact told and that now is
now it is it is wide enough for anyone
but dinar to get through all right good
are we are we all wait are we what's
that
there's there an order to this yeah I
look at you when I go you out yeah yeah
yeah no no I'm not like he would not
want to go last or anything like are
there turns here no no it's just
whatever not like that this is literally
like a whole bigger this is crying no
well yeah either why I'm either one of
them can get through I just I miss
t-step focus right through I don't hold
yeah and I was in yes because I have a
whole time and I rigged it out of crazy
and I throw a rope down to you okay nice
I can't fit through the whole overhang
we're gonna dig all right yeah well can
I take my sword
you bite it it's like a can I do a smite
in a thrusting like like I hit anything
you like yeah you can still do it sham
the Sun board a hunger wave right and
went on to render smite you divine smite
yeah so he's awesome yeah so just try to
like poke it into the hole and then
blast it go fry directview so I do yeah
so should I tell you roll damage yeah
I'm fine with this because even the
minimum damage of that and they look
back to d8 exam and then to d6 for those
no no idea for that to get there is good
and so your so get out you you you
missed the step through you throw your
ropes through and then wet earth just
erupts and knocks you back a pipe
cleaner now with the Soviet Emily
exactly so then do you can get you
exactly does he just was the only one
gets nothing
yeah I mean you you you're out you're
out already first like you're your final
gal yeah are you still in there with me
well the holes big enough now now yeah
but it's there is plenty of passage but
we come through like transom yeah yeah
hey yeah so worried guys 0 damage that
whole time come on and I'm like all
crusty from the Berkeley is good
actually
you think Maura thanks again Chris Chris
that's a tryst rib
you saved today yeah it is unlike
yeah yeah all right so we all come out
and then you do come up I'm liking my
bend over and I go I'm getting too old
for this
and I want to look at Krishna I want to
say I want to get back to the cart yes
but I'll write equation for what
happened yeah we're gonna have a long
talk when you get home right we're gonna
do your grams of intervention
yeah it's intervention yes it's the same
as anything thing so you guys pile back
into your cart
I assume this is the mostly quiet return
trip but if I'm if I'm wrong I'm going
to map us back mm-hmm I want to know
exactly where this thing was yeah
exactly so so absolutely go ahead make
that note let me get another history all
right
oh we know about guarded plan exactly
yes it's like a rock but small and when
it very small I mean um
technically I always have my bearings in
unfamiliar territory salute yeah yeah in
a pitch I could be like sniff us back
yeah okay yeah between you and me we'll
figure I know the old hole anywhere map
exactly kind of okay why don't you have
me do a history check not it's your job
your history - exactly it's how we're is
how we're doing it specifically for you
and your background that's why you know
what you know and then you don't know
now you're not you know Wow okay yeah oh
yeah here so you are you're on your way
back much much easier I go - yeah
exactly I don't know smelling on those
occasions you know you you have you were
out of the spoon care so as that work as
the Sun as the Sun rises it's much
easier to navigate your way through
these old overgrown roads you're able to
find your way back to the long road and
get north the dune Gideon was not a
great distance south you are able to
roll back in to red larch where the
destron Valley branch of the acquisition
incorporated franchise escort is is
centered at the drawn and quartered well
we have a long thoughtful look at
welfare yeah exactly
those were so much simpler yes so you
look so you look over left you can see
well versed wagons you can see his is
son dutifully trying to maintain the
business you know that in one of those
wagon holes he has in the back that
well-versed snooze in a way curled
around a hammer exactly that he called
Rosie baby Rossum is written on it and
then you look with Lee and then as you
look right you see four carts and this
is not a this is not a I've tried my
best to establish like what tier of town
red larch is you see four separate carts
at the drawn and quarter and they are
you recognize them instantly this is
these are these these are very similar
to the cart that brought you here but
these are these are not generic carts
this is Dragonborn royalty but not of
your clam so this is this is their
there's another obviously Gennari
or generis in the eastern ridge of the
sword mountain scala another Dragonborn
enclave farther to the north more
platinum caste generally speaking in
their upper echelon you can see that
there are four such carts out front of
the drowning courtier
that's not good probably another thing
oh this day am i right everyone as I
said I turned around like you found the
egg I'd say those are like more Goods
and I say yeah probably yeah
all right I'm assuming okay the way
today's been going you're not you're not
worried about it I'm very worried about
it okay just second you're hard to read
sometimes yeah it's a facade it's a gem
yet it's the face it's how I it's the
fake facade yeah yeah I don't want to
care about anything too much you know
should we go in yeah all right after you
all right kick in the door hey where's
my little eggy baby when the door opens
you see Royal Guards they're the highest
echelon Talent every ring every plate of
their armor immaculate and you see an
infuriated prophetess drawn currently
yelling at a what can only be called a
princess but as you're aware you know
you you have the human kingdoms and they
have a certain idea of a princess your
idea of a princess is a 100%
battle-hardened poet badass yeah
this is this is the absolute upper
echelon of Dragonborn society and as you
come in she she turns and you can see
that platinum cast to the scales and she
says I wondered what I would say when I
saw the person responsible for this
I have nothing responsible for
totally rescuing and takes work okay
yeah I'm not sure I follow also high by
the way in are hurt her oil dry oil her
retinue as soon as the hand comes out
weapons are drawn mmm
Justin archers like an official title to
bust out Prince of risk in our clan yeah
yeah okay like this is entirely not the
way so yeah so she's dating Prince dinar
I hear Prince and I'm just like kid
laughs yeah Sam she left up a Gennari
Prince is a contradiction in terms
as you are well aware but I'm not know
what I'm she really takes a lot of soul
about him 11 nope nope nope nope nope
she says my agents informed me that a
dragon born of a lesser clan had come
across my egg my egg what do you think
what do you think typically happens
under these circumstances I how do your
own by this I've saved your Eddie for
starters hold on
you're my clan better than your clan
second I saved your egg and I've been
taking great care of it have you taken
better care of it been a goblin yeah I
think so someone who got a stolen yeah
yeah yeah that's a good one I walk in
between cars I approach I'm still ready
to shovel from Tolerance every time you
come in here you're Kennedy ID and the
swords I'm assuming like a new person to
train them on yeah and I say to this
princess this
this is a good man he Dragonborn way
better than a man sir actually a servant
this is a Dragonborn but man he took
care of an egg which you lost an egg
which was stolen you forget yourself
drow hey I don't really like where this
is going at all
I agree with what's going on here you
have come to our base of operations for
soft fur sauce
listen I'm not going to get in a custody
battle over whose egg is whose eggs but
you don't have any right to come in here
making demands are you what what are you
are you queen of the drowning courtier
no listen listen I think we all just
need to take a step back Wallace I'm
really pissed off
Bryant rough day yeah she's just like
bringing like you know drought like
racial stuff into it well I was like no
no no no no that's not how we're gonna
play today
anyway I can leave right into it I'm
like I get it we're better than them and
I get that that all true apparently she
you're doing this and then while you're
doing that and she is not she's not
absorbing like you're you're doing the
whole thing like you're having your
great moment and she can't hear it
she can't hear it at all she has the egg
now in a royal case with her and she
walks to the door and she turns to you
and she says
I did wonder what I would say now I know
bang I wondered at what sort of creature
would be responsible for something like
this and I don't think that you have the
intellect to pull this off I think that
you have been manipulated by powers
beyond yourself and I pity you
that's the weirdest thank you I think
I've ever heard in my life it's lady
she's jesting would have been better as
an omelet and thought it was going to be
before I found 80 turns and she walks to
the door and you can see on the you can
see as she gets to the door and opens it
she goes like this ah that's the end
what gets me is avail of this week's
adventure positions incorporated on TV
what a pleasure
shadow council please hang around we are
going to have some good time now we need
to have a [ __ ] thought we had good
table talk section of the show or take
advantage of the restroom facilities
will return refreshed and winning out
for a bit
so here
you