cementec enemy but past addresses the
fastest whether you were to make it past
a second and that depends
play a brash and reckless to choose a
course in solution you saw was prudent
in any step of her poker to don't become
the putrid it's that well said I'm
Kristen win no Steve but don't you do
these systemic bedroom marks up to the
top of the peak of beneath this meanie
they come like sharks to win while I
swim in that learning goal by Carl Barks
through its suspension national parks
through it I'll send them all in a
natural box the post time most of the
parks included they do Brett for a
cleric confessor this is a record and
like to continue professor to speak in
my official advise sign on the dotted
line English of the twice I am Tycho
Brahe excommunicated tax I am also a
minister's heroin drunk CEO attack
positions incorporated the day I'm
Garrett for K working and I am running
the game dungeon dragons for my friend
should I write Dragonborn narcissist
dinar Blitzen very nice I have stayed a
meatus Balcon rolling through with
walnut dog grass for 20 more money off
on the nose to my left we have Kate
Welch as Rosie bee sting or not I grab
his grandma and we also have a [ __ ]
interloper here my left none you you
might have recalled from earlier
episodes that my game was invaded and a
few consistently via text message by
none other than Patrick Rothfuss and so
unsatisfied to pull the strings from
afar he has now penetrated my inner
sanctum which is not a euphemism believe
it or not but he is here to join us as a
character who will be revealed shortly
um we also have my friend Chris Stroud
as Chris trout
emerging from a mist shroud
oh that rhyme right shut up what now you
want to stop you you may or may not
recall the horrors that were visited
upon you very recently and it could be
that we have new viewers who are just
joining us for the first time so let me
set the scene if you will you had going
to say you of course I mean the c-team
the newest franchise of acquisitions
incorporated with an exclusive license
to contracts in the desert valley
exclusive you had taken a job called the
raids must cease and you were able to
bring those raids to a close by
defeating what appeared to be a pirate
gang of goblins and after managing them
and re robbing all of the things that
they had previously robbed and then also
for a period of time becoming a kind of
cart pirate yourselves and having
emerged with an incredible cart cobbled
together from bizarre chunks the best
option in these indeed you are now
rolling back toward the town of West
bridge where as you may recall on you
had taken a job from one hair of and our
dragon the proprietor of the harvest
game who has a novel aesthetic at best
you call it asks related as adjacent
you'd be right yeah I mean that you have
it on the Astra's nobody wreckage in
astral fridge very smooth very nice the
way out there I have an astral pun but
I'm gonna leverage later oh good um I
had it I've had it for a couple weeks
now I think you to it and you [ __ ] me
on this oh I thought you'd get another
one
something like you looks like right now
yeah we're over sorry because it this is
how it goes you are rolling into town
just as people are putting together the
last bits of business in the open
markets you can see people taking crates
of chickens very seriously at this hour
you are rolling in via the east exit of
the town and right by the small cart
Shack saying that has been since
dismantled where you purchased three
health potions for a mere 20 gold
incredible savings for 20 gold yeah
that's the stream is that the type of
stream we're operating here you tell me
listen I'm I'm 100% down um but I'm cool
I'm with a kid Nina listen Josh are you
down with nugs
so as you're rolling in you roll into
this the central bustle where you know
the harvest in 2b and there have been
changes even just in the last couple
days since you've been out since you've
been gone
we all know something I'm sorry I know
the holiday I had really happening and I
really I'm in a lot of pain so up
kitty-corner across this these crowds
and the movement of people and currency
you can see that a new venue a new Inn
has established itself quick in the last
two days in the last two day and the
main thing the out front are two statues
fix fundamentally there is a dick aspect
to these statues and in fact right in
front of the door you can see that
streams from these peeing statues cross
over in front of the doorway you looking
at it you're not sure if it would be
possible to get into this place without
getting peed on like it would be a like
a mission impossible type situation like
with the beams yeah like you think that
you would have happened
no you would think this is like some
Ocean's eleven like you would need a
team yeah
to manage this this flow basically and
you can see the sign above that says
Grand Opening clefts clefts become
possessive over all right great
and yeah in a lost sort of ruling listen
I'm a writer to tie process I have a
point I've got a picture with your word
the Gainey's penis cookies your rating
no it's just regular it's subsurface
scattering you can take them listening
no hmm so sort of moving around I'm
video favorite yeah the Kings edges are
like a national symbol in like Belgium
so like that didn't be sure yeah yeah
but they're clearly not Elgin no I'm
picturing like the Bellagio but also
like Austin Powers yeah yeah yeah pretty
more difference - yeah exactly always
are no good and a low body no no imagine
it's a situation where it's like imagine
that you could take the dick and then
expand while retaining the ratio yeah
yeah don't dream yeah dream every night
no but you can you can see a figure who
is moving towards the harvest in and
then but after he's taken a couple steps
he turns back around towards clefts
clefts and takes a few steps and then
sort of reaches out for the statues and
then puts his hand down
and look back over to harvestin and
begins walking in that direction
you wrecked from the from the carriage
you recognize this somewhat flighty I
mean you you have had challenges with
this character in the past this is a
person who has not really taken advice
has not absorbed your maternal waves and
always has a new idea about how to find
success and it really is a a couple
weeks here a couple months there you
know that he was into magic for a little
while I just wanted him to be happy for
the first 50 years of his life but at
some point you get tired of it you get
exhausted yeah you're not listen
grandmother you're not telling me
anything that I don't know you see your
son de ribas who is apparently being
torn apart by the act of choosing an inn
I am utterly unsurprised I'm only
surprised to see him in this town not
that he is having trouble with this most
mundane of choices listen listen
apartments like bus dicks but when I was
high yeah exactly
how do you can choose exactly I mean you
think there's every possibility he could
be trampled by a cart yeah in the near
term I'm going to turn to everyone and
go I'm really sorry about everything
that's right and then bark out rebus be
stinger the top of my lungs well good
the is I should I do the brief
description you all listen ah sir we are
playing Dungeons and Dragons this is a
game we play together this is a sort of
a large figure
broad shoulder half-orc power but I also
have linked half happen
1/2 1/4 half whirling yeah there's
another of that works it's like a when
you see them like the wiener dogs that
are also like poor German Shepherd
you're like what they did what did it
yeah I see the end result how did we get
their work out top tiny legs party in
the back
presumably sorry all the time so he's um
you know he's big like work big um he's
got a sort of a robe but it's also kind
of leather and it's kind of studded it
kind of looks like a trench coat halfway
between ravenclaw and like really
disenfranchised high school emo teens
you're the same yeah and they got to
reload what temperature would you say
the topic is cold is it a cold topic
he'll work you guys he's got hair that's
dark but it's obviously then dyed Raven
wing black and there's kind of some
bangs hanging down a little bit in front
of his eye Danny bang yeah he's carrying
a big what is could not be mistaken for
anything other than a wizard staff
really tall wizard staff and uh but you
know big big half work and kind of kind
of walking with the slouch yeah the
hunch
how old is your this glad mama confirm
now if you don't remember I have three
hundred and two children how old are you
um uh between us or like a he looks he
looks older older than you could justify
that haircut oh yeah yeah sure yeah boy
he does not have this haircut um yeah
like Trent Reznor kind of
so yeah as soon as he hears that he kind
of he hunches over further further
he's got the permanent slouch and was
like like armadillo away thanks for the
cameo I'm doing here what are you doing
here you're supposed to be at school the
school we're paying for what are you
doing in West Ridge I'm studying abroad
mom yeah I thought you're studying
abroad don't that you were bad at I know
[Laughter]
you don't know anything about what I do
because you don't do anything either my
companion
don't embarrass me friends are your
friends - fine yes these are my work
associate we're trying to get some
things done just don't that lot more
tired eating any of these people not yet
not any of us I'm gonna grab well er are
you - going out yeah talking about a car
dad hey Ida daddy called down and there
is there is still a part of me that has
some affection for you very small but I
am genuinely true what are you doing in
Westbridge how did we end up here at the
same time they have programs word go out
and you study aha really experience
would really be good out here
yeah like studying he just stays a long
time my castilla this what a drug things
that you've told me about this drug this
drug is it drugs again through this it's
not drugs mom God I'm not to [ __ ] food
right not gonna hang out yeah
oh oh oh all right now doing here
I'm on a quest Noreen I had you were not
planned community we set you up there
you were supposed to be super happy
there yeah I was super happy there and I
learned a lot and we can talk about that
another time
I wanna you're about that sort of on the
throne we were out for two days and we
got like four quests done so we're
turning one in all right is that fine
with you come on let's just go have some
food
have you eaten many things no still a
beautiful all right we'll come on come
on
right so uh you and it's a good thing
you were able to coax him like livestock
in terms of his size and just presence
you're able to coax him over toward the
harvest in you can see some shapes
through the window that you know to be
buds I mean at this point right yeah
you're able to do your your eyes on here
is this what you do if that were the
door and joint insufficient you rolled a
cart straight up alongside welder tosses
the door open the back moves around to
the front of the cart and starts to busy
himself polishing something and he looks
up at you in a terrified way sick what
are we we haven't to define the
relationship talk right now
do we have a relationship no well
they're caught stealing no sir no DTR
for me I'm for my son okay Jesus his
eyes are getting like he's like don't
worry about it yeah I'll tell you when
you're older it's nothing like that and
then I walk over and I put my hands on
her face and I cast cure wounds cuz
you're still hurt I give you life how
many how many a wound to heal how many
points is wondering you get a da 1 da
pleasure is mother
bill casting ability to see it as a
populist movie they are about the rest
but I just not just you have to be safe
let's agree to therapy that's why I
think so one D April 5 and then I found
that man did you yeah that's right NAR
no all right so why every good and throw
hey down there
hey nice up to 11 loving it okay so II I
don't know you
q is this dragon guy oh this guy he's a
friend I call my friend yeah not that
kind of fun what do you know I might
have an extract you yeah yeah if we
verified acid we don't know what
happened here you know what I mean or
not happen my god I know are pregnant I
had a beautiful baby
look at this event how work that's how
Dragonborns work um yeah let's let's
head inside I'll explain everything once
we are sitting it up a meal exactly as
your cart pulls up alongside as you're
getting yourself together to re-enter
the harvest in you can see a curious
clever looking fellow bald of head flax
silky robes looking out from behind
streams of urine over at the over at
clefts clefts it seems to take notice of
the party and then re-enters the
establishment okay
I don't know if it's pragma or not some
fragments yes
prime mr. Franklin all right so here is
the situation so real quick before we go
any farther I want to make sure that you
guys understand the cool stuff that you
can do when the shadow council in the
channel gets you good now we know about
advantage draconic entitlement was used
to great effect last time there was a
very pronounced WWE motif which of
course I endorsed hundred percent the
Neurosci bringing a status allow him to
intimidate those and establish your
place in the pecking order
it's awesome grama Massey allows you to
disappear in plain sight and
people's sympathies the tentacular
spectacular it is a tendril of maddening
chaos stuff which you then attempt to
control it's not guaranteed forest
friends has been used to profound effect
multiple times murdering countless
creature yeah
just shunting them brightly and to cross
of various kinds guy you feeding the foe
functionally John but it's been used in
all kinds of cool story moments so far I
expect more of that we want to push
through our cool stuff push through our
goodies this week if we can so make note
of those numbers put them to work in
your roles you enter the harvest in you
haven't seen the artwork seems to be
more or less what you saw last time
there are a few open booths and you see
the proprietor hair of and our dragon
still standing by the empty Dyess that
currently holds nothing but clearly in
his mind the negative space is a
standing tall did any of us bring the
soprano inside with us absolutely I did
excellent no no no no that is one person
could not tell is huge okay so what we
having it oh absolutely we did yeah I am
I care I am carrying it hey got my back
a statue in front yeah yeah just well
how I like it
yeah I'm in heaven yeah what does a ton
in this you can get you'll need to head
back out grab the okay alright tree
better can you go help so humbly rain
but they're going right yeah honestly
you're having a half work probably
helped a lot
oh yeah yeah no I go oh I thought a 30
feet of movement to talk anything about
thank you guys humper you open the back
of the cart and as you as you try to
figure out which is mechanically how to
get this mat
heavy stone out as far as you can tell
from nowhere this black-robed figure
emerges from the other side of the cart
like a street magician sort of maneuver
yes exactly
the neck is sort of serpentine right any
trouble hello in exactly open oh he says
I may have a matter to discuss with you
before this statue crosses the threshold
I don't see why I would be the case are
you the artist from some zone on this
robe emerges a card and upon this card
it says pragma cleft of clefts clefts
incredible works profound topics hmm not
an artist
the did this but certainly other works
you might call me a patron of the Arts I
have needs in the visual space
I have wealth to get these to take these
concepts as they are from the ether and
form them into a solidity if you will a
good place to be I think we may have
much to discuss
hmm Miyabi said which I'm supposed to
take this dance should I take this in
now yeah we got a quest to complete here
but yeah we could certainly have this
conversation once we've returned it
really angry if you like general oh well
you Michigan's like super angry though
egg to bed don't be fussy in the morning
if you take this statue in to the
harvest in
then Hera van der dragon will have it
and that is not to my preference I'm
strange
hello I hear about your property yeah
yeah paid for it
how are you Kevin k2 thing yeah that's
true
well BC immersion is very confused but
not actually that I kind of I I go and
like he's not getting it is he super not
getting it I go and he's there
yeah either to struggling or now lifted
right yeah go to it and so I say to you
you want this I like I'll thieves can't
him like and I'll say so how much are
you looking to pony up for this thing
but I'll say isn't this a nice but looks
like this is some quality a selectman
ship here but the thieves can't
underneath I'm saying exactly picking up
any of that absolutely he responds but
he does so with the left eyebrow up and
so you know that that inverts the second
half of each frame quarter what he is
able to communicate with you is that he
is willing to offer up statuary of his
own from his private collection in
addition to lodging anytime the party is
on the long road at clefts class and he
assures you that it is it is better than
those who typically speak to thieves in
can expect but what this sounds like of
course is that the McRib is back I hear
that and go alright I don't follow any
of it it's not this here is actually
belongs to the proprietor of the
harvestin and so we have business to
conclude so if we can take care of that
I don't see how the two are related I'm
not you know what I'm McRib
yes I'm friend oh okay I'll be are we
were
back id's guy I'm gonna go after my mom
sometimes just you know she gets so
angry sometimes I'll go in yeah you
don't know just start you fruits will
because know somebody I'm you live in a
just about it night well-crafted it's
different
it's nice would you like to roll in our
camp yeah sure how nice my god yeah I
really like rallies my cell my ideal but
we want you to learn much about an IV
don't forget we're magic you know
remember use your cool rules right now
oh yeah well what have you determined
complete entire situation to his mother
I am intrigued it does sound like a
pretty good deal we have got not gotten
an offer from this hair Evander Dragon
fellow
for what he wants for the soprano so
maybe it's time to ask him before we
bring the soprano in let's see what our
reward from heroin would be sure and
let's make the better trade his family
is it know we're like raiding carts and
now we're filling people singing bar
what is a school the only good one
clearly love it
perfect that's why we're in this write
your essay yeah willing to reward yeah
but in say how much okay would have
written it down in my little hand you've
got legal ownership over more doesn't
Commission did properly it's very
important alright well let's talk about
your into the IOC yeah alright yeah
let's
Harrigan paint outside lay next to his
empty days yeah yeah yeah yeah you can
you can slick with tears you can tell
that they're raised raised bits of the
wood where tears have stood long okay um
hey so we what we happen to have that we
know the location of the soprano it's
very close by he reaches around he puts
his hands on your shoulders
please don't touch me I appreciate you
very much however me okay we have to
know before we venture out into the
danger that we know exist what is the
reward that we can expect from returning
your soprano to you polished
unharmed without a scratch the reward
that you can expect for returning
rightful property to me right you go out
on a limb for you we expect to be
compensated for that kind of thing well
you want you promise the reward you
understand for did we mention a reward
before but not quantitative I'm the
expression on my face is one of I'm
sorry about this callous it's not out of
the bounds of reason but it seems like
yeah daddy like oh I like the statue I
don't want the other guy yeah exactly
being you are the best I want to give
back then yeah okay he says there are
pieces that are not on display one piece
in particular that reflects a storied
conquest that I would be willing to
offer up as well and of course he would
have the use of the in oh yeah this is
the visit whenever we would like that
for that correct it could start as soon
as tonight where is the soprano this
isn't our base of operations yeah well
it became a perfectly good cart smack
smack yes you got a card in it I know
all right
yeah real estate let me ask you this
what do you want to look at bunch of
piss well I'm not trying to build a
museum I'm not kind of name but I'm not
saying I what how about do you want okay
yeah you're going yes yes and I academia
I I really look at I don't particularly
care and it does seem like this guy sent
us on the quest he's got a collection he
seems very very sad if he's offering us
the same thing and I'm just going to say
let's return it to its rightful owner
yeah I speak aside to that both of yous
like this is one of the first
experiences I had with with a art
outside of the Underdark that kind of
resonated with me like I began to
understand and now we're treating this
like some sort of a business transaction
yeah acquiring appear in the business of
business you understand there's no like
grandma saying
well oh I see we're going what are we
going to report back and these asses to
the Home Office act and you want to come
back with something back with the best
possible price understand I'm in favor
of giving it to heroin if you guys are
I'm particularly seeing advantages yeah
I betrayed in my mind it's his yeah it
is to give back I don't even know it's
like anybody could have approached us
and then the person out there push this
and he was raising his eyebrows lot and
I don't know if that's like Oh what if
he has just like a super-good in like
what if it's like look we know you go
check on it
yeah I know to the other guys we go I
don't need that ironic ton of likes
contrary yes Travis how the hell I just
kind of walk up today I I'm like like
juice on my mama Donna yes but this is
the guy you spoke to at the you look the
guys want a Bernard Tomic left yeah no
wonder no so we charge yes absolutely
crying Manny was it dangerous Oh quite
dangerous
I don't know I can hear that session was
a died she said Henry hell she's from
the Greenway yeah yeah yeah that mystery
his point I just I see my mom in a year
and I come back and she's all blends you
sent her out to find the but the thing
but master bee stinger he treated young
one uh this was a quest we were already
sent on we happen to be able to retrieve
something for this gentleman it wasn't
actually related it was just fortuitous
I love to tryst
drought dad voice is that now a small
one yeah I and if it helps any or your
mother
comported herself very well of course
but that is really needed so like I hold
up my jar of eyeball look what I got
yeah she got bad yeah guess he says he
says young man
we are all dust these asses will ya
he sweeps his hand around I'm just
saying they're like my mom don't look so
good and that doesn't seem really cool
to me and it seems like if she got hurt
bringing anything back then you do more
than say like hey you can sleep in my
room that make some tacky [ __ ] yeah
brought it back we got some influence I
wish I said that she goes where it is
where is it
I live through business I was just
saying that nearby tree bit look at me
don't look Samantha why don't you have
anyone in your mind who's what I'm
elderly folk song or not are she
commissioned them with us to retreat I'm
fine with that you say Commission but I
don't see this guy like giving you any
money here this is all about hunting the
percentage yes we've got to get the
extra June
I completely understand but you don't
have influence over we don't have this
once over people like these two people
have influence over people here so if
you want to get more money maybe like
all right I can start to disseminate I
try to milk them yeah yeah no I don't
want to persuade a lot of intimidation
though Mateusz you got all right we're
not persuading party oh no I literally
huh yeah do you ever say I go what I
have in two medium and it's like I
wondered if you were at three two points
are you like all like Claude offers yeah
I got room I got no I face in front of
you I mean I feel weird yeah but you
were like sometimes screwed up like
we've covered in acid what happened ah
goblin spend a whole bunch and um I
think I was most you guys robbed
yeah God I got Cod you I saw your
clothes are all cut up and you have
evidence of like God has been physical
and so I look at that guy and I look at
my tiny elderly mother and I look and I
just missing
the edge of her bloody garment and I
look at him like a seven-foot-tall
half-orc would would who's just seeing
that his mother has been injured letting
her [ __ ] Aaron I got the advantage on
ya mm he says is that your cart out
front
I say yeah I'm also standing by the cart
like a protecting it FEMA dude engine
are we gonna get ya
you have with the dancer oh my don't I
hold Karen storms to the front of the
harvest in and draws the door back guide
wings back hits against the wall bounces
most of the way it closed again and
turns and is toe-to-toe with pragma
cleft throwing it out first one you see
mammoth and say okay he wanted to pay
for that by the way he has money for
that stir the pot a little bit yeah yeah
entreated Walsh said I like the idea a
you as a as a dragon born of the world
know what's probably gone down in there
feeling he's trying to pass to give it
yeah yeah get him by Regina call each
other through the streets yeah Aaron
reaches over and tries to get a palm
around the back of the head uh but
there's no hair there's zero hair yeah
pragma cleft brings the knee up into the
groin whoa these two old men are going
at it in the middle of the street when
curve and our dragon sees the statue in
the back of the cart
he reaches in he jumps in you can see
his legs kicking out of the back of the
card that legions trying desperately to
pull it pulls it and it falls onto him
Oh God
he does not move does it fall into a boy
I know part of him got skull yes he did
I don't know our weapon sit there I was
just got an egg and I'm just like this
is why we're better than them
it's just kind of a sight but they're
just scrappy talking are you kidding -
we're the best no no no I'm right over
my pool no I'm right next to I donno and
I think yeah you squished like a bug not
like a bug but there does appear to be
some involuntary movement in his left
leg I'm a private left is moving back
silkily in a liquid way much of urine
back through exactly indeed lexing
you're in - he prizes
you got a Mendham slipping back through
the crowd and then back through and
getting it from both sides from the
statues just drenched on his ball cred
but he doesn't break no he doesn't break
it all and he'd slithers back into class
clips all right I start happy with our
settings red berries I do okay and I can
perfect this guy is this guy really
screwed us
it's like mess up she's he's in a bad
spot I can put a spy but I'm good so far
he was able to that's really how we
wanted to go probably yeah he was able
to Jeff Hardy's death savor the 20 he
feels good but well not good in the
classic sense but but you've made a
great case I mean seeing that seeing
that marble ass calm down I mean that
must have been the apex of his fantasy
I'm out of healing I have I even took a
quick nap health potion oh no you also
have an I have a potion of your earlier
oh here now would you like to tell the
class
wow you came by this potion as to clear
your healing oh that's right I forgot
the classic is known we participated in
a separate yes separate D&amp;D game better
at Wizards of the coast the home of
dandy why does me and Rosie yep in
character yeah as BRE
yeah I'm somewhat a climb back were
their betrayal yes and we were permitted
as Chris Perkins insisted that we take
our winnings and bring them to this case
yep we were certain to do he said we're
cool yes that I guess I don't know
everything I have a very much Andheri
facing a middle game China Masamune Liam
and I get to a pat ball and Perkins gave
you superior healing all right no sir
meta game for a second every time
someone from the outside [ __ ] with this
game Jay takes a village angrily
supposed to done this guy isn't working
he's gonna explode it yes he's a brace
from tax so train to a gigantic frog
roll them bones we'll see what happens
you want to give you want to give him
the here's a question can you give a
potion to an unconscious for this has
long and uh yeah yeah there's a long
been a thing that has ml is ready for
now are you ready with the omen peanut
butter are you using the potion of extra
healing or are we using the potion of
healing that you got from those found
earlier oh my phone we know it works in
my health potion but that is like a true
chaotic thing that I would do and I'm
not sure what you have to eat I play
real you got to play it on the pocket
okay I'm a clear with no rules just
right well I'm a guy when you hear your
family and you're now staying stepping
away right well yeah yeah we're both
coming out with functions who's going to
get there first well I think yeah I'm
not really role really oh yeah yeah so
let's say this is a dexterity Oh
all right that's time do you mean go
find out 18 who is gonna be me man
yeah are you just clinging on to it yeah
you'd be I was 11 I just like like stiff
arm just
heisting leaky on some hey and yeah
that's where that's what you get out of
it hat some a yeah rosie be singer yeah
I don't anymore
so to help potions that we bought in
town before we set out on request I
believe that they are not traditional
health potions but I'm going to try it
on this gentleman anyway and so far as I
smell like LED shading yeah right what's
the worst could happen actually
something you put on a like a natural
medicine that hasn't been vetted by the
FDA it's like it's an alternative
healing mechanism do the healing potions
yeah it's homeopathic yeah we have two
possible options here one is that it
works great together is that we find out
what it does so the other is being
immoral murder your accomplice to murder
me that I produce as if from nowhere a
document and I hold it up to him
and I now we're not legally responsible
for anything that happens to you are you
so much and I take the quill I love a
kiss ang and I sign what could be his
name is just like a graphical yeah yeah
yeah
and then I put that away it really it is
but man yeah right magma flexes like
that's what even is name another guy man
and then you think that our individual
elevated appreciating that yeah hmm we
have my basket so you roll him over
yeah it's squash e'er maybe then you
would like yeah on the front own well
I'm trying to find his mouth
there ya go no you can find that okay I
find a hole and I pour it in alright I'd
have a bundle uncork it and the bottoms
up folks and just going on down in the
car you see you see the bone structure
hmm good warp and liquid ever see Rose
you see if you got home you see it you
see it fill out and become symmetrical
and then you see a metallic sheen creep
from the mouth and begin to cover the
entire body I want to do in our cat a
check like as you know [ __ ] gets weird
yeah yes with a little bit let's see it
oh man that's a great big ha 17 okay
yeah yeah this is he is apparently as a
result of this potion and you begin to
get very curious about its manufacture
so I get down I was already kind of like
checking them out I was worried about
him yeah yeah and I'm going to look at
that
it's very conscious is this going to be
like interesting interesting side effect
or it's like this will spread and then
he will calcify and turn into metal and
die so he appears to be coated in a
metal it would take you would need a
much better number to know what metal
but you can feel over his mouth that
he's still breathing okay
but he is completely encased in metal
okay also through that process I did
pick his pockets okay that's a difficult
I thought anything anything you didn't
see it mom I'm super good at this it's
about eight gold three copper which is
called ketosis childlike innocence it's
you know I'm super good at this no we
saw so there's a heavy heavy statue is
down rolled away yeah and there's also
apparently a statue of a man I was
reverence or statue
so we problem up and flick ERISA panel i
really light is allowed to go to sleep
guys really tired I will be able to the
am Gemini the thing that we could maybe
do okay and it's that we could join go
to class and because it's well known
that their adversaries blackmail him
into helping us because people will
probably think he did it and not a
walnut it was on grad yeah friend is
super smart good at this oh and 30
before 20 yet
anything all the factors go out the door
no but that is the same well I guess
that is something that we could I'm
invited you
I'm impressed well there was a crowd
right well I'm game and there's a few
more like a ministry yes well more money
in that potentially than than the rest
oh yeah I mean if we want to squeeze a
patron of the arts this is how you do it
what's going to ruin his whole feeling
it'll handle thank you scandal it just
founded a hotel that network you know
what I mean yes it's a new establishment
you mean you're usually in the red
before yeah exactly
I'm on board good enough I hear bad
effects we are bad people
he's what he's we're doing we're better
than likely grievous you can see the
feet from the soles you can see it shift
back to scuffed leather and then you see
that process reverse itself okay up the
legs how do I have so I always go
through the torso and then out around
the hands comes down comes up and then
as it as it that she sort of removes
itself from the head he sits up and
begins to breathe very very hard and
distressful swipe his arms out in front
of him just trying to determine if he
understands physical reality or if
there's something about it that maybe
has eluded him thus far friends friends
come down we've just saved you from the
brink of mortal peril what happened your
ass fell right on you
what's she real good Wow you betrayed me
no we were tempted to betray you you
taught me to the apperance yeah that one
did betray you
yes but you're good now because of our
quick work saving your life with our
life-saving potion if you were betrayed
by anyone it was your own zeal yeah your
hubris
she's like a bless you birth I came out
I came out of the inn
I what happened after I came out of
these not important
yeah you need an old man in the na J's I
just picked a statue up I'm like are we
gonna take this inside buddy or not a
lot of fries hey get this room you
Yammer and he says he says the world's
not ready
he said say yay said he's not ready he
was right before he gets out and sits
down and just waves the group in and
sort of teeters drunkenly to the front
of the harvestin bring bring that oh
yeah yeah oh yeah that's good yeah yeah
where's this going
he points over to the diet
I'm Scott on you along with my quarter
staff I throw it up on Aaron just take a
cap I've done and done mark that done
yet I'd quest complete this and I used
to walk the Betty kidding yes yes he's
play Suki is just placed his face
against the cold marble just holding it
sort of like I'm almost like a junior
high yellow danced back and forth that's
how it what got you the first time buddy
be careful with this we've only got so
many healing potion yeah that abscess it
face for blood thirst so it will be
having question is there a reason that
the fellow across the way from you
Fredrik left might have wanted to tempt
us into which we did not we rejected it
really okay career but he seems like he
wanted to soprano just so you couldn't
have it is that that's something that
sounds right to you yes
oh it's 4:20
I don't know yes that's good yeah this
is good soup honey do you have any jokes
that you would like to tell I'm honest
but I got nothing planta grass so that
it gets like if this leg really
indicates dresses they know there were
time for a upon the types nodes at the
iPhone for a week I think is there there
we go
this thing right there yeah I'm anyway
some about this later on say something
about seeds or stranger oh yeah oh my
dad goodbye gather his favorite strain
it's good Barry we're just going to move
forward three new person that he says oh
I constantly steal and destroy statues
that come into town for pragma quest oh
oh okay this is a thing that you to do i
well yes well yes performance it
happened it's happened a couple times a
couple so beautifully because he has he
ever stolen or destroyed any of your
statues would I know
those pragma cleft dabble in unnatural
arts yes I don't know if you've seen any
of the pieces
no no really like me at all anything Oh
what is enough he's what he's already
done constitutes an occult act in my
estimation dang it unnatural at best
bloom in our tena I help ya I'm like
what yeah yeah which is why I think
alone at the end it yeah he says we
bring from yeah yes because he he pulls
himself up on the base stands back up
snaps a couple times and people come out
and prepare a booth in the corner for
the party and he says the offer remains
room and board
anytime you're in Westbridge on the long
road and sandra and what forward a piece
from my private collection people that
love argos hey of course while he's
saying this balls in the back scribbling
and it produced a piece of paper and she
goes now this is what you city slickers
call a gentleman's agreement everything
you just said and then as a bottom just
a little signature and then it says one
piece of art and art is also infinity
goes just so that we're all even one is
all art i'm gonna try to get in the
senate is acceptable acceptable sure
wrench oh look at that one later on so
should i have the piece delivered to the
cart uh yeah definitely doesn't matter
what it is we should definitely ride
through town with it yeah of course
elephant yoga right look I got Ephrem
magazine from the collection sure yeah
they're a class if they're swapping you
know and stealing stuff from each other
we can be like look what we got for his
party women no there's not no there's a
money-making opportunity out here we got
it okay with that yeah we live in the
street game and they argue yeah just
back and forth
so the multi-course meal comes out stews
salads steaks
cart after cart comes out and you can
tell unit and while you're eating this
eating constitutes a short rest for this
morning by the way is functionally
speaking you spend you spend an hour
resting and not doing strenuous stuff
nothing more strenuous than talking
kicking it hanging out yeah that
constitutes a short rest now during a
short rest
Rosie beestings yeah you can expend
cattlemen your dice yeah an asteroid
level you have 3d eight worth of hit
dice you can roll each of those and add
your constitution modifier you can roll
as many as you like after I shot rescue
do not regain hit dice
this is basically a pool of personal
healing Oh that you can leverage
whenever you're doing a short rats
awesome
after a long rest you get you know it
has them rounded down I think is this
okay dancer concentration yeah exactly
so you can you can manage that yourself
all right if you'd like to yeah yeah
just because I know that you were low
for tandem okay I'm thinking that I'm
wait that's how you do it but but yeah
okay fish who pieces Apple contacted in
the prom
and you can you can see rumps know that
much you can you can see there's
something you conceded that Wilbur is
open to the cart for someone out the
window and they are putting in something
that has a cover over it slid into the
bag but the same dimensions as the
soprano their vows all right they're
about one fill the cart with like a big
ol pick at the exact volume is a block
of marble yeah yes we're not but what
happens where did they go oh man you're
going exactly I'm sick you can tell that
he says I say heroin is trying to get a
glimpse of this from each from every
angle so to still just walk to a new
part of the of his establishment and
then see it this time so each time he's
deriving some new pleasure from not just
this individual soprano but from the
configuration this year marble choir
he's assembled and whatever secret music
it has is isn't private for him I'm deep
in my cup at this point oh yeah there
are come over there are cups you're
gonna call it heroin over slightly this
is German here where's Wilfred see what
is it isn't he to the car
no why do you love a button so much I'm
just asking a question do you do you not
clean to a degree but this is this
- is this is this a fish eye I mean yeah
I think so
hey so what do you say so this is a
fetish right oh there's all those those
books that you used to have remember
those those were my art books mom oh
wait he says now come with me
gladly follow you anywhere exactly so he
takes you up the stairs and around so
that you can see the configuration from
a different angle at different
perspectives and from this height gazing
down at it it still looks like a bunch
of starvation Rosie's first down another
topic after a pucker goodness ah you're
not you don't get it okay
but being it's like it's like an AoE
almost like here's enthusiasm for this
project
yeah I'm pretty drunk yeah exactly and
so it's such a certain thing where you
can you kind of to kind of get it yeah
you kind of get it maybe it's maybe just
one of them isn't enough to understand
it yeah maybe it's the it maybe it's the
the universal nature of it yeah maybe to
see we've all got but you know oh it's
beautiful
you know what I mean I do I Rosa kind of
gets it but I say like I absolutely get
it this is really nice thank you for
shoes them up there kind of looks like
they're sharing that moment like two
explorers of the unknown like myself
it's really some stones like this was
the right thing to do Saint want to just
scare it off into the distance like
thankfully luckily pretty good Italy
yeah yeah look
and eluded but you like food but you got
that you basically have the egg oh yeah
it's not on the package right here
trying like some things rolling on yeah
yeah exactly so hungry but he he says
you know your rooms are your rooms are
down this hall behind us off of the
upper your hot behind the upper wing
okay behind us again okay
and then he trails his hand along the
railing and then down and greets more
guests to share his enthusiasms great
okay if it is about that time because I
think I out that times we met maybe an
alarm around our cart because I don't
know if fragments can be all that into
our shenanigans yes yes there's multiple
this multiple ways to to manage it
there's cart alarms yeah I obviously had
that um where everyone is going to stay
is important yeah do you have any useful
spells here entry bit I know that's
ideas more useful women alarm which I'm
gonna work it's called barn mom the
spell is called a barn you put the card
in the barn that's not what much before
I do alarm you do alarm on it and then
we're out all night is going to sleep on
it for what would be first watch for her
for hours oh so you'll wait in the cart
no on top a lot of the cars oh cool
beautiful night sky I'm not in this
palace of material reassuring father
they say if there's a room is anywhere
near the cart you know I think I can get
some distance from it but I kind of want
to steep in this environment you're the
form of of the beyond that I haven't yet
internalized absorb so for it so for
your part you're going to sleep up on
top of the cart the initial part of the
evening
put alarms on parmesan yes and then I'll
just keep watching up there and then if
it is basically if anything enters that
a zone you're identified yeah okay I'm
just you're identified you just you do
you want also hear it I mean if
something's on me
I'd like to know should I tell you or
should I have the alarm when you as well
hi I'm John one's on you you're being
stabbed you know whatever you think
it'll be mental alarm out here you'll
hear it you can hear it alright that's
funnier that way yes if I don't know
okay
Soviets out what the dragging orbiters
well cool alright all this forward to
myself four rooms upstairs yeah
somebody's going to sleep that with the
cart you can fill those out up there too
and the person how obviously well bird
is normally sleeps in the cart that's
you met him sleeping in a cart that's
on-brand for him and that is how that is
how it goes so everyone else as you said
in your cups right it's time to it's
time to lay out flat on grass how'd you
end up with your hit points did you
reveal all were you able to talk back
out yeah okay I will actually kind of
Shepherd her back to a room because
one's mom's had a couple June she'll be
up like [ __ ] all night and then
there'll be just one more and then
she'll be singing and then I do not she
needs her sleep she's been hurt and so I
kind of like heard her into her room I
do not appreciate being herded but I am
too drunk approach exactly it's fine
it's fine you you you are you're able to
appreciate this vast boy of yours this
way that's voice now big boy um is there
do I have an answer for my question okay
yeah yeah which one is it cue mark 3 my
minute remember it's okay cool alright
good cuz I'll need that info it's like
chat man yeah yeah no I got shadow man
see I got shadow many foreign movies no
no I got a shadow council you're good
jacking me up exactly so go got alright
just title run nerd
alright so this is this is how it goes
down
let's get a perception role from walnut'
dong grass all right well you
oh that's far away so that is a
cumulative 20 okay all the 15 and I have
a question or four five yeah yeah I'm
crazy perceptive
no exactly this is so you hear what must
be professional people trying to get
into this look you yeah yeah you don't
know like it was just at the I mean at
the very edge of your perception any
other time any other place you would
have rolled over and gone back to sleep
okay at this point I don't want to give
away my position so I'm lying there like
very still and I want to use force
friends to summon just just as many reps
as possible
whoo I just want as well this just a
part under me to be lousy with rats oh
yeah right
rats are actually naturally very clean
and our fault they're dirty
much like pigeon okay we decided well
these I don't know via these rats are
not me okay that's fine for the dirty
okay yeah yeah yeah babe they are
boiling up from every corner you can see
them you can see rats running along the
channels reserved for water in this town
up along the roof just a chain unbroken
chain of rats pouring flowing like a
liquid and then falling off of the edge
while other rats are crossing the street
elements but my secretive in Sanford a
exactly like the life come come hundred
terrifying unlife thank you boiling up
around and you hear wet sounds okay no
yes
what around the edge of the cart
underneath an alarm has not gone off yet
we're going to manage the first
scientist okay I hear a wet sound sounds
sounds okay can I like very quietly like
people I mean I have salt can I like
stealthily look over the edge
yeah absolutely absolutely I'll be
giving that Stover 0:07 yeah we're going
on there God where are you
so you you peer over the edge and it's
just enough to Creek the cart a little
bit and you see three goblins but these
goblins are these goblins are unlike the
previous I would say they have all their
ears acid burned no they these goblins
are flat our bid decks in black leather
armor with oiled rings attaching it you
can see their long ears are drawn back
behind them and they have rings every 2
or 3 inches back so the ears are
actually held back together behind them
and they also have a mask a black
leather mask over the front ok yes a
ninja goblin be like that's so cool they
start Stavanger awesome yes it's more
incredible now I'm sad them sent me a
bunch what would I do
oh hang can I just van for two seconds
yeah yeah yeah the alarm goes off in
your head okay okay great
ah wow that's happened home late at
night is this this is past midnight
because it's pitch black I do anything
today I would probably still be up
drinking as long as they will give me
booze and since they've got like a free
ride here I will just now be up in the
common room like drinking until they
will not until it's morning
and if there's anyone around that will
listen to be able I would like try to
chat them up to that's pretty much my
evening I'm not going to better yeah
yeah um what do you think it's yes what
am I saying there's only one there's
really only one thing I can do its I got
a get a wolf it up yeah I had had you
know I already better yeah no I go back
and forth um no I'm at this point since
you know I creates a cart I'm going to
immediately use wild shades and turn
into a direwolf um things are dire a
dire ass wolf guy that's true
didn't say my own time I thank you um
and then I'm going to just hell instead
of trying to attack I wanna howl really
long and loud and see if they would like
everybody else weak possessive Oh get
some oh yeah yeah
jaian really really all thank you my bad
signal okay yeah we should work up and
like I like the idea of having verbal
yeah I would be useful a howl hello and
then like the neighborhood dogs also
start barking I like that I'm like super
into it gonna start a howl yeah that's
what I do I love it I love it so just
immediately looking at them and just
while they are looking up at you
thinking that they have one type of
opponent something completely different
happens instead oh yeah and I'm like
silhouetted by or not although yeah okay
turns up just a chest full of air
expelled and this potent how um and the
WWE t-shirt yeah exactly
that's like Street me like really three
different poses okay
you notice I get it exactly from an
Oakland so I'm going to need uh whatever
you want exactly
let me go ahead and get initiatives from
everybody and then I'll arrange I here I
incited the initiative I was gonna say
that and I waited the egg up I went to
get this is like directly brought a
little drier lane I went to get six
dinar
but I said he's kind of bear fans we've
got his rest so I just go to wake you up
what's happening in the cart okay very
good I don't care so just like go fix a
ship door open we have dragons
I'm letting the beggar like lightly
nestling like a little crown libelous
and Remus your sleepy uh rolled up next
minute e.g who would repeat this all
that you were where exactly was our
youthful vigor yeah so the the played
the pace the place explodes like your if
deep thirst are being quenched here you
have made real friends that you think
will last into my life forever
no really understand me no they totally
they totally get it super interested
band oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah what
they want it because they know play for
you guys could play you know what I mean
it's that type of thing any making
jamming I think I think that that
reference was too real for me and I need
to take a second that actually death
penetrated the scalp so um but there is
explosive there is an explosive window
shaking how immediately outside the in
and then other animals in other animals
in the town begin to join this chorus
all the rats are howling I say rats and
wolves yeah I will keep [ __ ] I'm a
kool-aid man out of this in you know and
if there if the door is convenient I
will go out the door and if not I'll go
over there yeah I mean there is the the
cart is very close to the front okay out
and to the left as you as you peel
around there are three shapes that seem
very well acquainted with the work of
the night they are shifting and slipping
as they look up at this giant wolf that
is on the top of what you know to be
your mother's cart there's a little time
and still the statue could be a sealer
wolf the wolf is a head of some sort of
Rat Pack exactly but now Rosie
you are drunk and now great
it's almost impossible to sleep because
it's it
also [ __ ] clock out there yep it's
dogs
I recognize the house here I'm like yeah
that's my girl
just for fun yeah yeah justice isn't
very origin just the voice drunken style
auuu that you have seen it okay and this
is a this is a this is a direwolf okay
and I got you awake right you're up yeah
okay
so we're all going down all right I'm
going to follow progressing Lee has a
crypt either it's the crunched door or
the smashed window whichever he went
through and be like you would treat this
you know how much that's gonna cost
okay whatever we'll deal with earlier
and head out as well do I get a chance
to move and and take an action this
right here is you coming out drunkard
yeah I'm hiding the shadows mark so you
going pro yeah okay scary grandma I like
that
scary gramma from the shed yeah Gary
grandma techniques now walnut don't
grass in Wolf Wolf nut that's me what's
next how whoo let's see uh uh and don't
forget your [ __ ] don't forget all your
cool rolls put them to work
okay well you have and what you didn't
what do I did no idea no one kids climb
all over animal yeah Bob stress
yeah great left okay so I would like to
hang on now when they ask you yeah [ __ ]
how they came out yeah yeah this life is
not delivering for me today look good
not great
yeah um good news for me how far away
are they alright thanks for the car they
also they are you you have seen them
emerge from the door behind first one
then another then another and then you
are below are the are at least three
that you know about fantastic super gobs
so I get pack tactics advantage when
you're an ally so that's just far enough
to say that I've been intro yeah nice
and I want to leap off of the cart and I
want to get one of these little goblins
in my mouth and I want to like cool do
so with this advantage oh so it just
cancels out because I have advantage
exactly Wow
oh yeah cell Devon bread I did I
shouldn't have said anything just
secretly rolled the dice means well that
isn't right keen +5 said has a 24-7 24s
very I I know I think the God would
lives in your mouth yeah so that's going
to be a 6 plus 3 is 9
piercing um geesh
yeah that's what I love it I told you
that you should do a bite I did a bite
did I'll bite anyone
yes so just right off of the top the
full weight comes down just crashes yeah
and then the teeth come down lives
inside the mouth
his friends are moving couches yeah
you're not renting yeah yeah no no no
it's gonna yeah he's going to stay but
yes that's that's exquisite even from
beneath you it appears to this goblin
appears to have maintained its composure
even in the face of giant wolf hood
that's much better
Thank You dice this is what I was trying
to do before uh he swipes at you right
on the underbelly not my underbelly yeah
I know you you know that you know that
that that portion is prized by goblins
that's for Kershaw nothing tries to Jack
you again is your what's your is your oh
no class 15 my armor class is 14 okay he
finding purchase with the first he stabs
and then drags the dagger into that most
tender realm the vittles indeed for
another five okay it is at this point
that his fellows
join the fray the first one makes a
swipe that you cleverly shift out of the
way and the other one is also a piece of
[ __ ]
Dennard listen so I'm in the room I'm
not your I gotta have to use an action
to get out oh my outside maybe my
understanding is that you can okay Matt
all right I didn't know you guys were up
to you guys yeah I guess it was because
the gap yeah all right um it works once
before I could like try to and I feel
like these guys can't be as intimidated
as easily or the other ones looks fine
with the WWE promo yeah uh we can use
that I can try just save yeah put it
work yeah don't acid the dog I'm not
gonna no I won't ask it is your chronic
entitlement I think okay yeah I guess
well not just their chronic mouth fluid
right right well I just want that I just
want the fighting to stop
yeah yeah so I go out there and I start
freaking out and like berating them let
them rob if I go oh yeah then I got five
minutes a play time and I start getting
in the closest one space we go would you
do a little goblin cousin are here to
rumble Mean Gene point back it we're
back at Chris me and Mean Gene here
we're gonna wreck some goblins like
actually with you which is all run by so
sirens look at some intimidate role
going yeah all right it's very good so
am i rolling with my intimidate book yep
blank teen is very good beat this goblin
you're right there in his face the
microphone is there personal about daily
pressures toothbrushes the sword pretty
okay he pulls down his mask it's just a
mass of sharp teeth underneath but you
can tell that be the chin is quavering a
little bit you go in there and then okay
Chris trout I go Mar I want to own the
mess around anymore
tired of this
Scotland soon they on the night view my
tentacles I went on leash them do it let
them lose the tentacular spectacular
yeah now remind me some of them you can
go it's okay
basically you need in our can check that
Lieberman don't determine the type of
control you have over it right okay
because I don't need it because the last
time this manifested it emerged from a
horse yes not where I wanted it to go
through I know and that's because your
arcane role was not great was not about
let me ship some arcane role all right
uh with disadvantage no Wow
okay okay disadvantage I we go I got
nothing to operate on managed so that's
a ten oh I'm sorry so that one was yet
hedging and you're you had your ship
some of the thirteen and then this one
worried as a force in your arms pretty
cool Alyssa I don't want that's what
that was the one that I yeah is it
there's a kind of trash critical fail
okay so yeah yeah one is inaudible
before we were adding the baby you can
handle it feel very low now add that in
your heart yeah yeah let's play little
beer your brain exactly we ratify
umbrage yeah so there is an assortment
of rats here that have been shredded by
your goblin oyd close because you're
looking for I wanted this exactly it's
like and so whereas before there was a
giant sharp tendril that emerged right
this is five lesser tendrils that burst
out individually from the bodies of
these rafts and then begin to rise
around the field like jagged serpents um
hungry for flesh I wasn't I was right I
wasn't like so aggressive eating right
pod so is that good like I'm a truck
trainer what I need
Victorine it's a little bit tricky
nobody cares but it's like no no nope
they'll they'll emerge and do their own
thing on the enemy train now Grievous so
I burst out of the inn in it to see
goblins yes there's a full carpet of
raps on the ground wolf there's a wolf
attacking the cart and then there's
unspeakable tentacle horror yeah first
force yeah imagine that makes made out
of rubies
yeah that are all teeth okay that's
worse than I was thinking yeah so I my
thought is to purify this with fire
yeah that's an attic anyway this is the
only and obviously he is being
mind-controlled by somebody that's my
only explanation narrating as I'm
talking down to this goblin right and
although honestly I might not even be
able to parse that because you might be
just some huge hulking lizard beast and
so yeah I got my back I pretty much like
new life precious cargo
yeah well actually I'm not I would not
even think of of Phi I would Thunder
Wave I come out I burst out and it's
like can Gandil you know yeah staff down
is just kaboom out in front of me
everything everything is wrong here I'm
going to destroy it all new cart this is
a good car all right let's get what do
you got oh yeah how does it work um it's
a wave a wave of thunders for sweeps out
from in front of me each creature in a
10-foot cube provision a dainty 15-foot
cube originating from me must make a
constitution saving throw on a failed
save the creature takes to DA thunder
damage and it's pushed ten feet away I
want take advantage smashes I apologize
in advance yes I denote you're wrong
your wife your wife
so this constitution says that's a fire
that's a 1517
yeah what's here feels right um yeah my
lip it me like really low actually go in
my di next page here we go
oh no we're still safe one more little
blank system there are no Spang goof it
8 plus the modifier right so it is uh
it's an 11
yes don't you're okay all right do i if
you don't say it you don't have you dad
to d8 you can say for half day again
okay and if you say you're not pushed
here can you give me the damage so I can
apply it to various creatures yes we
take also everything so like 1d8
there are all my eights my name is I
would love to like someone r8 my family
my fancy dice bag was kind of courting
me uh it's a super impressive three
points of damage and also everything is
pushed ten feet away that doesn't make
it safe okay okay so three so safe for
half okay great but I don't have to go
anywhere
also everything within 300 feet heard
that hmm like a big boom of thunder
mm-hmm now the neighbors are up what
they probably always get car alarms
there's a noise ordinance in this
neighborhood so if you saved I did I got
they're good you got 21
okay um but here is the problem
yeah hormone cards exactly wolf I just
got can you get your kid under control I
didn't try they're just they're doing
well rats
electrolytes why everywhere yeah like
for like a surf documentary like just
this wave of rats peels out and bursts
past the cart is shoved a few feet
forward but coriander is able to keep it
under control
that's really good for coryandlaura our
trailer need to take three damage no no
but the uh you know that the egg has
been pressed against the back by this
big your back by this wave oh boy you
don't get for yeah
it was neutral on him before and now I
don't like every way that rosy be singer
um I'm behind you so I don't have to do
it no no no but I am extremely upset I
can only imagine these are my friends I
got it I got it mom oh boy okay I am
hanging up the shadow the Goblin that is
particularly terrified of dinar at this
point I'm going to come up and just poke
mine but with my course ass as hard as I
can
what's in whoa whoa whoa the natural
twenty elite but daddy yeah yeah it's
the alcohol I think it's poison oil a
backslider France gone so summers and
eggs you never grab your weapon dice
down and roll it
oh nice okay so that's three 6s 9 plus 3
is 12
each will make my unarmed so I could
well assume he's still alive
oh yeah okay what so that's their good
enough file if you mean yeah and that
was a lot more damage got you yeah so he
takes he takes two solid hits one to the
side of the head one to the solar plexus
well but from launch exactly look like
Slam by and then within the head of the
button you don't you're right over here
right the buzz head you see him he
smiles and pulls his mask back up okay
you like again
yeah let's mess with it man yeah yeah it
just it's a new it's a new me I can see
you got show it off yes it's like out of
yours to call its great matter I got
online hold on we're going to go
paintball aunty right walnut Don grass
or
not on grass it may rely agree to start
uh just are barking at your nose yeah so
I want to crunch down even harder on
just keep chilly turn yeah I want to
like double down as dick hmm let's see
it even harder see how you double down
can do that bite right I'm 12 that is
not he is shifting himself underneath
he's given you he given you two good
stabs and now he's just keeping himself
just out of the wrist out of the reach
of my mom oh yeah yeah yeah the shake is
crucial this this fight is going to
continue but he stabs from underneath
got five points of damage I don't even
care
it's nothing didn't even care it's not
even a big deal nothing to make he
slashes he slashes up high and the
dagger glints off of one of the giant
fangs
um sharpener pain is premium thing one
of one of his fellows leaps onto your
back and gets a gets a big handful of
fur and you're moving around and he is
trying to put the dagger in the in the
back zone and is unable to but he sucks
yeah he sucks
he's the worst I'm just like too great
and he's just like marveled at how great
a wolf I am so the cart the cart lowers
on it on its wheels torture yeah I
scarred hunch right um it has cart hunch
um and yeah yeah for good I know we're
over the top you see you see a goblin a
top now a wolf unlike you this is a this
is a a warg
oh yeah just just fleshy with a gnarled
fleshy face channel approaches yeah I
pulled back into matted gray fur
reigns pulled through the back of the
jowl and this this word you've never
seen this before but this work actually
has a second head Oh
and then around around the left of the
cart is another of these goblin
Beastmasters but this only has one head
I don't know if I don't know what
happened I do yeah I don't know the
situation like I don't know if it had
two heads and then it lost one or like
half off and if a remodeling was deluxe
model yeah exactly it's like this gotta
get the leather this is C heaters this
is the e^x yeah exactly right but they
are they are
alright well maybe now I can they have
it well David they have a different yeah
they seem to have a different mo but the
rest of them are our skirmishers they're
interested in checking out the cart
couldn't even take care of discovery
exactly right cool but these these will
these wargs are sniffing the air um and
they immediately leap toward dinar oh oh
god damn it the game against rule right
so that night the Beastmaster atop the
single headed board curls a javelin that
goes right over your shoulder the rule
of work itself Kristin our know how ya
ward kid oh [ __ ] okay that's sorry was
it a lot that's nine points of damage
and you need to make a strength saving
throw for me take advantage yeah do I
know should I take it seven sucks okay
so go to five years so ten it's all
garbage yeah so anything that the
javelin goes over the shoulder and that
puts you just off-balance enough for the
ward to barrel right into your chest and
put you flat on your back leg us know
where the two
the two-headed warg seeing this
delicious feast laid out in front of it
has advantage on a prone foe hmm
yeah what's your our that's awesome -
yeah yeah those are both hits let's die
here fine campaign six five six and five
all right
it's bad news out here guy yeah but you
know what your daddy's here with an hour
eat okay okay that is the bad guys and
their new mean friends dinar flippin and
lay their broken egg on my back I just
mowed I go off right on can't go back to
bed it sucks alright uh and uh probably
my yeah is that an action stano yeah
it's your mood action I get a bonus
action if I shield of faith myself which
I will do for you what is out plus two
bonus to AC for handy my direction yeah
it might be a good idea yeah yeah so I
do that bonus action getting up is my
other action or is that my move yes okay
uh so these are wargs with pilots on
them yes yeah um
so I go to the one that's messing with
me and I technically they're both
missing yes the one that's messing with
you the worst the double head I guess
the double heavy on seems more dangerous
the one I have more HP uh so I yell at
the driver with command and speak a
one-word command to a creature you can
see within range target must succeed on
a wisdom saving throw and I safely okay
you can get get going yeah
very smart that's really good yeah
that's did a really learning wizard say
yeah I should have no waste lightning no
no yeah it's just finish now okay yeah
ducky
that enrollment sucks cuz he was gonna
fit um he barks a few commands there's
there's a commonality almost between the
speech of the warg and the speech of the
Goblin he barks a couple commands and
then you can tell that one of the heads
doesn't want to follow the command one
of the heads wants to get another bite
at that juicy dinar went and he does so
layer 20 a see you yeah yeah but he
wrote a nineteen minutes plus of cream
on so you take three points but he is
able to pull the beast he is able to
pull the Beast away and they run down
the they run down the street I would
appreciate our healing program of my
friends something superior yeah yeah yes
what do you on the top shot yeah
stronger than yeah Chris you're up um
all right yeah turning into a glistening
metal god I was gonna say whose can know
nothing so we distributed them right
yeah yeah I know everyone have one
button you didn't want out no cuz I have
natural healing spells which I didn't
use on myself so here's my hand yeah I
made this bad one run away Frank you
know I heard that yeah it was a great
turn alright so that was run we're doing
my last who's the one realize exactly
what a guy Gladwell in the last snap
yeah and then they ran away hard work
has gone okay okay okay I see how well
that worked so I'm gonna do dissonant
whispers Wow um [ __ ] feed me a potion
trying to tickets the fight now I'm so
close to death now not having seen these
creatures before and now having to
imagine them as described which one
would be worse if they came back the
drive the rider or the the Beast well
out of the two life's want to choose and
dissonant whisper to the one that's
that's the most likely to stay away
these these goblins are definitely a cut
above but the Borg to physical presence
on the field of the ward and then you
dinar is not dinar as an impressive
presence and it pushed him I mean it
knocked him to the ground would be yeah
okay so I'm going to do it to that thing
if we can deal with a writer if you want
to jump off okay let's see what we got
mmm oh wait a minute
I think you've elephant yeah you don't
so wisdom salmon throw again give it a
shot that is [ __ ]
you Borg yeah take bad getting the
reward yeah what did you think when you
want you going you're like you're to go
to the hell out you'll never get that in
their head
you've been passed over by the
department oh you're a dead end at that
single head the rest your life middle
head management they will never match
your 401k your I'm sorry that [ __ ]
you'll never be best in your toilet work
alright so I'm not gonna take stock
he's going to take too far Chris 3ds I'm
sorry you're gonna take 10 psychic
damage and he's got to take his speed as
far away from us as you can
his speed is really good okay I already
hear that Michael made a brother run
away that's good yeah they make a break
for it uh he follows the other two
headed Ward which you assume is probably
happening a lot yeah it's always it's
always the two of them those single
henry lords just behind those words
exactly
all right let's cut wrists Rob now it's
back to dream Asst yeah so I need
there's how many goblins or three
goblins right now in this middle area
behind the cart there is one literally
beneath her and they are locked in
mortal combat there is one that has
great handful of dire fur on the back
and is attempting to this wolf like
markedly different looking than the
other angry wolf this is not like a wolf
at all in some key ways this is not a
natural wolf a big big big boy only one
head but attacking Gaza which is
probably on our side right yeah okay
nobody else is on him
those balloons no right right now right
now he should have welding in his
control via sleep superior yeah
Dragonborn yeah a guy you met earlier
your friend friend with your mom
obviously not a bad person
you did heal i healed your mom in front
of you over there maybe I did feel good
so they're right so the goblins that are
surrounding her like is probably there's
one two of them are rolling around over
just dance or one of them is rolling
around two of them are getting there
when it's been nice one is trying to
ride this thing and got bad English and
then there's and there's a loose one
that is near dinar but they're all very
close together it's a bit of pitch to
melee okay so I can't I could not manage
like burning hands to get a Kyle of them
I would say I wouldn't use burning hands
or thunder waves
I mean I would yeah a lot of those
spells I would say that's a dangerous
context okay then I will do own cubes
okay no kids no walls no well I was a
ray a little rain right it's a rabies
shot here here yeah and actually before
I do this because we've been jumped
several times yeah I would like can I do
a quick perception check to make sure
nothing else is going to jump out real
quick go ahead and through it you're
gonna do your credit rating in the lid
making it landal is wrong
everything's great too drunk and just
magic missle arms the Goblin that is
riding her around okay great so I know
Goblin yeah damn 9 um 12 what guess
that's great and I've got a role for my
wild magic surge I did not roll for the
previous you're saying it's gonna roll
that tell me what my wild magics are
just your home off his mom Oh God you
roll the one than your didn't you'd
Revis how does it work what happens when
you're all on tree pit what is wild
magic do we have this really bless I got
everything I got actually no where's
that I did the right here no I made my
choices
you couldn't mess
us from the outside yeah it wasn't
enough to marry at all all right here we
go
I finally see it now thanks for coming
yes thank you for coming on the show
thanks for coming yeah that's a good
friend her kin sent you to kill me do
you got away in yeah so you know I would
like to point out that the magic missle
was super awesome and effective and yeah
yeah yeah saw that you undamaged on your
wave was not real yeah yeah I got it
really up to you like is it really you
accomplished yeah I mean it's just
calling it auto hit so and so you you
hold your rod aloft in this in the night
but do it a lot three bursts all right
three Nando leave out of is it too much
three first yeah it first we thought of
my mother goes free Andrea right I bury
everything okay Bello no there are three
bursts from your rod free staccato
bursts sure you are all right
pulse it up yeah exactly yeah yeah I'm
fourth expert aren't you they can use to
yes but that's too far I think now you
made a deal okay don't they come and
contact a center mass with this goblin
and you see it I mean you see it you use
this before Oh always in self-defense
you see this goblin actually leaned into
these darts he's not he's not put off
guard he has trained for this and then
but after but as soon as you as soon as
they hit you feel that old swell that
reflects the strange coordinate of your
training in magic and you reach up to
your forehead you can feel a seam
growing in the middle of the flesh of it
and then a second later it splits open
and there is another eye in the middle
of your head can I see out of that
absolutely hundred this is all so I go
my man you have advantage on perception
checks okay yeah that was it now lavell
see if there was anything I was the one
that your church totally other class so
if he ever when you do a magical [ __ ] if
he rolls a one on that d20 I get there's
a whole crazy pants table of delights
that we get to check out deep role knows
one is it per good forever will see
things happen
Katrin sometimes things happen it is
leave it maintain it yeah um good thing
I look at your new eye and I'm like wait
what is this hold on what's it about you
tell me later you always you know you're
so judgey of my lifestyle choices judgey
judgey judgey rosy be stinger yeah there
are there is a profoundly wounded goblin
that stands before you you have already
instructed him yeah in the way of your
mountain cult yeah now there are and
then there is a menagerie of goblins one
on top of like I look good right wolf
nut know it look like [ __ ] one on top of
wolf nut dumb grass and then one below
just raking the belly of this beast with
his dagger
alright I'm going to attempt to do and I
shall roll for it he I believe that the
Goblin that I've been attacking is
profoundly wounded oh I would say so
and I still standard yeah but would
prefer not to okay so here's what I'm
going to attempt I'd lecture I would
like to stab my quarterstaff directly
into his chest to push him onto the
ground and vault over him mm-hmm to use
my unarmed strikes I support this 100%
ecological no no listen I don't I'm not
the boss Alvin alley
I know I know but that's this is what
I'm going to describe to you how about
maybe some
stuff yeah oh yeah I'm an employee base
you okay Brad we're on the same page
Elsa can try the advantage on this I
just want this banging-ass moment that
moment has got to happen so I will take
advantage up too so that's probably a
good thing I took about 24 Hey okay so
grab that damage okay so that's going to
be a nine to my friend in front of me
mm-hm
yeah yeah that murdered him oh yeah
Avraham Avinu yeah I mean basically you
you do the this strike straight to the
center of the chest and it gives okay
love it I'm way into it I'm so your
acrobatics this is no this is my two
arms
do I need to acrobatic over sir if you
want do the awesome yeah also [ __ ] which
I will reward you for them yes alright
so that's a 21 mm-hmm yeah exactly so
quick strike you should feel the center
of the chest collapse and as its falling
back you use that as a professional
gymnastic surface yeah pushing yourself
over and through the air straight direct
true that's right for gambling to the
next yes one below and then one hi I'm
gonna aim for landing on the shoulders
of the one who has on the shoulders of
my of my will I love all of this okay
unscrews head like yeah course yeah so
I'm going to read you two unarmed
strikes against it which will be of 10
so which I assume is not going to hit
okay and then another 10 which is also
not going to hit so I'm on him but yeah
just so you feel you thrilling yeah yeah
you flip you up on top of me yeah it's
on me you're on it yeah and I go yes one
big one might think that he could be
surprised by that and therefore she
could conceivably gain the Banta maybe
this type of [ __ ] works in a crisp I
have seen it happen I have seen it
happen i Maryland is a narrative I
determine a year so you were right up
there so basically your battle surface
is now a wolf
yeah um and so this obviously this is
that that David is yeah you can pack
tactics right away
yeah if you have a tiny halfling friend
at the backpack pack tactics great back
back back I got there first
I'm gonna be edited exactly exactly yeah
yeah you don't know I thought you know I
love you 100 I could not love you more
affection so but that's that's the
that's the scenario now walnut dawn
grass
oh yeah you got pack tactics friends
down here yeah and you got friends up on
the back uh-huh I'm how like or yeah
well tell me what's up being well possum
I could I mean you've already got that
one on the ground yes friends again what
candid more friend again friends what
happened to your tentacles stay away by
Thunder yeah what happened for the
others alright home I want to try up I
want to try play one more time do a bite
yes for some of the 13 to be a 17 17 the
other one is are very good great
I do the Lord 13 damage 9 a fight slowly
sink my teeth into them and anything my
head I'm like [ __ ] good god yeah oh
my god just like just like pressing down
yeah just waiting for that it's like a
gusher I like that's good that's the
situation you're waiting for that moment
where it actually you know when you go
to crush a spider and you're just like
you know when you murder animals a beam
or like when yet where like when you're
squishing the tick and it just like
there's that moment right kids enjoy
you're like yeah that is very just like
working through there and then what you
see is as your buzzer you're biting down
you see glinting red serpents burrowing
into and through the armor plates
oh no oh the Goblin yeah
[Laughter]
and these creatures erupt out of the top
of the Goblin the cap and then
immediately reach out tiny hairlike
tendrils and pull themselves up onto
your back I love it cuz it's like
exactly that same Prince Martin okay I'm
very excited I don't yet listen I don't
you like curse by a rage monster
I know what you like I'm gonna die well
knowing so so here here's the situation
your friends are we thinking so yeah
here on there every week every week sort
of around your around your sandals you
see you can see two glittering snakes
okay peel their way up and around the
main neck of the wolf prime neck yes the
juiciest the whole voice of us actually
Private Ryan carapace is delicious my
maximum tender thumb and so these two
you can see them seek out its feet and
then burrow in underneath the armor of
the Goblin site who is now trying to
swing on you but is profoundly
distracted
what is your armor class 15 okay yeah
you determine if you have Ruby serpents
on you you get disadvantaged how it is
I'm sorry I mean I don't I don't make
the rules I make some other words but
the second one is able to get through
that is five points for you okay
donar bliss in someone bleeding up
against the wall you got eight hole hit
points now I got five actually five
years old yeah cuz the second head took
a little snap on his way i snap into a
slim dinar thank you um no well I got to
lay on hands I got to get back yeah lay
hands all over yourself I know well me
and the egg I gotta save a little for
the egg
so assuming it's still
a functional you should check bag yeah I
know it's like I want to if I want to
know like ah this is I really want to I
sell something gift that's true yeah
I'll look at the I Elliot I checked yet
I go huh the cloth is soaked so not good
no unless there's something about
Dragonborn eggs that we don't understand
were they ah you could drop the lay on
hands on that I have I mean I know but
I'm almost dead
what is denial worth more ah it's salvia
or the egg which he considers an
extension of himself oh my god yes the
resources huh yeah [ __ ] raised bed
well I'm not in any immediate danger
you're all fighting over there yeah so I
got to heal the being wrong I want to
feel a zombie out growing is it I'm at
the end of my character art I realize
the maturity and I die no no a job yeah
I'll get a red job is joining us
full-time thanks everybody
so everybody part of sea sponge my hands
into this backpack of goo yeah and try
to lay on hands it so I've got 15
potential healing points I can do it's
up to you you tell me what you want to
dog give it like I should save some for
daddy right you're gonna be stingy with
the life oven are you going to friend
you with the healing potion over there
cheap all the question is am I am I able
to see what's going on because I know
you're that shitty sobbing and I'm
consuming trails help me really and
you're just like tentacles to BPD
weekend goes guy in that goblin not only
million
Jim Bob rice is all up in itself yeah
all right I'll uh I'll do 10 Keeling do
this and give it a try
I can I can yeah I'm assuming I can
throw it to you Mary Ocean now the bad
potion you know have no more class we
saw pour that into the egg you can hope
for the best do you how many place 10
okay a blend with the rosy don't you you
reach into the folds of this of this
ship that you've put together to hold
this this creature you pull it out and
the top of the egg is almost translucent
with cracks mmm
so you hold in your hands you whisper
the the words that you were taught yeah
and even Rona but you can see you can
see her face in the sheen of the egg her
face all before it filled it beforehand
fills out solid yeah I get it yeah are
you beautiful
no not unlike your real-life daughter a
name yeah same this is a lizard person
yeah so um whoa lizard hey hey all right
I'm not to it oh that's an ARCA trace
shibez just hold I want to check out I
understand what's going on no I'm I said
oh good that is a plump gob yeah
listen my son is taking care of him I
have a good boy in that armor and he is
many snakes I'm going to have business
my boy is my way both in a child on the
battlefield ones do me proud isn't one
of them also choking your Wolfram to
death I think it's really rustic ask me
yeah yeah see the only way you can go
where Hoshi would you like it yeah
around all Kevin on top of us yeah ready
yeah what's it going to take for me to
get my potion to here juice yeah and
walk over yeah and is that
yeah I sell fishing yeah Bree you still
playin everywhere
it healed you gobbling haha yeah whoops
I feel so good you know yakety sax well
I run over there and I've seen you lay
hands on the eggs I know something's
happened and I passed you that potion
proportion of me drinking a party yeah
yeah
just uncork 'add yeah hold it out like a
hamster in a ball it's known only a
little bit cuz how I guess I've got to
keep moving into the middle three one
Delta yeah take off so I can go baby
good video yes fish you took care of her
no thinker yet it is it's okay yeah it's
a superior feeling now does he know
superior point oh yeah it is like a
through walls like a better tier he'll
say metal but for longer gimme your
juice thanks do I go full help no oh
well you might it's entirely possible
that you might do you create you gained
24 uh yeah good yeah yeah later on with
that later on this is not as good yeah
but yeah it happens when your little
three yeah everything looks like I don't
know yeah three this is there it would
you like to contribute the to two words
like tore ass off the guy like spooked
away they're not coming back are they
because I've got super perception with
my all of my eyes see future I can see
through time I you want to roll it for
several yeah these free I do one other
[Music]
22 in my left pocket a jar uh we that's
a sweet eye reception third year twenty
twenty or thirty whichever makes you
happy
yeah you are the better life yeah yeah I
guess bergenpac again thirty make see a
your you're looking around in the you're
looking down the street down another
alley you see a tiny Fleck of this of us
does the stuff a roof on the edge fall
down
you look up with your third eye and it
perched right on the edge of the roof
little words of the love they harvest in
that so it's only one head so it maybe
it's okay okay and is the goblin still
on on it absolutely um so like if here
we've got Waggin Waggin with all the
fighting lawyer I'm kind of here yeah
and where's this in it's like I'm kind
of behind waa exactly so here is Travis
here is the whole know you're the mind
yeah okay I actually know something
really cool UNC yeah I can make a snake
pub down ha
bachchi we can have it you good we're
going to AH right and there to keep so
nobody I have a little have a bunch of
those I just have the one so we're just
perfect you guys make so enormous crisp
urchin I love it so basically to your
left is the harvest in the ridge line of
the Rufus right there you're standing
off by the entrance of the cart is in
front of you okay and it's this thing
getting ready to pounce
okay looks like that it would have
pounced very will had a not been
detected okay
that's professionally kind of oh you
know what Count de Leon I um since it's
up on the ledge of the roof yeah I'm
going to do thunder wave again except
this way this time away from everyone
and towards just the bad guys okay hoped
of like blowing him fully off the roof
and then he will fall and it will suck
for him like I'm losing Chevy's word
friend I love all of this kind of blow
the roof off the place okay what else
really like huge this is what you said
be to school for Mom and if you are
proud of me better I can tell ya oh
here's the bride Wild Magic roll what's
wrong with your cannot it's no allergic
it's not wild via n7 points but if they
don't make their say
exactly well you can a second arm know
that that is not going to do the save me
baby the room you've knocked it's it's
10 feet away from me so I'm assuming if
they're up in the air I'm gonna actually
knock him up into the sky and then he
will fall at that land and into the moon
yes he doesn't make it here's his feet
or on the edge perched ready to jump
down on the party and in this blast of
concussive force knocks him back rolling
over you can see the ward roll over the
Goblin as they're pushed back past the
spine of the roof on either side but
something else happens which is
unpleasant which is that the new friends
that you've made in the harvest in have
been watching you do magic and be cool
and they are now absolutely covered in
broken glass yeah that's that well the
price of admission when you hang out
yeah would you like a few a few a few
plates few scales of the roof are
knocked back and blown back is it
properly there and cool to young people
it's very cool and you can see that's
yes friends damn oh and yes yeah that's
a friend the damage all right that is
the that's the dream is that the tree
was playing yeah
dreamers maneuver that's so dream of it
is surely Grievous rosy be stinger uh
you stand before a goblin who is
wriggling okay with enthusiasm and for
or um mystical demon snakes from beyond
our dimension positive Appel with you
doesn't what's making them wriggle into
the of them okay uh well I'm on my tank
at this point you'd be way better at
judging why people are brig lling I do
not want to get into ok ok so I'm
fascinated by the tentacle snakes and I
sorta
like we're going to talk more about this
later but I'm going to go ahead and you
do a hit on on the toy 1616 is good okay
that's going to be a three
I'm sorry a six total UK and then I will
do my own arm strike mm-hmm which is a
15 okay so he's not 57 not it okay okay
um then I will just oh oh oh cool it
there Shawn I'm still out there your one
hit and then with it my second time and
then be like I meant to do that
make sure to even foes and watching it
wasn't he's crying about its friends
friends he killed sixes on walnut on
grass okay so I were elated the thing
this under me it got myrtle aided
greatly so then there's just the thing
that's on me exactly and Rosie else are
there right fingers on me and the Goblin
and the snake and the snake so forget
about those right in the goblin collapse
under the weight of epic okay no I'm
very strong um and then I don't want to
move because then you'll have to do is
check to see I'm very good sure yeah she
tell you where that right
decrement well then I want to yeah I
want it all in - um I don't know what
he's talked about you walnut uh and they
all fall in Cho no I mean if there's
other stuff
I don't wanna be walnut right now that's
not a good nobody would like shake off
both of them and then still bite him
could that be like a movement need to
see your regular movement they'll have
to contend with it okay guys cuz me
they'll have to deal with your movement
your the giant wolf right you know what
I mean I'm saying I want to shake them
off but still fight him yes now yeah try
to shake it cool okay what would that be
strength you're gonna you're gonna rue
the day twelve easy
I need an acrobat scroll from you yet
nine hmm you fell off I fell off that's
good enough you have a crappy shake I
fall off your album still on um okay
that's fine uh so then what can I work I
can't do anything kind of like go away
with him then did you pick a sailor yeah
just take him somewhere like what can
you look under the cart you so this is
like a canal city right no you said they
are throwing up in the canals the rest
will come up from Canada chances got
nothing yes in my mind we're going to
connect really no listen I like that
that's off I was like paying my own word
picture no no it's ko where are we right
now
yes sorry I'm delightful day oh right
I'm pretty sure you sit in my foot pound
yeah I'm not I want to just run a like
taking a little bit farther away from
the group and melted em because I'm
assuming that somewhere hearings an hour
crying over there I'm better now
yeah it's fine I'm gonna start kicking
ass in a second okay then I lay down
with my coffee I'm just gonna swing this
sword and hope for the best now I want
to honor I want to just take him out you
want to run him away yeah I just want to
write more okay so you you run past the
front door and in your peripheral vision
you can see hair of and our dragon out
in what you assume is his night where
it's very similar to stay where honestly
yeah great um except it has a cat you
run him out sort of into the square that
was full of people earlier and that is
when Ruby snakes burnt yes yeah oh I was
rolling a lot of dice yeah no you feel
you can feel him lose his footing on the
back as I I think that is good for him
yep he loses his footing on the back and
you you see him fall in a heap to the
left of you and then you see him you see
him raise his dagger
defiantly but then you see directly from
his palm erupts a ruby serpent
sorry you didn't get to do this he looks
at it in terror for a moment before he
collapses and then another Ruby serpent
erupts and they appear to be fighting
over the bloody dagger cool that's
what's up hmm okay those are gone tough
but there is we this is Ruby fake
parenting yes no enemies
I'll give you a good pet yeah exactly
yeah belly rub I met on that little
wounded Bella near yours yeah yeah a lot
of the entrails back in so harem and our
dragon is now looking at the destroyed
front window of his establishment the
harvest in there are moist compresses
being applied to teenagers inside these
raves right here so yeah devolves
quickly into like an i wide shut [ __ ]
yuck is it bad yeah but really good at
but 50% of the participants are statues
yeah he's moist compressing his statue
no no no okay I said it's no no Eyes
Wide Shut Oh gotcha got to be a great
example on Domino masks yeah Harriet
aravindh urban approaches yoo-hoo
there's been interactions in the past
sir I would like an explanation very
briefly hmm well I think that they were
trying to do a stealing thing and we
stopped them and then my horribly
disappointing son Grievous destroyed
your end I'm really sorry about that
he's going to pay you I eat the damage
it was a horde of rats mom I have any
your heart from the Lord of Wrath and
there were a hundred wolves huh yeah
sorry about that
Rubus will be taken care of whatever the
cost is repair yeah he holds it hand up
oh yeah
she got Maps the center of his palm with
the index finger of a left-handed more
than I don't I say I say I need
estimates from three contractors and
then we'll settle up and if you want to
make a real point of this then we'll
talk about the safety of the people that
you guaranteed space and you're in very
impressed never watch I'm just a lady
oh hi I'm taking gray with him where did
he learn this lesson one wonders and he
does it he says I need the address of
your uh lodgings that's here you here
for anything yeah we were inside your
clothing a broken one and that one is no
glass and this one I think that this was
a hit job from a bald man pragma cleft
my gloves class incredible works for
found topics I think I think he hired
them and I think that perhaps in little
rebus paying you I like this I like this
I want to see some I want to see some
persuade oh Tron okay I want it I want
to see some social skills liberating
because I have to say I do like I do
like the rhetorical yeah strategy
because as we know his affection for
pragma cleft is really at an all-time
low minuscule okay I will grab a mass oh
yeah sounds real good yeah all right so
um I wouldn't it's been much been a tale
for me okay grandmother okay listen my
son as I mentioned colossal
disappointment but I do not he nods
considerably
yeah you probably met young men like
this in your in your time
but I do think there was a scrap and
straight with you and pragma and he
seems to really enjoy stealing statue
that he belongs to you now
she believed that belong to you
we have a statue belong to you going in
our carts and I think that it's his
fault he hired these goblins to try to
steal just to make your life a living
hell
we got caught the mill but let's focus
on pragma cleft let's get let's get some
answers out of this guy Yeah right he
looks over at clefts clefts here in the
middle of the night yeah and re-enters
his in and emerges from the end with
what looks like a Smith's hammer and you
see him crossing the street he's going
to break the doggers right off those
threads right now I know uh in it in a
with poise dignity and purpose and then
you can see that you can see the spray
ghost going wild starts out as a as a
precise arc and then like each overhand
swing of this Smith's hammer it becomes
an aerosol spray um and you think it
might be time to leave this town yeah we
gotta leave [ __ ] we've done our jobs
here yeah we've uh let's make Mick work
okay folks let's get in this cart while
he's smashing it up now's the perfect
time to just tiptoe past all the dead
bodies
wake up coriander say something soothing
[Music]
[Laughter]
it was the horses sleeping through all
that I am I'm again the torrent of
racketeering okay almost even Neal she
seen some supreme iam yeah yeah well
she's been hanging out of you guys is
what's going on you think
might be time to leave yeah all right
over to where you swing the hammer
around no no is if there is a as UK
anything he just over there going nuts
with this thing and you get a scene
you'd like this I just say is a one I
mean I'll just underway here all these
windows to and I'm like I'm sorry I'm
sorry I'm sorry about you please yeah he
is he is just um insensate rage just
driving this this hammer here so the
Walther lights are starting to come on
inside you know I think they are to
building to the time you family if you
want to just like exactly something
super right yeah yeah okay and so as you
as you could you come back through the
as you come back over to the cart as
you're climbing exactly he said you're
climbing up onto the bandage onto the
bench seat you look in the window and
there is a half-elven girl there with
just the most tasteful slight cut on the
cheek and one of your friends from
before and she just she just watches you
climb up onto it and she leans a little
bit as the cart pulls away make you been
alright so who is riding inside the cart
who is writing outside the card I Owen
strikes yeah it's early you know no mom
it's really it's early it's like so
early it's like this is like when your
dad gets you up it's like that early I'm
sleeping in the cart you know I mean
you're sleeping inside the cart you have
but you have my you should you have to
sleep first before the back axle and you
you have to wake up to go back to sleep
yes
I want to turn back into I want to turn
back into one that I want to climb up on
top of before I do like a dream only
sure so now I want to leave extremis can
I really feel for him because like at
the worst thing to Walnut would be like
a disapproving mother figure if I want
to be like he didn't get up there kid
and then climb yes but no you didn't
they're horrible and I say your shitty
kid hurt my beautiful baby
I just throw that info out another way
and and I go to Frankie's just like that
don't worry about after you have when
you're preparing the cart and getting
ready to go
well ver opens up the back doors and
push us out to more goblins Oh kill you
to God weary efficiently killed nice Wow
I'm sure you can all thank the animal we
have two words liberated murder anyway
we're not a [ __ ] coke environment
kill another murder in common
I've had my hair done consummated a very
impressive yeah yeah yeah pushes him out
pinches the back of my utility right
inside the car and I'm sorry
so you can hear you are there the car is
pulling away you're leaving the statue
still has its cover oh yeah I don't like
at all it is a rich wooden base a topic
is a likeness of parov and our dragon
the loose silken tunic no pants
whoo and what's the second uh it's just
it's there's product she's moving like
and we can sleep and then at his feet he
sort of like laughing into the distance
and then with him on that Dyess is the
crushed and broken
pragma cleft beneath a statue
of this sort that hairband our dragon
specializes analyzing not as a table
yeah yeah and then there is a written
around the base in the wood it says the
victory of hair of and our dragon over
the vile rogue pragma cleft
we get Antiques Roadshow like what do
you think excelling at mice for this
because all that's a pragma yes he would
have bought it just to break it and
we're like well I will put this near
center square yeah exactly the door
still open I'm didn't just work it out
just came up at that view you could know
I think this might be a kind of a great
memory of our adventures Becca if it had
a collar fit as a value it's apparently
the only thing that that drives this
enterprise yeah yeah we're the art lover
not anymore
that was the old yet yeah I changed that
was very good so you are rolling south
on the long road back toward red larch
we are we equal or any of us not driving
I'll be able to take shifts arrests
absolutely enough time this week
yeah yeah there's nothing if you can get
the rest of the you can get the rest
that you crave of the dead yeah from
before you pull into town about midday
you're familiar now with the bustle of
red larch at its busiest it's not too
busy yeah um it's not on the sign
exactly it's not too busy the end but
but I get it you roll down the you roll
down the Main Street which is just
itself an extension of the long road rim
take your left you can see as you're
pulling through you pass well verse
Ragan's his establishment is there to
the right
okay does he make any motion to jump out
of carts or to see skips if he feel like
he wants to good it doesn't do or yeah I
think he might be hoping created to stop
the cart yeah I didn't want to do like a
Hollywood action roll yeah tuck and roll
buddy yeah you're ours now you belong to
us
yeah hi how are you welcome to the team
yeah he's been incredibly useful
yeah great our cart Toyota he's given if
he's like then and nonverbal signals I'm
just gonna pretend I forgot you would
barely gonna keep rolling passage
Rikki's repairs like free card yeah yeah
kill table day you having a good time
he's having a good time yeah okay well
Kiki okay so you pull around you pull
around to the left
the drowning quarter is there just a
couple buildings past on the left once
you arrive you can see the acquisitions
incorporated sign hanging from the
drowning quarter
mailboxes there well bird jumps out of
the back at this point I mean really is
like not even a minute's walk over to
the hardest wagons ride and we say uh we
completely request their buddy this
whole thing was for well versed right
there's a reward our Lord did get carton
when I was through there there was you
paperwork we would hope to get a reward
from the couple yeah yeah yeah yeah mail
in your proof of purchase yes yes the
next two weeks worth of episodes are
going to be your are my like accountant
by then exactly this documentary from
health of breakfast yes and and there is
a form that you fill out that denotes
successful learning Amish permant yeah
exactly it's probably done on the way
back you just hand this to Alvey next
time she rolls through sure leave it
there she can take it back so welder
comes around the front of the cart he
says yes that's it oh don't get attached
I'm rolling stone baby okay you have to
understand I attach things
professionally
ha thanks I got a clinger here all right
well you've been super useful and love
to keep having you along but I
understand if we need to go our separate
ways
I'm I'm right around the corner
oh I know I'm right I'm right here if
you want me I'll be asleep in one of the
cards Wow into it's like red she likes
that honestly Millie exactly uh he sort
of tawheed toddles off um he has a few
of the favorite yes Bobby wobble I'm
gonna walk I'm nauseous but yeah you're
exactly it's it's a but now got to have
a soprano he grabs he grabs that you
also practice no yes not like a gift
Yankee but there's like no astral
aspects to it um he grabs so he grabs
the tools that he'd that were in the
previous cart you can see him walk
around the corner across the street
safely sure okay exactly he makes it
back yeah yeah he he knows he knows the
proper etiquette in front of the drawn
and courtier to the left and right of
the door are two goblins sure they look
familiar
they live in good day today look the
same that way you're kind of saying
remember they've been long enough armor
somehow I like today I do they look like
the cool ones that we were just fighting
they look like they are professionals
okay um they do not look like midnight
assassin all right like businessmen
exactly maybe
briefcase no they're they're menacing no
briefcases but no they're not menacing
you they are standing they look like
bouncers honestly okay all right Oh king
of the goblins in there is yeah yeah
just real briefly um can we assume like
I would probably check out the corpses
if these guys didn't to like you know
they don't
to be doing that sort of thing but I'm
all about the looting now I was too
drunk to remember that I'm probably
asleep in the back of the reason I Drive
in it I'm pretty hard exactly
I'm living so that I would consider
consider it for an Xbox been back up
repentance did statue
yeah Home Office good hustle out of
there I'm not going to be mad at us for
not being like okay ten minutes to loot
these guys well keep in mind creative
spell use the tentacle salute the idea
right why didn't you think of that
exactly I had some lessons to teach my
boys yeah I got a lot of parenting good
yeah exactly
oh you guys yes but that's that's the
situation that is before you okay so the
as we approach to goblins
they're not giving us any flex okay hey
we're we're the local acquisitions in
ink franchise we're here to I believe a
dimension at the mention of acquisitions
Inc one of the lips curls up and you can
just see a hint of a thing behind it and
then it goes back to have a beautiful
smile net we have some documentation if
we need to prove that we belong here
one of them just not just head toward
the door okay
what about it we don't work for that it
might work for us now yeah yeah yeah be
our Goblin yeah well we know on the way
and I need to kill enough goblins yeah
on the way and I'm just kind of like
touching my necklace with before goblin
ears on it
Oh smooth and you say I kept on to
Goblin today I would probably don't know
yeah yeah all right Melanie when you
when you when you get in felt nothing
when you get in
prophetess drawn is behind the bar and
very pronounced he has a hand on a rag
on top of the bar and her hand is
clearly holding something below the bar
okay
the drawing courier is completely empty
up for a single Goblin mm-hmm who is
mode of dresses perhaps more like that
gentleman you saw last evening no
special ear expectation the skin looks
lightly scarred as if by flame but with
the with the care of a magical healer
right so smooth but you can tell that
there was a grievous injury at some
point in his past after we thought okay
he is finishing a drink as you come in
okay I'm going to look around of you
guys make sure everybody's seeing what
I'm seeing I mean who's that dude yeah
it would be like I'm going to go talk to
Stalin to try to distract him a little
bit so you guys can even get some
information of prophetess yeah we I
guess so you're the only one going to
the Goblin yeah I'm gonna I'm gonna just
try to act eccentric and talk about what
he's drinking old ladies gigs talk to
anybody
can we ask prophetess the crisis about
yeah exhausted
never seen him before if he moves in any
way that I don't like he's gonna figure
out how I became the rank I was how long
has he been here 10 minutes just been
sitting there drinking cuz he did he say
anything not to be okay I saw an edge
laquifa guys oh that was a great company
I don't think fine you're fine okay
alright I you possum right he's fine I
almost died table and I'm like what are
you drinking friends you you look a
little dry can I get you another one
yeah his his brow furrows okay not a
common speaker yeah he says
acquisitions incorporated ffs why uh
money mostly right yeah what what why
what do you ask
I'm going to give you a piece of advice
you can do what you want to with it
don't trust acquisitions incorporate it
and certainly don't trust almond wrong
okay ah you look he moves his glass old
it looks in the base pushes it forward
okay leave something on the table under
his palm and walks out the front okay
what did he leave on the table it is a
small white card like that take a look
says care of splooge off the returned
and there is a symbol at the base of it
that you recognize but it's a it's a
corruption of a symbol that you know so
imagine the symbol of acquisitions
incorporated with its proud lines the a
over the I imagined it inverted in such
a way that it is an eye and then a V and
then below that in rough characters it
says of the six okay that is all we have
or this adventure yes C team
what a pleasure so good to have you all
with us Patrick Rothfuss thank you so
much for coming playing with a smart
pleasure I appreciate it
hey listen so we're going to go and
utilize the facilities shortly
thereafter we will return for tabletop
don't go away
you