time is the enemy the past and threatens
the fastest weapon you wouldn't make it
past a second and last a question
play it brash and reckless to choose a
cautious solution you saw was prudent in
any set book or poker - don't become the
putrid it's that well-fed I pursue in no
mountain too steep for dungeon too deep
to send expendable marks up to the top
of the peak of beneath they see you Eve
they come like sharks to it while I swim
in that money build like Carl Barks
through it so send your National Parks
drew it I'll send him home in a natural
box with a close tie the most of the
parks included
save your breath for a cleric confessor
death is a lesson and life is a tenured
professor but if you're seeking my
official advice sign on the dotted line
and wish of the twice hello I'm Tycho
Brahe here Penny Arcade and pax
I am also Jerry Hawkins no I it
up no yeah even mess with you no it's
right here I'm talking prior begging
packs I'm also a mini fest Hereward run
CEO of acquisitions incorporated but
today I'm Jerry Hopkins and I'm running
a game Dungeons &amp; Dragons for my friends
but I don't mean friends in the generic
sense I mean I'm talking with some very
specific friends biblical sense
yuck to my right
Dragonborn narcissist dinner what's him
yeah yeah no to the right of my right
reppin the natural world walnut dunk
grass the Brahma thank you oh you are
hard ass course lady heart glass she's a
hard last giving men a hard pass he's on
the brow she's on the prowl for barred
ass now well not this one yeah to my
left not your grandma's grandma except
in those rare cases where she is your
grandma's grandma Rosie beat a stinger
catch the crossbow dizzy
I got a good one here that's unclaimed I
feel like you let someone anyone this is
up for grabs
what are you doing oh I was going to say
to the left of my left emerging is those
from a mist shroud with wrist strap let
me try it yeah it's not good it's not a
good way you guys do it as fast as I do
is it
it's about that
well no no and we we have to we have to
jump in with both feet
because rosy be stinger has to catch a
metal sky bird I'm trying to put in DMV
terms dragon that's good no steel we
have to get from here to Rose you ready
a dragon in less than two hours go yeah
exactly a metallic dragon yeah I'm
metallic dragon yeah yeah airplane tell
you mininum dragon really hurt like I
didn't know that you can be unsubscribed
from in real laia gently nurse that like
button is that Darth Warren now when
last we saw our heroes they had very
very recently returned from the
notoriously is it no listening are you
the notoriously xenophobic Dragonborn
enclave of scala in the far north near
the spire no blue now all kinds of stuff
happened there um not including but not
limited to gladiatorial combat
observation spectator of said combat
yeah I'm at all not I was yeah I wanted
to get that glove here here but also
also in due time
while the spectator was occurring there
was a a romantic interlude interloper a
quasi romantic interlude it turned out
that lo and behold spice caraway also
known in some regions as KITT thieves
was actually Brahma Louie a in disguise
his spice yeah yeah exactly but it
worked out it all worked out it'll work
out
you managed to return home all the way
home to the drawn and courtier where you
found the deposed princesses Scala
sorsha and Crenn are her daughter in a
sort of self-imposed exile while Brahma
Liu da and the anchor of resistance that
she established in Scala tried to wrest
that place from the grips of a resurgent
Tiamat cult
basically it was action-packed basically
um when I was there actually running it
I was like did we accomplish all of our
goals and then I went back and listened
to it
and I couldn't believe that it had all
occurred was in a very specific amount
of time believe it or not but that is
the that is the scenario we find
ourselves in you are back in the near
the warm hearth of the drawn and quarter
of course prophetess drawn proprietress
working hard to make sure that people
have the calories and libations that
they crave to jams there she's double
jamming that I don't again who knows if
it's connected with the sort of elevated
stature of the drowning courier and
perhaps red larch in general and sort of
maybe the water Davian foodie community
you know what I mean like I don't I
don't know how they communicate a
hundred percent birds maybe but word got
out as I suggested
people are taking full advantage of
cornerstones not in season no doubt no
doubt the the true cornerstone
enthusiasts maybe they're a little bit
disturbed by this trend but you know
that's that's the situation has the red
larch
branded completely to dinars yum yum Hut
no no no you don't see any alteration in
the signage not yet huh I was like you
keep putting the sign up but every
morning that's gone yeah yeah get in the
fire I hug it outside how's it getting
inside you're sticking out there I would
like to hole play now I'm down okay um I
have spread out over two tables that
I've pushed together all of my
cartography equipments that the area
down here there are not two tables to
push together I should I should
emphasize that no it's as I suggested it
happen it's this is this is good news
like I said I mean you haven't had a
chance to exchange two words with profit
since you got back I have one table
it's the place is full you may have to I
roll to intimidate a nearby table go for
it just a 1000 just just 1/10 the
regular face yeah is it foreboding yeah
exactly no youyou glower so give me give
me the give me the body language oh um
she's very upset just comes over you
know whenever you're ready oh that's
good truck work yes so let's go back
eating okay a couple of them move over
and sit on the stairs okay they go up
and now there's a couple people sitting
with their legs off the miniature stage
over by the hearth it doesn't seem like
a negative outcome really for them you
have your your table thank you spread
the map all the way out and yep thank
you and the Pens are out I've got a
quill between my teeth and a studying
I got the noobs I got the pots and I am
I have a look of intense concentration
on my face and I'm looking at a map of a
red larch and I have positions marked on
it from a previous engagement encounter
that we had many weeks ago they tell me
more so we went into the carriage house
to clean it out and we found information
that had been left by what looks like
ghost children mm-hmm and they had
marked a a map if I'm not mistaken there
were scraps of paper I don't I don't
know if I made this map er if they did
but it looked like at the on on their
positioning they had they had the
positions for red larch at spring and
summer sorry that they're the wandering
Crypt what they had decoded can you in
winter as well winter yeah okay and
winter was right here
like it's not indeed it is not I mean
yes this is it this is obviously a map
these these children were not you know
cartographers in the service of the
desperate Valley branches aren't
acquisitions incorporated right they
it's not a nor percent of the best right
it's like one of those novelty Maps you
might get where the the picture of the
of the landmark is very large right yes
though it could be seen from space and a
very large ball of yarn but it's not you
know not that you're not seeing it out
there from the ISS okay right right so
youth youth you suspect that these all
refer to relative locations okay so the
map that I have made it's not illegible
them the map that I have made then has
positions for the wandering Crips where
red larch
is in the northeastern part of my map to
the east of it I have the location for
spring to the south I have the location
for summer to the west at the location
for fall and just north-northwest of red
I have the location for winter where
were spring spring to the east oh sorry
I'm backwards yeah so those are that's
what I'm looking at and I'm studying it
and I'm trying to figure out if this is
consistent with our experience of the
wandering crypt as well as what these
these clumsy child markings mean in
relation to where we are so I'm just
like there's lots of lines that have
drawn with like the the D&amp;D equivalent
of a protractor yeah and a sextant is
there it's not doing much somebody
brought it yeah brought it they thought
it would be I thought it'd be useful
they left it so I'm just I'm kind of I'm
kind of oblivious to everything that's
going on around me in the end while I
study this you hear a you hear a loud
some on the table next to the map and
you can see that in profetas you know
honey be like dance through the common
room of the drunk courier she has left
the bottle nice she can she can see that
something is occurring Saturday require
fuel of various kinds nice I smile at
her back as she walks like so I know she
doesn't she doesn't actually need my my
acknowledgement at all but I uncork that
ball with my teeth and I stared down at
it okay yeah I mean you can you think
that you can overlap these do you think
that you can overlap these these things
you can try to arrive at what they must
have been thinking but as as children
all right it they couldn't have gone too
far away right they can't have wandered
so far right but by the briskness in the
air and the falling of leaves outside we
can assume that winter is upon us use
that you may encrypt disclose you may
comfortably assume that if there if
there information is correct
from a series of adventures that
occurred you know long long ago you you
think that you can overlap these two
experiences and arrive at something
Rosie puts a lot of trust in the
directional sense of ghosts chilled yeah
so yeah you know it's the importance of
plan it's never forget okay
it's narsil throwing corner array ball
bouncing often and dragon boy I think
there was a moment where the high energy
play had been diminished and there was a
tender moment with the that painting in
the background right now she has she is
actually running directly up the
banister and is now running along the
second floor a banister as well I look
at the Nara it's just a jungle-gym just
let's get like a little judgmental like
hmm not gonna build character quick look
she's either gonna learn balance or fall
and learn another lesson gravity but
she'll learn this age they learn say I
said hey somebody's gonna get hurt this
is in a way that's like keep this up
yeah everybody thinking her I'm gonna
walk away from this because causing me
like it's too much
it's like contact anxiety about before I
go I go this is why we don't have
fathers in my group we thought we
decided we decided there are none there
was a reason because we came to this
after much consideration some while
rosie studying this map she senses that
somewhere on the elemental plane of ice
rebus has managed to get his tongue
stuck to an iron golem again we're on
the Joel remark
she doesn't want to know it's just
distractions waves it away like like a
fly no not now not now not now did you
have like a do you want to play with me
don't saunter over I don't want to look
at this danger this accident waiting to
happen
this you guys listening close enough I
come over
close enough she falls on catcher maybe
uh it's Dragonborn it's fine
so you see this guilt see what they're
starting on when you're - Wow her dark I
come over and I look in I got a grin
there what's what do we what we're
trying to do here well I do that I
switch two bottles of ink so that you're
using a more appropriate one for that
[Laughter]
but not disrespectfully just let me help
people I think thank you because I
thought you're trying to keep me from
drinking the ink like like I might
accidentally swill it without my help
yeah thank you oh that's true I got all
the time and I explained the situation
and you're you're familiar with this
shirts piece of evidence that we got out
of the carriage house as well and so I
end this with like if if my calculations
are correct
go on that means that this wandering
crypt whatever it is is beneath our very
feet I mean this this place well roughly
I know the girls love it
oh no not here not no not literally but
but very very nearby them but I don't
know how to test the theory I don't know
how to find it good good go well we just
like go well we could hang I'll follow
my nose yeah oh okay wait but this this
character off his leash
could this did you say that cuz that's
we found it last I think it's alright
stripped truffle pig yeah you say when
you say it's nearby or it's a nerf you
like Crypt commercial as though you had
always been there
yeah like whoa dad I just felt like
somebody was talking about crypt this no
it does not like grave dirt last time
it's not like it's true right dirt wolf
Knight is the one who found it right we
have to get away from these jams even
now I can tell to Ken's Sam you gotta
get him out of here okay
yeah would I being this close to it and
it being in it bearing my sigil among
many others would I sense anything or is
there or maybe it's just not close
enough this time yeah it wouldn't be
it's not ambient in that way in any case
at this moment it's not overwhelming you
it isn't whatever it is is attenuated
yeah does legardie have super smell as
well supervision I don't think so I
don't know that he does you know he
might be more in tune with it than I am
I mean how do I draw that we know say
I'm just a half listening and I like
point of order and I start walking over
and then just Kern art Falls and I just
like catch her without looking and then
just like walk over with there's like
snatcher I'll be there we did it there
is an entrance to the to that mine right
one in town the one with the shambling
horror yeah the monster came out it
would be a good place for a clip to dig
and hang out for yeah a season seemed
crypt II where was that in town
Rosa this close right walk in they're
going to the antiquarian the quarry is
basically attached directly to the town
it's where we'll find our chords in the
northeast school - man Sam if you recant
cthe RIS got the offal figured it out
very bad mystery we could go sniff
around the mine I mean maybe I could
I don't know I doubt would I have the
same smell ever has the same snowing
there's other giveaways other than the
spell yeah no smell is very important I
think we'll be able to sniff it out for
other senses we could try to taste it
was all just lick the dirt and totally
that's how you become Treatise I don't
know what more like yeah that sounds
right what else would be attuned to the
to the Crypt other than it's like the
only thing I can think your focus your
focus here yeah um remind me there's
lots of options well yeah but it remind
me in the crypt we saw we saw may Lilith
symbol everywhere we saw mine yeah it
was one of the first times you'd ever
seen the previously hated single
herbalist yeah I wonder if I could use
if I could try to use Locati is like a
dowsing rod yeah oh just sort of hold
him out see if he was a tug what would
his interest be I guess is the question
well is it his interest is his interest
might be in pleasing you if you have
yeah I mean there's there's definitely a
there's definitely a factor to consider
there because he was definitely trying
to do make good and he physically
suffered as a result of it as well
that's true okay close to I divined
sensed and got punched in the face since
sensually speaking although that's true
okay was very sense yeah well we have
something better the drug I just made
yeah there's there's a lot of there's a
lot of science that you can see princess
or chef although you know no honorifics
please in in public so yeah where she so
she that she is cleaning her claws with
a dagger that she keeps in her low back
she is she has approached you and she
has reached out wordlessly for Crenn are
yeah
we know it's Roberts not Curtin she's
not let go it's like the hang in there
poster yeah it's like except with a tiny
baby lizard it's just she's just hold
your hands out and then she's just like
what I'm gonna doing everyone focus your
discussion though I'm just like yeah
exactly so you're in so you're able that
area that extra gilli over the extricate
the tiny creature extra Kate's yeah it's
like one cake is plenty I mean my
experience thank you right once what
having one Kate is like having two cakes
it's okay kidding weirder I know so this
work show has sorta has kronar and she
holds Crenn are closed and then Crenn
are sort of buries her way into that
traditional wrap that she knows so well
and she sort of like source is sort of
like centers on you like squares up to
you and says spring okay here you'll
know okay and then she tips her head to
profit then profit has a lot of plates
and so she makes a motion of the head to
sorta the best one that she can offer up
and then sorta leaves out you can see
out front
you didn't make note of it before as you
were coming in you couldn't connect the
two things but she has a very small
simple cart and horse and then she she
gets up in it covered
seems chilly and cold but she's got
anything didn't yeah no I mean it's it's
she's just talking about just a spoiler
no she she looks back in the window and
nods at you mmm
and then her her simple conveyance blows
away
dinar just just grins happily and then
turns back to the table just grinning
hmm dummy
are we all aware of your like shared
parenting agreement or like should we
yeah anything she made it pretty clear
she told everybody yeah yeah I was it
was it was loud it wasn't meant to be
secret okay you know that there will be
a coded exchange gotcha Wow doesn't
really get this thing is just goes I'm
sorry she's gone is it good you go from
judging parenting to you're all over the
place
yeah it's great I could be a dad like
once the season that's easy
mm-hmm I'm gonna start writing writing
some stuff in my ledger while we're
talking okay
yeah so Locati might be a good dousing
rod we could sniff it out again get wolf
nut or Swezey out there dinar and I are
pretty much useless until we actually
find it yeah within 60 feet
I can I can divide sin tonight sense and
then you could sense evil or well last
time I guess divine sense when we were
starting to walk into it and then it was
like so empowering I like it was like we
much like got it nothing no it knocked
him over yet okay okay and yeah maybe it
was behind it or something yeah we can
oh we could go try it at the mouth of it
is this like holding me out of wait till
I get hurt like yeah yet does it hurt
burning yeah that is kind of Rossington
mouth what time it arrest one yeah it's
it's it's evening time right now okay
we had a long rest in the car you know
whole voyage right like because we
stopped down in what sculpture town yeah
don't see we want to go at night like I
saw well I'd prefer it just because of
it
let's trip of the shade yeah Sam love me
some darkness oh that's true yeah
usually
I can't see on the time you can't you
don't have dark vision no I'm the only
one who doesn't anything weird I thought
dragon wearing being the best in all
would like yeah I think great don't need
it
oh yeah I do I can touch one creature
and we're into the ability to see in the
dark for eight hours up to eight hours
up do you
I don't know do we want to go in the
Dark Link well if we don't run into the
crypts and there's darkness monsters
that's funny yes costume with your big
sword three point we found the first one
at night yeah that's true I didn't we
found the other wine in the day I but it
was in a basement I never saw so dark
okay so now I guess then it doesn't
matter if it's night or day well unless
we're fighting nocturnal three to the
elves do you want to take a vote yes and
put to a vote all right okay let's go
let's go now nighttime spelunk nighttime
night day oh darn do that okay um I will
just can I get a vote I'm gonna touch
you right on the snout darkly I can
smell in the darkness yeah yeah it smell
the dark all right is it walking finger
do we need a cart over there it's not
when you were you're able to walk there
that's right now for the last stones Day
ritual so it's it's not far at all you
remember though before ya go I gotta go
see a guy about a cup upstairs yeah
point of order we should like pack a bag
sandwiches I don't know we haven't had
some frozen rough-and-tumble fights when
he finally Jerry told us we would never
have to worry about saying I just food
but then I'm just saying my good berries
wedding I mean listen listen there's a
difference between worrying about buying
food and like making the campaign about
trying to players that's better
that's separate we are oh no wait you
know what it means these like Bessie
weird obviously there's that there's a
zone over there but what I'm saying is
that that doesn't mean that you can you
don't need to prepare
okay it just means that I'm not gonna be
like hey yeah go see what's in that Cup
yeah well we got brew another option I
want to I have a potion of
fire-breathing you do but I would like
to scoop another flask okay so I'm gonna
run up the stairs
oh it's important that I stop off at my
room I go in and I it's like on my on my
way to go the thing I go Mara shut the
door
make sure no one's in there and then I
peel up the floor board or board and I I
guess something something small and
metallic and put it in my my pocket yeah
um what is it who know I don't even know
that um and then I'll go it get
something out of that the cup what do i
what do I pull oh it smells like sweet
seawater Oh what color is it
that is seafoam green okay um go to the
doctor for them so then I would like to
use my detect magic on it to devise what
it is you bet
so you do a whole hog right you go like
flicker
hmm yeah yeah I know the presence of
magic within 30 feet and I can determine
the school and I can see auras dude yeah
you think that this you think that this
draft will allow one to breathe
underwater
I can do that any old day I pour it out
Wow I can cast out any day I trashed it
out all right No ten seconds of reading
just like a drop so he's choking for ten
seconds right yeah it's only water
breathing
so I think what said that I can maybe do
this one more time last time yeah sure I
must try one more time yes yes what do I
get this time let's see I can't tell
what it is so it'll just be in this fine
yeah it will just be fun
it is a like a topaz blue blue topaz
doll color
topaz blue crystal not orange mm yeah um
what does it smell like me a picture
lilac oh this is the best this is just a
me a brand potion no guys point anybody
brand potion company yeah exactly go
straight in here walk through it
absolutely not that's what I did do
anyone else need to do anything we're
taking I'm gonna take 10 minutes to to
conjure development my unseen service
loftus yeah yeah she just unseen at you
oh I will guess he's unseen but I do put
the value great as soon as you give us
back could see you summon him yeah okay
yeah cuz that's what it takes for it
it's like Clark more mark more tuna mmm
but you have him and so then it's like
you you sort of know where he is and
then you just like lay it down yeah it's
the same one it's the same sheet I hope
it's pretty beat up
ya dirty ragged but yeah it's from the
doone-gate in looking you could see some
of its former glory and what it once was
a little shabby it's moving more into
the crushed-velvet
ghost yeah yeah is there anything else
yeah I'll make our Clark more looks just
swimmin yo sublime gonna let him hang
out with corriander outside I will pack
a basket of cornerstones and make sure
that my jar of eyeballs is good to go
that's good I'm the entire to get
berries anyway let's you know what else
[Music]
crypts hate so take a single white
hard-boiled egg yeah a shovel it's a big
hole right we want to fill it in
that's what they hate
I hate it I grab the biggest shovel well
we are the biggest shovel we have a
theory right that the seeds from NEMA's
ear would be the things to pin the
wandering crypts down right I don't
think this is this is to metagaming
have you ever described have you ever
discussed that on on the show or is this
is this some discord well no this
is this is not this is the the stab ease
in elder Brian and then once Nazir was
destroyed the the seed pods are what was
left over I will tell you guys not
occurred to Walnut okay okay she has the
pod with her in her satchel gotcha I
like to believe that uh seizes the tail
just like yet kind of ruptured shaped
like this okay yeah yeah there's not a
critter so that I could never see that's
cool no I don't know if his record -
Rosie okay so we'll just we'll just
pretend I didn't say anything
it's fine I'm sure that there are
smarter characters I could occur to both
of you now that you me I do I thought I
was a natural association but as long as
she's got him with her Joey said oh yeah
and then she also has a bag of the the
water which I don't think does anything
but its water
the glider which flowed up from the tree
the tree had a basin of water that's
right yes oh yeah that's right yeah I
thought you were gonna like do tests on
that or something from the name is area
hmm no oh well the tests always keep it
see what happens he loved drinking
strange stuff yeah that's true do ya
really do me okay great I got a
tester it's that part of being the horse
person yeah probably
it is now I'm of hoarding in the body oh
okay so I within yeah right ion or hoard
don't know uncork the towpath thing and
I got like have like a have a taste it's
great right here and she just kind of
like sticks it between your gum ealier
yeah it's just saying actually I
wouldn't shy from ninety play yeah
I taste a little bit but what am I so um
again it's bitter cold Oh
when you when you dip your finger into
it and you pull it out and you see ice
crystals starting to bloom around you
let me grab those I think you'll see ice
crystals sort of sprout on Chris's
tongue ah and then out onto his lips and
start to spread who's cool icicles
hanging from his beard ah it was just a
small nut I think it'll go away does it
go away oh yeah okay so the
fire-breathing potions show he tore like
it away yes you've got that good beast
on look around you're loose to your
children yeah chilled way down the the
ribs of The Lizard King sort of
constrict and try and keep you warm when
they go back they do they do they
constrict to keep me warm
yep they sort of knit together does your
essentials this is a headless desiccated
yeah former king with a bite taken out
artifact oh it's not best may I attempt
Arkana on it and see if I know any more
about it
mhm let me try here let's see what
happens okay it wants to protect its
wearer
it longs to I wanted to protect it yeah
until I started eating it yeah but I got
most of it but there are there depending
on the stimuli there are it will react
quickly to protect the where hmmm okay
okay that's plenty for me to understand
I have been curious about what that
young fellows been up to
finding he's been learning how to warm
me very good boy I want to also hmm take
a moment before we actually go to just
appreciate you Gerry
just to think about I've been waiting
for this day's journey was how important
nice try Bella Gotti is uh know
something that's something is happening
that we're gonna we're getting ready for
a task which usually we don't go out at
night and do and I and I want to address
him and say I know you didn't I don't
even taking it pretty hard from putting
my eyes out and I know you didn't mean
to do it
but if you want to make good get me into
that crypt find it if you can sense it
let us follow you there and I want to be
buried in it yet but give me part of the
way let's do some work there first then
the fun part is what businessman plug
into outsides like before we were all
gathering at the foe but I'm already out
there way to get busy is you are not
wrong
he is definitely agitated I mean there's
there's still there's still a few people
down in the common room but people who
have been people who come to the DNC
enough sort of know about ligardi they
they know about the people who live
upstairs they have some expectations
sometimes they're gonna see a snake you
know what I mean like sometimes they're
gonna see this other creature really
that's not I mean it's it's like do the
combo is pretty powerful but you can sit
he's just sort of like
skidding around nervously and then as
you give him this opportunity to help oh
this is create even have this now we got
publisher going yeah I got a stew down
it goes up and then it is and then tilts
his head and then goes over to the front
door of the drawing courtier and sort of
it's the kids the base corner and sort
of like tries to go up the wall mm-hmm
and you see him sort of like edging up
almost like a the way a vine the way of
vine will not edging yeah I both stay
edgy yeah so it goes up like this and
sort of like skitters we could wait
exactly this but exactly and then but
it's continuing to go up even while the
tale stays on the ground oh pretty long
exactly and once it hits about five and
a half feet in it loses all of its
supplements and becomes a sort of
amethyst staff with ligarius head and
mouth split open at the top like this
tight Eyez on both sides take on that
all the to bear up against a ball he
goes okay I uh good boy
but I still seem through it exactly I
experience like this I could tell what
he was doing yes they saw my vision
exactly so you can so you can I'll go
one or over - yeah just we my virtue of
me seeing that I'm growing larger in my
own ability exactly and then as you
grasp it you see as though you have
normal vision
it's so using euros you're beholden here
your awareness is where the head of this
staff is okay that's convenient
yeah so you can just think you just
think about all the just think about all
the incredible opportunities you have
what it boys it's just a periscope now
forever see over edges it's a peeping
stick yeah how long five minutes feet
can I go to one of the windows of this
well it's just a word snake no you get
nothing from it yeah this is it work
yeah it does work I can see us a good
peeping stick talking to our most
favorite items um just real quick cuz we
did have a thing we had to breeze past
because there were just cultists
everywhere when I just um
touch for mother and like I mean I guess
she shouldn't talk to her out loud but
just kind of says like you know this is
gonna be we're gonna go to a deep dark
place and that is not a place for
actually maybe she'll say it out loud
but very quietly and I don't get anybody
can hear her yeah um she's like yeah
we're gonna go to one okay Mike deep
dark place and that is that is that is
not the place that is not usually the
place for us and we have dangerous work
and I don't know if we're if we'll come
back
she says daughter you found me in a deep
place mother that's all
I'm one like us and then um noses she's
not nuts but talking the things that
aren't people always makes her feel nuts
and sounds like she could fix like
spooked by almost like I'm sure it later
that will be a really it's spoken it
speaks rarely you know yeah
but getting the shell heart shell hurry
over to everyone be like oh it's cool
nope fine wouldn't like that would creep
me out I would be really happy it's in
there but like no she's well spooked
okay everything talks and legends
dragons this is a spooky underside yeah
but not the thing you keep lash to your
hip yeah every single day oh this is
wherever your heels your dirty
girlfriend we're we're edging toward
Halloween content it's true you know
what I mean not me not gonna be the best
not too fast
this is gonna be the Halloween Haunt a
little boy in mind eventually eventually
yeah
we're tying a belt around our neck just
here at the head in from everybody here
at the c-team the nerveless end is not a
character in the classic sense is a true
card punishment all right so why and who
said that like cyanogen they're like
your energy so does anybody else have
any of any other artifacts they want to
have a conversation with talk I'm having
a conversation with corriander while
away from you yeah
and me restored I'm like who's
Amy you walnut I'm like sort of stalking
to Percival hello thanks for going my
mouth right now yeah keep my teeth clean
thanks for cleaning my gums we never
hear or whatever this but good work I
can do stuff too guys it coriander's
sort of hauling the the cobble
underneath her golden hoof I just fed
her she just Paul in the grounds no
customers out there too long down that's
right yeah Clarke Moore that's been what
I'm thinking about this Clarke me both
there's trying to speak and its
celestial tongue yeah to coriander but
coriander is making a sound like a
broken clock in response but they seem
to be having some kind of conversation
tonight that's what I don't care at all
it doesn't sound like a horse oh yeah
chorus even sound right you know no it's
time it's novel okay hmm it's
fascinating it's just a kind of rosy is
enjoying it it's a sort of chatter
interspersed occasionally by the sound
of a like a dull Bell okay yeah okay
it's neat I think this is how celestial
sends yeah I don't know why water really
think it sound like English in a bag of
water okay all right I like that I feel
I always thought it was more like
angelic more like that's the chord like
yeah okay that's fine this look at
twinkling so good
home it's a warning no fine let's go to
work let's go to the my graveyard at
night yeah we're doing it you love it
you love every minute okay so we go down
to the quarry and we do it we go we go
there and find it we find buying it we
find the crypts and we did it okay so
that's how yeah so by the time we get
close enough that we've started to slow
down just as instinct from whatever this
monster is and the in the mind that
we've seen before I pulled back to and I
tapped in our and I say what can you is
there anything you can sense right now
like let's try it let's try it right
here I don't wanna go any closer yeah I
guess what's doing it the lips so I we
should use this sparingly because I do I
only afford her rest
okay but this is a perfect spot for the
first one I think I have to roll or
anything use this feature a number of
times equal to one plus your charisma
Mon frre
okay so you have four yeah I just do it
within 60 60 feet I know the type
celestial fiend or Undead
oh by the way I give you dark vision but
that means that I don't have dark vision
so I'm just following you okay hold on
the tail yes until the end of my turn I
know the location of any celestial FINA
and an within sixty feet and I mean just
going on last time I did this and I got
just got punched in okay exactly
you you know what it would feel like if
I do it in a month yeah I mean it's like
it's like this sonar wave just comes
back and knocks you over but that
doesn't happen here with you you sort of
set your feet brace yourself for this I
know I cringe winterly okay that's just
like testing a stove like yeah yeah yeah
yes you just you hold your hand out into
sort of like the dark mouth of the
quarry and you don't you know sense a
thing okay nothing okay well back to the
end we try sensing nothing we don't want
to go in it and I'm just kidding oh
we're definitely going it well it
doesn't understand sarcasm
[Laughter]
yeah no no Oh we'll go we'll check out
um okay how cool I know I want I want to
say something to kiss but I think we
should go farther for it yeah I just
want to get a sense of the mouth of the
cave for the quarter yeah the cave mouth
of the cave mouth yeah a technical term
I'm sorry I'm getting a little inside
baseball cave mouth yeah PhD in geology
don't see it's just how big it is it's
it's big enough to wheel multiple carts
in no kinda now up side by side okay
pretty right good boy yeah I was gonna
saying so I don't have to leave Clark
more at the mist rinse it's not high no
if I won't ride him wide yeah yeah but
I'll walk in with us yes I mean it means
he's valuable he's another combatant
yeah keys sparkling yeah and he's yeah
it's just sort of sort of casting out
yeah does he emit light I guess we never
really cleared I could throw some
dancing lights on underneath get him
some ground effects yeah we're doing
who's your face yeah yeah if he's got
some like refraction going on
potentially let's let me conjure the
glow man and I'm trying to maximize the
refracted light so rather than like a
traditional are you riding you just no
no he's gonna walk on so either rather
than like conjure the glow man to ride
up here as though he's riding on his
back I've conjured the glow man beneath
like clinging to the other side of a
horse as it as if you almost fell off ah
no underneath don't wanna cast that
light up and through 10 it's undignified
for him gross to look at no one's really
happy with it but what are you gonna do
they're saying there is a sort of
ghastly green light now okay the light
of the grave
foreshadowing when I see um
Cathars cast this spell and
I'll go up next to him and I want to say
this very quietly so only he can hear me
a nut stance and I go Chris this is
difficult for me to say but my magic has
been corrupted so you may want to use
your sparingly because I will be of no
help when we enter the Crypt is that so
does that mean that dinars the only one
who doesn't know
so walnut is really only to keeping you
a secret from him at this point she's
very proud totally perfect I do want to
make sure he was unconscious so he
doesn't know how he got a revive too sir
yeah cuz he would have been pissed like
you couldn't you didn't bring me that
whole time yeah well you know that you
did a good job
Rosie only knows that she wouldn't cast
her spell that something was up yeah
yeah you always have you told her though
what what was it it was your ad magic
yeah I didn't explain what nothing
that's right you were like I'm sure it's
fine but yeah yeah um see I just don't
feel like something happened and I I
don't know I don't know what happened
but when we went through that gate my
Magic's broken what is it what is it how
is it okay you can't do it I can do it
it takes a long time and it's corrupted
by these Ruby tendrils I put my stuff I
don't think that's a corruption there's
a upgrade it's way back there now the
magics slow and then itix hard and it's
it's it's my natural magic it's my
birthright magic yeah I want you to have
anything to do with it looks like my
magic polluted hmm
my magic has not been affected seems
like your saviors as a leaves or leafy
you normal no this isn't like a body
swapping thing I don't think so
okay I think I've cast enough to know
your mind me yeah I'm you have never
seen anything like the effects that
she's talking about that's what I'm
honest and all real quickly oh we're in
the grass
so I'll just cast druid craft as if I
was gonna make something bloom and like
that it's like you know dead and stuff
so it would normally spring it back to
life right and I'm assuming tiny little
tendrils came out of it it's like grass
flowers yeah you tell me what he see
yeah exactly
so you know it's like as if you're
starting a lawn mower yeah you know how
if you if you pull the chain slowly
nothing happens mm-hmm
basically you just comes out and then
you can put it back in right but if you
really pull it the resistance kicks in
as you are working your magic you think
that you can pull it you feel that there
is something underneath it that you can
get access to like a dark underground
river beneath your wisdom that at any
point you could just crack into doing it
would flow out Oh hmm well when so when
I'm doing this oh I look at my god oh
wait I didn't you did not feel I didn't
last time oh it did whoa so this is just
like a really small thing so she's she
feels like she goes oh wait actually
and then concentrates and she was
pulling yeah so you you reach down mix
itself into it and you see the bloom
yeah go out and then you see a sickly a
sickly purple sort of pearl essence
spread out and rot from the root
and then there's a second wave
underneath that that casts that out and
then the blooms begin I'm sure everybody
saw that but just keep your attention my
god this is what I'm talking about
did everybody see it I think if they did
I just go weird happening outside this
crypt huh I might mean something
check the Crypt guys check out the cave
mouth hmm very suspicious blooms are
here so there is some corruption that
you were able to dispel it but this is
all wrong this isn't right it should
look like spring grass but I can I can
on this and see if I that's gonna be
worth some to me oh my god that's your
20 year old the floor for those
listening at home yeah which is a good
strong brand for yeah classic there's a
reason this if you rolled there's a
reason that he'd hide I chose this
cavity I dice yeah I put the symbol on
the world she want her on the floor
exactly yeah it kind of looks like a for
me been my fault yeah you up yeah
so you you kneel down and then you pass
the Gotti over the blooms and they sort
of sparkle you can see even on the the
eyes that are on the top you can sort of
see the blooms and grass sort of lens
through the top as though his entire
head is clear okay like a magnifying
glass almost and I you aren't able to
discern it but you saw very clearly that
there is like a war going on inside the
spell
I see this is perfect
I was gonna say I have this rules no I
say I think I say that I think that this
corruption has something to do with your
God's at war with the mouse God and the
mouse God has to lose I don't have any
love for this guy sorry look I know you
came from your good boy no choice but
your dad sucks hey family you choose
right that's right hi how do I help to
empower your work hot in that in that
battle because this solves both problems
well you wear one of their symbols
I've already do anything else what
others what I know something this the
strange pact that cthe risk drought is
round - you are not familiar with it
you've you've never seen I mean you're
not really the Warlocks are not mmm
super common in the Enclave I was gonna
saying there's no like thing that we do
delay the closest thing that you have
seen to any warlock affixed anything in
your tradition would have been a
daughter of Mahlon mmm right so I don't
need it you don't know and you mean you
don't know how his focus would even
absorb a symbol of Maliki um yeah I say
I say oh I don't I don't know many of
the old ways I don't know what you could
do
perhaps we will find them maybe you know
I look over tonight I go hey whenever
you're ready I'm like halfway down the
cave I'm like coming out all the money
like I killed the Crypt guys dinar can I
get a perception role did you actually
go a little further ahead where
like mad work maybe a handful of steps I
mean I have no spaces price it's a 1
there's a watch it uh what does quite
more singing I think Star Wars but what
should I roll for clock running no I'll
go for Clark now guy don't you don't you
worry about it you let me work all over
in from how many forces here old how
many times my mr. Bottomly expiry six so
you're looking around you hear them
whispering back they're here they're
almost certainly about feelings just a
kind and you're looking around just
trying to find any evidence of passage
or any of the signs that you've seen
before there were telltale sigils as
you'll recall sort of burned into the
glass of the stone and Clark more nips
here pauldron and tries to like pull you
over toward the wall my my hunch all
right well since I don't see your easy
literally nothing I will and my eyes are
closed
I will what is it boy what do you say I
forgot he's asking like I see you can
see you can see a symbol
I'm scratched into the wall along your
right
we don't know if it's some kind of a
sentence or something like that it's a
like a sequence of symbols that are
written in sort of a scroll like um like
not not a trained hand like much more
it's it's much looser alright and I
don't recognize them you don't okay you
need dark vision I get glow man's throne
well that's true that's for yeah yeah
yeah so alright so I see these symbols
and I know we're looking for the Crypt
and I know you go cuckoo for cocoa puffs
for him yeah so I go ah geez
ya know they're over there commingling
and I would just turn around and I get
down to your level and I go and on my
tippy-toes there's some symbols over
here okay I like pick you up just show
you and I go look at these symbols it's
like it's yeah I'm just like limp yeah
everything held look at these I'm like
my noodle arms just swinging around do I
what are your languages again cuz you
have any if you have a Griffin than I do
common elvish halfling enter conic and
we also we studied the symbols on the
world last time yeah yeah these are not
the sigils from the wandering crypt no
okay those are those have a very
specific like you know right away when
you're looking at them that they don't
really want to be looked at you know I
mean like yes hopefully right they don't
like it they like to sort of swim
underneath that surface right this is
clearly edged onto the top and what
looks like a chalk or something like
that
ah I think it was written by a child and
it looks like it looks like it's written
by somebody who doesn't write this a lot
okay and you think it might be elvish
but what it says is your name okay it
says darkness evil children of the night
and it's written by someone who doesn't
know elvish yeah there's misspellings a
lot of the accents are wrong but you
think this is what they were trying to
write now you spelled ni te yeah it
sucks like it sucks okay okay um well
I'll relate that to Denar but with
obvious confusion yeah I really
it sounds menacing but like cartoonishly
menacing yeah I don't like the Crypt
yeah yeah yeah it's tough I don't think
this is the crunch yeah this doesn't
look like the angles it's can't
delineate
please yeah sure he understands just a
dumb boy you thought the Crips yeah
sweetie it's okay hey what do you guys
do over there sorry we were just
checking out it I thought I saw a little
snake ah no it's just the snake in my
bag really nice so we're looking at
things too
yeah um I think Ben come over come over
here keep forgetting our snake I've got
some weird writing but it doesn't look
pretty oh I'm going over and you guys
are both elves so you read it right yeah
yeah oh yeah oh yeah this is yeah I
don't know what that evil kids yeah
night kids older than this is lame Ben
was rehearsing back here smokin buying
the teenage art Biddy here yeah job is
there can I do a perception check see if
I can find any other evidence of passage
here oh sure okay
hello Betty Boop but dude I'm gonna do
hey it's Chris Barker that's forward
genetics test the demon wool help try
trade boxes yeah yeah I'll pick up all
this box no you're you're you're digging
around I mean you see the occasional you
know chip of stone like a hand of a
pickaxe or something like that but it's
does the shop look fresh
pretty fresh yeah okay this town do we
know if there actually is any good gangs
here like it might be some some some use
tunnel snakes hanging out here yeah
exactly how far have we gone so far uh
we got super far oh no anything because
this is early about 160 feet maybe all
right yes so I am going to annihilate
make sure that we're going in the right
direction I cast an eye elation right I
think I will try to locate object yes so
this is a little new spell for for Daddy
describer name an object that's familiar
to you to you you sense the direction of
the object the object's location as long
as the object is within a thousand feet
so basically I get a little
beacon for it so what you're gonna
search well I've seen the gate now so I
have to do that or have experience with
this script I mean you have been in part
of it yeah so I I know what it looks
like so I can picture it so I could do
that also if I wanted to get really
specific to I could just look at your
this symbols those symbols are always at
the gate yeah if I even needed to see
that and like draw it I could just do
that but I think between those two
things I do I could picture and try to
locate within a thousand feet so
basically if we're anywhere close if
we're anywhere close all right we can we
could give up this this particular
thread okay if it wasn't in this
direction oh that's true yes sure so I
do that so you do that you don't detect
any instances of those symbols okay in
that in the formation you're talking
about like that like a gate or okay
that's that dark foe yay all right
there you know how to take an instance
of that within a thousand feet Rosie's
crushed she's like no I did the map work
and I did the calculations and it should
be here I don't understand it might
still be here I imagine that little
arches is has a diameter of greater than
a thousand feet yeah because oh it just
made sense that it would be it would
have been easy for it to be ha I guess
so maybe that could be does not work
that way all right I suppose if the clip
really needed to it would create a
quarry sized hey she's just doing like
this math in her head over she says
she's thinking about her map yeah she's
like drawing the air so it should be
exactly it should be here read large
North West named what time of winter is
it maybe we're early maybe we beat it
here yeah hmm does this smell like
doesn't amend as a smell like smell
grape dirt all the time but this is my
own problem
[Laughter]
condition last time it was it made like
a a noise like it made like a thundering
noise it didn't and something was
bursting from the ground and I came up
from the ground like displaced or earth
right yeah
can we lure it is there a way to lure it
instead of chasing it is there a way to
come to you you can continue to study
the documents sure hmm I just made this
how the whole set up shop of the cable
we're not extra information is that the
thing that's happened or no extra
information what do you mean like extra
information from somewhere from like ah
I see well I have any extra information
that you might you might try from
offices you might dig around you have
you have ways of contacting people but
the main thing is the quarry is in the
northeast section of town I see okay
you're saying oh okay okay and oh the
part of the Northwest is not in the town
proper on the children's version of the
map I see I see maybe that the quarry
would like wraparound or something yeah
yeah that's that was a good fairy but
yeah I do have it Northwest over at
large okay hmm okay so good best you
were already out and about we should
just keep rolling just keep dowsing for
it yeah let's go okay I try one more
time okay what is in that section of
town is there anything it was so what
time of night is it have people all gone
to bed yes you guys hey you guys haven't
been out is it's not that late
yeah okay there's a quick strike in yeah
yeah it's winter okay so it gets dark
early but freezing exactly
so the map that the children have
provided that you would sort of lay over
again you don't know the scales you're
right but their mark that's identified
as winter is to the northwest of town
okay not in town okay yep all right so
what if anything is northwest of town
are there any landmarks there or is it
just the like hills it's when the summer
that summer hills are gonna be on the
other side okay that on the map is empty
okay okay all right well we can go check
it out no I'm already walking ahead if
that's what you said like yes yes I'm
sure going okay yeah sure
I'm gonna remember that weird girl are
the wall yeah did you make a note of
course Jerry how you met me and then to
the matter if you're on yeah more
there's plenty of room underneath for
glue man to stay put so he's down there
okay absurd the mirror instantly
underneath bruises taking it hard she's
we're walking to this new location but
she's just like hi as a wild goose chase
and I she's she's this is like her thing
hey she's so proud of this cartography
she's cartographer a little too and this
is not acceptable
think about how long Coleman has looked
for this thing we can't get disappointed
on the first day I know yeah yeah okay I
just feel like we're so close and I
really want to try and sniff it out
i Amy knows that this won't be helpful
walnuts looking at you'd be disappointed
and this like this is the worst thing
it's a time yeah yeah no no just for the
just for the wolf so I'm well known ball
transform into her wolf self yeah
whoo-whoo-whoo-whoo and then maybe Rao's
son of the neighbors yes give it a
little oh yeah Rosie Kirk perks up a
little bit she likes it when you're home
Rosen rebels mmm-hmm I'm gonna commit
she when she leans up her neck to howl
at the moon you can see that the row of
teeth on the outside is like purple
amethyst and there's a second row of
teeth that's cool inside the other layer
so I don't know
do I feel anything is wrong or do I not
now you feel I feel the teeth incredible
oh I look at Rosie really happily and
it's like really bright white eyes it's
too much yes the big white dog pile it's
too much too much Rosie says it's too
much before chicken stock oh well I was
just thinking you're thinking like yeah
woofs are great because it's been so
long as the last time that you would the
last time you were in wolf form that was
there was it was on the dragon's hoard
with Bravo oh yeah I like wolves are
great now you know deep brunch Ram
that's all you guys it's like I'm
distracted so I sniff I smell so your
cover's blown now I mean I got a senior
in this creepy wolf form oh I don't know
that big you can say I'll go butcher go
listen you look all weird
chiku plucked up yeah different Mac
you're different
oh I know feel free to roll again let's
see if you get it wop wop I don't think
so well you don't know hey anyway I'll
take the 90 that's a one that's the one
yes nineteen exactly
yeah plus a bunch over total so you
start to sniff like you you basically
the cart and the party have pulled out
of town
it's a moonlit night see Frost's
starting to form on the on the grassy
plain often and you're traveling farther
and farther away from the long road
whenever you've left town it's always
been on the long road this is a new this
is a new place yeah
it's not a road at all this is just a
you are traveling raw through a field
like a deer turn yeah exactly and you go
interesting that you're sniffing you
sniffing around but you don't pick up
it's not in then what you sense is not
in on the air really don't their massive
paws mmm I mean you can look down and
just through through the soft pad you
can feel travel I feel travel you feel
travel on so travel mm-hmm
so wolves don't bark but I can't whine
as I why not you yeah so you so she
immediately starts to whine and like so
you start to pass back and forth trying
to find where the travel is strongest
and you do you bolt she bolts off to the
northwest just starts bounding over the
plane okay we forgive chase running just
on my tiny little legs but I don't make
noise as I'm going okay
Oh be like continued like making that
wrong how old boys can you scoot me up
my yeah yeah and this has been more
than ten minutes right because I still
locate object going yeah oh yeah but if
it's been more than ten minutes I think
yeah it's good point ah yeah yeah that's
good me yep
so you are is this this is quarry it's a
completely new type of prey hmm
and every every step and then you're as
you as you're running if it's not if it
isn't stronger you're just adjusting
course so you can see this sort of like
zag pattern that is slowly being
perfected toward the quarry okay not the
other quarry this is like the prey yeah
right I've hunted oh intercom and where
you are what you say you but you reach a
point where you find it that is its
strongest and then any direction you go
think it's weaker its weaker I start
okay
like like you know like an immediately
dog yeah yeah so again this getting this
any enhancement it's like these paws are
excavating this thing it's like you're
right you're straight down through like
a rabbit warren but you're just digging
straight down through the the substrata
of this ecosystem you going straight
down yes I mean like I dig like a dog
does yeah yeah yeah where it gets a
shovel out like y'all laughed yeah not
like Haku no no no I
yeah I look up you and then make that
like scary chittering noise oh yeah
you're something teeth move
independently yeah I'm moving I'll move
to give you like half purchase in here
yeah you a shovel yeah so I grab the
shovel and I we were pretty sure it's
delightful is deep deep deep down oh no
Rosie on top of Gardner is looking
around for another obvious entrance that
might be a mouth to this thing for you
guys yeah yeah like Lucas before in the
hills you had seen something actively
burst right out from the ground you
don't you don't mean this is relatively
flat you don't see any you don't see any
disturbed okay earth around this area
okay whatever we doing to make it bursts
out last time it just did it right we're
just driving by at night and it was a
creepy night yeah waiter howling at or
basically that popped out yeah puked out
the corpse of whoever owns staff of the
mat that's right and that's right velvet
dig Clarke might get in here started
hoofing at it yeah
hmm I'm feeling this is not the way to
get into it though yeah I get impatient
it's good exercise I mean yeah I mean do
I get like any sort of like you know
buff after this cuz I'm all sweaty yeah
you get all very good a job yeah I got
the blood pumping huh I have a jar of
eyeballs but I can't help any other way
I am so glad I gave you that like I
thank God every day I was thinking about
it earlier it is mentioned in every
adventure if you could be like yoga
horseback thing least cast them out and
then parse them you will know when it is
time to use the jar Bible it's deeper
than 20 feet yes
oh you know why deeper than 20 feet you
can try it again I'll divine sense okay
in the middle of this hole
okay find it yeah I trigger my divine
sense again at 60 feet Jase you know
that you are if you have felt this
before
you are surrounded on all sides by a
magnificent conscious evil Oh found it
yeah exactly like you you you know it's
like now it's the the metaphor of the
stove is correct
hmm like now you know as I when you did
it the first time it's like hey I was
trained to do this now you know what
this is gonna give you you know that
they touch back yeah
and so when you reach out for it you're
ready for this sense but you sort of
feel it just constructing this other
world view around you hmm
and do I feel like we're in the center
or do I feel like you feel like you are
absolutely surrounded on alcohol sighs
right yeah so we aren't like up again to
the rim of it we're like on top of the
middle so there's no obvious entrance
and it's gonna take too long to dig how
do we get down how do we get in there do
we can you miss a step you have to see
where you're going
right yeah do we don't have any digging
forms what's on this map is there any
other detail other than that we had the
town oriented is it too early I could
just what just jam my sword in and smite
that's how we dug our way out last time
I was just blasting all the work yeah
I'm done here I do have a ruffling earth
but that only gets us 20 feet okay
that's a start I mean how much can I
guess I don't know last time it it just
when we were digging our way out and the
cave was closing I ended up just jamming
my sword in and then smiting to blast
the hole open I got I imagine it would
clear you know 10 20 feet
I'm just loose earth I'm trying to weigh
the
I'm trying to weigh the these aspects
like how do we find the entrance we
don't just like blow a hole in and then
like climb in all I thought I'm starting
to feel like God wanna get in there
because it means that I could
potentially learn more about freeing
than that mountain right because I'm
psyched to go now you know you want only
that gig do you want a piece of this I
want to get in there this is where you
learned the most right right yeah but a
lot of it is telling me just get in
there and mess up as much as you can
like I know that that's stupid
yeah I feel like if I just get in there
and they just it's legit so I know that
it's such a turn for akathist yeah I'm
keeping my eye on you too because I
don't I don't see this yeah you have
your nose is ready yeah man over time to
watch like the tells switch and certain
ways your sockets um I feel like this is
a puzzle and we're not we're not
thinking of it as a puzzle of
brute-forcing like you're right it's
true that's that still digging yeah I'm
like snarling um Mike I did shovel a
perception check just to see if there's
anything I'm missing from this this from
that ditch points oil shirt a top Clark
more okay let's see at 11:00 it's
nothing great nothing yeah you see you
see a couple of your friends in the hole
you see an increasingly agitated cthe
ris the cloak of stars sort of swishing
behind him as he paces back and forth
okay the sharp point of ligarius tail in
his staff configuration sort of clawing
into the earth as he goes back and forth
can what Locati have any like thing to
douse the okay well I'm gonna yeah I
want to try to do that so like I will
saw I'll hold
the Gotti out like again to try and use
him ah wait you know I
I find his center of gravity and see if
I can use it and see if it will act as a
compass and like rotate in a direction
on its own nothing that's awesome
is awesome I think yeah I'd have to do
it up above me yes exactly because it's
a little bit too long yeah but I find
that Center and then I okay so you can
use tipping back and forth yeah and then
once you get it balanced it just starts
to spin oh just a circle so we're right
on top of it then mm-hmm maybe what it
means
I want to let me see I want to get my
degree
yes I want to get I want to learn about
repair all right yeah only married right
now yeah a technical minor
oh man for that dog in that house it's a
very joke um I want to see whether or
not I know it's been a season since it's
been here our season either use Arkana
or investigation even to see hazards
been disturbed here you seem to sense
some kind of travel but didn't leave any
sign that I can observe oh yeah let me
try let me try our canna cuz apparently
I don't think investigate can't show me
anything that's sure you're all just
trusting me going nuts in a hole yeah
well I ever confirmed it's everybody
nuts in this yeah spinning your eyes
grow look I could see in the fallout
it's like my tex avery like somewhere
i'm confident that you know exactly
where the Crypt is yeah yeah we do so do
we not think digging it all like can I
not some and more digging animal surgery
to carve a hole here we go
right wrong time of day look you can you
have displace earth place that just just
displace on some other heavy earth you
know what a ruptor this answer the
shadow council has granted us some
moments reprieve shadow council mayor
Labor's please you we're gonna head into
our commercial break but don't go
anywhere because we're not done playing
we'll be here when you come back bunch
of them when we're in a hole and
everyone's we're looking at them in the
hole and then chorus had his rod and he
was using it like a makeshift sort of
compass thing but I should I should
emphasize quickly that rosy be stinger
has to catch a flight so our game is
gonna be a little bit shorter today but
it's very exciting because we do have
our friends from the wheelhouse workshop
here and they're going to talk to us
about gaming and mental health and we
get extra game this week oh no don't
forget at twitchcon it's right proper
Saturday which is why I have to leave
yeah exactly
coaching on proper Saturday doone-gate
in special Halloween episode coming up
hour and a half new characters it's
gonna be banging boo now as I said
spooky this is the whole team right this
is the other people what are we thinking
about some whole team lot of people at
this point well that's just like digging
digging DJ to gain frantically how
they're just hot chomping at no doing
are just steam pouring out disgusting
and then um she's clearly just extremely
frustrated with this whole thing and
then she comes out of her wolf form and
she grabs for mother and just stabs her
into the ground and she goes she just
she was what do I do it's right here she
sits right under us
and she's just sitting there and she's
looking at it and she's watching janar
she thinks think you're probably
thinking more but
I'm already digging more than none
exactly she looks at for mother and she
um she puts her hand out and she touches
the blade and she remembers what she
said to her in the beginning when they
first went out for the night and she
says that you found me in a deep dark
place and she's feeling so like they're
so close to being there to be you know
like we're omen wants them to go and
it's it's under her and she can like
instinctually feel isn't she so she
reaches into her bag and she grabs the
seed pod that they got from an emissary
and it's got all these runes all over it
that she knows they they say mem is here
and she puts it in the in the dirt and
she covers it up she closes her eyes and
she's like I want we need to get to that
deep dark place and she takes the water
out and she pours it over the nemecio in
the tree in the pod yeah on the pod and
then she picks up for mother and she
just holds it and closer as she waits so
you were down in the hole is anyone else
looking down so you say you look down
and you can see your adopted
granddaughter in this moment of
agitation exactly you um just trying to
help you so you're over here digging
screaming non-stop you're paid for it
show that your shovel is like kind of a
rout and you're trying to get it out of
the rear and then she has her eyes
closed and she has four mother and you
see up from your seed now I hear time
short and I'm like what's that up from
the scene you see a young Dryad grow oh
and her eyes are are closed but she has
a sort of gentle smile on her face and
her hands are clasped against her chest
and she says mother does the war still
rage she says that to me - you all right
Isle or her mother I open my eyes
and I say I say she says this a Worstell
rage I say daughter the war ever rages
and then I smacked in our and I look at
her and I say I say I say I need your
help I need your help to get to the the
deep dark place that is my purpose I say
what do you need I need what it doesn't
seem to take any notice of dinar at all
okay that's great that's good a perfect
childhood she says below the soil
I will bring nightmares but as an order
of balance what will I bring to the
surface
there's nothing here it's a field it is
a it is a field this is the suit this is
a sort of field where the when you first
came into this place
this whole play this whole region would
have been yeah oh no I know I got you
I'm all right I'm already there I look
at her and I say I say what we should
always bring to the surface should bring
a tree that would form a new forest that
would make us you know whatever I think
that's maybe that's okay though we make
the force we that's what right the EPA
thought that the forests the creek Rutan
Forest was once everywhere
yeah that's they didn't think that
that's what it was maybe they believed
that they believed that uh so yes so she
says we make a new forest make any
forest here she nods and she says
perfect
and you see her arms enclose herself and
then you see her body twist and then you
see her feet split into a thousand dark
roots that push down straight through
and you cannot safely be in this hole
anymore oh I'm out backing out yeah I'll
scramble out now so you are dignified so
you see you see them trying to pull
their way out of this soft you know soil
churned for a thousand years they're
sort of pulling their way up by roots
losing ground gaining ground pulling
themselves up to the top okay oh can I
use my my new level six - shadow step to
them of course so from from the back of
Clark more I can now as a bonus action
teleport from places of dimness or
darkness or shadow so instantly I'm on
the lip and I'm extending the staff of
the master - down nice nice nice so
grabbing this extra leverage here at
your able take your lean back yeah
and pull them up to the edge and the
dryads form is unrecognizable as what it
was before but you can tell that it's
influence in the soil has expanded
substantially it's now sort of rising on
this dome of black wood and it is
starting to rise in the air as a massive
red larch and you can see and you can
see my wood it's bursting everywhere in
the air you can see seeds sort of
blowing around in this dark winter wind
settling on this settling on this cold
soil and then with just enough warmth to
push down and it's I mean it's as far as
you can see these seedlings have spread
in this explosion
and this do you continue to hear this
Rumble and then it's answered by a
second Rumble deep below this plane and
at that after about fifteen seconds of
this additional rumble and then another
sound you can't place you see two bursts
of soil erupt yes on the plane itself to
the left of you and to the right of you
you can see them burst up from the
ground and spread open you're looking at
me like I know it's your daughter
approach the tree yeah I like it well my
cuz yes she why she's beautiful she is
another I said dislike that's my
great-great so it was so what okay okay
well it just looks at rosing is - tada
it's good it's a good look
so um Rosie is I'm looking warily and
all these seedlings in this tree which
still is is growing and toward these
what has exploded out of the ground just
everywhere else you can't tell it is
similar to what you saw with the cart
okay in the Hills that's it north of the
doone-gate in alright entry yeah so
let's and there's two of them two of
them this is significant party splittin
I wouldn't not split I'm gonna go left I
think we should go left we went left
alright think about it left yeah yeah
left plant alright so I'm gonna pull us
all beckoning everyone including Clark
more let's go and I'll go into this
left-hand opening
absolutely you recognize it immediately
you can see that this entrance is
exactly like maybe even identical to
potentially even the same mmm entrance
that you went into in those hills months
ago when you first learned of the
wandering crypt you can see that
foreboding stair that goes down into a
litter not feeling yeah yeah are you I'm
just like wearing nut of the crypt of
you I'm just like PTSD I remember what
he did last time
no cuz this is a like you'll are
glancing sideways at me and I know what
you're thinking and I return it like
like I don't feel it like because me
doing that in that crypt the first time
was this has become more important than
the Crypt which at the time and probably
now I took is a great failure but I know
what that gate represents now it's not
the god I want so guy hate and I cannot
take him on like this are you saying all
this sir I am I'm yeah let me I'm
convinced in his meaningful gaze yeah
yeah we can i cold feed me interpret at
all yeah both hugs will smile and tears
yeah you fall there there's like guy
that was a season ago yeah no winter I'm
a different okay Rosie still does not
entirely trust you because once we get
down there all of your good intentions
may go that's all what's very bad right
I'm not saying let me take the necklace
off okay don't worry no one let's say
it's staying on yeah I'm saying you
don't worry about passage I got a bone
to pick with that gate anyway yeah okay
but do you want to pop down there real
quick before rosie has to go yeah yeah
go down let's do as far as we can Clark
more to glow man in the belly down those
steps he's lighting the way for us oh
yeah so
okay so you are you make your way down
you can recall in your previous
experience these stairs were slick and
dangerous to climb as you tried to exit
before as you are walking down these
stairs just as you did last time you can
see what are plainly traps installed
into the walls in the passage that your
approach you see them close and seal and
as you enter their room it is not the
room of the fountain that you saw
previously this is something else
entirely you recognize it instantly
walnut as a kind of ritual space and you
can see that the ritual looks as if is
frozen in mid-performance
and all the participants in this ritual
are here as well frozen petrified into
stone what do they look like they are
this is the raiment of the Enclave pax
anima so you can see that there are two
priestesses at the center and you can
see their ritual circle has endured for
however many thousands of years in
perfect readiness but those who had
attempted to manifest this ritual were
made unable to do so you can see one who
wears a kind of crown clearly meant to
symbolize mela 'the the lover goddess of
Aliki who represents autumn and winter
you can see her crown of horns you can
see that she has attempted to protect
another priestess who wears that the
horn of a unicorn
she is like per tried to protect her
with her body but neither of them were
neither them could be rescued but the
one that she has protected
where's a amulet of Maliki and then some
amulet has been miraculously unharmed
maybe due to this protection it's hard
to know but you can see elsewhere around
this circle which is plainly a ritual of
binding to capture whatever happened
here yeah they're all they're all
they're sisters who had joined with them
in the ritual some are trying to escape
this room some are clawing at a black
gate that stands ready at the farthest
portion of the room this black gate
unlike the previous ones has 5:5 the
places where symbols in the middle I'm
not 3 I'm overcome with but this is I
mean this is yeah panting this is this
is potent like and they don't they are
taller and flawless yeah like this isn't
well this is an older this is your this
is your heritage on display here do we
so we can i I see that aim line as well
okay and without the same like that
urgency I come up and I'm saying like
three four
what's where's fine this amulet is not
black it is not a piece of a this is an
ancient it's an ancient icon of male if
it is not corrupt in any way like here
may Allah the maybethe is imperfect it
isn't perfect flawless
it's an is mouth okay um condition I'm
gonna walk up to it and just like like
just with such reverence take it as an
artifact of yeah I mean you you become
certainly become the third in this story
but you know obviously thousands of
years later
and you were there in this perfect
moment between these two women yeah I
just I I like touch but I like touch
both of them and I feel that ancestral
something like flowing through me and I
take the amulet and I take it off and I
just look at it and I look at cthis
because he understands the significance
of it yeah
and you can tell looking at it closely
that it is meant to interlock with
another amulet chef kostow mailer was
placing that is our game for this week
sir we had to cut it short
um she's heading south but you're gonna
see more rosy bee stinger and the c-team
of course at twitchcon this weekend
don't miss it two days do gate Denison's
Halloween spectacular and come check us
out you gotta go I gotta go alright
hey we'll be back shortly with the atoms
from will house workshop don't go to
work
you