time is the enemy the pastor threatens
the fastest weapon you wouldn't make it
past a second and last question
play it brash and reckless to choose a
card solution you saw it was prudent in
any sepulcher poker to don't become the
putrid it's that well-fed I pursue in no
mountain too steep for dungeon too deep
to send expendable marks up to the top
of the peak of beneath they see Yugi
they come like sharks to it while I swim
in that money bill by Carl Barks through
it so send your national parks drew it
I'll send him home in a natural box with
a close tie but most of the parts
included save your breath for a cleric
confessor death is a lesson and life is
a tenured professor but if you're
seeking my official advice sign on the
dotted line and which of the twice hello
I am Tycho Brahe hey Penny Arcade and
pax I am also a mini fist hair word
drawn
CEO of acquisitions incorporated but
today Jerry Hawkins and I'm running a
game of Dungeons &amp; Dragons for my
friends to my right Dragonborn
narcissists dinar beliefs and yeah same
guy same guys Phoebe's denier to the
right of my right repping the natural
world walnut on grass walnut on grass
crazy birds getting wild a lot of that
skin that skin sound is what I like to
my left not your grandma's grandma
except in those rare cases where she is
your grandma's grandma Rosie bee stinger
it's like in three acts it's like
there's three distinct acts to the left
of my left emerging as though from a
mist shroud like who's this now good
first round means yeah so we have we
have been gallivanting for a certain
percentage of time we had our first live
game at the Twitty pond
I had a super good time that's available
on the YouTube now for Penny Arcade if
you want to see it it takes place I
guess in continuity in any rate it's
like not out of continuity if you want
more if you want more of the doone-gate
in what I'm trying to say is our
Halloween special is available for you
it's got a couple cool twists that I
think you'll enjoy but it's also
available for the new reader viewer
whatever a person who consumes this
medium is called beyond that this is the
penultimate which is to say the second
to last episode of this season of the
c-team of course we'll have our
Christmas special at PAX unplugged
obviously hold tight for that that'll be
our first live game where we're in full
costume so that should be a treat thanks
very much to nil and everything - Danny
härtel it's gonna be pretty flavorful
but but we're let's not get ahead of
ourselves it's entirely possible the
entire team could be killed we can all
to be your doom gay character no yeah
it's possible you could all die that's
not what I'm talking about now when last
we saw our heroes which is to say
acquisitions and corporative team see
holders of a exclusive license to
operate in the Des Moines Valley
headquartered in red larch indeed they
had returned home from the notoriously
xenophobic Dragonborn enclave of scala
their friend having been chopped
one might say by a shadowy envoy of
qiyamat a lot of stuff happened up there
after they came home the team recognized
that it was the time of year that the
children
had made a map of the ghost children
that had a kind of fort years and years
ago inside the carriage house they
looked into the mine they thought they
might be able to find some evidence of
its passage there what they found was
some graffiti from naughty local kids it
wasn't quite on the tier of the
wandering crypt but it's it's okay
because they went elsewhere outside of
town
to the north and west and they're placed
the nemah zir into the ground a siege
weapon of ancient eldritch enclave
manufacture an ancient weapon designed
to bring terror and dismay to their
enemies the drow they placed it a tree
grew up and then also deep deep down
into the earth painting the wandering
crypt immediately after that there were
two bursts of earth just like they had
seen very very early in the campaign and
they had an opportunity to explore one
of them where they found a kind of stone
diorama of a ritual of binding that they
explored for some time they also found a
black agate
inside this region that required not the
three symbols they were previously
familiar with to gain access but five
that is as I recall where we left our
adventure um we can play Dungeons and
Dragons whenever you'd like
indeed indeed now you seized an amulet
of male if as I recall and you could
tell because because we were we were
crunched for time then but we're not so
crunched for time now we have all the
time we want to well we have two
episodes yes yeah time is he at me now
but you could see you could see that
this
male if symbol this amulet clearly has a
place to lock another amulet into it you
can see from the bottom it has a kind of
mechanism so it's a it's a two-part it's
like that it's like it's like it's like
the mystical magical version of the best
friends necklace this is obtained shit
manufacture looking around
clearly there's like not the other one
they're just looking for it Carter's yes
Rosie is examining these statues and and
she touches one just sort of to prove to
herself that it's made of stone and that
she looks over at walnut and she asks
are these your growth it would seem so
do I know that well yeah you don't you
you recognize it inherently okay as
being you know that you are in it a holy
place that has somehow been contained
there aside this but they don't look
like I said trying to suggest before but
it's possible aid I didn't have time to
I'm not I'm not gonna keep saying this
to make you feel bad I'm good that's an
ancillary effect so be it but they're
more beautiful on that they're taller
yeah yeah absolutely
there's about they are taller and more
more live there's sexier than walnut but
well no not hard it it doesn't like that
is that wallet you you're you're you
know taller than other but like elves
are always going to be on the higher end
these features are just are simply more
elven imagine that there's like a DLC
option you can get at time of purchase
that just like elevates everything horse
armor yeah exactly exactly sharp like
sharper here is finer he's got the four
K mod
oh yeah I know it has subsurface
scattering Nvidia true elf yeah yeah
it's got the upgrade but basically we're
talking about is I mean you you
recognize that this is your that this is
your heritage basically seen in a way
that no one has been privy to for
thousands of years Wow yeah so I mean
really loving this amulet but then also
maybe some reverence but also this I
mean this is information that people of
the EPA had lost because male if was the
betrayer right because she ceased to
answer prayers of course we would come
to learn that it wasn't her fault
not her fault but this is Malthus frame
what you are seeing here is a unified
EPA where the rituals clearly as I
suggested before that amulet you were
able to seize was the only reason it was
not annihilated was because the
priestess who in this ritual had taken
on the role of male ahthe much as
Catherine's ad was actively the
priestess who was taking the role of
Maliki does the is that symbol on this
amulet does it match what we know of
Millis yes okay yeah yeah this symbol is
correct okay it's the opposite the EPA
has very sharp angles and it's and it's
the way that it's iconography is
constructed and this is simply the this
is simply the reflection of that you're
right I'm just trying to figure out if
we have seen enough of these icons if
we've seen five before even if we don't
put you've never seen fully five yeah
you don't know at least they all had
different ones than we had right we
didn't like have our recognition of them
yeah you couldn't evaluate it we have a
symbol of Maliki we have a symbol of
male s we have awesome oh man
yeah we don't have anything oh no Emma
Mila okay so we have a you have an
amulet of me Layla and we don't have a
symbol valet key do you know one like I
only know what the like the Grove
separated from me little symbol is right
right right and so this is essentially
this is an artifact there may be another
like it somewhere else somewhere okay
well this is great
but it would be a it would be a life's
quest to try to find its mate so she's
gonna put that along and tuck it away
okay same thing
wait I'll just get inside the armor yeah
design I think have one she puts it on
now we're gonna know okay great no yes
restricting anyway we already have that
we have that necklace I called it all
then all the constriction happens over
there whatever that's fine just hold it
right there okay I mean I look at you
and be like oh you know convey some of
what this is to me um when I say this is
feature creep this is a mystery that
we're not here for this today but but
I'll need to come back someday you
choosing to you don't think this is
related to the Crypt Wow
I mean maybe but whatever they were
doing didn't work Christopher he said he
says may leekie do you think it's
possible that the the other part if
there's more to this amulet that it
would be deeper incorrect
this is this is walnut you're talking to
yes I said walnut we've been working
together for a while then she goes hmm
well if it's not here maybe it is maybe
there's more deeper down I don't know
anything about this ritual it could be
that they were binding it from deeper
inside hmm and it looks like the
priestesses tried to escape right like
there's some figures yeah yeah exactly
yeah exactly but even those who are out
you know it's on their knees or like
half stumbling their entire body is
petrified this mid stumble for however
long this room has been here what does
it look like they're running away from
what it whatever it was is where this
gate is positioned okay hmm they're
fleeing the gate and as I suggested
before they are around a symbol that
they have carved into the ground that
has become petrified as well sorry no no
more than anything it isn't anything
special it's it's perfectly legible yeah
it's a it's a druid spell of oh I'm
gonna make a note that I write that down
yes you have a ledger I do and I want to
put it in my life wait how is the do
this is the first this takes like the
first document sir yeah just on this
floor oh yeah she's doing an etching
anyway so I'm gonna edging of this
binding spell situation okay try that
I'm looking at the gate let's see if
that's any better yeah yeah were you
what are you feeling right now well you
you keep glancing at it
you know that I'm thinking about it yeah
but I'm not giving away like there's
enough there's no right like lust and
and I find that curious you because
there's no reason there shouldn't be
less right right but it's that you can't
win here you're not a craven we don't
trust you look why isn't he being creepy
yeah why isn't mean you creep that's
worse than being a crow you can you can
see it's sort of featureless mouth in
the center of it then you know what it
wants mm-hmm like it wants symbols it
wants to be communed with it wants proof
that the person before it
has the wherewithal to enter right
theoretically these priestesses did open
it right because something came out of
it maybe yeah I mean something about it
upset them does that mean that the
symbols would be here somewhere
it might be that they just didn't
realize that that gate was there and
then they saw them ago and they ran away
scared scared to turn the stone yeah
yeah I wonder if there's a way to
restore them do they and this shatter
them all let's not shatter them not
shatter them maybe they've got the
symbol inside I'm like a pinata somebody
ate it
our pinata is impressive and the dress
comes on a big can I get her earlier no
smell the candy comes in mm-hmm how to
pin you on a table in here full swing it
was most childlike looking statue but
one easy breaking yeah um can any of you
try to talk snatches presumably they
were alive maybe there's still some
confidence I'll try yeah-yo statue yeah
without yelling yo well okay I ask you
like is there of what you know is there
a any kind of a greeting that they might
respond to the most strongly so that if
there is a whisper I want to get at the
most potent thing that they might
respond to trees rule yeah all we have
is one chance yeah well one opportunity
yeah yeah one shot I I don't know of any
greetings I could also use my spell box
um though also be good uh I don't know I
don't know if there's any greeting that
we would know okay Alyssa hello well you
got the spell box for Amy I say yes I
reach out and I say hello petrified
friends oh no oh it's refined getting
anything back am I getting it is he
getting angry do you think I don't hear
anything yeah because I don't have any
like then
mine's here that I can tell exist so I'm
just it's just sort of them talking to
stone
here's opening the port yeah I'm getting
I'm getting a lot chatter sorry staff
this channel yeah I was gonna say uh you
detective magic before we got in here
right yeah I've divine sense divine
sense
um do you sense anything coming from
these folks don't going if I open myself
up to this it's gonna be crazy again I
feel like it yeah it might just blind
you again just double me over I mean we
can all laugh at me on the ground I did
like that again you didn't I got a
little bit nervous but you again all
right
ah all right I can trial divine since
the statue is maybe I can try to like
focus it so I'm not just like getting
gut-punched by the gate yeah
what's the find the specific verbage on
doing scent indeed because I've only
used it a million times I was gonna say
what does it tell you like if you were
gonna Center at 60 feet listen I can
just no location of any celestial finger
on day I know the type but not the
identity so I wouldn't know like a
specific yeah barring fun yeah sorry
thanks I can use it once my charisma
waterFire so I can use it a lot
charismatic as shit
absolutely so I try each one of these
statues I would like you to roll a d20
and I would like you to add your
Constitution modifier 15 okay
so much like the experience you had
previously no it's okay no much like the
experience that you had previously where
you were basically driven into the
ground by just an awareness of
malevolence you have much the same thing
you still have to
you have to steel yourself against one
of these statues that's still even after
thousands of years is still able to
provide support but this is the polar
opposite of what you felt in the
fountain room when you first entered
into the wandering this is the absolute
opposite it's not bad okay so you love
it
is that why we're in this holy place we
both know what that sounds normally Amy
this is role-playing is I mean I kneel
down next to this this symbol on the
ground the spell of binding and I've
like brushed off some of this dust from
it I don't know what it is meditating on
it Wow Jen Hodges is in the corner I
guess by dreams a lot yeah it's a lot
right so you can see it's a very simple
rendering a very simple drawing yeah but
it looks as though it is a like a sharp
crystal in shape that has been that they
show very clearly as being big
in the ground at an angle okay and then
the rest of their circle and runes of
binding exist around this crude drawing
that they've made in the center
what is the crude drawing exactly it
looks as though it's all sharp angles up
here but it's all sharp angles that have
been driven down into the curve of a
hill okay we got pink ocean okay yeah no
pink ocean is it symmetrical just case
no and where is this in relation to the
rest they're just right in the center
hope you can see that priestesses around
it mmm does it look like there they were
driven in or popping out can we tell
what's in it in the in the Sigma the the
stuff in the hill the point it looks it
looks it's not clear from the image okay
it's just it's clear what they were
interacting with what information that
they had has been ensconced in this
drawing do I know that's a genius hmm
bet the Druids we step in that that they
pin the sharp line as I try to finish
shortly yeah that is an alternative
history proffered by the contact with no
yeah no I don't think I don't know if I
think I showed that deal no yeah there
was I would say there's many things from
that meeting you have not shared yeah I
always shared that I had it I did share
that I had with you yeah so I will go in
confidence to you yeah and say that it's
from my friend Kyle showed that piece of
this like I was told that this was a
part of what this or this ritual was
that they were trying to that they
referred to it as a shard link that's
right something else they don't call it
a wandering kept right they think that
that is unnecessary poetry yeah and they
grew it grew up body for itself after
they imprisoned it is
my question to this ok ok so the
question that that I had written down
this is out character obviously is that
did we free it and who destroyed the
joys uh-huh
these are great questions do I have do I
have have I have I had a scribble in my
ledger anything you have had that you've
had the only scribble you have in your
ledger is the piece of information that
the secretary anof 'red you called the
wandering colors and he called you the
wandering Krypton diet gotcha yeah so
you haven't shared anything that the
secretary in has written yeah so I was
thinking now walnut would probably pull
out her ledger and be like back story I
just said so I do have some extra
information that now I'm hearing that
maybe there's other interpretations of
what's going on and I think the part
that she would want to want to share is
that of a size yeah I said reports of a
mouth as we would generally think of it
as a conduit for nourishment are largely
apocryphal
well I don't know that way apocryphal
walnut doesn't know that word which may
relate to the wandering crypt rising maw
wide no effort is made by the creature
to secure nourishment as we understand
it how then is such a massive creature
maintained one key maybe in the songs of
the desert valley and then it says the
psalm brush a traveling folk who dwell
in the Sun bar hills have a walking him
they call how do you want to pronounce
that gelateria della teri it it's so not
a delete riot no that's that's my event
oh yeah one that describes a punishment
reserved and speak well this is the part
that I think is important when the hills
dance huh bring the ones in Chains those
behind the wagon ha take them to the
summer cave where we trade Devils for
angels and then it talks about
translation and the Secretariat is
clearly one of the past a lot of
information on but the part that I think
is that concerns me is that it talks
about trading people for other versions
right like bad for good and then also
about nourishment and it just seems that
there's just a lot
there's just a general theme about
eating now that is concerning have you
ever talked to us by here no God says
poison I think so I've given enough
about like so following these were
trying I'll synthesize what who knows
what yeah but like after we returned
from that situation on the gate
I would have shared that I think I would
have shared that info okay then we went
regarding that we went in exact saw it
may Lilith trap I saw my god trapped in
some warm right in the very first time
and you yeah I mean you saw the form of
it yeah we were adjacent to their very
first conversation well and then indeed
in this dunya lating sharpness that
existed in the cracks between when you
were in the forest a test market yeah
yeah and I think that I don't think it's
a secret that I'm not a big fan of the
meat and mouths that's not my god
somehow I made an agreement with this
right now my god yeah oh my god I can
see this bumper sticker on the cart yeah
he saw yeah that that it's holding the
earth hostage for some reason or is able
to which I think is because the ER wants
to be held hostage because these are the
all-powerful one why would he be able to
be taken off there's the same all they
know is that ruling it out like that's
right I told you that and they wouldn't
get trapped cuz he was too weak unless
weakness and strength are on an axis
that we don't underst
there may be some mothers hey what are
you guys done I think no matter what
we're gonna have to go deeper into this
this crypt right I think we should be
very very wary because we know from omen
that the stronger you get the worse it
gets
that's right and we are much stronger
than when we first stepped down here
that's true um but if we don't know
these five symbols then how can we
proceed further into the crib yeah is
there another was another entrance I
thought we were oh yeah there's no this
the gates just it's what it always
justiça there are other I'm assuming
this place to another
we've seen another bus so we need to go
find it different mouth I think cross a
different cross so I'm thinking about
the deleterious poem the walkers and
chains behind the cart and trading
devils for angels prisoners yeah do you
remember what we learned about the last
stone spiritual about feeding the quarry
yeah that cake yeah did it was just
miners who got trapped in there right is
that the story yeah it was angel food
cake anybody know yeah well I was
thinking if your prisoners trading
devils for angels means like sacrificing
prisoners to this monster in the quarry
no I love Kate Welch not now Rosie
beasting how my brain is getting this is
so incredibly wrong or I am delighted by
the entire process okay then needs I'm
wrong but no I'm having fun being wrong
so that's my theory is that there were
prisoners they sacrificed them for
something and that's what the songs are
about and if we can find out where they
would sacrifice those prisoners then we
might find a mouse that we can use back
to the quarry right that's but we were
coming there and there was nothing to be
found so maybe that's not the right
place hmm
we have something that we have to do
here though whether it's you know from
me omen made us to come down here can't
you figure it out like we still need to
do that this particular gate I mean we
can officer it out it's not part of the
same organism like that's that's very
useful but it's not summer so we could
see another place to go I'm with I'm
with walnut I do yes tell us what the
boat is no weather we're gonna keep
going down here or leave okay
yeah I won't go in there yeah oh yes oh
yeah back to the cornea there's no other
option right yeah Karen there's there's
this room exactly right and there's this
back gate but you'll recall that as the
NEMA's here drove down there were not
one but two bursts of soil oh yeah we
went left that's right yeah yeah the
only reason is decision just left which
is just because the last part of them
yeah no no it isn't even about that is
there no no no I just wanted to make
sure that you got your plane okay what
just sounds like was a near thing in it
it was near and I did make it almost so
you should try uh maybe go to the other
room yeah so we climbed back out yeah
and then go to the other hole I guess
and say we're out and now we're just
going back in again can't take a short
rest
what kind of statues that are gonna have
in here I'm a big fan let me try to find
so as you pass through you walk by your
new daughter another substantial red
larch beyond I mean beyond the genus
this is an exemplar of this form and you
can see around in this field sort of
twinkling in the moonlight
you can see little shoots even now only
having been planted an hour or so ago
you can see little shoots out as far as
you can see here starting to sort of
plow their way through the frosty soil
but as you as you you sort of cross that
by section you can see if there is
another entrance down kick down that
door like I'm here for that other
ambulance yeah we're dead
no so as you as you make your way down
this other staircase the staircase
itself is very similar to the last one
but the room here is the self same room
as near as you can tell that you went
into at the very beginning
yes bedroom fountain then get off indeed
I have a drawing of it right here
exactly so there is there is a there is
indeed a fountain in the middle and you
can recall leaving this room as quickly
as you could yes as acid began to sort
of over match the pool yeah and then it
began this the stairs and so forth began
to salivate making escape difficult as I
recall dinar had to basically pound his
way out of the again yeah it's a theme
yeah is the gate still here
the gate is still here how am I send
this it requires three symbols to say
well gate this is the gate this is the
gate that you recall although if this
gate is very similar to the one that you
saw below the lighthouse right huh
same same symbol then now that was it
Pete it appears to be that of the same
manufacturer okay but but as I said you
know before you had a single symbol that
you could incorporate into it it's sort
of complex diagram oh that's right okay
so what I would like to do now you have
many symbols yeah what I would like to
do is
I I told Rosie sure put your hand on
that necklace I've never let it go and I
want to is there asset in the know this
this room is much as you saw it
initially it appears to revert to an
attractive state and remind me what was
the was the action that that led to the
acid release you an attempt to enter the
Blackgate without the requisite symbols
okay okay we have three now yeah so uh
let's let's refresh ourselves of that I
have three now should I attempt or
should we maybe take a look at the other
very rational it's a breath of fresh air
you have you around these gates yeah
guys horrible memories of this when we
almost all died and so do i so I'm
lingering by the entrance legs it
halfway up the stairs just like things
go south it won't be a TPK
I'll throw crumbs in the quarry for all
three years if we go like it so if I
adventurer forward now that I have the
requisite number one will you all come
with me too
would you prefer that we check out the
other entrance
the third one up above first was that
you okay so this is the only other left
and right really to the left wicks or
right Twix yeah you stop you're a seed
everyone why are so you offer us the
choice yeah I really come with you in
saying like yeah was is this the is this
to play because there's no other there's
no other does a common place there's no
point entrant act let's rinse and exit
in this room oh it's just the game well
this this is as near as you can tell it
is identical to your very first
experience
um intersecting with the wandering crypt
hmm I look directly at Walnut hmm
cuz I'm waiting for your answer to his
question oh I said I've got on my ledger
and I go oh I'll follow you in again
absolutely uh I go you know you have
unfinished business with your God we
dealt with mine last time but I want to
write in my ledger
you ain't communicate I want you to say
we're in the crypt about to enter gate I
look at you little wimp gate 3 is the
lamp game five is the big game hey big
boy gate big big tough boy you turn that
gate on and then I'll come down the rest
of these stairs turn the gate on yeah
you want to see it well is how you're
working okay I wanna make sure you're
gonna be a theater spider find out yeah
I'm not sure either or acid spider is
heaven for Bentley sorry yeah alright so
I will clutch my this new necklace of
the three symbols yeah I'll go ahead and
actually just draw it off wrap it around
my hand
you got the three here yeah you're on
the gold yeah and I begin to approach
the the black gate with it expecting the
focus the foci to start to rotate then
twist and find other facets yeah exactly
once did um so can I get a perception
role from you Rosie you sing good thing
14 okay cool
so as you well Blanc Blanc you know my
numbers are better so when you as you
are as you are approaching with this
with this cluster of symbols you can see
them sort of they're almost like moving
in a breeze they make a sound like
marimbas almost just very very low like
it's almost it's almost just pure
vibration and you just know it's a it's
a it's a note that's so low it's just a
feeling
mm-hmm and as you get close to this you
can see these symbols
fill in and they sort of like shift
between other symbols you don't
recognize and then resolve one by one
into the symbols that you have so the
symbol of male a--the the symbol of your
earth and then a third symbol that
doesn't doesn't have a isn't
identifiable to you but you know must it
must identify some other consumed
divinity oh we're talking about that
sideways about we're talking about yeah
we're talking about yeah the sigil of
Obama and then you see so you see them
you see them fill in and then it's
almost like the center of it exists in
the same plane as a compass where I sort
of floats inside the rest of the gate
and then once it sort of finds whatever
mystic access it's designed to discover
you can see those pieces slide out into
the gate and then you see the gate
itself move farther back into the stone
around it hmm and now it goes just
completely down this isn't even a
conscious thing but rosie has stepped in
front of walnut it means it doesn't mean
like you're you're way bigger and very
strong and capable and a bear really in
some some cases the floors of the arm or
the staff it's both it's it's her whole
body is now she's like up - up - walnuts
knees exactly as you can
EPIK terrified not yet brave very scared
you can hear it behind you because these
these staircases as you recall there's
multiple staircases that go down into
these chambers right and you can tell
that these staircases have begun to
salivate there's nothing there's no
you're not being cast out there's no
acid rising there's just something
delicious about pray that willingly
enters the mouth
that's what I'm talking about exactly
what I said I look at I go okay this
shit wet is never spit that's right it
was it was all moist when he came down
his first time it escapes bet my life on
it yeah yeah my bottom dollar so you can
see that I'm I'm so like I'm so
disgusted with disappointment oh yeah it
is just common it's so trivial it's it's
this is the same it doesn't matter that
this is a crypt that does this it's like
watching a earthworm eat it's like who
gives a shit
mmm I'm hungry mmm mmm I ate it I'm
gonna pump it out just like animals do
there's nothing worth worshipping here
this is garbo a furious you say what's
out loud yeah yeah you can you can
accept that
yeah cuz he's yelling it into the metal
hole yeah yeah exactly an so he's sort
of he's sort of mumbling and hissing
directly into this into this tunnel and
at regular intervals there is a breeze
would have would be more sustained and
be more consistent but there's a linear
mm-hmm there's a sort of linear
curvature to the air as it comes out
it's cold damp air and then as it passes
you you can also feel it come back right
it's breathing oh cool that other
chamber was a lot better yeah I know I
turn a supreme chamber yeah I'm rolling
my eyes I say oh breathing another
cornerstone of the unknowable
of the infinite oh yeah yeah laundry
crib and a breathing hole okay I write
the gate is open it's like some
creepypasta shit you're saying this as
yeah before you have finished writing
the gate is open you see below it says I
will notify omen drawn I go tell them I
said sorry that was my last joke now
let's get serious
Darkwing Duck yeah there's nothing in
the rules that says dog can play makes
ball very say as we're feeling this
breathing happening yeah Rosie says just
to walnut very customary thank you very
lucky I love you I know let's do this
okay I want to coax Denard over I know
so we are like halfway out gallon boy
it's just like kind of he's like you're
firing above the step so you kind of
have to like lean and look out and if
skin I mean it's just like all your hand
holes are getting more and more gross
and I take care to discuss number like
the same kind of disgust I feel like
yeah right God yeah we're lucky but just
watch it procreate no it's stupid I
agree it's not fun I
it's gross did I hate a drink do you
want to sit here insulting it all day
you want to go through your gauge no I'm
gonna go get indigestion are you all
like lined up behind me that yeah I just
tied us all together with the rope which
you missed new pants and I ain't also
those on the podcast I lashed everyone
together grandmas rope you I saw
something
right now I will just get over yeah okay
smart I'm gonna fix the error in my mind
and I'm also going to cast dancing
lights in the form of the ER before me
Wow Wow like a like a the prow of a ship
nice the only should I worship with the
earth I'm just coming oh yeah like a
Care Bear like you can throw right here
no I draw that symbol in the air
anything harder in front of us like a
lantern
ideally yeah yeah as much as well as
much as the deal you want to exhale do
you want to fix it to a position near
lagari I got a suit just like in front o
ahead I mean if it helps I mean either
way I'm controlling it mentally but if
it helps me to give it a saying like you
know you you know be the thinner you
want to see in the world you know that's
for sure oh yeah I have an idea get you
go ahead please I placed this I draw the
the earth in the air a little bit behind
Locati
and through those facets Oh projected so
there are symbols that you did not draw
oh that orbit there and they're there
they're purely fundamental concepts
simple it is just simple mathematical
expressions moving up into the algebraic
little little floating fractals yeah
mathematics simple well yeah give it
time but divided that's not the old
school division like a sedan yeah
it's different variations on the curves
of the ER itself yeah different
perspectives extrusions these like
causalities of this who knows symbol who
knows more of its truth being revealed
yeah I'm ready to go in his mouth there
isn't a dialogue with itself about
certainties if you if you had if you
were going to anthropomorphize the
concept you would think it would be
something like comfort we didn't week
and we never have this table thank God
okay
we never have to stop we can just play
this until we are very very old like it
we can just playing it did you say
palliative man you're talking about that
we're just gonna not air the rest yeah
exactly always gonna be private it's
gonna be my house okay I forge ahead I
start to walk toward her I got the
Cheetos crunchy kind not the puff sink
no thank you thank God right somebody
fuck sorry I didn't sink yeah yeah no
out no you're bringing up the rear
always yeah okay okay meet you
exactly overhead mmm
I'm so pleased whenever somebody
whenever I see somebody link the jiff or
the gif I guess where's it yeah yeah I
guess I guess super cranked like that's
that's Tala Lena shit Oh fully erect
right no angle we're shifting Gordon a
blood anyway so Chris Drago chick
Chris drought enters this so you've
moved from this sort of domed room
through this oculus into a second
chamber and then you can see what looks
like it's almost like a like a gray pink
stone imagine like a imagine marble sort
of shot through with pink quartz okay so
it's so the light from the earth is
subsurface scattered
is glinting down through the stone
itself and as you look down you can see
it's almost like actually speaking in
esophagus you can see that it has the
equivalent of just ridges that project
from the outside from the outer ring of
this cylinder mm and it goes down
farther than you can see how how big
around is a cylinder the cylinder itself
is probably 25 feet and this is a this
is a stone you're not describing like a
hole yeah it's it's a shaft and that it
is ring okay with this sort of
descending threaded viral yeah exactly
so it's not all that it says it's a bead
through it okay that's mr. snow I know
how why does this spiral is it Traverse
the ball absolutely absolutely so coming
coming perhaps you know three and a half
to five feet it's very gated right um
it's pulling out from each of the sides
as it goes down and we can't see the
bottom you can't and is it it's so it's
oriented like we entered the room and
then turning it goes it just starts to
exactly that it goes down and then you
can sort of Traverse this odd you know
organic seeming corkscrew hmm sure I'm
gonna just in case yeah real quick I'm
just gonna grab some my most powerful
spell actually never mind never mind I
don't want to do anything I'm a friend I
go to clap you on the back doing those
classic enhance abilities and I just go
well I hope you're feeling strong in
case you have to drag me back heaviest
of all the metal armor scraping against
the stone do we can we set up any kind
of like safe point here look before you
go down into this shaft is there any way
we can do a recall yes only yes town
scroll yeah yeah yeah
whatever what are we looking at in terms
of how wide is this plant or like what
were five feet he said we can't walk
down we can walk to a weekend but you're
you're I'm having trouble
Clark more would have you more trouble
but you need somebody down there yeah I
get some of them a nun some of them
everywhere yeah this guy's this he's up
stuff up top there's no Clark more shit
on these yeah I'll I'll let him be the
judge get out here you down there quite
okay every every place that the lighter
that her is not present there is a a
profound darkness okay so we're walking
into a mouth no please for young prince
breathing mouth now it's also talk
should we try to talk to this giant pole
yeah or we could can we
I feel like throats don't talk
yeah well you I think I've said enough
that if it was gonna talk to us it would
have talked at this point I imagine
really even if it couldn't hear me like
my my feelings about it our apparent I
think that's a that's a surprise what
are we looking for we're hoping to find
that last symbol or it was the only way
that's all that's all I'm just told us
to come down here and take care of okay
yeah there we go yeah we gotta go down
after I try to I try to offer you a like
the save point stuff right do ya do you
like do you well yeah but like I like if
I interpret your anxiety about it I
would say don't like don't worry we we
have always been in this room you've
always been at the lip of this of this
shaft we've always been at the edge of
this thing and we will continue to
always have been here I do feel better
and I'm so comforted by that idea yeah
we live on the lip of the shaft even
after we're consumed we still have been
here at one point
relax Chris he lived a little loop of
the shaft he couldn't help it he died as
he left
let's go let's go down so lead the way
this March yeah boy the farther it's a
up near the top there's a highly uniform
in its construction it goes like I say
the staircase equivalent that you're
walking down and around ranges between
Oh between a foot and a half right but
the farther you go down there are small
breaks and it between that have to be
traversed nothing nothing sophisticated
there's close calls but you're seasoned
adventures this is you know this is
nothing new for this crew we're one
seasoned adventurers one sec Wow
pachow no but as I said so it gets less
and less uniform and more organic
seaming the way it is it always sort of
reflects you know at some level that
it's this is its body in some way but
it's always sort of performing and
pretending to be dungeon yeah like
there's something about that then it is
attractive it serves some purpose may be
the method it learned exactly but the
farther you're getting down in you're
starting to see deep pox deep will be
fuck you're starting to see Deepak
Chopra excuse there is not I'm relieved
yeah honestly I found my son
no he's not here he doesn't have any
suck he's not here yet tell us the
blueberries are super thanks to you
thanks there are craters ok holes sure
oh boy I'm trying to avoid these
savannas terms don't but there are they
sort of look dug out sort of where the
where multiple veins of this courts are
sort of joined out you can see that it's
sort of dug or mined out it doesn't look
like it's been cored out or was just
malformed know it looks it it has it has
that organic cast there were multiple
things of this material joined together
whenever there's enough of it it looks
like something happens cuz it does it
look like something burst out or that
someone came in and mined it go ahead
and proceed it kind of hurt i'll take
advantage oh yeah you're gonna eat it
that's a twenty-one yeah there's scrapes
around the edge like right around where
it would emerge this is not the sort of
scrape from a tool it's much too fine
hmm all around the edge okay and then
you can see light scrapes against the
surface that travel away from these okay
so something something's hatching out of
these males I let everybody know like
chess for Easter is just exactly casters
there's there's there's gonna be
something waiting for us to spot um yes
so you are traveling down this gullet
for eight hours
Wow we stopped to rest at eight hours
I think stopping to rest is a good idea
okay okay the Queen's sensory track we
sure okay we'll turn around this I could
spin
or should we stuff and you're like wow
man it's easier to walk now drag make
camp
but yeah exactly so so whose and tell me
your watch order I'll take first watch
usually it's a kid through something so
jihad there's long sleepers oh that's
right yeah you guys handle the first two
mere mortals yeah my eighth grown boy I
like it I can do for what this can do
for you guys
Tamia we're gonna love it wait my babies
wallet unrest yeah in the natural world
tiny no walls yeah once you give me a
perception check beat no please oh that
is good that's gonna be a 21 so you hear
a scraping yeah yeah something fine it's
fine I'm going to is it closed
you can discern it appears to be coming
from above and below
oh I'm gonna wait listen I'm gonna wake
anybody up I want to see that sounds
like it when I want to wait for it to
get ladder in the mimic a flat arouse
the troops but I mean if it's just this
thing you know it's an old house it's
the other way yeah exactly
no but I mean if we're gonna fight I'm
not so you hear so that the sounds reach
a crescendo the closer they like the
closer they are getting and it's like I
say it's just you know that it's coming
from both positions but they're both
bouncing around in what is essentially
this pitch black cylinder and then they
stop
I'm gonna wake up they just stop they
just stop this dead stop okay if I wait
like five minutes so they come back up
just is still quiet it's quiet it's a
dead quiet and i've dark version do i
see anything you don't okay well I guess
it's just the noise that it makes
I'm sure fine um I'll keep I would keep
going on my watch I don't agree with
that but okay
you would wake I mean so what walnut
does Gillis it she's not a min/max er we
need a line of what would walnut do
bracelet bracelet rainbow bumper
stickers yeah
can we find a word that means dudes it
starts with W so good should be $4 so
this is actually writing this down what
would walnut wear um head-to-toe
Summerlin summer line so no cable on um
no I think that she is going to maybe
like have her hand on her sword and just
kind of be very alert and I want to say
that she has her hand like near near
cthis like she's like gonna shake him
awake in her hand
yeah she's have her hanna.patterson
refresh me on that that elven trance
like we are able to get our rest but in
that four hours we're also aware of
what's going on around us oh I think it
is that's that's what I recall yeah so I
mean it may be that I'm aware of this
sound but I also just make you're at
your best
oh no right now yeah yeah yeah but I
don't wanna wake up the caster willing
right it's but yeah so I'm not I haven't
stirred either is what I'm trying to say
like it wouldn't be a surprise to me
that we heard something so if we get all
the way through my shift tell me if we
do yes
okay then when I my shifts over I
and then I just put my hand up when I
spoke in your head poking my head yeah
yeah so I don't want to alarm you and I
certainly don't want to alarm the people
that need their sleep there was not one
but several noises scratching seemed
like maybe something as close to us but
they haven't done anything for a few
hours
so anyway I'm gonna take a rest now
well that's it Oh any pound this is one
of the dumbest yeah yes wallets
conscious mind we're out here I know
okay
having heard that the good news I right
now take watch I don't I don't make any
special needs either good here give me
the perception check that I crave don't
romeo for their Catherine's drought go
here we go ready for the for if it's a
four oh man can you imagine me it's so
fur ated okay it's not for so it's gonna
be too forest I think that's a hell no
where's my perception you tell me that's
Chris drought I'm sorry we level then I
own perceived since so it's 13 on
November 2nd in some cultures are 13 is
some it's a very lucky number so that's
true
2000 so sensing should I even
collaborate on the Mayan calendar could
I shouldn't cover your worldview
Thirteen's little 20 ask the non twenty
number it's about as close to 20 is you
have that being 20 it's yeah yeah
exactly
drink responsibly so you are sort of
getting everything set walnut is in her
sort of pharaoh ultimate vampire breast
scenario but many of you
100% and then as I described the lower
you've gotten the more there are sort of
like pox and missing sort of like slats
in this endless corkscrew that goes down
and as you're getting everything set up
you look over and you very plainly see a
massive spider Oh white body
blue blue specks sharp legs and it looks
down over you at the party and puts its
puts the long sharp tips of its legs
over and sort of like it's reading a
menu or something greedily yes with
those eyes yeah and it says you serve
our master what have you brought us
hmm consider this one moment how is it
speaking to me how yeah is it mind a
mustard okay this was bringing the
language I know milky white eyes making
me hungry yeah
hungry for milk that's man you eat these
three so I say not in a whisper but out
loud was louder than I normally would
indeed we do serve the same master I'm
trying to wake y'all up yeah does it
work dinars just dead to the world yeah
yeah I brought you a dragon now we may
continue our passage okay for what
exactly I'd love to see perception rolls
I just want to see how it works I know I
just wanna see well I just wanna see how
the scene is planning right the phones
just get folded in ready another fist
yeah and then Rosie you're up exactly so
just open your eyes and you're ready for
work right and then and then you could
you can sense another one you can just
sense the clack I of the ends of the
legs yeah looking down there's like a
cord of saliva that comes down and just
pulls along the side of your face mm-hmm
we do serve the same master but this
feast is mine
I must preserve my strength that I may
continue you understand
oh it is it is the way of all who serve
Him you you you get the sense that it
has done something with its body that
denotes some kind of respect it's almost
like a salute like it lowers its head
briefly in recognition of something I
think you can write it exactly know yet
exactly only I contain them only I can
write them now this is time for
initiative respect apparently did I wake
up nope oh wow so what for what kind of
above it is that should I go last then
yes okay well I did okay that's a nice
one
that's all right we got about 15 okay
how about you Rosie for
[Applause]
it's perfect / - I like it
okay I know the Gotti is with you now
easy a hundred percent of the time
I need him he is a sharp and dangerous
in addition to all the rest of the other
cool stuff that he offers you for the
primary one being vision all right guys
it yeah yeah to tame them is your cause
I think to train them yeah tell me about
this about Liguria as a staff like as a
weapon of maybe not bludgeoning but can
i pierce a sharp with the base the base
of it is a perfect point of this living
crystal you've seen iterated in all
these forms throughout your adventure a
big wisdom yes 66 yeah damage 66 Locati
damage it's a new type I just made it
there like there's a conversion to
actual damage but the Guardian is like
twelve thousand to one yeah so
absolutely so walnut on grass
you are now seated and then you can see
right over cath wrists robe you can see
that this this torrent of a rapid saliva
she start to he does not react to it in
any way across the world the way you see
no here's ring morning I hear more
dancing yeah my job thanks ah track your
spouse yes no he's got you just in the
boxes right here
those don't wanna cast it I still feel
like you know what will happen you got a
cast
if you can't like us don't cast it on
your friends cast on I want these bugs 5
foot diameter sphere unoccupied space of
my choice so how far above us are them
are there items are the our debates them
no it's a it's up above you perhaps 15
feet perfect so in this space between I
would like to Dave Matthews there
doesn't sad time right uh yeah
I would like to cast flaming sphere at
the hospital
I know that it's hard for me to cast
spells unless I really let it rip and I
wanted you to tell me how look I want to
smell so you're gonna cast this flaming
spear yeah okay for the for the folks at
home why don't you let them know what it
does flaming sphere is a five foot
diameter sphere fire that appears and
unoccupied space in my choice any
creature that ends its turn within five
feet of the sphere let's make a
dexterity saving throw future takes to
d6 fire damage on a failed save or half
as much damage and on as a bonus action
I can move that sphere no Rama in the
staff just don't people move that
spheres exactly it's crazy I want to
hear you right no it's nothing
so yeah I want to put it above us you
know so it's like ten feet above us or
whatever and you just put it in there
and then as always
the flames are cream oh yeah it's very
important creepley I agree the flames
are green emerald fire natural world
whatever yeah so they're not in it but
but when wait if they're brazier within
five feet of it when they end their turn
they make a dexterity sitting throw so I
will just nag you yeah yes their time so
that's it deeply on and then she gets to
her feet I guess gotcha gotcha no as you
are summoning
this or right yeah it's it begins as the
size of a like a grapefruit melon sure
and then you have to work very hard
dutifully diligently to expand it to the
regular size of it and there is a point
at which it reaches its maximum size but
you don't think that you think it wants
to be bigger well I want to pull I know
that there's a place that I'm not
supposed to pull from the place that
makes my magic weird but I feel like I'm
worried that my Magic's not cutting it
without pulling from that corrupted
place so much like a weed whacker just
pull it all right can I get a
Constitution say from you good golly
good golly twelve so it expands to this
green orb and it just rests in the
middle of this spire that goes up for
powers mm-hmm and it shrinks a tiny bit
and then is shot through with violent
and so it bursts higher than the party
up on this other level and it begins to
cast out licking flames on that entire
tier whips love it
air burst yeah well mr. Elvidge yes yeah
it's like laser Zeppelin yeah and
finally confessed you're out trying to
just trying to read up on this on this
new spell yeah you got some some new
products yeah what is it for this is
from your fault line mm-hmm you'll love
it
what's this feast you'll love the
pattern automatic I said night pattern
okay tell us about Thome morning yeah
what about weirdo is your your is your
tummy hungry what about your mind's eye
face what is what I say good go says
encouraging things Hey even the spiders
are like okay I see what you were trying
to do one okay to hear more yeah not
sleeping you still being a good place
this is a this is a 30-foot cube that is
gonna I'm gonna fill it up with that or
glowing brightly and if the creatures
within fail wisdom saving throw than
they are charmed oh really
they're incapacitated and cannot move if
they take damage they won't be roused
from this condition but my stunt of its
concentration for a minute
oh yeah okay they'll be yeah I mean so
they're basically hypnotized yes if they
don't take damage but only for a minute
yeah are we gonna hit next one yeah they
basically I mean we want to leave if it
worked we can essentially do this so
there is this massive flaming orb are we
a six level or what is this massive
flaming orb that's reaching out with
hissing violet flames in all directions
and then here just above it stands this
infinite impenetrable symbol that even
to gaze upon it is to lose your mind so
I look at it all day every day yeah we
don't tough you give it a try rosy bee
stinger yeah so you are at a point on
this sort of stairwell that goes down
and up yeah and you can see fully two
spied arrows
Sandra spied arrows yeah each side okay
those are the ones that you know about
are they at a place where there's like a
Platt
form near them for me too but you can do
you think you can go straight up the the
staircase if you want to okay well I
don't want to and get access to that
Spidey rose I want to teleport behind
the uppermost one oh if I can do that
there's shadow step so bonus action I
can teleport from and into dim light or
darkness within sixty feet it's pretty
dope and then I get advantage on the
next melee attack I'm a newly warms yeah
so you stunned them but I'm going to try
to continue your stun with a whole a
whole devastating pile of shit yeah I
try stuff stuff I want to see it wait no
I wonder one of those classic Rosie
martial arts I need like films 6 D 20s
okay so the first thing I'm going to do
is just a regular melee attack from
behind which has advantage and that's
gonna be 12
that's my yeah that's a 19 mm-hmm and
then my sister regular second melee
attack is going to the 11 in the shitter
okay and then I'm gonna attempt a
stunning strike which for those who have
forgotten it is after him to creature
the melee weapon counting my hands I can
spend a key point to try to stun it as
to succeed on a con save or be stunned
until the end of my next turn so I'm
gonna try to continue your stunt mmm oh
I guess you just have to roll up con
save anything there yeah it does not
make it okay so it is stunned and then
I'm gonna do two more unarmed attacks
which is gonna be at nothing and 23 and
of something okay so that's two
successful attacks both of which are d8
great Sanderson understand so the damage
for the staff will be a six and then
it's damaged for my hands will be 12 YUM
yeah more and out for the staff okay and
it's stunned until the end of my next
turn okay so
right that's a premium that's a premium
staff experience muck stuff yes or yes
we had a splatter at full health but
stunned ah
and then we haven't earth trying rather
yeah yeah then yours which is stun guns
and damage chest yeah and you guys can
all attack mine freely operations
incredible so you beat the shit out of
this thing Goodman it could have been
there keepin more damage yeah and you
guys didn't know I could do all the
stuffings you're really a mess yeah you
think it's the best you have a role to
save versus like how cool Rosa you fall
down with the talents of all right now
popular everyone exploit a tude that are
up at the top stunned
once done they took damage didn't get
stunned again yeah yeah by you I'm just
pretty sweet it's like wherever it you
would hit like the solar plexus of a
spider yeah that's what you hit I guess
yeah like it's most tender now walnut
your turn right evil yeah exactly do I
was just gonna say this evil orb is
gonna start flipping out on them at the
end of this turn at the end of their
turn that's fair anything exactly now
two spiders crawl out and up from the
rung below and go wild on dinar what's
in it no because he's asleep
and he is delicious Papa wait come on
you don't you don't yo you don't get
palp Don that one yeah you don't get
popped on that one thank you there's an
air pump
oh no yeah that's a yeah you get double
pumped on this next one is that wah-wah
you know it's it's it's womp adjacent
let's say that okay that's my voice now
can you roll me a constitution saving
throw my friend so rosy one and add that
see HP yeah I mean one thing the time
I'm doing a saving throw
d well I have it over a protection there
chief chief I get a bonus equal to my
charisma or her so plus three so am i
doing a constitution you are so do we
get the Constitution in the Christmas oh
yeah that's him so +5 yeah oh my god so
a shooter to a for fun well that's not
good at it and that was role-playing
take 14 book weighs 14 points you should
have saved saved stay well give him safe
steam look obviously no you also so you
are awake up oh well that's good you
wake up I know but I was saying that you
wake up and there are two spiders yeah
like really big spiders in my turn no I
can't no so at the end of their turn
Jax saving fears it won't surprise you
to learn that spiders are pretty decks
yeah I know but just do it
actually I thought that would happen
thank you fuck that one up too alright
more of these things now yeah I guess so
so what are we talking about there well
I'm I get to roll it it's 2d six fire
damage yeah each so five for one and you
know what you got to pick dealer's
choice
and then ten for another one chase
that's nice and they smell like barbecue
okay miss them tube so these are the
ones that so it's reaching out and it is
actively getting these dudes oh yeah or
are you just gonna these are safe these
are safe and how they there they stay
ship the bed on the side okay so five a
three for one what is that a mate I'm
not good at it that's a seven seven
thank you hey girl that's 100 that's a
lot of fear dance at 43 yeah okay so the
one that the one that you do you use
nuts on it yeah and then it's just sort
of like vibrating there in the dark yeah
gazing upon this symbol and then you can
just see this
sort of
slowly revolving malevolent fireball
lashes out like the crack of a whip it
just just right right across the the
jowl region so this this spider that was
in front of you is in the absolute worst
shape of its life der Blitzen
you are now awake her a little note that
order of protection everyone within ten
feet gets that as well automatically
bonus on saves yeah my charisma have
finer modifier on saint-mande yeah save
if you're within somebody if you're
within ten feet being kissable distance
yeah you get plus three you know where I
am II yeah you'll always be in the range
all right so I'm awake yay yeah we went
downstairs then aren't even said hope
does that asset hope there's not spiders
little background info on him afraid of
spiders in history I was having see
nightmares about no wakes up see spiders
freaks out did I just immediately grabs
the story they have favor autonomy he
was and just thinks afraid of them okay
this is a phobia sterile ER you like
actually frightened by them like do you
know no it was like freaking out having
spider night terrors yeah yeah yeah so
they're there they have they have know
that you have gotten up and gotten ahold
of toothbrush he's sort of like
withdrawn and scared up on their little
legs
no he's just see the spider grab this
sorting just wakes up screaming good
well let's see it do we have to pause
should I roll it will do your turn
no cause it yeah yeah yeah right never
see it don't slow on my stuff three I
feel bad
I'll just go regular plant just I'm
saying I know I know I did all right
don't close to me is there the one
that's hurt the most
I kinda wanna go after that guy want you
do one of them one of them took a pretty
brutal I'm gonna go for the warning
close to death we I mean you got you can
see when you can see one that is
scorched all right like it's the white
bulbous abdomen
now it has a pronounced scorch advantage
for the biter a station of age so yeah
yeah that's a 10
oh sorry I forgot to declare if I'm
gonna do a great weapon which I am so
I'll just keep that as a it's then
becomes a 10 plus just plus to 12 or a
there you got it man womp womp womp
alright so much to D 6 plus 3 plus 10
plus I'll smite him oh yeah I'm gonna
die I hate spiders 5 1 I get to rear old
one keep forgetting to do that and so
hey Cass 14:24 oh and I'll smite him for
a smite certainly 3d8 no regular divine
smite just tack it on so I'll do a 3d
ages plane I don't have to roll fancy no
it's one no it's just attacking on extra
damage it's all a cart yes so it's
basically like I hate him I connected
and I just juice that sword for an extra
pop at the end great six Jesus bad 40
right that's one of you two attacks
that's one of my three attacks I'm
assuming he died it's very curious you
come up below
holy shit underneath you flip it back up
and out into the empty space in this
column and it passes through the
fireball and emerges on the other side
of mist alright so next attack denied
let's know if you kill a guy I get an
extra attack and then I get mice and
then still part of the attack on the
first attack then I get a second attack
level see when our blitz aim is bad news
name is the first stay asleep appear
yeah yours is hosed yeah you you take
care of those guys we got the weak one
alright but you've got the full health
almost down go to whoever's next
yeah the other one that was cavorting on
top of you right here in ready to go
alright
Dingles yeah that's another good I
forgot to take advantage hold your thing
in this aiming yeah all right 18 so
that's a 20 oh yeah it's real good
there's no question I see it blue eight
two nine ten eleven twenty one I'll
smite again oh my god I think I can do
that again season two of them I think
some paladin's right now right well get
some of this what did you drop 28 yes
Jesus Christ he's dead
oh my god yeah he's absolutely dead in
fairness so and so yeah walnuts so as
SCIC comes through this next one what I
get sprayed with spider goo no that's a
good job with you sir oh no no no no joy
so they do the witness thing is the
upward strike flies out shrieks this one
right here you just come down straight
through the middle and it just the
entire front of the spider that spider
face if you will yeah just splits in
half and the heavy abdomen just drops
down droops over the back and falls down
you see along the blade you see the face
of a dragon flashing in the side of the
blade you can see a dragon has like
joined him in this fight failing my rage
exactly so you have me - so you have one
more attack yeah okay you should use
this so we can go to brick alright who's
closest so I'll take advantage as this I
see there's one there's one that's over
you I mean turning him getting him down
might be difficult I have a I have extra
little weapons on me I haven't really
used a Shaolin I have a dagger a war
pick and a whip I could whip a war pick
at him from Hibbing
yeah I have a Whipple war pick a great
sword and a dagger as my gear I just
always use the story back alright I'll
whip them but see this isn't like my
great weapon so I always use my grave up
in a binge
I'll use it vanish because it's fine
weapon hmm yeah enjoy it just keep it
rolling
maybe you'll get one no 15 18 plus 6 so
24 so yeah the Planum 1d four plus three
slashing okay the mess no but you can
yank em down tickle it's just a little
tickle yeah well no you ain't come down
yeah yeah this is the foreplay to size
plus 3 so 5 so 5 ok / and then you put
the sword behind you and then from the
belt the whip cracks up on the top of it
you can see the tip the whips sharp tip
plays along the eye cluster at the top
and it withdraws itself is a whip mainly
weapon yeah I guess I could divine
smiles snap at the end she's burning all
my spell slots on these divine spines
but it is funny yeah I'll do a level two
so it's wish I could do some damage to
the earth and a four so tense one of
your hips is like nice over your tongue
exactly so then you bring the weight
back one quick pull wrap it back up
right on the belt and then post shit and
I stretch I'm like 60 feet up you hear
tiny shadow counsel me earlier space you
it is time for our commercial break
thank you so much for spending your
Thursday with us we'll be right back
hello i'm jennifer cail Arkham's and
mrs. Casey teams hey so when last we saw
our heroes we had a chance to witness
the power of this fully armed and
operational battle dragon board
raid it was killer birch is dead it was
grotesque yeah it was it was I can work
in the commercial um could we get back
up to the top of the initiative cycle
with walnut dawn grass we
so what do I see I see one crow second
boy yeah you see one gross looking boy
across the way who's in a pretty savage
state just sort of like shakily trying
to keep itself up on the tips of its
legs and then you know that there is
another one above you
well the one that without that's one
that Rosie is worth right
I know Rosie is with the one that's
opposite yeah yeah
okay she's fucking up pretty good I'm
gonna use my move to just like push that
sphere i ramming into that creature
creature just know just occupy its space
yes Spirit Bomb yes and it says it must
make a saving throw against the spheres
damage so that means like I do to d6
that rolls like if you move it directly
into its space yeah yeah okay go ahead
cool question is does this better want
to make a saving throw or is it just
like I'm checking out I could have
casted that three and I would have
gotten another d6 that's juicy stupid
keep that in mind for the future yeah
okay
I just big deals of damage directly to
the creature or is there a save involved
no this is the save against the damage
okay very very good safe delicious does
he take this oh yeah he takes half
damage so forth so forth okay and it
stops there that's the one that's up top
yeah yeah it also sheds bright light oh
yeah it's definitely they don't if
they're you know so they don't like
light creatures if they're all white
because they're you know yeah I think a
little keep dwelling spiders that's
right maybe they don't like it my dear
you think about me fuck them up I go and
stay out good first rope I liked it
well yeah what's the scene that one's
cooked yeah that was yeah that one is
that one is currently being broiled yeah
it's locking in the juices and then
obviously just opposite you can see you
can see the tip of the staff of the
master
poking up from behind this great abot
the destroyed one yeah yeah and it's
still son yeah it's goofed
it's goofy dandy uh hit my gosh I'm
gonna do something that I don't usually
do and that's not that exciting so take
it easy
roll roll well Wow yeah I'm gonna do
damage actually they're amazing be seen
I'm gonna use a canned trip that we once
thought would be good for this character
who turned out not to be vicious mockery
yeah oh and remind me oh that's a versus
that's wisdom save right okay do he make
it do I bother to roll well here oh
there is this right he make it okay then
there's no point it will get it'll make
him take disadvantage and a little tiny
damage okay yeah Oh Jake Jake you're sad
make them a little bit sad yeah okay the
goal you know how you're mocking yeah
exactly
yeah keeping my knees don't land you
know what I saw what I want to say is
like it would be like you're my meal
tonight but instead I say like my meals
ruined cuz they're gone this players are
gone you thought you'd good next in the
order it's not me anyone who Rosie go
it's like it's like a newborn gazelle
it's just like try and do this and it's
like you feel like you find a part of
your mind that has sufficient
metacognition to make you feel like an
asshole like you are like yelling and
trying to be mean
to it yeah I take this answer exactly
like you're the one is you yeah I know
it feels bad
you know you need this are you this I'm
sorry baby actually Rosa fir'd KB
stinger yeah yeah um so this this uh
spider in front of me is looking rough
right okay okay so then I'm just gonna
keep giving it the sauce ah
Jamelia attacks in an armed attack which
will be
a 20 and yeah I will guys I promise a
discord I'd keep my 1 so that's an 8 and
then an 18 okay two hits
dish it up okay okay so no one is a
quarter staff attack and one is a kick
quarter staff is a seven and the kick is
an eight oh this is kick ass so tell me
how it tell me how it works okay um so I
took two swings at it and I was going
for that that's a go abdomen I like to
think that it's only got like two
unbroken legs left so I smush it in the
abdomen with my quarter staff and it
goes and then I take a leg I like sweep
the leg under both of its two remaining
helps yeah and then try to kick it off
the edge well yeah that is that is
exactly what happens being these these
all these all connect damage is
sufficient for the kill but then this
it's destabilized and then you just kick
it yeah
straight off yeah then it just it it
takes a second for it to peel fully over
the edge and then it falls but you do
not hear it land oh boy um I hate it
the midair and I use your line I go and
stay out
the creature takes its turn okay what's
it want to do pass through the fire you
cannot see what happens it's your turn
walnut dunker I push the fire higher and
I can push it up to thirty feet do I get
it you just keep pushing it further up
oh wait yeah I want to pull it down
towards us the fighter went no the
spider keeps going up - spider was about
yeah this the spider was like right on
the rung above you yes and is it fleeing
upward away from us who knows you can't
see it yeah I mean my face oh you're
just gonna keep pushing this eldritch
wrecking ball higher up for its licking
flames to scour the rest of it
yeah yeah it's an incredible sight you
see the you see this or pass through the
earth there's a moment where the symbol
of the earth exists sort of completely
ensconced by this fire cast everywhere
and then it goes up and you can see
these amethyst tendrils just reaching
out and just scooping out anything
that's that exists out on the stairwell
I think of that and then I think that
that's actually it for that spell yeah
if I weren't already totally all aware
that your magic really right now I think
we'd know it for sure after all this
yeah so that was my bar that kinda cool
so much for my actual action I'm so rosy
shadow step down to the rope so I'm
gonna measure like the rope Oh fell so I
want to it's still tied to dinner at the
end I'm gonna have myself tied to the
other end and I want to jump over the
edge and see if there's anything below
oh my god attack something hiding down
there how much rope do you have enough
to hang yourself no I have like a
hundred feet of this thing okay a
hundred feet it's good swing yourself
down yeah you don't see anything down in
that lower rung you're looking around
you trying to catch a couple stacks of
it no your dinars back break yeah you
don't say anything you just do it and
like I say hold on big guy
I jump off no I'm not hungry Rosie
beasting me already again okay and there
is a spider above us that I cannot see
dad area well there is there could be
okay and I also I assume that because of
this ball of flame there's no dim light
for me to teleport into to use my
shadows it is it is very very bright
okay
as you move farther
this okay um well I don't know if I want
to go up there by myself but yeah I
don't think I do
I think that I will rejoin my fellows
especially cuz I just thought you'd jump
yeah yeah I don't I'm swearing because I
didn't see anything I thought it is so
quick yeah it was cool so you're gonna
be a gonna come down you're gonna come
down to where dinar is yeah okay yeah
sounds good so walnuts describe to me
how your you are you like just hanging
didn't I get the go you go after yeah so
after the thing he's asking cuz it's the
monsters turn and I did it yeah I goof
I'm trying to picture no so I did a bed
so you're something so are you just
really like free climbing like you're
just in the road like like it was around
her waist like she was like repelling
okay there we go
so so it's so easy you beautiful you
brought yourself in and now you're on
the stable ground sure okay I mean if
it's the next rung then yeah I would
exactly I started make sure I don't know
if you were suspended or currently not
dangling in the middle oh well that
would be great no I also think that I
would have chopped off yeah exactly
exactly then he goes and then I go yeah
so these climbers so you can you get
down there you you land you're looking
around you don't see any targets you
sort of cast your eye around the the
entire circumference of this cylinder
and then as you turn back around to the
original point the spider is there in
fact you see it appears to crawl out
from nothing and then as soon as as soon
as you see it it leaps bodily onto you
dang it I swear a ladder an altar attic
18 with your bow bullet what is it what
is this we're mean like translated into
it common oh oh translated in that
comment it means like oh oh oh it means
a like nothing grows and your mother
soilless yeah
do can you imagine how our dealership
man is not fertile exactly your garden
even if garden bring too many meatballs
so 10 points and then I need a dommage
points five points and then I need a
constitution save from you and I am not
within 10 feet anymore
oops you do presume - ah oh
17 oh pretty good alright so now you
take half damage how are you Wow oh shit
what'd you say to me I did not do it I
took 12 points but this spider did I'm
not worried about it
what are you at now so 29 these the
black things find find some entryway
into your gambeson sure they just need
to get all the way in and you can feel
it going through but you're able to push
it off yeah exactly bull it's the same
it's the same dinar blitz in you hear
you hear walnut shriek from the from the
level below exactly this so how far down
is the roof there she is just one level
down so she's about 15 feet maybe below
that's better
that range for that help yeah 11 feet 10
point 5 years
alright well I guess he's shaking off
the wild eyed fury yeah confusion just
still spiraling down so I could either
walk down yes exactly any place we
wouldn't be yeah I mean you could you
could pull her up from there or I could
run down to that level but then you'd be
one more level down I guess it's
probably not smart to fight while you're
tied to me like too much so I'll let you
finish her up there's skin
oh you should get by you get Bennigan's
yeah if I wake you up
you do yes you honestly well here don't
look at it it does seem like what dinner
with you if you do it well I I didn't
realize it would initiate another attack
well then I'm gonna go down there then
yeah go down there I'm gonna run down
there I'm gonna say I'm gonna kill you
like I killed your friends I hope one of
those was related to you as I'm covered
in blood
crazy fight don't mess with my sleep has
smearing their blood on my face ah as I
go down you're just the best part you're
running down it's like as soon as you
sort of come around you can see it over
there the whole time you just look
fucking talking to you oh you're coming
or and stay right there you piece of
shit I'll be over there in a minute you
could and you're gonna get it you could
really talk to him oh yeah no way one
the half dead spider so so I'm gonna
murder this thing so tell me how it goes
I've run over that I stab shove it let's
see it I do this this I do it that
happens this is the last one right or
the other one retreated up what are you
gonna come through a fireball yeah it's
the last of our multi so far but they
apparently are is it so uh yeah
sir just keep running past if we're all
tied to me say is there xq4 ready no all
right I'm just gonna go run there and
I'm just gonna run right up in his face
toothbrush and all advantage mm-hmm and
great weapon mastery good good thing
your ticket what are the five Wow twelve
twelve mrs. angry those two angry Xena's
nut get mall I gets two attacks though
miss on the first tak yeah alright well
now I'll just go regular boy style
you're there boys that's a fourteen I
get plus tan let's go 1414 is good oh is
it good take that spider to d6 + 3 7 10
and I will smite evil - Dead
[Laughter]
so you use basically a lateral slice
straight through the lower half of the
front four legs it just can Falls
forward and then skitters its way off
and falls down into the hole that is it
for these friendly spiders oh okay yeah
you're just like banging into the side
of the walls down there well I'm like
freaking out how far are you down 50
feet well no no I mean in terms of those
15 feet Oh 29 out of 46 and I can shape
and then get all those HP back I'm 33 I
do not want to heal myself no one bit oh
yeah 33 fine yeah it was a good point
yeah so right you are now in this tunnel
you hear no more skitters good mmm I go
I'm good hmm
help me you know I'm like really nicely
all I know is killed karma her magic is
all busted she can't heal herself she's
at 29 she's like for less than me dinar
look through I know I'm like at least a
twenty three or twenty nine I'm a 33
I don't fiddle fine this is fine I
couldn't help you when you were needed
mimosa should we rest on the ledge
post-battle all right you just rest and
your hips go into a shirt red shirt HD
yeah
how much do you heal in a short rest I
said in fact well you can you expend
them yeah there's a resource that you
have that's the oh you've got the whip
over there
yeah you oh so you can expend those as a
resource during the short risk without
okay okay that's I and then you other
long wrists you can earn some of them
back mm-hmm Thanks which is why they say
why not a long rest
okay so used a skew of mine for the
folks keep you two at home were you back
up to now uh 39 okay it's a five no take
me to 38 you hear a sickening thud dirty
not oh boy what are you resonates up
from the bottom
oh it took that long I'm going the wrong
way
yes and that's 49 and I've used for as
you say if you guys want to fast-track
this then aren't he and old us I can
test fly oh yeah your flight on that oh
yeah yeah let's do that
you dangle that's like bait I got one
one out of their tummy yeah geez oh
let's just lash everybody didn't iron
yeah that's fly Gary
yeah all right so I'm gonna do this is
like a lot princess bride here I make
everybody a little uh like the like a
seat like a loop for me to sit on yeah
okay tonight you sent it over it's in
our shoulders anybody want a peanut yeah
I do I say would anyone like a peanut I
don't have any I have really gross good
berries I'm sorry I'm going like I like
that you keep having me keep the good
very well I keep making them and I think
something happen you know what I like
them so you so use you summon the strand
right it's thick mmm I put Rosie in the
Bjorn in and I hold my two babies like
safely or yeah with the magaz feed yeah
exactly but you're getting you're sort
of like by that by the end of this
journey you're starting to get you're
starting to swing around and around a
little bit closer you're like and they
put your sword like pushing off of their
steps kicking yeah exactly
it's it's so dark as you get down that
your feet hit the ground it's like when
you're it's like when you're on a plane
that's landing but you're sort of dozing
and all of a sudden it's like okay we
land okay yeah that's a new sensation
for me I guess the ground is real and
it's something like that like the shock
of it against your feet
mm everyone's sort of like drops a foot
[Music]
here we land on this exactly so at the
base of this it's gotten more and more
crystalline the mix between the sort of
gray white granite and the other colors
of stone the mix is shifted radically so
down here the stones are multicolored
and almost jewel like on their surface
they interact in a strange way with
light and there is a great volume of
light just before you spilling through
this arched doorway also is a doorway
okay what do we see you through the door
you'll have to go in there we have to
decouple oh yeah beep um can I do a
perception check on that door yes sure
now the door was kind of I will also
perceive some cherry walnut low as well
hey seventeen yeah okay I mean you can
you can see there is a shape that the
light itself is you know voluminous but
it has but there is a shape in the
middle of it moving
something in there there's something
moving okay I want to do it all right
Hannah check my brilliant Dragonborn
eyes I'm just enjoy it they don't lie
and just enjoy a little roll just for
fun all right gonna be a 20 yeah Hume
you think that this may be related to
the Nemus your Oh at the shape or just
get that sense that the shape we didn't
the magic that's coming off of it
and also your gas as - it's rough it's
rough position based on where you came
in and how far you've gone down do you
think that this may be related to that's
good
oh this the pot indeed okay okay not a
city no yeah yeah there's this what we
you plant it to get us your age I had
okay my daughter yeah let's put let's
proceed yes I like the feel of that
touch the feel of them is your name Azir
brand seed proceed with
love for your label now
so so you enter into I mean what has
been transformed it's really almost just
like an antechamber you can see that it
has that same mimicry but it's hard to
tell I mean it could be the someone went
into the wandering crypt at some point
and our ideas about what a dungeon
should constitute it's hard to it's a
chicken or egg problem right because it
these these shapes in these forms don't
seem to have any mortal purpose you know
they're just expressions of itself so it
deep inside the marble walls are just
shapes curves and and arches there's no
it isn't there's no like a BA relief
like no one took the time to carve
something down here this is just a look
at natural phenomenon it's just that
what constitutes a natural phenomenon
for this thing looks like something
constructed it's like a like a deep
dream yeah yeah using a dog like
cathedrals yeah yeah yeah right so when
you went as you enter in something that
you are aware of this in a way that's
different from the other members of the
party you know looking at it what it
must have been like to see something
like this come down and there's probably
a sense for you to kiss to imagine
because it's glowing bright like with a
natural light of sunlight okay so to
have something like this pierce the roof
of your city and then you can you can
see almost ghostly images of enclave
warriors just spilling out of this light
and so you can imagine what it must have
been like to have an emissary strike
deep in the town but you can see this
thing is bored straight through the roof
of this chamber and it has bored
straight through the floor of this
chamber so the Nana's ear even now it's
bright it's brightly lit but the
mechanism of it has done its work and it
is still twisting and burrowing down on
both sides both the ceiling and the
bottom and you can see that there is
like a occur almost like the the steps
and but wherever it drips from the
ceiling and hits this light just hisses
away it's like have you ever seen like
um like a raindrop from a glove or
something like on top of a hot stove it
just hits the net Azir it hisses away
like that Nana's ear does not tolerate
any part of it and it is from this
chamber you can see in front of you
three doors but you know you know deep
in your heart that no harm could
possibly come to you here hmm like the
Nana's ears is the nose ear has made a
garden of protection and comfort in this
place hmm well I love it I love it I'm
gonna stay here yeah yeah and I I say I
say I say it's okay we're safe here
we're safe down here now I say and I'm
like touching and I'm like oh yeah I can
feel it like way down and I wish found
whatever bones
okay we're both upset yeah thank you for
that yeah sure but so you touch the
nimis ear yeah why not whoops yeah just
roll if you feel safe check yeah yeah I
think that's gonna happen if you look at
safety
what are you married so much need to
take 42 damage no no no
no no you don't take 42 damage but you
know upon touching it you know that the
Warriors of the Enclave could travel
through it oh I was gonna ask that like
one who is this Hollow you know that the
Warriors are the Enclave because you had
that vision of them emerging from it and
attacking you know that this siege
engine like a like a Trojan horse or
something it's other purpose is to act
as a conduit for gleaming warriors of
the surface so as I touched it I think I
go I go oh I think this is how I think
this is how we get out Mike
this is definitely at least how I get
out great huh but no I look and I go I
think this is how we're supposed to get
out I think we can go up this can we go
down oh yeah there's some other more
conventional methods of like this door
yeah yeah but as I said there's three
doors and as he has you're pondering the
mysteries of this hmm light column you
hear a like a pounding whoa on the left
door on the left of the three Doors ah
happy pounding yeah when you're gonna
pound party base freedom yeah yeah it's
rhythmic oh nice hmm your sister rockin
certai on the door and I said I say okay
well if we know we can get back to this
place we just need to remember which way
we go and I look at dinner and I go
which way do you want to go yeah you
probably avoid the pounding I've gotten
this far in life by avoiding the
pounding I go to this good advice yeah
can I can I give the doors on once over
yeah sure I never do 11 you have no
perception boys no I just look at stuff
I'm very surface level look at the left
door look why not
lock my percent way this RIT's a really
great it's a rich route of the year
thirteen you forget things around the
route to see the door it's yeah so these
the Doris don't appear to have any
there's nothing especially novel about
their construction they seem relatively
simple
they have a wide handle on them that can
be pushed down and pushed in but as you
go to examine that left or the middle
door begins to knock all right so but
there's nothing discerning or
incriminating about they're identical
besides the noise yes there is you can't
tell right just carry so left doors left
was rhythmically banging there's now
stopped oh and as he is examining now
the middle door is being new okay we
have to make it go through the banging I
don't know that we can go through any
other it seems like when we go up to it
it is the banging one yeah does that
mean that ostrich are slain to the same
place maybe uh-huh let's just take the
route down this is red this is a tiger
puzzle you know there's writers we
should go through the doors you should
go through this place is intended for us
alright the knocking becomes frantic on
the far right door okay so it's going
left to senator right yeah I want to try
to figure out like I want to gauge what
would be knocking but I'm not sure what
I mean that maybe investigation yeah
sure investigation is usually about yeah
right yeah black lights
that's CSI red larch if you wanted if
you can use perception to try to figure
out what's going on yeah let me let me
perceive or the other option would be I
wanted to try and like Arkana the nature
of what might be behind the door if
there if I get a sense of it let me just
do perception first in and fail that's
all right no I'd say 13 you think it's
being struck by a tool or a weapon Oh
someone trying to get out with an is
frantic is groaning collectively frantic
yes okay
but it's gone from door to door to door
and they've all stopped so obviously we
all stand in front of a door and open up
I mean I'm fine with that that's fine
that's good there's no way the wind
let's make a deal
either you always stick with the door
always move after the first one right or
you still put all of them at the same
time let's open all the doors you're
disqualified a lot of people don't know
that but we should open them all at the
same time all right
okay who wants to hang back from a door
I will I think you should you're
squishing I think you're so yeah you
have more controlling abilities the rest
of us differently theoretically yeah
yeah yeah okay okay um I'll be at the
left door all right
Oh dark I'll take the attack okay on the
right so as I said each of these doors
has a large handle sort of set in the
center of it that you can push down with
some effort mmm that disengages the
mechanism let's try it okay yeah one two
three yeah you pull it open in front of
your door ready but walnut of course in
front of your door
walnut you don't see anything Rosie you
don't see anything you look sort of into
a vast dark room you think you can see
tiny glints in there but you're not sure
and you are standing weapon ready and in
front of you is a boy I hit him whose
weapon is also at the ready oh oh I got
a human boy do you think it's it's human
it could be half elf what's it look like
yeah hair short like a almost shaven
hair
he is wielding a Tabard that is too
large for him and he has a hammer with a
pick at the back it looks like a it
looks like it should be a mining tool
hmm and not a hammer but it does mirror
it does mimic a clerics weapon hmm
I can Rosie if I go you guys are you
guys are away okay but you can see that
he has opened his door and he has his
weapon and he has the boy has his weapon
as well mm-hmm
I'm not gonna attack a little kid yeah
bless this boy yes all right
thunderous might see how tough he is
pull a sword on me yeah I get
advantaging his boys yeah I got a bird
wants to build slide boy oh man it's
worth it yeah so uh that's been like we
had to get down here who deluded he is
trying to get out of this room he looks
over his shoulder and then he still has
his weapon up and he's like like um like
a little league like a little boy at
that base he's he looks he's ready to go
to work you know this would not function
Yeah right
but you you're you're saying that he's
ready to get out of this room and he'll
try to get through you if he can okay
Rosie but he doesn't answer me
yeah Rosie's gonna already be over there
by the way like you you ask any
questions of someone and she sees this
kid yeah and she's instantly grandma
yeah it's like Oh sweetie what are you
doing here and she she like goes to
reach and try to prepare him he looks
over she looks over at us the arms go
he's like no and you can see he reaches
inside the Tabard and pulls out a symbol
of Tamura okay and he says are you
ghosts I don't think so you see she
thinks about it as as he emerges into
the light of the nemah zere you can see
that he is not completely solid okay
it's noncorporeal yeah I see okay um
it's a year it goes dude we might be
ghosts - she's gonna try to talk kid
yeah we might be ghosts to each other
because you don't look completely solid
to us either
he says I need to get out of here my
sister fell through something she fell
through a door and I need to get my mom
okay
where's this door she looks over his
shoulder back in the other room in that
room okay where's your mom but she's
back in red larch okay what's your mom's
name he looks over you just like she
reza drawn and Cory here is it
prophetess yeah he tilts his head a
little bit he's like I haven't seen you
there ah
we're friends of hers we're friends um
we don't come around often um
I think it's a really good idea for you
to go get your mom and get out of here
and we were we will go and find your
sister you stay safe he's never meant he
looks he looks at all of you and he says
I will remember you if you come to the
drawing courier my mom will take care of
you okay
are you can you get out of here safely I
got in here okay all right he says my
other sister is down here too two
sisters I have two sisters okay by this
time we're all clear this is omen right
okay sure yeah okay you're lookin at him
yeah yeah just like yeah you're like
it's like oh it's just like all the
drawings I've seen I mean was a child
um okay so you have to you have two
sisters down your where's your other
sister one fucking door
one fell through a door she was talking
she was talking to my other sister okay
and then she touched a door and she fell
through I don't know where she is now
okay you may I need to get my mom go
here's your mom well what's the occasion
he breaks off past the minutes you see
him leave the light of the nemecio you
see him fade into the opposite corridor
okay
what's interesting yeah let's go find
these kids right now yeah I'm going to
the room yeah Rosie and wallet are just
charging in yeah you know solving these
kid crimes yeah
so as you exit the NEMA's ear room that
that a light that loves you as you enter
the other room you hear these doors
close and then you hear the mechanisms
in them twist and you think that you
think that he may not have been able to
get out without help but as you as you
enter this room tortious along the wall
and a great chandelier all bursts with
emerald fire along the sides and then
you see that it is bathing a room that
is chock-a-block with wealth Oh mmm just
like like nice um like Carl Barks drew
it like where do I start swimmin yeah
yeah I think it's it is are they in bins
no it is this is the it isn't it it is
it's a madness okay it's just wealth
beyond avarice does it look you know
well that's like don't care does it do
they look corporeal to look real or does
it look like some kind of vision like
that you have to get that that's
reasonable it's reasonable in the
opposite on the opposite walls let me
give you all the information then you
can make the best decisions the opposite
wall you can see two doors set in it and
these doors are of a piece with the
wealth okay they aren't yes absolutely
almost mechanized they look like round
clocks
mmm by the way like absent-mindedly
i-i-i just like it's incredible and I
just dropped a the hoards person bag and
you just start to drag it open mouth
cross as I investigate others yeah yeah
you can you you take it and then you try
to drag it through it wriggles out of
your clutch oh and just starts moving
around the room like a snake the jack
filling its gullet dice scooping it just
crawls around and as you can see it hit
something it looks like a like a junior
hockey trophy or something it's like
this crazy golden cup and so it takes us
some work to get that you know the whole
base in there but it gets through there
feels self-satisfied pulls up and then
is eating some more gold and ends up on
a pile of gold and then interests have
rolls over full and you can hear the
light snoring from the front of the bad
girl go retrieve it imagine it's not any
heavier than when I held it exactly
exactly so you go over and retrieve it
you know you want to check out the gold
yeah well that could pretty much
convinced me that it's probably chill
yeah but something occurred to me which
is to I go to walnut and I say do you
want to tell the secretary that we just
saw omen oh good point
um pulls out her ledger and she'll say
um let's just say I entered the gate
went into the pit saw saw a child saw
omen as a child trapped in a room and
I'll say he mentioned his sister fell
through a door mm-hmm
the writing comes back on the ledger
immediately and it says take all
precautions
and one that says that outlet and she
goes take all precaution and she goes
again inside a mouth a hungry mouth that
just really need everyone to be just
like focusing on their gamer says that
yeah hundred percent okay alright well
as long as we know where we are
yeah I go alright well had your fill
this gold looks let's go
yeah do you reach down you're checking
out the gold yeah yeah absolutely do a
perception on that uh no no better
interception I want you to do a wisdom
save with I've disadvantaged plant you
get a plus three because you're near
dinar yeah okay
what but with disadvantage okay this is
sixteen this is all bad that's an eight
which is a thirteen nope
did you pass the program did you had the
three of me too yeah mines games only
two so you reach down you can see that
your friend catheral and his weird gold
worm yeah
are have eaten their fill I need wisdom
safe from you as well with disadvantage
really alright not a great one avis so
you're gonna let same roles
this is auspicious which one wisdom it's
uh special it's a flat especially sales
because you're getting exactly
thoughtful a date well you got plus five
when you're safe there yeah and there's
three from the thirties or you know you
know that you're not alone oh you know
that you're not alone in this room
in fact over on the opposite wall on the
rightmost door you can see the
mechanisms inside the door clicking and
you can see two children seated by it
okay the child on the left is much
smaller but you think that you've seen
this hair before you think you've seen
this sort of profile and she says come
on
see if you can open it she's talking to
it the other child yes okay
the small one is talking yeah larger and
she says ten Tia I think we need to wait
for almond I think we need to wait for
omen weed we don't know what's gonna
happen if we open this one and she's
like are you scared
and she says no I'm not scared I just
think that we should wait for omen and
she says I think you're scared and the
girl looks back her golden blonde curls
falling over there the shoulder and she
says all right and you see her reach
over and then as she touches the door
there's no door at all yeah she falls
flat and is pulled through like pulled
through the door as if it doesn't exist
at all and then you see the girl's face
look back toward the other three doors
and smile but now this is what you
experience as you have these two coins
between your fingers reason B stinger
right but they're all your coins really
every coin in here is yours and what you
know more than anything else but you
know like your own bones is that cthe
wrist drab walnut dong grass and in our
blitz in I'll kill you to have it
that is our game for this Thursday it's
been our great pleasure to spend quality
time with you yet again here on the C
team come back next week obviously for
the final episode of the first season
like I say so we're gonna go back we're
gonna try the facilities you come back
and see us for some table talk in a
moment don't go nowhere
you