time is the enemy the pastor threatens
the fastest weapon you wouldn't make it
past a second and last question
play it brash and reckless to choose a
card solution you saw it was prudent in
any sepulcher poker to don't become the
putrid it's that well-fed I pursue an no
mountain too steep for dungeon too deep
to send expanded their marks up to the
top of the peak of beneath they see you
become like sharks to it while I swim in
that money bill by Carl Barks through it
so send your National Parks drew it I'll
send him home in a natural box with a
close tie the most of the parts included
save your breath for a cleric confessor
death is a lesson and life is a tenured
professor but if you're seeking my
official advice sign on the dotted line
and which of the twice top and most
parks and fluids in your ticket when you
receive one in the mail okay
i attack obrajes panicking my house I am
also a minify Hereward run CEO of
acquisitions incorporated but today
major focus in a running a game Dungeons
and Dragons for my friends from the
squeakiest chair in America something
for you to savor to my right dragon for
narcissist dad said yeah alright you
earned this right hey
to the right of my right reppin the
natural world walnut on grass no to my
left
you know the mister outright oh I'm not
your grandma's grandma except for those
rare cases new wife's cuz you look like
a fuckin sorceress not miss route not
your grandma's grandma except for those
rare cases in which she is your
grandma's grandma it does happen from
time to time
Rosie be stinger check out they call
back to Game one what incredible journey
has been to the left of my left emerging
as though from a mist shroud mistress
travel
now this new shit whoa hey whoa listen
no that's me oh let's let's try to
create an atmosphere of support for one
another
maybe PUA oh yeah that's true that's
true and you're dressed for the occasion
that's right Shannon Rosie is real and
she's obviously here with us now when
last we saw our heroes it should be it
should be established I suppose that
this is the final episode of season 1
ever
hello the eye of the sea team final
episode of season 1 is the vinyl episode
of season 1 Cologne Lee for the collect
we are wearing oh it's gonna be eight
second flaws but why should I joke
that's a good joke all stop
you deserve nothing the best I do it for
you guys when last we saw our heroes
they had entered the increasingly
strange cavity for lack of a better term
of the wandering crypt there are many
stories about the wandering crypt what
exactly it represents we've sort of gone
over those during the course of this
season but very very recently let's get
right back up to it
it took them along in that period of
time where they actually had to stop and
rest but to get all the way down
whatever constitutes this thing's
windpipe they entered a large chamber
where they could see the mechanism of
the holy men Azir from the ceiling down
to the floor having ground itself
directly through the wandering crypts
body and held it in place beneath the
earth walnut sense that this was an in
fact a place of peace they moved from
there through a set of three doors that
are knocking at each of the doors they
opened it and saw a young ghost indeed
the ghost of a man of his hair award
drawing which you might have heard me
reference earlier in this show the child
was
indeed the child was distraught and
required assistance even getting out of
the place he left the party continued in
and they found you know whatever a
treasure hoard whatever that represents
in the bizarre biology of the wandering
crypt let's see so Rosie knelt down to
examine some of these coins and as after
someone said be very careful yes just
wanna this did happen no Chris Chris
trout
you made your save as I recall you know
no but not so much with so this is the
gullet of your bag that you have as a
second level horse person it's just I
mean it's just its stomach obviously as
a multiplanar dimension that connects
back to the home office but you know
that it is full of whatever this stuff
is back there is it gold it's hard to
know generally speaking when you touch a
coin you are not driven into a kind of
madness so let me go back to what
occurred previously just so we can get
the channel caught up with the state of
play I see that your face has already
adopted the proper mask of anger and
marshal rage now having having rubbed
two of the coins together
Rosie bee stinger isn't such that she
became convinced it's that she was
seized by a sort of incontrovertible
knowledge that her friends the people
that she thought were her friends would
kill her rather than let her seize this
gold which was her right and in the in
the intervening seconds you've had to
sort of recalibrate your memories of
these people
you've gone back through the adventures
that you've had the close shaves the
emotional highs and lows and you can't
help but wonder if it was all for this
did they need to secure your trust so
that you could help them get into this
place they could use your body and your
blood to enter into this chamber and
then seize this wealth from you wealth
it is yours you know it you know it for
a fact historically speaking this has
been the sort of time where we were all
initiative
can I do a little bit of role-playing
I'm not gonna I'm not gonna take that
from you at all I thought about this a
lot I want to hear it um okay so I I
pick up these coins and just rubbing
them I'm rubbing them together and I
everything just suddenly becomes very
very clear yes and I finally I I see it
all everything that you just mentioned
going through all of those memories of
this whole last however long we've been
adventuring together and everything's
falling into place at like um of course
of course of course there was a way that
I could be emotionally manipulated by
this elf and and get into places where I
was feeling protective there playing on
my natural instincts and it all makes
perfect sense and I start to laugh oh
god oh god Wow Wow
you guys almost pulled it off you almost
did it I should have known
you know okay listen I I've put up with
this long enough I've got some esoteric
lunatic
I got a horny elf with daddy issues and
an idiot baby uh-huh
and this is this is what I have been
carrying you and protecting you all this
time of course of course you're here to
steal this from me of course
great
all right um I hope you know what you're
in for because I'm not going down
without a fight
I might be an idiot and a baby but yeah
you guys shouldn't my compliments from
me what we do with these two
oh it's just I will say if you want to
leave the Crypt and we don't ever speak
of this again we can go about our
separate ways I can go back to the life
I was leading before you three can do
whatever the fuck it is you do and we're
good how about that fun guys you guys
just have to turn around get right out
of the script or gonna yeah wow that's a
natural 2000 shadow council merrily
receive your servant your literal
servant rosie be stinger has offered
unto you a blend of course if you are a
subscriber you can get this red box from
Hollywood Academy if you're not a
subscriber we'll give you a coupon to
the store I'll leave it up to you to
determine which of those is superior
this is terrible news for the rest of
this party what did you come up with
there Chris oh oh you're in the shade
alright we both know rosie be singer
it's only a matter of time I mean it
really is a killer be killed you gave
them the offer yeah to leave they have
not done so um you you and you have no
idea like if these people are capable of
treachery on this scale you don't know
what's next like that you can't plant
this is this is a type of this is a type
of betrayal you can't plan for but you
don't know if waiting is a good idea you
don't know if you'll survive it
Kathir is saying like you do to the
matriarchal nature of drought culture if
we've somehow offended I mean I don't
know what claim there's nothing coming
out it's gone to the whole mop this is
what it sounds like
Oh grandmother if we have a fend any way
kids in the whole Scouts where's your
gift always sarcastic man yeah can you
redeliver that as always sarcastic rinse
it out write it down yeah Oh grandmother
if we defended anyway please allow us to
make things right I can't believe I
thought you were some kind of buffoon
this entire time and it turns out that
this is your true nature
oh I've been called a buffoon many times
and I indeed my yeah well you're about
to be a buffoon who is missing some
limbs so I'm afraid that may be very
true okay what am I gonna do oh don't
tell me grandmother okay exactly so rosy
and cthe RIS are here she isn't going to
be moving a top a mound of gold the two
of you are closer to one another
emotionally what's like yeah yeah how
part are we as a group right now but
they are separate from you by about 20
feet okay
you and Catherine are very near to one
another okay now when you say about 20
feet how many feet exactly 20 feet okay
great um about exactly about exactly 20
feet okay so the first thing I will do
is because I know a bunch of these
absolute maniacs are spellcasters yeah
we use my chris destroyer yeah we need
to make a Christmas tree I'm going to
use silence I'm gonna cast it it's a
radius of 20 feet just I was asking and
I'm gonna drop it right in the middle of
all of us and so anything you guys that
requires a V right anything that's a V
spell you can't and then for bonuses
yeah anything that moves you lose your
voice you can't use it in that sphere
well yes because and then for bonus
action I think I can take with an
unarmed strike to stun to attempt to
stun
barring a con save and I think that
probably the one I'd be the most worried
about would be dinar so do some
breakfast please
yeah yeah exactly so what's the arrange
of the silence is just 20 feet so I put
it block in the middle okay and so only
in that 20 foot radius but I don't know
if you guys would know or see it it's
just a silence radio new we don't know
yet yeah when they go wrong I don't
think it's a visible go yeah
can't talk yeah no it's just quiet okay
I'm away in cowardice it's just it's
just nap time in there so so I will then
do a move toward dinar and try to kick
him right in the kneecap gonna be a mean
one
just a little yeah yeah right there's
the back of the heel the Dragonborn hide
their testicles that's where I was right
little-known fact my leg bends the
thumbs are tricked six feet so yeah you
have to do a con say versus my wisdom
which is
13 what content episode just toss your
dice okay 14 yeah
well you still get maybe a punch which
is at 21 against your AC 18 okay so then
I will do a punch right near me for 10
points of damage like crap yeah so she
so she has immediately sprung into
action and I go holy crap yeah yeah so
yeah so you you recognize instantly
because she has moved across she's quiet
you know you've seen her go to work
before but there should be something
happening as she's moving across this
sweep of coins
Oh am i stealthy a little monk feet so
don't think anything how much silence
work so does it just everything that
happens in there is silent I will read
you the description okay so the duration
in ten minutes
no sound can be created within or pass
through a 20-foot radius sphere centered
on a point you choose within range
any creature object entirely inside the
sphere is immune to Thunder damage and
creatures are deafened while entirely
inside it casting a spell that includes
a verbal component is impossible there
right so we couldn't exit the sphere if
you're in this fearing talk sensitives
nope she has created a very unique
scenario will it look different there
any it's already visual cue that I've
been no knowing in fact you've retreated
into a into a classic calming technique
like you are you are up against a
betrayal of the of a caliber you haven't
experienced for a long time you've
constructed your life in such a way as
to minimize this sort of thing right and
so you as a monk of the order show you
have many tools at your disposal to
regulate this type of this type of
anguish
so what did I say what did I see her do
from my vantage point do I like I like I
got full view he's being like huh yeah
he was she's back on her bullshit did
you see me
she I assume you may have seen me pick
up the coin and then turn yes yes what
and also also issued this dark edict
yeah okay I just wanna know like what
you want to know all the information for
20 feet away I want to know if we're
like conveniently behind a hill and we
come out we're like hey family no I know
yeah he said some horrible things just
um so can I do a perception check to see
if I you know that it's in anyway we
lucked up but then that would be my
whole thing I want to attack but I also
you know attack attack it this is a TAC
see no soon RTCC a TAC see oh yeah well
I'm just I'm waffling right now because
it's okay now so you just said this
horrible thing to me I don't do it horny
I'll flick daddy issues which is yeah
accurate to you yeah the first thing
I've been putting all remaining you know
familial bonds I'm too cool okay so okay
so I after having this happen don't say
anything which is true and I'm just
absorbing all this because of course
this is how it would be and all good
sense has gone out the window and I want
to grab that like I'm holding that
amulet that I got the made with anime
Lilith amulet from earlier in the crypt
and I am just thinking all these
horrible dark thoughts and when I do
that on a wild shape into the giant elk
form oh it is our first I'll commit this
is the first time out and for those who
don't know the majestic giant elk is
rare to the point that it's apparent is
often its appearance is often taken as a
foreshadowing of an important event
birth of the King maybe not in this case
so here's the thing no no we got two
hours
so just push turn into this elk and then
set my sights right on Rosie and it's
like blind with rage and I want to use
my charge to go we are 20 feet I can
move 20 feet straight towards the target
and then hit it with a ram attack
although I'm next to Darcy she is no
next to dinner so she is close yeah well
can you surround me I wallet is so mad
at ya it doesn't matter I can just hit
if I can hit you I hate you okay yeah I
mean you're not I'll hit you with one
side I don't know yeah we'll just do it
mostly it was antlers I'm blowing this
so I'm gonna charge at you and then
we'll see if I can get I guess plus 6 20
so I'm gonna hate you with that jeez um
but the important thing is to know is
that if I do that if I hit you with a
ram attack and charge on the same turn
you take an extra to d6 damage but it
says it could just be 7 so we'll just
make it 7 so to d6 sorry guys it's the
first time no no listen it it it's the
first time we were in elk you know yeah
we all take yeah plus 4 is 10 plus 7 so
17 damage yeah okay
and also you must succeed on a DC 14
strength saving throw or be knocked
groan okay nope did not save your so
just knock there straight onto the
ground
yeah which I honestly had coming yeah
that guy deserves essence yes so here
shake so can we say it can we say that
the horns of this elk yeah are strange
like so imagine that the sigil of the
EPA where these horns are actually
geometric inst instead of natural kind
of
smashed exactly like yeah well it looks
like there it looks like there amethyst
they have some kind of a coating on them
but any place where they get scratched
you can see the gym extra teeth like the
wolf did well you haven't seen oh it's
like 8,000 teeth it shoots teeth no
places like that I just saw the idea
that the the horns themselves mirror the
the order Kalyan
now dinar blitz in you have been kicked
in the leg right now by an old lady who
is on the ground
[Laughter]
good old lady you know there is a
demographic for exactly this material
well yeah there is let me tell you about
a table talk okay so I can't talk so the
things I can do sure but you're prone I
think you get advantage when piranhas
leaves dinar we're gonna de-escalate the
situation I think I just want to fall on
top of you and hold you down big
Dragonborns body try to hold down a
little Wiley grande honestly it's
flatten you out yeah no no yeah
everybody cool out
so here's what I'm saying but you can't
hear you so what I'm looking for from
you is a strength plus athletics chick
strength let's drink to it
what yes okay so that's good alright 23
okay now I want dexterity acrobatics for
you know what did your ID plus your
decks and your acrobatics yeah does that
count
that wasn't a saving throw right that is
a 24 don't all right so you seem like
life is no from the top rope you just
become like a shadow that is going to
fall on on Rosie and Rosie immediately
rolls out of the way and you just face
down in all this gold I want you to make
a save
all right join me my brother all right
this is what I need from you my friend
all right I need a wisdom you got some
wisdom nope all right let's roll it you
see what you get well but I have money
that's why I was asking yes the order
prediction so I needed to get plus 3
that's 6 all right you're facedown and
is it oh you can smell is these coins
and as you push yourself up and you look
around the sophistication of the
treachery dawns on you like how complex
this this child hundreds of years of
experience still somehow just collapsed
under an adolescent crush you know what
I mean yeah immediately you know exactly
why I didn't make sense why she was
trying to kick on your leg now you know
you know perfectly well she she is going
to take what's yours and this is exactly
the sort of thing you bring this hog
back to June are you are you aren't
Dennard the Exile anymore
you are that you are the dinar that they
thought you come back and it's a new era
so he's face down he is okay laughing
into the gold yeah around there yeah
it's kids getting in the cracks like a
pig in gold no there's like one it's
like one really cold one like in the
gorge a like in the neck and you're it's
at the other side of the pillow it's
like what's it it's like one for gold
yeah I say let Rosie try to steal that
one it's in there good yeah I can get it
you're facedown and you are are you
still prone or you still prone I think
ain't Goldie but you've rolled out of
the way I have I did not get squished
but I'm still down and there's also a
mystic elk yeah yeah enjoy the change
I'll lay down too but you felt but you
when you when you had come in contact
with this gold yeah you felt it
you felt it exert itself on you and you
shook it off rather quickly the thesis
was assert oh yeah just the concept of
this betrayal yeah yes just on the at
the outset like the where did this
emotion come from it's not mom yeah
exactly exactly it feels like someone
else's thought hmm no stranger to that
I'm going to there's a problem I really
want you to get out so I may have to
hold as far as my my attack but you're
at the end of initiative here I would
suggest that you definitely do something
well okay well okay there's not a lot of
options all right so um if will I incur
anything if I try to exit the the
silence I would love to go over to
closer where you are oh and back away
from from the two of them yeah you could
you could exert yourself farther away
okay you could you could get away from
this area here and it wouldn't and I
wouldn't take it probably I don't know
what the boundaries of the silence yeah
you you could get you could get out of
it
it's range is not greater than your
ability to move would you infer that I
turned I can't talk nothing II mean uh
no no no no oh that I see I see yeah
there's no evidence VII yeah yeah yeah
okay no no that's super useful I'm gonna
use that all right your your face up
yeah yeah okay I I tell both of you shut
your eyes and these advantage okay the
one thing I have that doesn't require
speech is hypnotic a turn so
oh and I think is it does it hit like is
it an attempt no it's a wisdom so yeah
they say I'm against it would you see it
yeah okay if you see it say something
yeah yeah okay so you are required to
save to do is provide if you didn't
trust me and show your eyes then face
down you don't want to see it yeah cuz
we're still faced it but I did tell you
to so the wisdom safe with what am I
what's my DC so 15 I'm gonna take a
manager look at thing that is just a
very bad tape so you you did your
absolute best so now that perverse
drought trickster has placed one of his
sigils you've seen this before this the
sigil that he wears around he's just
made this chorus a ting version of it
here in the center he's found some spell
that doesn't require this you this
region so you see it but you see it
above and basically they're they're
paralyzed right yeah they are what are
they it's charmed yeah so there you go
constipated to speed zero
yeah I'm just back to normal so you so
you can't attack if you're charmed you
can't attack the first route great but
there's lots of other targets here okay
so I'm reading that chart here they took
the charmer or target the charmer okay
and you have advantage on any ability to
check to interact socially with me well
you can talk we exactly get in there
exactly so you you you shake your you
shake your head you see this symbol here
you think that he's trying to you think
that he's trying to communicate with you
in a way that the others can't see Oh
interesting
he is a symbol
Oh and so I'm like oh he's cool to these
concepts yeah yeah okay so I'm on my
back and I see this symbol and I'm I I
think at first I missed it yeah it's I'm
like at least this Trixie drow right
then like no he's trying to he's trying
to use a way to communicate with you and
he must be just to communicate something
exclusively to you got it you know that
he means you know Harmon that your
friendship is real he's he is a strange
character yes perhaps on account of his
advanced age his upbringing you know he
is littered as an exile for long but you
know that you will come to harm by him
and that you couldn't bring yourself to
harm him okay no Rosie be sneer yeah I'd
like to get up why don't you
hello that's my move right okay you
stand up yet okay am i within range of
anyone yeah yeah you're very close to
dinner okay
I think I might mmm but if you got a
movement of zero so you have to throw
something if you want to don't do
something but if I'm within striking
range of Denar when I stand up true cuz
I did just roll out from under him yeah
that's true yeah I think early been
arranged
yeah sorry I think it's also a quarter
staff I mean it's pretty good thanks
Steph the master can get around okay so
I think that I will continue to beat up
Donora
yeah until one of my stuns lands on him
so all right let's dish it up though
we'll do a whole suite why not okay
warlock
that's a 17-second you're a CIA teen
right okay no hit no hit yes hit that's
this is one of my melees and then no hit
so only one of my punches lands hey I'm
gonna do try to do it faster like like
right now on the strongest part of the
of the back plate yeah and you you feel
it you feel it sort of ring your armor
and then you feel several other
blows only one of which is able to knock
the wind out of you written like that
under but you have to do another
constant please Peter Shh
all right thank you plus two plus three
cuz I get my charisma modifier nineteen
yeah but you're damaged
yeah mmm-hmm right punch is gonna be a
you got hunched yeah walnut dog grass
revving the natural world yeah this
sucks
here in this here in this strangely
silent plane here you can see your your
friends have lost their minds or maybe
you never really knew them I want to I'm
gonna okay alright here's here's what I
would like to do I'm going to look at
you and make a move like I'm gonna
charge you I like you know dude this
kind of thing is just a gold yeah and
then I'm gonna use my move action to use
my whole move which is a lot um and I
want to I want to back up my speed is 60
feet but I want to back up as much as
possible am i outside of the range of
this island absolutely and then I want
to yeah can i like kind of like a taunt
or something like I want to like yeah I
don't know me out here like I just do
really really taunting stuff yeah hello
your nostrils at me and stuff is
controlled by a roll so it doesn't
matter you can get like an intimidation
this is my voice or something is that
how you want to do is what you want
iris honestly if I could go do it let's
try let's try intimidation Plus
I'm figure this one yeah is it there's a
lot of gold around like okay that's like
a massive treasure Chand there's only
one Doreen no there's three doors that
you came in yeah and there's two doors
yeah yeah 419 okay doesn't necessarily
mean you can't even get as far as you
get no but you're really turn my
attention away forget it rise yeah so
you so you need to start I mean you've
already figured out how to spend half of
this you know well no there's no just
cool oh yeah yeah you uh you're still
next to me where are we how far into the
rumery deep all right would you door
because you across the to the to sort of
in jewel inlaid mechanical doors yeah
the ghost girls indeed so we're closer
than they'd be much closer all right yes
and I get up like like getting out of a
snowbank
just like there's gold just falling off
me crazy wild-eyed and it's like this is
all mine this is mine you all need to
get out so I'm gonna try to grab Rosie
and throw her out of the room like out
of the door like get out of my room this
is my room now
oh through the other do that whatever I
guess closer so for it was those two
doors are closer then I'm gonna try to
just hurl her out that's my attempt I
love it drink drink this is I would say
strength athletics decks acrobatics I'm
gonna take advantage and this is not it
safe right so strength and athletics
again alright so that's a 20 mm and
that's a 23 okay what do you got Rosie
probably not that the 19 no sorry 21
then you have 23 yeah exactly
so you so she so you expertly dodge into
this grip this massive grip so describe
this situation so well so I'm prone and
she's Cameron on my back Sony kinda
would get up on all fours scattering
gold everywhere and then just crazy wild
I just whatever is closest just cuz
she's the closest it's not good she's
hitting him it's because she's the
closest right this is Dan his room and
his gold Sony grabs grabs it like a sack
of potatoes and just wants to throw her
out of the room like and that if that's
the closest door it's just like that
yeah and if you could hear I mean be
screaming it this is my room everyone
get out exactly you still probably don't
even know because this is just
retaliation so you're tossed bodily
through the air I mean it's gotta be 15
20 feet and then you sort of the take
two points okay so you land and it'd be
more if a heap of your inviting gold had
not broken the first part of it and as
you as you hit this the the pile of gold
scatters and you see to to to look miss
shapen it you can't tell if it's wood or
it's a polished wood or like volcanic
glass but it's broken in two pieces it's
sort of underneath it's spread out as
you as your body impacts this sort of
gold dune and you can see that the two
pieces would plainly fit together and it
has a hole at the top you assumed to be
worn okay at some point but the symbol
on it is one that you know very well
because you have a symbol exactly like
this it is a black glossy placard
and on the placard is a barbed s but it
has been snapped in two pieces which you
know is not that's not advisable okay
it indicate indicates in an inability to
hold up your end of the bargain
I see do I take am I afraid of this do I
feel compelled to put the pendant back
together no no no in fact how and I'd
like to get as a wisdom save for you
right now I'm gonna see snaps about yeah
yeah so you you as soon as you see this
your terror as seeing this barbed s in
this surprising place cuts straight
through everything that you are thinking
before it was just madness you lost your
mind
you have a dim recollection of
physically striking dinar of being
trampled by walnut did you remember what
she said yes no I won't do that to you
and so but but you know you know that
these two pieces like this is a this is
a debt marker of the shadow Council is
issued when you accept their bargain and
here broken in this place you wonder
what could have led to that okay so you
are so this is this is actually the end
of his turn but I want I wanted to
communicate what had happened as you
connected with the ground so you are now
maybe five feet from this door that
seems to move inside itself like a like
a fine watch Springs and gears and it's
sort of like it has a whisper quiet sort
of sound something you can mostly feel
eco-drive yeah so it's it's nice its
inherent its any price
visit first job okay so I've just
witnessed you throw her I also can't
like from within them it's just like a
doll yeah yeah I'm upset hardly at that
the force of it all so upset because
that unch are to absorb an attack was I
hoping that let it last a little longer
and I I'll say I will say that do you
like she like we had her charmed nurse
now she's broken out of it okay so like
I'm gonna be like yelling and pointing
accused it's really like it but in
silence you can hear I'm saying I'm just
like I throw and I was like and I'm like
you pick up use this and use this part
like you to drought
everyone out get out of here this is
mine now it's communicable spreads so
I'm now I'm not outside of that range
you've taken you back up me but I am now
aware of this silence zone so I would
love to do is this is tricky because
you're not closest kills no yes show
snapped out of it I think she's still
the enemy I think you're still on my
side it's pretty exciting it's just
making silly jokes that crazy dinner
yeah what are you doing I get out of
there
listen you know let's go Oh what's a
glass like yeah I don't know how how
like how conniving would you be under
this spell like is it like what I try to
trick everyone make you think of Mary
would you mean no no you are you yeah
you Arden are utterly without with new
information yes there were no betrayers
okay you're not someone else
yeah yeah so I would say like get out of
get out of there don't like go like grab
her go bind her up before she comes to
cuz she's still in the ground we can
snap her out of it sort of track convey
you you're on the cult you get her you
get her and get out with her get out of
here oh can you hear him now cuz it's
back in here yeah yeah that's awesome
and we out we both of us are does yep
okay so off of that I I don't understand
the get out of here part yeah but I'm
gonna make a perimeter around the where
you perceive to be right and I'm gonna
try and get in range of you sir so that
I can annihilate yeah so I can where I
got that that could be here to be we got
a good man you got that can annihilate a
grandmother well I got some thorn whip
that's a classic we always ever
connected with it but right yeah yeah my
tentacle lash we've had some wobble
since I'm now that pulls toward out if
that's the thing I really want to do I'm
gonna do it anyway because the first
thing that comes to mind
so yeah they just I'm like you stay
there we're gonna figure this out I
don't mean you any harm
Thornwell oh gee
alright I did that sick so my my my
phone was a seven plus oh it's no it's
fourteen what is it no with my AC no sir
no okay so just wait just real quick
it's really hard to connect with or nope
happens with a lot of people we're gonna
make fun of people like you guys this
was ten collection no so so you you here
cuz Chris saying something and then
doing the opposite almost immediately
and then just from inside inside the
darkness of his cloak this lashing whip
comes out of what appears to be his
solar plexus and then just begins to
lash frantically at the gold around you
yeah absolutely and then it sort of it
retracts like the
like the power cable and vacuum okay so
I realized that you are still attacking
me but I've broken out of this madness I
recognize that I was in a certain kind
of madness before but I don't remember
what I said yes this is so healing what
I feel like we should have done this
conflict a long time ago how does this
informal Jerry I'm glad you're having
fun does inform you like so you that
lashes hit those coins yeah I said I'm
gonna spray yes done back and I'm done
towards you like like like okay maybe
interpreted that fat lash as like a
warning so cuz I'm giving you a lot of
credit now that I know you're not
pulling it so I was like woah woah woah
woah woah woah I'm sorry
no I don't know what happens but I'm
back if I'm normal please don't dude oh
it just who hold on
drought let's let's talk about this
that's ruble and yeah you're that yeah
yeah I'm out of the bubble I've been
knocked out of it okay yeah that's
because I'm still a man yeah yeah you're
see this sort of conscience is going
yeah ambling like back up against this
door I like pushing myself because I'm I
think I'm reeling from the shadow
council amulet that I saw and and still
quite frightened by it and so I'm
pushing back away from you in a way that
is it's very unbecoming and cowardly
looking to come and I'm begging you to
to stop it I said you been you please
your backup to the door the whirring
intensifies and you hear too pronounced
clicks whirring intensified in real life
when you said that I was just gonna say
whirring intensifies absolutely so
that's that's Catherine's turn Rosie
beasting okay so I hear these clicks on
the door and for a moment I turn my
attention away from the dress and I look
is there any difference that I see in
the door yeah there are different so you
saw it has inlaid gems yeah but
different parts of the interior stroke
sure of the door are exposed at
different times and you think this some
of these are you think that some of
these gems are different than they were
right right it's like it's like watching
a puzzle build itself oh okay
and that's just from me touching it it's
from you pushing back up against it yes
I think okay so then I want to like lean
away from it and see what happens okay
so you you take a couple steps back and
you look down and you can see a girl no
and then you can sense that someone else
is behind you and there is a young boy
that looks exactly like the boy you saw
the third two the three doors and she
says omen auspicious gone she went
through the door I think you should go
in and try to get her and he says I
can't do that but we're all gonna get
lost in here you need to come with me we
need to go home and get mom and she's
like I'm really scared I'm really scared
about what will happen to her in there
but I don't think I'm brave enough to go
in and then you see that sort of fade
away no I assumed they couldn't see us
this time no no they were not really she
was not reacting to a grandmother at all
okay you were sort of interests you were
sort of in the middle of this
conversation
so you've seen you're seeing things that
did that aren't chronological right in
the classic sense okay I'm not gonna try
to attack anyone obviously so now you're
just you're watching you're watching
these new gems expose themselves inside
this is your turn you just want to just
want to observe it yeah and I have
hopefully like put my hands up awake
from like it's a waste row in a
submission away from the door away from
Katherine away from anything I'm looking
at walnut it don't remember her turn
into an elk but it's very dope so I'm
impressed but you support it do yes I
so do just that do I remember that it
casts it yeah yeah because you have to
concentrate to keep it
oh okay then yeah it's gone okay and we
immediately hear screaming everyone just
get out get out
it's your chain um is it open it is that
what we determined sure yeah so I hear
you saying everyone get out right to
that yes to that effect it's not I don't
know exactly what you say well you'd
have something where we tell people to
silence their friends but like not for
the audience like for the participants
this in a movie like a real phone winner
he's just saying duck tales theme song
lyrics I mean it drives me crazy
so what do I hear you say exactly he's
telling everybody get ya sub-clause well
it's like it's not it's not aggressive
it's not this madness it's like alright
alright so it's an artist it goes in
almost a paranoia like all right I got a
street see here all trying to play me so
I'm just trying to play you sort of
things so it's not aggressive but let's
just say I'm offering it's just like oh
yeah I mean yeah yeah yeah so are you
gonna stay where I am and I'm gonna hold
action to see if he makes any more
dangerous anything happens but the
minute anyone anywhere in the room does
anything aggressive and that's gonna
hurt myself alright uh Denar blitz in I
would like to have a wisdom safe from
you my friend eight plus there is only
moment 11 where you think you might have
been wrong but you start to doubt
yourself hmm
for a split second and then you're like
no I've never been wrong yeah that's for
dinner but since your turn alright so
they're not doing they're not moving
sighs slightly
right there well there by the door yeah
Chloe it's working yeah it's like all
right I'm deep in the room oh yeah
you're deep in the room as an elk so I'm
just like like through like like a kind
of a sarcastic seething like walnut over
by the door mm-hmm
leave with them I'm not feeling great
I'm gonna heal up for a second here
and I'm just gonna Wow Oh pull out the
sword but I'm just gonna take a knee
right right where I am
take a knee look like I'm doing laying
on hands actually casting fine Steve I'm
just like a breather I need a breather
you go over there and that's my turn
okay it takes a minute to cast this I'm
assuming a cage would be like horse yeah
I don't know how long they see combat
takes a little bit it take well and this
is like a time casting time is it tennis
yeah Hey look I'm just trying to but I'm
not being as aggressive what's this like
I never so he is here oh he's so he
needles here and you see this you see
this gold so as he as he puts his knee
down a few gold coins spread out from
the impact of his knee and you can see
him sort of cataloging each one but he's
just sort of counted the individual ones
so you can see it's like his mouth is
moving hmm like he can't count in his
head any man and he and he immediately
starts to pray and I this concentrated
praying does not look like lay on hands
well have you seen Leon kids and that's
sure seen it there's no bushes exactly
even laying on handsome nuts yeah it's
like it's fired
I want to while he's praying I want to
take my turn to walk up to him and just
try and scoop him off with like an
antler just be like you go towards the
door just like we're all going towards
the door oh you trying to bring him
along with the party yeah I was trying
like well it was Christmas Day
I hold my action oh and you're doing a
thing he's describing Oh weird it's
still not gonna do anything around so
you get oh so you you you're gonna you
got a book it to get over there but you
think you can get there I'm happy they
do exactly exactly
when you get so this is not an attack no
I have us I just feed a 60 so that's go
well you can easily here's me back
within this space
how many using that you got across 60 no
I want to yeah not Jim towards the door
you're getting down um and then she is
trying to she's trying to push you and
sort of scooch you is it's not an attack
no it's just like well my summoning
circle yeah exactly
she's trying to push you off I need a
constitution safe from you because oak
whispers I get plus fire cuz I got my
charisma you say hey it's a one fucks
your stability you have to start over
oh you're pissed yeah nice job so I'm
I'm still marching at you I don't fully
understand what this is just because I
was think anybody's ever been submissive
to me as though I talked to them on so
I've seen this in others I've never port
behind it right about broke some others
thread yeah
and I say look Rosie we'll figure it out
it's this room it's these coins they're
there they they're changing us they're
putting ideas in our heads I know as you
say that you're been like a wave pool
time I write a wave of disk gold like
it's almost as though the room is tilted
this gold starts to go and sort of wash
over the middle of the room and pile up
in the opposite side
but the room is not tilted this is just
it's very minor
but this gold is sort of moving around
the roof sort of rumbles with the action
of it yeah gold is sending us thoughts
and now it thinks it can move around
like it's like it's a big boy
I don't care for that makes its people
exactly I'm trying to assess whether or
not you're still oh I think I think yeah
I I look I think I look very shaken and
completely afraid do it yeah yeah good
do something I'm not insulting you but
you better have long staves yeah see
that's a point of that's a point of
commonality that's something you guys
could talk about later yeah you know
what I mean you know I look at you and
and there's there's a kind of like the
fear of like a cornered animal in my
eyes and it's got to be new that's new
yeah that's not that's not this coin
spell this is something else and I I
look at you and I say we need to get out
of this room and we need to get them and
come and make them come with us exactly
the same so you can see that rosie is
here right yeah Rosie is here and you
have this is the first chance you've had
to really get a look at this door which
you think you're trying to imagine a
scenario maybe doors and obviously this
said this is something that would be of
interest to dinner blitz in it could be
that doors have their own parallel
systems of love right so imagine if you
will a sort of dark courtship between
doors you feel as though this door is
related in some way to the black gates
yes it's it's like an upmarket
it's it appears to have multiple
multiple mechanisms inside it like
configurable custom and aftermarket yeah
yeah all right it's good a lot of homes
in this one
wait in this rig um Rosie bee stinger
okay so are you still yelling stuff at
us
no I'm this is more of a straining
capable thing there's like like an anger
and a bloodlust buddies it's kind of
hiding okay you know it's not like a
frothing madness okay it's just like
okay so I I go a check on you guys it
looks like you are not making eye
contact with me but that's okay cuz
you're an elephant
eyes are in different places yeah it's
kind of like it's on the side on the
side which is its new yeah and I'm not
gonna I'm not gonna read too much into
it it's fine um so I glanced back and I
see that you guys are making array over
here um I can't tell that you have the
same well no so I was on the ground
doing my summoning spell and she knocked
me over so I'm still down there just
quit it's been messed up I start wearing
okay glaring at each other well I always
say that you on the ground and you
nudging him yeah so so it's not clear
what your state is yeah yeah so there
may be Rosie did pretty like pots read
in a spot a lot of butts yeah I mean II
waiting on my book so but I believe that
woman is capable of getting dinar to the
door which I believe is what she's
trying to do so I'm like okay bigger I
was trying to get this door open
you and me okay um and so I don't know
that I have any kind of it can I do a
perception check on the door I mean you
might have to interact with it a little
bit okay so you might have to play
around with it so I will put uh two
hands on the door to see if I can get
the trigger to to do stuff again just go
right up to it so you you've sustained a
pretty firm hit from the combat sure
earlier 50% exactly and there is a
trickle of blood from your nose and as
you are sniffing it back up as you reach
out like this it travels down over your
mouth and then
underneath your robe and out along your
hand and then out across the fingers Wow
into the door and your hand moves a tiny
way through it hmm okay
I draw my hand back and I without
looking at cook thirst I say no is this
running freely now okay boy jeez and I
pull back and I'm like you saw that
right
she says that and blood is misting out
from her speech like you have to text
this oh my god yeah I've seen it I'm
gonna try to back away from the door and
it's just it's hitting the floor and it
wants to go into blood and so it started
so you can see that there's different
rings there's different Springs and
mechanisms in here and one of them wants
that and you can see that this sort of
started to fill new gems are appearing
inside the sort of grinding wheel inside
this until there's only maybe one left
one left to be revealed
Dennard what's in all right so trying to
send the Steve this is like early
shining when he starts to go crazy
not only is like fully crazy but the axe
yeah yeah trying to get an ally because
I can't trust any of you
but now I got knocked over my something
circle got messed up so then I just I
look at the elk and I just go well not
leave and I command leave use commands
yeah I did can't do anything to that
wisdom saving but because I'm close to
you don't I get a bonus yeah for my
allies you're not my Ally yeah yeah geez
they're wise yes wrongfully betrayed
it's 20
something good but it was a 22 yeah so
he's he's now he's trying to boss you
around
yeah and it's always it's always strange
to have that sort of patrician air that
aura of command come out of dinar oh no
but it is in there it is in there it's
like it's like it's like several version
of wearing your dad's coat it doesn't
you know I mean it's too big
sucks right so so you so you tried to
command are you moving um I only go no I
think I'd stay his plan here was it's
the command leave go back to summon
Steve exactly yeah so you need you know
it was just like what good I'll clutch
and there's the only friend yeah in my
mind there is a scene where you don't
you stop trusting heart Borg is very sad
no in my mind it's like Clark Morgan
gets all paranoid - no well no grass so
your friend mm-hmm is being Denar again
yeah cuz this is that foreign out of
character warning really actually it's
just I don't think you've ever tried to
command any of us before I tried it once
early and makes even when he was first
time he was at the gate oh yeah that's
right and he bolted in retaliation right
so it is an unusual thing 15 18 alright
so as you commanded her to leave you're
like why would I command her to leave
like I don't know what's happening in
here I'm here to turn into a tree or a
bear or wolf I don't want her to go on
and you start you start to question the
last few seconds it's sort of like one
little stitch one little thread starts
to poke out
anyway you have a what hmm did you
really
and you can't it's like it's like me
trying to remember it dream they're like
not in the morning but like around noon
the next day hmm you it's just do you
you can't come up with anything you
don't know why you felt those ways
phlegm out of it you are okay at this
point
don't ever pronounce the case even my
son knows the case smart son
so at feeling that I've been commanded
you know been commanded by dinar and had
those horrible things said to me right
Rosie I this situation is like so funny
it'd be like elk form
oh yeah the pod like this is so not what
this form was in like intended for and
so I come out of it
bonus action whatever and I look at
dinar and I grab him and then I use
produce flame and I just start whaling
on his face like and it's like she's not
even saying anything she's like seething
and making like that noise and it's like
in her head she's just thinking like how
dare you how dare you community how
could you do that
I hate Rosie also and some other stuff
things that are not safe to say on the
air and I'm just I'm just too hot for TV
but if it's just a range spell at the
tech but it's on my hand but it would
have been a 1d8 but it's just for flavor
so yeah I can roll damage but so you're
just moving your head back and forth and
she's just like like pauldrons you're
just like just every it's like the
opposite of like everywhere you want to
be it's like you don't want any part of
it okay yeah it's important that these
are so emotional that they are not
connecting in a meaningful way but it's
just like those flames like licking up
the arm tears of rage oh yeah there's a
rage like we are well beyond that
and it's just cast is just casting light
around the gold and the jewels
how much do I remember from being crazy
do I know you - is it a - yeah exactly I
think that you know more than anyone the
effect you have on people no I do I do i
infer that the the gold messed me up do
you have the coins yeah she touched the
gold - I'm like oh I'm out of it and now
she's in it who knows well I'll find out
on my turn
yeah Chris Chris Joe get off the coin
you guys done the coins are doing it
come on yeah anything out thanks for the
help
hey welcome that grandmother is not
doing hot yeah I'm spewing blood or else
I would be contributing to this
conversation but hopefully I'll like
turn to you guys so you blood coming you
take two points of damage
oh boy so this is real okay no so
there's a show no it's not just the show
on Twitch it's real yeah I okay so I
yelled at you I'm gonna turn my
attention back to you yeah exactly and
you see it there and you see the final
you see the final gem almost be this
looks like manufactured in the mechanism
and then you hear it you hear it stop
and see it physically stop in there the
other two wheels still want whatever
they want but this the door opens and it
opens about half way and then beyond
this door you can see a shimmering
curtain and you can hear what sounds
like footballs
it sounds like barefoot falls on a bear
no not a cloth
an earth sign footfall oh no it's just
that slap of a barefoot and it's sort of
like um it's sort of staccato it's not
even muttering trying to imagine it yeah
like a limp like a shuffle yeah softer
mr. Kotter scatter tender stick some
type of deck but you can't see anything
through okay
you almost imagine like behind the this
sort of silver curtain
it looks like moon jellies or something
you ever seen a moon jelly yeah yeah it
just there are there is just sort of a
continuum of moving swirling shapes and
this is viewed it's not that that's like
a shape beneath occurred because it's
pressing against the curtain is there is
there like any a sense of light and dark
through the curtain like through the
weave of the curtain no no it you're not
sure this is any kind of fabric at all
and then one of the shapes behind the
curtain begins to push closer to the
curtain and then a figure emerges
pushing through that sort of silken
gauze and then continues to shuffle
forward but right now just complete
Silverlight almost like a state change
imagine that there's been a transference
from one stage of matter to another and
then the closer she gets it remember
remember when um walnut retained a glow
long after being exposed to divinity
right and this is similar to that but
it's boiling away
closer and then this shape is shuffling
stumbling and then falling to all fours
trying to get itself to the door I
raised Locati and press that head as
close to that figure as I can to get a
better look so you see just a waterfall
of tangled blonde hair and then I looked
at almost a shredded to small shift of
fabric that might have been the right
size at one point but is no longer
sufficient
for an adult it looks like an adult
wearing a child's shift
I turned to I turned to Rosie I say are
you all right I like kind of shape
you're in are you and myself waiting
you're not leading as soon as it as soon
as as soon as it filled up I mean you
are a mess right but it is it doesn't
want anything else it's not coming out
of me like that
okay yeah oh I'll say if you're good to
go we need to get her out of here
her yeah okay yeah of course
so she's crawling toward us she is she
is she is here sort of in the edge
trying to get out of the door okay and
you know she's in now is like she's gone
down but she's trying to get up she's
trying to pull herself up what anything
that she can but the door itself just
swings farther open mm-hmm
when she tries to get up and then she
falls out again on her side I I'd like
to go to her let's see yeah
help her up she is her eyes are wild
like they're just they're moving around
just they don't seem to focus on
anything particularly like they did her
eyes don't seem to be aware of any
individual person okay it's still your
turn are we still in transit condition
of his gun we're just playing regular
old D&amp;D um I'm gonna start in instantly
trying to soothe this person like
darling Shh it's okay it's okay you're
safe here with us it's all right yeah as
soon as the as soon as you contact
happens um she shrieks and starts to
hyperventilate oh boy do we have any of
us have anything calming that we can
cast on her future
echinacea lay on hands incurable yeah I
can that tremor yeah yeah I guess we
should are clear waves there to her
wounds are not physical crap
yeah so walnuts just punching me in the
face and my head's turning left and
right and I look over as my head's being
turned and I see you a bloody mess and
then a new player is entered the game
and I'm just like okay I'm good I'm good
I hold it back one and she pops your
everything past you gets up she gives
you offers your hand look she's gonna
help leave your feet yeah that's like a
peace offering uh I started pulling my
hand like I'm gonna do it yeah yeah so
you you are now privy to this same site
as well walnut okay and I see you
approached walnut and I say oh thank you
thank you we can you help there's I
can't get her to recognize me or to even
recognize where she is is there anything
that do you have anything
and here will not mumble under breath
she goes yeah I got a key slinger and
the coins made us crazy and you are you
know that you spent all week thinking
that you think she'd just be like oh
it's okay in this place exactly yeah
thank you know she wasn't hurt okay hey
once again
okay sure I mean I'll at least you know
I don't want it ah I shouldn't use
anything on her Oh cousin the owner I
don't reach out with my mind and it's
subtle away as I can I want to jump in
there and be nice but give it to me to
to to tell me how it goes if I through
if there's any volume control when I use
awakened mind on it yeah I want it's
gonna be more activity about modulation
not volume necessarily but about
presentation
right ASMR true it's a valuable tool and
that's in that toolbox I start to
crinkle some foil I say friend I say
from this is the this is the if you
could be if you could understand one
concept is that we are not here to harm
you but I want I want two things from
them I want her to understand friend and
I want your name your name I'm squatting
down beside you yeah so she just stopped
writhing in your arms the she is
allowing the pet to occur without strain
and then she is looking around and
trying to find you like trying to find
the person who is speaking to her oh
she's reaching her hand out
I take I take her hand right she takes
your hand and then reaches her other
hand out to hold it and then she moves
out to the arm up to the face and just
to feel it
mmm yeah I mean that's fine it's all
right that's fine just okay yeah do you
say that yeah in your head say I can't
see either
yeah she is mumbling something she's
mouthing something but it's too quiet to
hear oh not even up not even up here I
can't get a great idea she doesn't know
she's not able to respond that way I see
but she's trying to respond it's like
when when Elliot was young you would
talk to him in in English and then he
would respond in sign yeah it's like the
informations coming in one way and this
is the tool that she has to respond to I
think it didn't occur to think it Mac
like this is the way right give me a
kiss yeah yeah well I walks over first
and then I with dust nice taste so every
face don't shake if you clean they go
over there yeah I am like even though it
didn't do a lot damage the blood
probably would bother me and also like
well no and it's also just like I'm not
mad at you I did it to him a little
embarrassed about what happened so I'm
just gonna be like hand on the shoulder
just feel like I got let me take care of
this meet myself too and just do a
little lay on hand oh thank you
top us off so I gotta get myself 16 just
to get back to normal so do as much as
40 do you have to heal twice as much
just to get the same high yeah I know
Tina was getting it I got a free baby
this yeah before takes me back up to 32
okay exactly
so um as you as you come over and invoke
VARs MELAS to heal your friends there is
a sound that starts coming from the
silver curtain
and the shade moves from silver to gold
and then as it mr. buck a chorus starts
to rise in volume of many voices and
then the door revolves backwards
and then closes itself with us on the
outside we stood yet with you on the
outside what acquired that position it
is incorporated are we yes this door
that's that mass of coins washes itself
back over to the other side yeah this
might be a good time yeah yeah after
it's happened this is like the jump
right can we help this woman to her feet
yeah yeah yeah she's gonna she'll need
substantial insiang should I carry on
she's like that yeah you might want to
she's like a like a newborn puppy all
right I just don't have it we shan't
rosie takes off her shawl and she drapes
it over this morning because your
clothes are shredded and she's probably
freezing
no get it ice cold it's not warm in here
right right and I see you you pick her
up yeah see you soon
tell me more what happens next well just
start making our way yeah back out yeah
I don't know what this like my hope was
to go inside this thing's brain and rip
it apart I still feel like this organ is
stomach related so yeah it won't spend
any more time it's just a part of my
body yeah yeah exactly so you pull
yourself back across to the other side
and you see the three doors that you saw
before and then you can see that on this
side there is no you can't see a means
to open the other side had a clear latch
mmm that's right oh it's trapped in here
oh okay um so I want to go up to it and
uh fry like I'm touching the door yeah
these are these are these are deeply
unlike the other doors like there's
nothing tricky about them yes I simply
have no handle
yeah or mechanism of any kind I'm real
tired of script and everything that's
happening in it and now we have a person
that were responsible for she doesn't
look like she's in good shape
um so I'm gonna start banging on the
door I'm like worked for the kid just
bang super super hard so you how many
times do you think five times you bang
four times mhm and then as you raise
your hand up for the last bang you hear
a clang and you see the door open and
you see you are certain it is the boy
that you saw before but as a young man
Oh carry on maybe 17 18 and is it like
when we see them what are they what do
they look like yeah they look at cereal
and then what you could derive from
before is that you look at cereal to
them mmm sounds play conceals when I
absolutely okay when I see him I'm like
completely taking it back but I just go
do you remember us
he says that's why I'm here mmm walnut
goes good we'll remember you he looks
down baby says you did it it took a long
time it he kneels he kneels down and
looks at the woman and then he reaches
out and tries to touch her but he cannot
he can't connect with him he says he
says this is the only thing that has
made this worthwhile is that eventually
this stops eventually this terrible
story stops but in order for in order
for you to do what you've done I have to
do what I have to do
and so he he he allows you to enter into
the chamber then Emma's ear and he
passes by you and then he pulls the door
he pulls the door shut behind himself so
that is the end of the first half of
this finale I know it's crazy
we are gonna sample the delights of our
mercantil culture with the following
commercials and we might also go to the
bathroom and then we'll return with the
last half of the season one finale of
acquisitions incorporated the c-team
don't go nowhere
hello last we saw our heroes they had
just emerged from the stalk lingering
crypt where had have done absolutely
everything it could to digest them turn
them against one another not successful
they were able to escape from that place
with the help of a young man that they
had seen before an even younger state he
appeared to know the woman that they had
brought with them from beyond the silver
curtain beyond three doors beyond two
doors and in the silver curtain if you
were a total C team nerd you know what
I'm talking about you stand in the
chamber of that the NEMA's air is ground
through the abdomen of the laundry crypt
Oh hop it up over we're even like
attached to your glasses
how do you plan yeah in your mouth you
tell me if that's better do better you
say dude glands like DSR like no lands
like bananas just like right under your
rethread rim yeah
to the vas deferens cool new yeah
because my board games Swisher is so
fine and so fresh I can't see so that is
it you now be in this globe and indeed
this healing blow as allies of the
Enclave this healing glow is nourishing
your bodies and spirits
oh it's like a rest I didn't mean to
scream I'm sorry I have a thing where
people touch me and I don't know about
it and I guess I'm so sorry
anyway it is pretty you know can you
know what it is preparing you for war Oh
every part of this instrument is
purposefully designed to strike terror
into the foes of the Enclave and to
nourish its soldiers just open a
compartment insist full of guns it's
just so cool it's very very major yeah
so we're now into the the chamber within
them is there and I see this big root
structure and there is your root yes
members and you you know that it is a
conduit right yes exactly
it is been this is basically how you
would deliver troops okay so I'm gonna
walk up to it and I'm not sure dinar
with the girl over right and I'm gonna
I'm gonna touch this neighbors rooms be
like like okay we can use this we can
use this to get back to the surface this
is what this is what it's for and I go
exactly exactly yeah it's red but she is
being healed as well oh wow
by this Mara she is being like her
pallor is being nourished even now
and her her speech is increasing in
volume still weak but you can very clear
her saying very clearly hear her saying
auspicious drawn mmm just over and over
oh why she's a guy that like is that
your name she doesn't respond to that
she's just like you master tasting the
word
she's just acclimating to it say I think
your own man sister
yeah she says where's 10d tell he's not
here we just came for you
we have to go back in you felt through
the door and omen sent us to get you
we're taking you back yes as long as we
can come back it moves we know it's
stuck not today
and then that the exertion even though
the conversation you can see sweat
standing on her brow yeah her hair is
just like a bird's nest
like it's just tangled um so so you you
know even even with the contact of your
palm on the drill like root structure of
the Nemus ear you know how to send your
friends up yeah I wanted to do that and
I want to do it in this order
um dinar break it first okay so you said
it that's very good so the tough the
tough ones up front yeah so you so based
on the meat right yeah so you send up
dinar you see a like a tendril like a
friendly root friend girl yeah a friend
role comes around and then sort of
cinches around your neck and then down
into the front of the of the armor like
a noose exactly
and then once it once it's able to cinch
itself back around on itself an instant
later like you come out basically at the
at the base of the tree that walnut grew
and I've got her with me okay absolutely
so you so you feel something similar it
reaches around very quickly it's much
easier if you're not covered in plates
there's able this Elsie's kiss it's not
what's that it did yeah oh wow it's it's
not your favorite general I mean like
like okay yeah it's their own it's not
your tender love choice but it does get
does Griffith and sees the chorus
alright mmm-hmm yep but there's no like
there's no tension on it or anything it
isn't like it isn't lengthing with door
it isn't like the fly spell like it just
once it once it forms a circuit around
you it just communicates you
effortlessly mmm
up to the base of this so you know this
now sorry do you go up as well yeah yeah
I like cast I got a glance over so I'm
very curious about the exchange we had
but yeah then I'll go up so you commit
you commend yourself up through the
trunk and you are aware of it as you as
you travel up you are able to see
exemplars of your order hmm commending
you as you as you rise out like a Disney
ride right yeah wholly unnerving yeah
yes but they're the ones who determine
whether or not you're deserving so it's
not for you so as you sow it is you
emerge more or less than the
configuration you were down in the
basement and you can feel the ground
rumbling a bit
could be strain it could be straining
against the Nana's ear but you can you
can definitely feel that there is that
there's unease in the ground beneath and
as I say does now dawn is rising out in
this field
northwest of red larch in the desperate
Valley and you can see that the sky is
sort of moving into pinks and golds and
then as you look out over this field
look back toward red larch you can see
shapes building themselves constructing
themselves out of what looks to be a
dark liquid and you you have a bad
feeling instantaneously this reminds you
very much of the method of
transportation that you saw from drawn
enterprises they have some mechanism a
potion mechanism that they use to move
themselves and their charges via the via
the soil itself without being seen in
any way and so they're being constructed
and they're I mean they're perhaps a
hundred feet away like they're being
built out here and they're being built
in such a way they're being built in a
formation that is already present so you
can see this sort of like almost like a
curved phalanx type structure
manifesting itself up from the soil and
there's a single figure that started
behind it and then you see the rest of
it grow up around them like a forest I'm
saying to each of you whatever else you
knew of that of that story I'm going to
spill it now sorry sorry just in the
nick of time
I wasn't playing honest with you pulling
the collar like yeah no I I said it's
more with the agitation and there's more
like I'm is I'm angry I'm thinking now
about this crypt that this this this
being that it's just it's just a maggot
the same as everything else this one
needs children apparently it's it does
not deserve to even be held by this root
structure I'm gonna send a bomb down
that elevator
whatever the fantasy equivalent of a
fuel-air the bomb is impressive we're
gonna have to get a ruling so but
looking at this phalanx I say the drawn
enterprises kill her and this is while
while they are marching toward you yeah
he is spilling this I like supposed to
killer don't they want her dead that's
awesome
why would they want almonds sister dead
we need to get her I think families are
always nice I point to them I go I don't
want that in there when in town any
bright ideas so they're clear closer
than ever and and that the two the two
halves of this sort of semicircle make
way in the middle and you see she never
named herself but she was clearly some
kind of drought matriarch mmm your
contact that brought you to what you
suspected was water deep based on where
the Sun was over the water and the
general bustle of the and also the
classiness of the me oh yeah remember
well
no let's talk about because validation
she says cthe RIS Kath risk drought I
have already like I have I am oh yeah
it's an instinctively instinctively says
this is not this is not our arrangement
why don't you bring that out here now I
have to kill her again just to get
what's mine and then I can have to kill
the rest of you well I won't I brought
so I brought some people seems like
you're in your element
I guess marvelous yet what do you want
either way yeah you know what actually
you're quite right
you're quite right I am gonna kill her
myself though just to make absolutely
sure it's done but it doesn't look like
she's going anywhere I think I can take
my time with that but by all means
gentlemen if you could manage this
scenario for me I'll come in at the end
and then we'll get it all dealt with do
things look like figures that are solid
like are they also oh no no they are not
they're not drow they are definitely
they have a type of livery you haven't
seen before generally speaking when
you've encountered people who work for
acquisitions incorporated they come from
all walks of life there's no specific
outfit except for certain badges of
service you might wear in accordance
with your task right they have a very
clear like a regimental structure and
uniform how many are there there are
about 50 the the tree behind you reaches
down a gentle frond and places it on
your shoulder mm-hmm and says mother
does the war still rage I look at her
and I go
I say it ever rages here and she says I
can I can see this droughts are there
others I say I say there I say there are
I said there's a whole army here she
says at one point in time there may have
been and then beneath this beneath these
ranks of soldiers hmm proud red larch
trees erupt high into the air screaming
in pieces armor plates are flying off
they're killing each other in midair
with their own weapons these bursts are
just erupting underneath one at a time
and then the remainder are running
toward the party can I get some
initiative yeah what's the condition is
that drought Hoshi has withdrawn herself
all you're seeing is her is her her
phalanx being thrown into the air okay
so we don't actually don't actually know
where she isn't in fact because a
literal red large forest is being born
around you I should I should emphasize
for your use for your fanfics they're
not only erupting beneath the soldiers
they are erupting everywhere as far out
as you can see this area is being
reclaimed by the Enclave no it's like we
make that face initiative nice smells
good r-13 I got a 380
Oh Oh got some words - you got to go it
hey big spender
listen you wrote that no chewing at all
no Chris RIS drought what am i what am I
presented with um you are you are seeing
a forest grow before your very eyes and
you are seeing soldiers run toward you
some of whom are immediately launched
into the air or torn in half by these
savage branches as they erupt from the
soil yeah yeah take it at a point that
makes the most sense in terms of like a
from a trauma perspective yeah yeah
centered around me above my head right
uh I want to I'm gonna choose the most
densely crowded number surely there's a
few three or four that have cover
through there's a they're sort of moving
through a clearing you think any point a
tree might erupt yeah but these few it's
not it's like um imagine like a like a
pachinko machine like a certain number
of balls have gone into this reservoir
exactly and they they are very surprised
that they have not been impacted yet but
that might that might not last very long
no I hope it doesn't I'm gonna drop at
that point hunger the dark oh and let's
see how does it work you're gonna love
it
tell me more I don't know they may enjoy
it you open a gateway to the dark
between stars a region infested with
unknown Horrors a 20-foot radius sphere
of blackness and bitter cold appears
centered on point with range and lasting
for the duration of one minute it's
they're gonna get they're gonna get
frozen in there with two to six cold
damage and if they remain they're gonna
get battered by beer battered by my acid
tackles I can just enjoy that flavor so
I'm gonna
it's it's really a zone control zone
control yeah which is where I'm trying
to figure out the best choke point yeah
exactly so like I say there is a path
that they seem to be flowing through
here you might be able to cut that off
for them oh yeah thank you for pointing
that out within that area that they need
to succeed in a deck saving throw or
take 2d6 acid damage as milky
otherworldly tentacles rub against it
when was I hired to write in this you
remember Steve this is Mary on ran for a
Lovecraftian horror creamy exactly so to
remain in there for it to occur yeah it
looks like I just could place the zone
yeah and so whoever's caught within that
that 20 foot radius
anybody who starts their turn takes the
cold damage anybody who ends their turn
takes the acid damage yeah okay awesome
and it's also a rough terrain yeah I'll
bet yeah all those milky ass tentacles
all right yeah we have the Homer of
Heydar I'll manage that as it happens
now walnut dog grass and in their very
seat of your power right now
so um less this level okay so I put a
hand on my daughter this tree and I cast
plant growth in the form that it all
normal plants in a hundred foot radius
centered on her she's become thick and
overgrown but I was thinking that maybe
it would cause us so core of the trees
like help them
oh yeah it's interesting oh yeah exactly
mmm
that is the best great job one of the
best uses of plant growth I think ever
yeah exactly so your intention is
through your daughter to nourish these
trees as they are born help her succeed
exact you know what I mean it doesn't
that's whatever that's what we all want
for our children right absolutely so
you're gonna basically you're going to
Goose the natural processes that she is
accelerating yeah i'ma put some will
spit on a sauna
Rosi bee stinger yeah um
there are foes at present yeah some of
them have decided that they don't want
to walk through a dark orb okay some of
them are going another way and as you as
two of them approach you they are
knocked aside by this apply the contact
of drawn enterprises oh she has decided
that you would be a great way to make an
important point in this realm Wow
so she is now she is now before you two
daggers held opposite out of the out of
the bottoms of the of the hands she is
flanked on each side by people whose
faces will not sit still
all right does that does that remind me
of the shadow Rosie that we met no no it
isn't it isn't it isn't a shadow in
origin it's there in control of it they
just it's like they don't have to decide
what they look like I think okay I mean
as soon as they get close to you you
start to feel like a terrifyingly gentle
probe of your thoughts like you you
don't you don't feel like you are
thinking them alone you feel like they
are perfectly obvious to someone around
here Wow okay well I start just think of
like a really nasty stuff like the words
filthiness the worst kind of pornography
and
vanilla stuff through food words and a
variety of languages and then I'm gonna
do some grandma Mansi
um all of these trees are casting
shadows everywhere so yeah I mean we're
just now it's bad in the dawn they're
sort of fingers are reaching towards you
right okay
in the dawn grass ah this is the place
so I'd like to use the shadows of the
trees to actually make trees that grow
up as shadow and entangle these foes
sort of like a almost like a candy cane
shape I'd love to go around them but but
almost they'll like a tribute to the red
larches that exactly so there's two
forests yeah there is a forest that has
been born
it's basically your grandchildren rain
right yeah and there is another shadow
forest that you are positing in the same
space there's actually three if you
count my milk worms yeah the old milk
points forest it doesn't know it's the
old milk worms trick yeah so these other
milk one so basically these shadow trees
are born around them and so they are
just they are ensconced in every way
just contained within these trunk
prisons yes is forming around her hmm as
well all three of them appear to be
seized by this other forest that's
filling the gaps in the rest of this and
the rest of his new growth okay before I
end my turn as a bonus section I'm gonna
do a shadow step so I can teleport from
and into dim light or darkness within
sixty
we choose the advantage on attack but
I'm not gonna attack I just would like
to disappear just dunno they don't know
where I am that you yeah I like it so
I'm gonna try to I think shadow step
closer to when receta of you guys are I
don't know if we separate it but I feel
like we have yeah yeah to overtime yeah
you never calling these days Sojin soca
thrist you can see again this these
trees are tossing people into the air
but they're also guiding them through
this these woods you can see some let go
around the edge of the sphere you see
some walk through and then when they
come back on me when they emerge from
the other side of the orb they are
deeply changed they have had an
experience that is not a pleasant one
and exactly and they are their new men
and indeed three such creatures emerge
maddened from the other side of this orb
and try to descend upon you three three
oh it's a bummer that we spent all that
time and that CREP doesn't have any of
my any of my good stuff we got we got
arrested didn't we didn't remember their
rest of us who did it yeah yeah yeah I
was wondering this all that's what I
thought it was on point
yeah I burned what's your exact pattern
and this one so I got nothing
what's a 15 okay take a 6 - that doesn't
do it so there so they they have come
out and you can I mean you can still
smell the sort of acrid stench my love
of this play of this grim an even
grimmer forest
that means to me that they have the
dance recently taken a tour of theirs
there's their eyes are wild and they've
begun to jibber in in an unkempt
unseemly way that's not professional
let's just start there the novel it's in
well so you were standing here you are
close to your friend yes Rosie and there
are a bunch of enemies so I guess I will
also alt an Iowa Chacon akin title meant
the group pump it up I got five I'm
gonna use five in the next twenty
minutes in Kaioken this and and times
two times three so yeah so I'm gonna
yell at all just you still have her here
oh yeah yeah I'm I'm a tank I'm a
protector here so I'm also gonna someone
comes out I'm gonna kind of to shield it
to but I'm just like everybody cool so
these are are so I properly understand
what these things are these are not
people right these are sort of things
but they can be reasoned with or talk to
or they understand yeah they're
definitely have they have an intellect I
can be manipulated right in this way
five your chronic and title very well I
want them to I kind of want to freeze
them with the speech so the trees can
start messing yeah or maybe even get
them on our side everybody cool out
listen here daddy baby you don't know
nothing about no hard time Dena know
something about hard times hard times
was in this crypt you understand me
baby daddy and you Ric Flair call them
Ric Flair you don't know nothing about
no hard time see you at the contact from
broad enterprises are the Gennari Dream
know them hard time try to get them to
stop maybe it'd be sympathetic
maybe they turn on their friends I can
tell so you tell me it I use five
and of promo yeah I like it
saving it up save saving the hard time
is it so you cert yourself top of my
life screen exactly exactly like through
this through this newborn forest there's
a distant truck onyx wreak that sort of
that exists it provides a substrate for
your words and projects them out into
this forest you can see groups of people
as they're running closer you can see
some of them turning on each other like
like behind trees you can see two people
like disappearing behind a tree one
emerges like they are they are out there
they are out there shredding each other
you think that you think that were they
not firmly ensconced inside shadow trees
even more would be happening up here
with the three of them now something
that you note as you as you speak these
words because the three biggest threats
out of this out of this crew are before
you and you can see the the contact that
drawn enterprises contact
can I get perception roles in their
lives please your several desirable it's
it's not for jus Boone do we have more
than one elder what a cavity box you're
born then we're gonna sign two of these
motherfuckers if you are a subscriber of
course you can get this red box with our
signatures if not obviously we have the
other shit from the store I said of
course I mean coupon things so you can
see I mean very clearly for a half a
second and then
like merging back and forth I mean be
difficult when you're looking at it
through this
this shadow grip is that her face
changes many times it shifts between
multiple personages like inside the like
but while inside the grip of this tree
trunk okay is it just me I got a 20 oh
yes absolutely yeah you're able to see
this very clearly yeah you're at you're
able to you're able to see that this is
either this is something that they are
it's a glamour or it is you don't know
what it is but you know that you know
not to trust this shape okay dinar boats
in is over cuz Chris trout I got a lot
of heat a lot of heat yeah so I've still
got I've got three approaching me is
that correct
waiter three they're right in front of
you physically striking you okay and
you're I mean my presumption is that
Chris doesn't really respond to things
like this yeah it's sort of like it's
hampering my regular movement yeah and
then there's the pain of it but I don't
care for that yeah it's really yeah
that's what this is why I took that the
damage then these these three beasts
I don't got much for them I let me just
can't even do that one right so it's
it's eldritch blast for them why not see
what it does stasia yeah here we go
that's not a for my friend an 18 for the
podcast yeah it's 18 and if you really
want my plus seven to that you can enjoy
and then so I'm gonna choose to separate
one you need okay that's a three for the
podcast
yes that's so so separated them and then
the one in the middle can just continue
to hit me yeah so how do you how does
this when kethry strobe issues and
Eldridge blasts
how is Locati built into that how does
it look I guess you could conjure it
from the head I don't know if it's from
the mouth oh yeah I want to and that
like using it like Zeus's Thunderbolt
where I actually game the head yeah cuz
then I get dizzy right but I think it
would be appropriate to slam his tail
down into the ground and then have it
shoot yeah exactly I want yeah so yeah
you let's go wherever where its eyes are
everything from the eyes so you so you
woman you pierce this fresh soil with
the bottom of Locati
and then his mouth creaks open and then
a single purple ball curious hungry
begins to lash out at foes one of one of
them is caught square in the throat and
collapses the other one was a miss okay
um so walnut dawn grass yeah what's
going on so I see this like person there
this is just like yes hello telecaring
out here so I am going to go ahead and
with my corrupt Oh magic trying cast
dispel magic on that person so it's one
creature within range which it is and
any spell of third level or lower on the
target would end and each spell a fourth
level or higher you'd make an ability
check using my spell casting ability the
DC equals plus ten the spells level and
a smells level is that is a tune for me
I'm sorry that's a three for me so it's
at 13 okay
try to strip all magic I want to see
yeah I get rid of everything on that
person okay so what does that look like
when you try to do it so when one that
tries to do it it's like I just like I
imagine her like like slashing the air
low just like pulling it off yeah
yes exactly exactly so she drops out of
the shadow prison that is holding her
the first thing that his spell magic
does is shred the grandma man see
so she falls so she falls down and then
and then it her figures coalesce her
features coalesce again Wow and then she
she walks forward as she's walking
forward she takes a moment to sort of
like slap her her sort of honor guard
yeah that is still imprisoned she's
walking and meet you directly towards
you without okay okay sure great
oh wait that's your turn using a
movement you the next turn is actually
Rosie beasting good she can't attack
attack wearing off like I'm walking
toward you yeah don't strip off
information presence right okay so I see
this I see walnut it destroys my grammar
man see hold on this creature oops and
then and then she starts she's like
going for walnut right yeah I'm gonna do
it again yeah no this is not something
that Rosie would normally do she wants
him she wants to act cautiously and with
with efficiency and and with economy you
know but blowing at Grandma man see to
stop whatever that is from touching
walnut yes definitely what's about to
happen
so walnut walnut is I think like taken
aback by this reddest thing and Rosie it
goes oh and then just like tries tries
to get the the shadow
the big red larch your your daughter so
she's now trying to lasso that and throw
it with no plan whatsoever directly back
at this woman there's not there's not a
plan to imprison her or anything it's
just to get them away get the fuck away
for your bitch so so basically what
happens is that your daughter is
watching all of this in a placid way she
knows that a thousand years the enclave
will be victorious sure but there are
moments like this do have a unique
texture and she wants to capture as much
of it as she can so that she can teach
others yeah great you see you hear a
crack echo through the woods and you can
see a shadow version of the tree of this
larch with her face in it and a strained
terrifying shadow version of it fall
down and collapse directly on this
interloper but just flattening her
knocking her to the ground okay you're
about the very moment see and she's like
I'm not mad it's okay it's okay I'm not
mad
but isn't that kids no voice again yeah
I'm not mad so um from the ground so she
is she is cracked and she is hurt by it
okay like usually no no personally
physically you can see she her garb is
unique in that it has where you might
have bolts or knives she has a
combination of thin daggers and then
what look like flasks okay so when she's
Quinn she has crashed to the ground
several of these flasks are broken and
begin to mix and pour over the front of
her leather armor she is on her feet in
a second like her like from the ground
to her feet at a moment's with without a
single moment's hesitation and then she
withdraws a dagger and then throws it at
the woman that dinar is holding oh not
what do you want to do dinner
Oh in that moment in a moment I would
tank that yeah I pit-a-pat know yeah
okay can't be poisoned that's great yeah
um you take seven points I was waiting
for the second syllable next turn is
dinar Blitzen alright so I'm like yuck
ouch uh so how many is she's the only
threat right right now restorations gun
it's bedlam yeah they're either fighting
each other being beat up by trees right
right okay so and though the force isn't
finished growing too it's continued to
spread out from these rings how far is
she from me the threat right now she's
let's see
two feet okay all right so she's kind of
close um I all will my especially with
with them holding something is very
important to dinner dinner it's always
holding his egg is always holding
something great stuff so uh I guess I'll
do trends better I don't know
you got a pick all right I'll do a
warding bond yeah so well while holding
our I'll touch her and then spells
boards a willing creature you touch
creates a mystic connection between you
and the target until the spell ends well
the targets within 60 feet gains +1
bonus to AC and saving Thrones has a
resistance all damaged but we share like
I have a bond so when she takes damage I
take damage you split it no I take it oh
you take another case yeah that's
perfect situation in our nice so I'll do
that as an action and then I guess she's
close enough so I'll kind of hold her in
good and tight and then I only have one
real ranged attack so there's gonna be a
little bit more
he's doing it I'm holding you tight to
make sure nothing spills out so she's
just like Merida later attacking really
how much is the thing yeah 86 to do that
46 7 right - yeah that does not go well
so this acid cone includes her and her
two associates nice for a heap
bookkeeping here okay okay that sounds
good yeah they're dripping out I mean
that it's you can see that like the this
mixture of materials is starting to sort
of like fizz and foam on her armor
mm-hmm
that's dinar Blitzen and now it's cthe
wrist robe so you've got two special
friends that all like you you like me a
lot how far are we away from this this
this drought woman combat but you are
off to the left you want to try to find
the right space for your hunger of Adar
so but you are not super far away when
you're only 30 feet from that okay I'm
just trying to figure out how much yeah
I can combine tasks multitask right I
think I'd rather like so these these two
are even as they beat on me I'm still
looking over at the
growl woman is the real sources no no no
that yeah
not these yes like sword lands
yes sinks in no no come on not this
tentacular spent spectacular is it erupt
if I can reach that that drow yeah I
want to place it near her yeah well
there are others day I want to do trying
to noon behind her because I know that
she's close to you right it's just far
enough away that I had the use in it
yeah ranged attacker forget yeah so you
want to try to find a host what's dead
near there exactly there's there's lots
there is carnage galore in this place
that you can take advantage of let's do
it and in fact I will take advantage
thank you for saying we go well there's
an Arcana yeah so we're looking at
garbage filth yeah that's a 10 and then
this is would be oh okay hey that's 20
or so did you it really happened
everybody it really happens it really
happened a good role good yeah right at
the end in the last episode wow there's
a lot of there is a true forest birth
northwest of red large and there is a
dark forest made of shadows that was
summoned by rosy be stinger now there is
a third forest so and you know you know
how it's going to work you can see
there's just bodies everywhere it's the
only interesting thing in your field of
vision is these shredded corpses so at
once you find one and you can sort of
see how you can erupt the closer one
here through a chain of other bodies
oh yeah so it says that I can judge them
and I have to each mentally yeah exactly
what would be the right spot exactly so
you find one and then it's just like a
rhizome it just turns inside out and
purple like shredding purple quartz leap
out and then it leaps out and then one
chain of this goes completely somewhere
else you don't know it's gonna found a
town or something it's gonna found a
town where purple tentacles can finally
be free a little nervous about that one
so this one the other one arcs over but
but not like an electricity like a
physical think goes over and then routes
around in this body this body sprouts
several purple legs hmm and then crawls
its way over to the next one and then
just makes a pile of bodies and then a
traditional fronds emerge from that and
one of them have one of them erupts
directly through curved back walnut dung
grass the guy who's making it oh yeah
exactly just like just like just like a
little thing just looks back and exact
but it's also it's her but it's also her
met her entourage these these tough
fellows who haven't had a chance to
really flex their muscle yet next up is
walnut Danko dog grass so thank you sir
thank you thank you very much I don't
know oh my god I sorry I just thought
about how I'm gonna call this holiday
Thanksgiving okay so real quick I only
got one left I hope it's a good one
I'm going to
this is all garbage wild tape wildest
shape the wildest shape a weasel yeah I
leave I go home sorry sorry no I'm gonna
do the spider yeah no not sorry why did
I say that I read that I'm doing the
wolf obviously yeah yeah back yeah yeah
can I get that one who shot a classic
wolf night well no I cast a wolf for the
end the ship widened the one that's
gonna do anything else I'm sorry I'm a
one-trick pony yeah oh yeah shoot nobody
get packed tactics okay yes
so I'm going to try and do one last
fight for old times sake I want to jump
in there I mean with the tentacles done
writhing are they forever writhing oh
they're just it's three huh yeah it's
there but feel free to but then I'll
bite one of the other guys no that's
contained okay you want a bite yeah yeah
I think but listen no one else's so what
are you saying is that no one needs a
Buy button up nobody there's people who
need to get bit fighter okay I'll bite
oh yeah they gotta get think I get
natural advantage on this because I'm
close to my friends cuz you're great my
what feels right I'm gonna bite what
feels right advantage I guess I was a -
podcast okay because that was the - oh
wow it's a fourteen that's not enough
well then I snarl out a real good yeah
so using 612 so you move up oh yeah
twelve snarl - boy that's the worst kind
you move up on your paws yeah and you're
you're snapping it but there's also this
tentacle that doesn't seem to have any
awareness that's fine a friend or foe
yeah sure
well I got Rosie beast on me okay ah
we've got three three deuce
I'll just give them a class these close
ones over here
whatever we just do this close it up
yeah yeah yeah so I'm going to do two
staff hits on the drow woman and
and I will - - punch - punch for two
friends so against her as a 20 and a 17
mm-hmm much better than cool and then
the punches shall be not enough that's
11 and a 19 statue so she gets to staff
hits and a punch
I will also stunned her with that first
snake pit which means that I get you can
actually get advantage on you think what
I didn't mean it okay
so uh so she gets a big ol cup full of
11 + 8 damage and then her friends gets
who twelve damaged from my mighty legs
amazing and she stuns alright
unless she does it con safe but
tentacles chest 20 alright yeah actually
womp womp womp it's the last one just
because it's the bad guys don't mean
that you don't get cool shit that's
right um shadow council mayor leavers
please you portentous drone has
delivered you a boon hmm it's true these
these brutal these brutal hits that
would have felled when you feel this is
as good as you can stun this is exactly
the point at which on on a regular
person this would be the place that you
hit and as you hit that point every part
of her physicality changes she is a
completely different person she brings
herself off of this tentacle and down to
her knees and when she looks up you
think that you have seen this face
before you think that you have seen
you think back to the picture to the
pictures that were drawn and the mirror
and this is a face this is the practiced
face right that this entity has taken on
and on her knees in front of you on her
turn she withdraws a potion pops the
stopper on it drinks it and melts in
front of you directly into the ground
melty travel the other two are free of
their shadow bonds and are trying to
make a break for it directly back out so
them if you would like to get at attack
of opportunity if you do right yeah real
quick everybody does all right I take a
yeah whip-snap take out flosses so
affectionately been labeled before we're
cursed buddy that's good that's a
nineteen oh one of the elders for us
eight points of damage okay explode
hey what I'm one of them one of them
just collapses as they're running a few
a few half-hearted crawls away the other
escapes navigating all three of the
forests you have I take my staff at you
in a rise back to me and like blow on it
like it's a gun on me an offended that I
continue to know that maybe they have
they have left and it's up to you if
that's okay that's yeah so they bought
they make they make their way out the
rumbling in the soil has ceased what do
you do I said take off Fisher back yeah
take her home take her to her mom yeah
yeah okay well so you say you walk so
you walk
ways through the trees were gentle
enough to leave a little space for the
cart it's tilted up a little bit you
kind of you kind of have coriander's
folded up for ian's coriander expands
tugs it off of this little stump and
your tray you expertly navigate through
this new maze that you have made I mean
I do have a thing about it my daughter
yeah yeah there are I mean it's a this
is a forest like there's no other word
for it
great good I was just gonna say that um
why would you have to say goodbye I was
just gonna tell her that the worst
ceased for now oh yeah so I say um you
know daughter for now the war has ceased
but they may come again may it always
and she nods her head and then goes back
and then the the trunk of the tree seals
up so it's a good a quiet ride from this
new forest which we'll have to name mhm
back to back to the drawn-in quarter
yeah
it's about noon that sign is swinging in
a crisp breeze acquisitions incorporated
logo below the box out front stuffed
with new jobs as you walk in to the
drawn and quarter you hear the sound of
a lute and you can see audre courtier is
there and she looks over you and then
without without missing a note says your
walnut Brahmas told me some things and
then she takes a moment just to look you
over and says I get it
hey Rosie guys cuz we have important
business and then stay when when dinar
comes in that's when the music stops hmm
prophetess has thus prophetess was
enjoying a moment ago Audra's gentle
teasing and there isn't there isn't a
moment upon looking at her daughter that
she doubts her identity in any way she
rushes from behind the bar and then puts
an arm under and then takes her away
from you and then in a quiet voice she
looks back at the inn and says we're
closed
that is season 1 of acquisitions
incorporated the c-team thank you so
much for coming with us and hanging out
and listening to our story it's been a
real pleasure it's one of my favourite
things that it's one of the best parts
of my life and a big part of that is
that you enjoy it as well hey we're
gonna come back with some table talk
here in a sec don't go nowhere but like
I said from everybody here at the c-team
thank you so much
you