JERRY: Hello. I am Tycho Brahe of Penny Arcade and PAX.
JERRY: (shouting) Shut up! RYAN: (snorts of laughter)
(laughing) I am Tycho Brahe of Penny Arcade and PAX,
I'm also Ominifis Hereward Dran of Acquisitions Incorporated.
But today I am Jerry Holkins, and I'm here to run a game of Dungeons &amp; Dragons for my friends!
To my right!
We have the dragonborn narcissist...
Donaar Blit'zen.
RYAN: (clapping) KATE: That's an opinion.
RYAN: (clapping)
RYAN/KATE: (clapping)
JERRY: The self clap.
JERRY: Don't encourage this. KRIS: That was for your character.
KRIS: Not for yourself. Which is good. RYAN: Yeah.
KRIS: We like the character. RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: Amy the Falcon... RYAN: Hate Ryan.
JERRY: maintaining... KATE: Oh god. Those guns.
AMY: (straining) I'm working out.
JERRY: maintaining the druid character, week after week.
Support you 100% in that.
AMY: Thank you. I appreciate it.  JERRY: Walnut Dankgrass.
RYAN: Fix your microphone. JERRY: Fix my what?
KRIS: Top your mic. RYAN: Yeah. Stop flexing.
KATE: Pop that mic out. Flash a little chest! AMY: You're introducing the most important people.
KRIS: You're too strong. RYAN: You need a V.
JERRY: How's this? RYAN: Get that V.
JERRY: Is this the right way? KRIS: Back to one! Everybody back to one.
JERRY: How's this, Laura QQ? Laura QQ, does that...
RYAN: Should we start over?
JERRY: I fixed the microphone. I may call for an air-horn later.
JERRY: What?
KRIS: What the heck guys? All right vamp.
Ryan, some of that classic jokes. Give us that heat.
RYAN: Ah... What's the deal with airline peanuts? Am I right?
Who are they trying to keep out of those things?
KATE: That's true. RYAN: It's like-- How much time I got left?
(laughter)
KRIS: That is not funny! Have you seen the news lately? Oh my god...
JERRY: What do you think, QQ?
JERRY: Is it sort of like a person talking now? Right. KATE: It sounds good, folks!
JERRY: Still Ryan. Still Amy. All right.
KATE: How about me? JERRY: You are Kate Welch.
KATE: That's true. That's me. JERRY: Not your grandma's grandma. Rosie Beestinger.
JERRY: We have K'thriss Drow'b.
OC, deepest, darkest part of the diary, character insert.
KRIS: Yes. No one can know, except everyone. JERRY: Exactly. Yeah-- (laughs)
JERRY: That's the optimal scenario.  KRIS: It's very public.
JERRY: We are back at it again, folks.
When last we saw our heroes...
they had just received their official license to operate
with exclusive domain in the whole of the Dessarin Valley.
You got the impression from the proprietor of the Dran &amp; Courtier
that it has been quite a while since there was a chapter of AcqInc operated out of this inn.
And there may be a particular purpose for that.
You were not able to get much more information,
even though you tried to (muffled) go the Mom route.
You were not able to get all the way into those protective plates.
You decided your roles.
We have Donaar Blit'zen is our Decisionist, after some wrassling--
RYAN: Leader. The leader.  JERRY: Leader, okay.
JERRY: Walnut Dankgrass is our... AMY: Documancer.
JERRY: Documancer, right.
JERRY: Rosie Beestinger. KATE: Cartographer.
JERRY: Cartographer.
Goes along with your astronomical fascinations.
KATE: I make all kinds of maps, Jerry.  JERRY: That's right. That's right.
JERRY: Skies, and the land below.
We have K'thriss Drow'b is the Hoardsperson.
KRIS: I am the Hoardsperson.
JERRY: Yeah. So it is your task to secure supplies for journeys,
also to keep track of the wealth that you generate.
And then ultimately...
to sort of push those funds in ways that will improve the franchise...
mechanically and narratively here in the Dran &amp; Courtier.
KATE: I trust you completely.
JERRY: You shouldn't.
JERRY: We spoke at length over the weekend.  KATE: Shit...
JERRY: He's like literally the worst person for this job. KRIS: No, no, no. He's a changed drow.
RYAN: We're all in the wrong roles.
KATE: Not me! RYAN: Which is the best. No, you're in the wrongest.
AMY: I want to believe that you look at everything we get and you go,
Does this have to do with my dark lord? Nope! Right in the garbage.
KRIS: That's very important to K'thriss.  KATE: Just over the shoulder.
JERRY: Just straight into some crevasse. Infinite crevasse.
KRIS: Yeah. AMY: It's true.
JERRY: But as you recall, Walnut Dankgrass,
there were two job scrolls inside your official pack.
AMY: There were. JERRY: That it is your task to cart hither and yon.
AMY: Mm-hmm.
JERRY: And the mission that you decided to take,
without revealing, necessarily, the rest of the information to your fellows,
was a job from one Lord Vizgig Cartinwheel.
AMY: Right. JERRY: Sent directly to the Head Office.
JERRY: The payment will also be sent there and your cut will be sent to the Dran &amp; Courtier.
This task is called, The Raiding Must Cease.
And it describes a rash of cart raids between Stone Bridge and Beliard.
Which is a region sort of to the northeast of Red Larch.
AMY: Okay.
JERRY: You have to take a-- You go straight up the Long Road which Red Larch is on.
Take a right on the Stone Road.
It's going to be the trip.
But, part and parcel of this job--
Indeed, one of the reasons that you probably took it,
was because it includes partial payment in the form of a cart.
And there is even a coupon...
AMY: Sure.
JERRY: included in the document that says, Waelvur's Wagonworks.
And then it specifically says,
Not Thelorn's Safe Journeys.
JERRY: And this is underlined several times. AMY: Right.
JERRY: And then below that it says, Prince and Princess.
And you had heard it was not far from the Dran &amp; Courtier.
Right across the main road that goes north-south through town.
Which becomes on either side the Long Road.
And when we shut our adventure down last time--
AMY: This is the part I was waiting for.  JERRY: Yeah.
JERRY: You were looking across the street and you saw a place from which
you would not purchase any of the products that they had necessarily on display.
And that was where we left off.
Now it is time for you to take the reins!
And let's see what happens next.
AMY: I'm hoping they keep the good ones in the back, and they keep the junk...
AMY: The ones for the adventurers... KRIS: Yeah.
AMY: they keep it behind the desk. KRIS: It's the consumer stuff in the window.
KRIS: Prosumer... JERRY: You want the prosumer-- It's got the big lens...
KRIS: Oh yeah. It's got wheels.
JERRY: Everywhere.
AMY: All right, so let's walk on in and inquire about Mr. Vizgig Cartinwheel.
JERRY: All right, well as you approach Waelvur's Wagonworks,
there's a sequence of-- sort of like an old trainyard.
There is a sequence of buildings in sort of a semicircle
behind the main open area where carts can roll in and out.
AMY: Gotcha.
JERRY: Basically, you think they must dismantle or re-mantle, for lack or a better term, the carts back there.
And as you approach, you see... a decent cart...
AMY: Mmm...
JERRY: emerging from one of these cart stables in the back.
Roll out in that turnabout in the front,
and then come to rest there at the entrance to the facility.
AMY: Well this is good news that the carts work. I've been thinking about it all week.
And I was wondering, do they even roll?
KRIS: That's the one they roll out anytime somebody walks in. Like they're all like this one.
JERRY: Yeah. KATE: The model home cart.
AMY: Exactly. Exactly. JERRY: They're all at least this good.
AMY: Okay, so let's find somebody that's in charge.
Do we see anybody that looks like they work there?
JERRY: When this thing rolls out, three or four children, maybe 11 to 13, run out. Begin polishing the wheels...
AMY: Good, shine it up good for us kids.
JERRY: Exactly, exactly,
Behind that, there is a small dry fountain in the center of this.
And then just beyond that you think must be the sales floor.
There's basically just a very simple opening in this shack,
that sort of stands out in front of the half circle.
AMY: Okay, great.
Well, I motion everybody like....
AMY: Do we want to... get to it? KRIS: Yeah, absolutely.
AMY: Okay. I didn't know if we wanted to do any backtalking like,
Hey so what's the deal with these carts?
AMY: Do we want this? Do we want to do this? JERRY: This cart sucks!
RYAN: Well once we talk to someone, I want to establish specifically what cart we get ahead of time.
AMY: Oh okay, sure, sure, sure. KRIS: Yeah. I don't want to get my heart set on it.
RYAN: Yeah. I want the blue one.  KATE: The Prince and Princess cart sounds promising.
AMY: It's true. KATE: Could be a really nice cart.
AMY: Could also be a lemon. All right. Well let's go inside towards the sales floor.
JERRY: Absolutely. You approach the window.
It has a sign. Just above it says "Waelvur's."
W-A-E-L-V-R-S, for those who like to write notes.
And you see a man set down a blacksmith's hammer
and then wipe his hands on a rag as you approach.
AMY: Mm-hmm. Okay. Great.
For someone who takes notes, this isn't the one they said not to go to, right?
KATE: No, that one is Thelorn's. AMY: Thank you.
KATE: I have this listed as a positive quality of Waelvur's,
Not Thelorn's.
KATE: And I underlined it a lot. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Okay. JERRY: Kate! Excuse me.
JERRY: Rosie! AMY: That's why I looked directly at you.
AMY: I'm like, I know you've got my back on this. Thanks.
JERRY: Rosie Beestinger.
AMY: Okay. Yeah let's walk up holding the missive.  JERRY: The coupon?
AMY: Yeah. Now let me ask you, wait--
Quick question for going forward.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah.  AMY: Did he name it, The Raiding Must Cease?
AMY: Or is that for like... metagame that we know it?
JERRY: The Raiding Must Cease is literally the name of the job that came into the Head Office.
AMY: All right, so I want to walk in and I want to say,
We're here about the raiding that has to cease, and we're here to cease it.
KRIS: We're not here to do the raiding.
KRIS: We're here regarding... raiding. RYAN: Should we ask for Vizgig?
KATE: We will end the raiding.
AMY: Well, I'm assuming he'll tell me where it is. RYAN: Just kick the door in and just be like...
KRIS: Take me to your finest Vizgig.
AMY: Sure.  JERRY: He reaches his hand out and...
AMY: I do not hand it over, but I open it for him to see it.
JERRY: All right.
Gets down and looks close. Because the coupon portion is near the bottom there. Says...
"Prince and Princess?"
AMY: That's what it says.
KATE: You better believe it.
JERRY: "(scoffs)"
JERRY: "All right, well no, it's-- That's... You'll-- Yeah, It's good."
AMY: Okay... KATE: See? Sounds good.
AMY: Hmm.
JERRY: As you turn around, you see that cart drive away and then head north through town.
You can see him leave, now there's just this dark rectangle inside this shack.
And a cart...
If there is a point-- Imagine a continuum...
where you have a cart, and not a cart.
Imagine that there is a point just past not a cart.
Imagine that there is, over here in this, where if anything happened to it,
It would be just as bad as not having a cart.
That is the cart that is wheeled out in front.
And the exhausted beast that is pulling it...
is clearly in the midst of some kind of existential crisis.
Two boys are steadily encouraging it out to the round with a rubbery carrot.
AMY: Mmm... great. Love that.
Okay. Well...
KATE: Never look a gift cart in the mouth.
KATE: That's what I always say. AMY: Never look a gift cart in the mouth.
KRIS: She's a beaut. RYAN: I don't get it.
KATE: She's a beautiful... I'll tell you when you're older.
RYAN: All right. KATE: All right!
AMY: I look at Donaar and I go... RYAN: Like a day?
AMY: Do we think this is the best cart we can get?
Like, as an aside,
Do we think we can negotiate anything better?
RYAN: Oh, I'm not doing this job for that cart.
KRIS: I think what we should... RYAN: I say that.
KRIS: Well, maybe what we can do is do the work, and then impress them.
And once they see that... they'll be, you know, so thankful...
KATE: That's an adorable idea.
KATE: Why don't I try-- RYAN: This will look good on our portfolio?
KATE: Why don't I try a little Rosie Beestinger charm on this guy.
JERRY: You're going to sting it a little bit? All right.
KATE: I'm going to sting it, I'm going to sting it. Okay. AMY: Absolutely.
RYAN: Who are we charming? Are we even... JERRY: Going to charm the horse!
RYAN: Are you charming the cart itself? &gt;&gt; KRIS: Be healthier! KATE: I'm going to charm...
KATE: Monsieur Waelvur himself, if I have to.
RYAN: Oh.
JERRY: Tell me what you're doing.
KATE: I'm going to lean heavily on my quarterstaff, I lean oh so heavily.
JERRY: Like, too heavily. KATE: So heavily.
KATE: I only weigh 28 lbs, but somehow--
KATE: I'm exerting at least 200 lbs of force on this thing. JERRY: It's a seismic event.
KATE: (grunts)
Sir.
You wouldn't make an old woman ride in something like that, would you?
JERRY: Lets see some dice here, kid.  KATE: All right.
AMY: What do you got?
KATE: Is this intimidation? Am I intimidating you with my old age or is this just a charisma?
KRIS: Persuasion. KATE: Persuasion.
JERRY: Yeah, this is "persuage", and I'm going to apply disadvantage to this roll.
KRIS: Dang, son! KATE: You're a turd man.
JERRY: I'm a Dungeon Master.
KATE: Okay well that's a 17 plus two so that's a 19.
JERRY: Yeah, that's a good roll. AMY: But...
KATE: And that's a three plus two. JERRY: That's five.
KATE: That's not as good as a 19.
JERRY: Yeah. KATE: For those keeping track at home.
JERRY: He says...
"If you had tried that on my father..."
"it might have worked."
KATE: I like the sound of him.
(laughter)
RYAN: Yeah, have we like asked this guy's name? KATE: Where's he at?
RYAN: Are we making a lot of assumptions? This guy just came out with an oily rag and we're like...
RYAN: persuading him? KRIS: He does work here.
JERRY: As a mechanic! JERRY: You just persuade anybody who has a rag.
AMY: He brought out the cart. KATE: It's Red Larch!
KATE: If his name's Waelvur's Wagonworks, he's probably Waelvur.
KRIS: He's got a name tag. RYAN: Does he have a name tag?
AMY: You can ask him. Ask him.  KATE: You ask him.
RYAN: Dude, are you the one who sent this? Fella?
JERRY: "We are contracted with Lord Vizgig Cartinwheel to offer our renowned Prince and Princess package."
"As part and parcel of jobs that he occasionally sends out to adventurers."
JERRY: "Adventurers like yourself."
RYAN: I'm a prince. JERRY: "Adventurers I am profoundly exhausted by."
RYAN: I'm a prince. And this is not princely, my friend.
KRIS: Yeah, we came here for a reward that's part and parcel, not a cart that's partial.
AMY: (gasps) Oh! KATE: Whoa!
AMY: Oh, write that down! Good stuff from the episode!
JERRY: He looks back at the cart, back at the horse, at you, and says,
"I don't know..."
JERRY: "See a resemblance." RYAN: Oh. Oh, all right!
KATE: Wow, he just called you busted! RYAN: Oh. You called me an old horse? Ugh.
RYAN: All right, I'm going to intimidate this guy.  KATE: Yes!
RYAN: I'm going to intimidate the crap out of him.
KATE: Rosie silently fist pumps. RYAN: I'm going to get all in his face.
JERRY: Cool, enjoy a disadvantage roll.  AMY: Wish I had guidance.
RYAN: So if you say that before I say advantage? JERRY: Yes, exactly.
KATE: He really wants us to have this shitty cart.
AMY: He's got so many disadvantages.
JERRY: This is Dungeons &amp; Dragons. There's all kinds of ways for you guys to live.
RYAN: Yeah by rolling two 20s, my friend.  JERRY: Yeah double 20s.
JERRY: I'm going to roll 40, you piece of shit!
RYAN: 11 plus 5 or...
KRIS: You got a hot...Oh, you got intimidate.  RYAN: Nine plus five.
JERRY: So 14? RYAN: 14.
JERRY: No... RYAN: (scoff)
KATE: (scoff) JERRY: No. I mean...
RYAN: So I get all up in his face and I say...
RYAN: Listen, oil rag, get me a better frigging cart!
JERRY: If he could get another rag out,
and then wipe off another set of hands at this point, he would.
Like I think that this has happened before,
and I think that he is familiar with the kind of game
that upstart adventures operate in this context.
RYAN: Dungeons &amp; Dragons?
KRIS: Could we talk to your father please?
KATE: I like the sound of him.
KRIS: I'm not rolling for that. It's just what I say.
JERRY: "I don't know where he is."
KRIS: Oh. AMY: Can I attempt to Charm Person at this point?
JERRY: Yeah.  AMY: Hmm.
AMY: So we're not fighting, so he does not get advantage.
KRIS: Ever...
AMY: If he fails a wisdom saving throw, you are charmed by me.
JERRY: You are hereby charmed by me! AMY: Be charmed by me, damn it!
JERRY: And not Walnut Dankgrass, I mean charmed by Amy the Falcon!
AMY: That's me. KRIS: (soaring hawk sounds)
JERRY: Wisdom save?
AMY: Yes. RYAN: Turn into a bear. That'll scare him.
JERRY: What's your spell DC? AMY: What is my spell DC...
JERRY: (singing) Spell DC!
AMY: 13. JERRY: K.
KATE: Don't you win this roll.
KRIS: Boy. He's going to be so mad--
KRIS: when he finds out he's been charmed. JERRY: No, he's charmed. &gt;&gt; KATE: He's charmed!
AMY: He's charmed? KATE: He's charmed!
AMY: Oh no, what a tragedy.
JERRY: So he cannot attack you, that's true.
RYAN: We're safe!
AMY: Well no, now we can get him to-- JERRY: Is he more afraid of you than his father, I guess.
AMY: That's what I want to know. Okay, so.
Now that we've done that, and he cannot attack me...
KRIS: I was very concerned.
AMY: Hang on, hang on. He regards us as a friendly acquaintance, though.
JERRY: That's right. Yeah, yeah.  AMY: So we've bought some favor with him.
AMY: It's not just practical.
Okay and at this point I would...
I mean I guess we're all out of persuasion checks, but I'll try it...
KRIS: I've got a really good persuasion check. AMY: Oh yeah, lets do it. K'thriss.
KRIS: What would you-- What's the best-- What are we trying to accomplish here?
AMY: All right. I pull you aside and I'm like... RYAN: Better reward, right?
AMY: Listen, buddy. This cart is just not going to get us where we need to go.
Just see if you can sweeten the deal. Anything. Better horse...
KRIS: Okay, let me make a persuasion attempt of my own.
JERRY: Okay. KRIS: All right, here we go...
KRIS: I'm going to take advantage. Are you going to disadvantage me on this one?
JERRY: I could. &gt;&gt; KATE: Don't do it. KRIS: You beast!
KRIS: You know what? I'm going to burn my advantage.
JERRY: Okay, all right. KRIS: Take that!
KRIS: Wind it back.
All right, so we got a-- that was a 16.
And that was a 19!
JERRY: Okay. Now what is the case you are trying to make?
KATE: Let's see some roleplay. JERRY: Keeping in mind that this is--
JERRY: I mean, you're looking around like...
You don't actually know how far the needle bends here.
But you suspect that with your oratory,
you might be able to maximize this scenario.
KRIS: Friend.
I travel with three very sick people in my charge.
KRIS: We have an infirm woman. AMY/KATE: (coughs)
KRIS: And... RYAN: I cough up some acid. (gagging sounds)
KRIS: And a reasonably disgusting dragon man.
And we don't know what her problem is yet!
KRIS: Science! Cannot describe it. RYAN: Lot of guesses. We got a lot of guesses.
JERRY: It's something we talk about a lot. RYAN: Yeah!
KRIS: It's a syndrome. Multiple things.
KRIS: But no cause. JERRY: She's at the crossroads of disease.
KRIS: Right. RYAN: Yeah.
KRIS: And I'm afraid that giving us this cart in exchange for the work we're going to do to you
would be like a triple murder.
JERRY: He's like, "Well the job-- the job's not from me."
"If..."
"Do I look like a lord to you?"
KRIS: Where's the lord that we--
We showed you the paper.
We just want to do the work and allow you continue with yours.
JERRY: "Here. Show me the paper."
KRIS: I don't have it, but--
AMY: I'll show it again.
JERRY: "Here, just-- just--"
AMY: Don't. JERRY: "No, no. It's like-- Come on."
AMY: Don't touch it. JERRY: "No, we're--"
RYAN: You charmed him already.
JERRY: "Yeah, yeah. We're--" KATE: We're good.
JERRY: "Yeah." AMY: Okay. I very begrudgingly hand it over.
JERRY: "You're new here. Just let me take a look."
He looks over and he says, "This..."
"This job went to your employer."
"From someone who employs us."
"We're both being crushed beneath the boot here."
KATE: Bureaucracy. RYAN: Yeah.
KATE: Subcontract. RYAN: We need to seize the means of production.
JERRY: "You and I are down here in this situation."
"We're both being manipulated."
KRIS: Hmm.
JERRY: "That being said..." KRIS: Roll to explain...
KATE: Still-- (cough) still need a cart. RYAN: Yeah.
KATE: (coughs) That's better than this one. JERRY: "That being said..."
JERRY: "that's the cart I have."
AMY: Hmm. KRIS: Hmm.
JERRY: "But..."
"I might be able to do something about the horse."
KATE: Nice.
AMY: Put him out of its misery? KRIS: You should. Yeah.
KATE: Wow. (laughs)
KRIS: I am hungry.
KATE: Zero tolerance policy for shitty horses from Walnut.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, yeah. All this does is it continues Walnut's aggressive policy against animals.
KATE: Yep. RYAN: Yeah.
KATE: Very anti-animal. JERRY: That manifests itself in each game!
AMY: I just wanted to play a druid so I can murder as many fantastical creatures as I--
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. It's like the opposite...
KATE: Squirrels. Eagles. JERRY: of Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them.
KRIS: It's garbage. Yeah. JERRY: So it's like this...
JERRY: He whistles.
You see another point cloud of these small boys emerge from wherever they emerge from.
They would now decouple this still objectively bad horse.
KRIS: Yeah.
JERRY: Wheeling back around behind, they pull out a marginally less angry and disappointing horse.
KRIS: Now we're talking. AMY: What color is it?
JERRY: It's black. AMY: K.
AMY: Interesting. JERRY: What?
KRIS: I guess-- JERRY: Laura QQ, why don't you come and do it?
AMY: We'll cut it out. JERRY: No, no. It's because you're a pro,
JERRY: you do this shit all the time. KATE: (singing) Laura QQ...
RYAN: We'll fix it in post. KATE: (singing) Fixing the mic.
KRIS: It's like pressed into the part that you do shots out of, when you're in... You know what I mean?
RYAN: The belly button? KRIS: This little hole here.
KATE: Wow. KRIS: Vampires like eat that.
RYAN: You do shots out of here?
KATE: Vampires eat this. KRIS: Yeah, if you're a vampire.
AMY: The vampire shot glass.
RYAN: (laughing) What are you talking about?
JERRY: What did I miss?
KRIS: Sorry. AMY: Anatomy. Anatomy.
RYAN: Yeah. College. KATE: You wouldn't understand.
JERRY: It's fine. This-- AMY: So we got a good horse.
JERRY: This horse... Well you have a--
KATE: Less bad. JERRY: Better-- Yeah. You have a less bad beast.
AMY: That's fine.
RYAN: One to ten. What we talking? JERRY: That has emerged...
JERRY: 3.2. RYAN: Ugh.
KATE: Less bad horse. KRIS: A ten's an okay horse.
(laughter) KRIS: Still pretty bad.
JERRY: This is a shit horse!
KRIS: That's bad. RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: This is-- It's like before, that was like not a horse.
Like it couldn't do the things we associate with horses.
This is a "horse" in quotation marks.
AMY: Okay that's fine. RYAN: Okay. Like a piñata.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. But yeah, don't test that theory!
KRIS: It's like a "horse-style" pull creature.
(laughter)
JERRY: "Horse-style?" KATE: Horse-product.
KRIS: Yeah. "Horse-esque." JERRY: It's like "cheese food?"
AMY: Oh my god. All right. RYAN: Horse in a can.
KATE: I want to ask, what's the horse's name?
JERRY: The horse's name is Coriander.
KATE: (whispers) Coriander. RYAN: It's our horse now. We get to name it.
AMY: And we're naming it Coriander.
JERRY: It might not come to-- Yeah.
AMY: It might not live.
JERRY: But the cart itself-- RYAN: Now I'll get real attached.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, exactly. But the cart itself is still a problem.
But there was no... you know...
JERRY: quick judicious play he could make for the cart. KRIS: Yeah. There's no wiggle room.
AMY: That's fine, you got Mending.
JERRY: It's not-- It's ancient.
I mean this is an ancient...
It's like when you put the IKEA shelf together but not quite right.
You missed a couple of those twists.
And so it has sort of a lateral...
KRIS: Yeah. It's got a cant to it.
I'm worried that if I use Mending on it
it will turn back into a pile of trash.
AMY: (laughing) Okay that's a good point. KRIS: So I'm not going to Mend it.
AMY: That's a good point.
RYAN: We don't have to take this job.
KRIS: But we do!
JERRY: But that's the situation-- KATE: We get a free cart.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. The situation here is that there is a high seat up behind the horse in front.
Small brass post to tie off the reins there.
AMY: Great.
JERRY: Sort of a flat roof.
But this is very much a working cart.
It's not really meant for transportation, but--
You know what I mean? Like you can sit in the way back.
AMY: Sure. KRIS: Yeah.
AMY: Cool. The pickup truck of carts. JERRY: Yeah, exactly!
JERRY: Exactly. You would get in the way back. AMY: Wonderful.
RYAN: El Camino? KATE: Are there windows?
JERRY: There are two bar-guarded holes.
AMY: Perfect! KATE: Love it!
JERRY: One on each side. KRIS: The bars are tinted.
AMY: (laughing) The bars are tinted...
(laughter)
AMY: I love it. KRIS: With filth!
KATE: Rosie is loving this whip!
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, exactly. It's Rosie's style?
KATE: Yeah! JERRY: Hashtag Rosie's.
KATE: She's loving it!
KRIS: So who have we been contracted to if not this wagon establishment?
KATE: Lord Vizgar Wagon--
AMY: Vizgig Cartinwheel. KATE: Vizgig Cartinwheel.
KRIS: Does this lord frequent this business? RYAN: Yeah, where's this guy?
KRIS: Where might we find him?
KATE: Well if you'd let me explain to you, it's on the map.
JERRY: Yeah. KATE: There's a map!
KRIS: Why did we come here?
KATE: I'm the Cartographer! JERRY: Goddamn it!
KRIS: You wanted to see this, Cartographer. KATE: Because we get a free cart!
KATE: (laughing) It's just replay. We lost ten minutes over and over again.
Okay. Rosie knows the way.
KRIS: Okay. KATE: Whenever you guys are ready to mount up.
JERRY: Oh. New mic? LAURA QQ: Yeah.
JERRY: Here. Oh no, this is... KATE: New mic!
JERRY: This is going to--
AMY: We're going to pause. RYAN: This is the glory of live theater.
KATE: I would like to describe-- JERRY: This is going to be a new tier of intimacy.
AMY: Describe what? KATE: I would like to describe Rosie climbing the cart.
KATE: Slowly.
KRIS: (laughing) Oh god. Just sell it. AMY: Like extra slow. &gt;&gt; KATE: Yeah.
KRIS: So he doesn't feel bad about his--
KATE: Rosie plants her staff and grunts--
I plant my staff and grunt with satisfaction.
Because I'm very excited about riding a cart.
I am extremely fit for my age. But it's still hard work walking everywhere, you know?
I'm very small and I have this big quarterstaff that I'm hauling around.
And I done a lot of exercise recently, so I'm like,
Ah you know what? Taking a load off sounds really great right now.
LAURA QQ: I'll check it.
KATE: And we're done.
KRIS: Wow.
KATE: I didn't get one foot in the cart.
(laughter)
AMY: I was transported, though.
RYAN: Yeah. AMY: Thank you, Rosie.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. Theater of the Mind.
RYAN: Yeah. Quite the picture was painted there.
KATE: All right. Rosie gets in the cart.
(laughter)
RYAN: Tl;dr on this?
JERRY: Cool. So in the back?
KATE: Uh... yeah...? JERRY: In the way back?
RYAN: Roof?
KATE: Uh... I don't know. She might want to drive.
AMY: Oh she can drive. KATE: Yeah okay. Rosie's going to drive.
AMY: Donaar, I'm sure, wants to sit...
KATE: Do you want to sit up front?
Do you want to sit up front?
KATE: Have you been good enough to sit up front? RYAN: No. I want to be carted around.
KATE: All right. That's true. You're more of a palanquin-type.
Yeah. In the back. Get in the back.
AMY: Palanquin paladin? Hmm. All right.
KATE: (gasps) The palanquin paladin! AMY: It's fine, it's fine, it's fine. I'm sorry.
AMY: I'm sorry! Don't give me disadvantage!
KATE: It's very good!
AMY: Yeah, I want to ride on top.
KATE: On the roof? Okay. AMY: Mm-hmm.
KATE: So we got one inside, one on the roof, one on the seat...
You want to just dangle off the back? Or cling to the underbelly?
KRIS: Can I ride the horse?
KATE: Yep! AMY: That's not how it goes.
KATE: It's Dungeons &amp; Dragons, fool!
KRIS: No. Who am I inside with?
KRIS: You're in there? RYAN: Yeah.
RYAN: Me and you? &gt;&gt; JERRY: Inside within? KRIS: Sure.
RYAN: Nice. JERRY: Within the cart?
KRIS: Yeah. How much puke do you have on you?
RYAN: Minimal. KRIS: I guess I don't mind it.
RYAN: Yeah. Couple of teaspoons. KATE: What time of day is it?
KATE: Are you comfortable? KRIS: Oh yeah. Good question.
KRIS: I prefer inside. KATE: Okay.
KRIS: But I...
If I have to do something where I'm looking at it and it is in full sunlight, that's where I take my disadvantage.
So it's not like I'm being scalded.
JERRY: All-day. KRIS: But I don't do my best work.
KRIS: Yeah. KATE: Okay.
JERRY: So you distributed yourself. KRIS: So I just put the cloak over.
JERRY: We have K'thriss and Donaar ensconced inside.
AMY: Nice. JERRY: We have Walnut Dankgrass...
and Rosie Beestinger riding up top.
JERRY: So you're driving, you're shotgun? AMY: She's driving. I'm up top.
KATE: Naw she's just on the roof, I think.
RYAN: Yeah. Just on the roof of it.
JERRY: You're sort of enmeshed in the cargo netting up there.
KATE/AMY: Yeah.
KATE: Where she feels most at home.
AMY: I'm just like, ah. All I can see is sky and not these fools.
JERRY: Yeah. So I'm not even going to-- there's going to be zero roll factor for you.
This is like the most basic sort of thing for you.
Quick glance at the map shows you where this stretch of raiding space is happening between Stone Bridge and Beliard.
As I said, you go north, and then you go east.
And it really is the first opportunity to do that at a larger scale road.
And then the town itself, of Westbridge,
is really where you do the turning there.
JERRY: So... KATE: Okay.
JERRY: You know exactly, 100%, how to get the party there.
KATE: Nice. JERRY: Easy pease.
KATE: I'm telling the horse a story about how my nephew once was in a raiding party and I find it very distasteful.
JERRY: (laughs) Raidism.
KATE: And by god, this raiding will cease.
By the end of this trip, Coriander is sick of hearing me talk.
JERRY: Yeah. AMY: Sick, physically.
KATE: (laughing) Coriander barfs three times on the way to Westbridge. KRIS: The horse is now identical to the other horse.
(laughter)
KRIS: Transformed.
JERRY: It just vomited out a second vomit horse.
KRIS: Yeah. JERRY: And you move twice as fast.
JERRY: So this is-- None of this is true. KATE: You're welcome.
KATE: You're welcome. KRIS: You're no longer encumbered.
JERRY: I know this is Dungeons &amp; Dragons but there are limitations.
AMY: It's true. Horses don't vomit, they colic. And if they do that they die. Sorry. That's it.
KRIS: Nice! KATE: Wow! Wow, druid.
KATE: All right. So we're now in the town of Westbridge. RYAN: Summon some eagles to cart us around.
JERRY: Yeah, you're ready to grab the reins and move this cart north through town.
KATE: Okay. Oh! We're not in the town of Westbridge yet.
KATE: But we're going there. Okay. JERRY: No. You have secured your vehicle.
JERRY: You get a hearty wave from whoever it was at this place that you talked to.
KATE: Todd Waelvur.
RYAN: Yeah. Never did get his name.
AMY: I did get back the missive, though. RYAN: Oil rag!
KATE: You called him "Oil Rag." Yeah. RYAN: Yeah.
KATE: Grab that missive right back.
RYAN: I say, so long, Oil Rag! AMY: NPC Number 35.
KRIS: That might have coincidently been his name, so... JERRY: Yeah.
RYAN: So do we know where we're going?
KATE: Yes! &gt;&gt; JERRY: 100%. KRIS: Take us.
JERRY: She's got it totally dialled in.
KATE: I don't even have to roll, I'm so good at this.
JERRY: There's literally like one turn. Let's see how it goes.
KATE: All right. We go there.
JERRY: So you pull the cart out straight--
This is the direction that you came from in your family's cart.
You can remember its comforts quite well.
KRIS: Oh boy. KATE: Stark contrast.
JERRY: Exactly. It was only a few days ago.
But that had soft leathers.
There was a nice bottle of silver wine in there.
It was an incredible experience.
It had the fiber optic lights.
RYAN: Yeah. The ground effects.
JERRY: Oh yeah, it was-- KATE: The bass.
JERRY: Oh yeah. It was thumping.
RYAN: We're rich, but classless as hell.
(laughter)
KATE: I'm really surprised to hear that.
JERRY: It's that new money. RYAN: Yeah.
(laughter)
JERRY: So you pull the cart out north.
You recall these events.
And you spend a mostly uneventful day of travel far enough north until it starts to get dark.
You think that you could probably get to Westbridge tomorrow.
Maybe spend the night in there and then continue on to the east from there.
But now it is time to set up camp.
KRIS: Ooh-wee! JERRY: Tell me more. Tell me how it goes.
KATE: I'm going to pull over next to a very healthy-looking tree.
Which I think will give us shelter--
JERRY: The healthiest tree. KATE Yeah, the healthiest tree.
KATE: Whatever the opposite of our horse is in tree form.
That's where I'm going to stop us.
KRIS: The horse is actually startled by the health.
(laughter)
RYAN: (laughing) The virility of the tree?
KRIS: It's worried. JERRY: What is this creature?
KRIS: Ugh!
KATE: I'll hop down and untie the horse and lead it over to a patch of grass and say,
You got to get some meat on these bones, kid.
It's rough stuff.
JERRY: The sweetest clover.
Yeah, you're able to haul him over, tie him off a little bit.
Make sure he doesn't go to far.
Which might be difficult for this horse, honestly.
How are the rest of you preparing camp?
AMY: I'm going to volunteer for first watch up on the thing.
But before we go to sleep, I cast Goodberry. Chat! JERRY: Oh, ho, ho!
KATE: Nice! JERRY: (laughs)
AMY: So I make up to ten berries appear in my hand and are infused with magic for the duration.
And it lasts for 24 hours.
You can use your action to eat one berry.
Eating a berry restores 1 hit point, and the berry provides enough nourishment to sustain a creature for one day.
No more food problems, and a little pocket heal.
KRIS: Nice. AMY: So I do this and I toss everybody three berries.
AMY: And I keep one for myself.
JERRY: That's right. That's your pocket berry. KATE: Why just one?
AMY: Because I make ten and that... adds up to math right?
KATE: Well, three, three, three, one?
AMY: Isn't that nine? And then ten?
KATE: Well but why wouldn't you save-- You know what? You do you.
AMY: I got it. KATE: Sounds great.
AMY: Because I'm great! No, I'm joking. That's his thing.
Because I'm okay.
JERRY: Yeah.
KATE: Because I'm druid.
JERRY: Because I'm reasonable.
AMY: Yeah. JERRY: It's a good brand. We can go with that.
KATE: Pop that berry right in.
JERRY: Exactly. One of these berries is like an all-day Lunchables situation.
KRIS: Right. JERRY: Just flowing.
JERRY: It's like a Gobstopper, essentially. Right?
How are you preparing-- Are you preparing...?
Is this how you look in-game as well?
KRIS: Yeah.
KATE: Just reading your dark rituals. Yeah. AMY: It's so dark magic.
KRIS: No. I was trying to figure out whether or not Alarm,
which I can do as a ritual, works in a radius that is functional.
But it is a 20-foot cube.
So I don't know that the lay of the land is going to work.
Although I'd prefer to place it away from us to where I would imagine somebody could approach.
JERRY: The optimal attack vector? KRIS: Yeah.
KATE: The cube of danger. JERRY: You're welcome to create it as a...
KRIS: Then I create it.
Does it fail? I don't think it does.
JERRY: So you see K'thriss Drow'b leave camp.
He just walks slowly toward the road that you peeled the cart off of.
You hold your focus up toward that red star.
And you hear four small-- it sounds like arrows almost.
JERRY: Like you hear things whistling through the air. KRIS: (thwip sounds)
JERRY: But you see four ruby columns...
AMY: (whispering) Whoa.
JERRY: launched as though from a geosynchronous platform,
describe an area of protection.
KRIS: Okay. JERRY: And as they plant themselves,
JERRY: you see them shimmer and become invisible.
KRIS: Do you guys want to hear this if someone breaches this or should it just be me that gets woken up?
AMY: It should be... everybody. KATE: Yeah I think everybody's good.
AMY: Should be everybody.
KRIS: Okay, let's do that. RYAN: I'm good.
(laughter)
AMY: Donaar needs his beauty rest.
KRIS: Okay. The three of us and you--
RYAN: I don't need every little rabbit setting this thing off.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. (meowing sound)
KRIS: I can define it to avoid wildlife. RYAN: All right do that.
KATE: And then still also... RYAN: And then tell me.
RYAN: I'll delegate.
KRIS: Okay. I-- RYAN: As leader.
KRIS: Good night.
JERRY: Good night!
KATE: How long does that last?
KRIS: Like... all day.
KATE: All day long. KRIS: It's a long time.
JERRY: Donaar Blit'zen.
How do you prepare yourself for sleepy time?
RYAN: Oh I post up on this nice little cart I got here.
And I curl up and go to sleep.
JERRY: So you-- There is-- RYAN: (laughs) I say, bye everyone. See you in eight!
JERRY: So in the back of this cart...
Is just like-- It just got wheeled out.
They must have just called back for it.
They did not clean the back of it out.
During this ride over it has been just a cacophony of nails, pins, S-hooks...
Like all the stuff you'd have to learn blacksmithing.
There's a few hammers, other tools, and then there's just this heap of burlap and leather canvas in the back.
You think it might be all-weather covering or something for the cart itself.
But you nestle yourself back--
JERRY: away from the sharper tools. AMY: Like a little dog. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Yeah.
KRIS: Yeah, he's just marching in a circle for a little while.
JERRY: Yeah exactly.
JERRY: Just scratching with his feet. KRIS: Yeah.
RYAN: I give the teeth a good brush, and then I just, night-night.
KATE: What's your toothbrush named again?
RYAN: Percival. And my sword's name is Toothbrush.
KATE: Right. JERRY: Nice.
JERRY: I like the idea that it's a dragon's toothbrush.
It's kind of awesome.
But as you curl up back against these heaps, you hear snoring.
AMY: (gasps)
AMY: A stowaway. RYAN: We're unobservant.
KRIS: Oh yeah. We're not good at this.
KATE: Listen! I was driving. It was your jobs--
KATE: to inspect inside the cart. AMY: You guys were in the cart with him!
RYAN: That cart could have been a mimic!
(laughter)
RYAN: Is it a mimic? KATE: Not everything's a mimic!
RYAN: I don't know that. I'm just learning this game.
KATE: Everything's a mimic.
RYAN: First thing I touched tried to eat me. KATE: That's true.
RYAN: I assume everything will try to eat me. KATE: That's fair.
AMY: Well what do you do? You're the only one in there with him.
RYAN: Eh. I'm all right.
(laughter)
KRIS: He's sleeping. I'm sleeping.
RYAN: This guy's got the right idea.
AMY: Just pounding on him, use him like a pillow.
RYAN: Yeah.
KRIS: You said it, buddy! RYAN: Yeah.
KATE: (laughing) You know what? RYAN: Amen.
KATE: That's enough adventure for today. RYAN: Yep.
KRIS: Yeah.
JERRY: You just fucking check out.
All right. I love it. I could not be more pleased.
KRIS: This is ridiculous. Can we also hear it? Or are we just--
JERRY: Oh no. Yeah, you're there casting spells. KRIS: I guess I'm too far.
KRIS: Yeah, I don't hear anything.
I should have set Alarm inside of the cart.
KRIS: Okay. AMY: That's too bad.
JERRY: Right. So you're out.
RYAN: I'm about to be, yeah. JERRY: Yeah.
KRIS: You wish it was quieter.
RYAN: Yeah, I was like, it's a little loud in here!
KATE: I'm still talking to Coriander.
RYAN: Yeah. So Coriander has eaten as much grass as Coriander's going to eat.
KATE: That's good. Okay.
JERRY: You just bring her back. KATE: Well that's not going to stop me from talking to her.
JERRY: Oh, no. No. Coriander's getting the full-meal deal here.
KATE: Yep. I'm telling her about the top three cart rides I've ever taken.
Because I think it's relevant to her interests.
Trying to find anything I can find in common with this horse.
JERRY: I love you're just trying to make that love connection. You know what I mean?
KATE: Yeah always. Okay so I'm going to bring Coriander and tie her back up to the wagon.
JERRY: Yep. Absolutely.
KATE: And I'm going to walk slowly past... the cart?
And maybe I'd hear something inside. Do I?
JERRY: You hear the sound of snoring in there.
KATE: Does it sound like a dragon snoring? RYAN: It's me.
KATE: Or does it sound like maybe a different sized creature snoring?
JERRY: Hmm! Try a perception roll. KATE: Hmph!
KATE: Hmph! Okay. Okay.
KATE: Perception is wisdom. KRIS: You can take a good one if you need it.
KATE: 14! KRIS: Oh you're all right.
JERRY: You think that this is a smaller, less guttural snore.
KATE: (high-pitched snoring sound)
JERRY: This is-- RYAN: Another mouse?
JERRY: This is not a large creature.
KATE: For a minute I think maybe this is what Donaar sounds like when he's snoring.
Maybe this is just his sinuses?
But then I think I should check.
JERRY: It doesn't make sense. RYAN: Check my adenoids.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. KATE: I've heard some crazy dragonborn snores before.
JERRY: CPAP. KATE: Trust me! But not like this.
KATE: I'm going to just, politely, open the door and be like,
You got everything you need in there?
You got a blanket?
RYAN: I'm good!
KATE: Do you hear a snoring sound maybe?
RYAN: Was I snoring? Oh I'm sorry.
KATE: It's still going. I'm like,
No I don't think it's you unless you got another mouth in there.
RYAN: (sighs) I don't-- What does it take to get eight hours of sleep around you people? I swear...
AMY: I'm up on the roof like,
Hey! I'm taking first watch so you guys can sleep. Let's go! (claps)
JERRY: Clap, clap!
KATE: Oh! I hear a little snoring happening in here. You want to help us try to figure out what's going on?
Come on down.
AMY: I come down. I'm like,
There's supposed to be snoring. You're supposed to be sleeping. You're all awake.
KATE: Well see-- JERRY: You two. You. Also...
KATE: We're all awake but there's still snoring happening.
And it's coming from inside the cart!
RYAN: Is it the horse?
(laughter)
KRIS: I need this to be simple so I can just sleep! RYAN: Yeah!
AMY: Wait. Am I standing next to Rosie? I immediately want to do one of these.
AMY: Where I go to protect her. KATE: Block her?
AMY: Whuh (sound of surprise)!
KATE: But your arm whiffs over my head.
AMY: I go way over!
JERRY: You keep reaching.
AMY: Uh... !
JERRY: One of these times is going to be the time.
KATE: She loves it.
KRIS: If I don't get my four hours. If I don't get my trance...
KATE: If I don't get my trance, I'm a... KRIS: I'm a real bear.
KATE: rude boy. RYAN: Look. I'm really tired.
RYAN: Is this what it's going to take?
I got to wake this thing up. And I just start shaking it.
JERRY: "Ugh!" RYAN: What's your deal?
JERRY: "Ugh! Ugh!"
And then you see this shape just poking out at random in these folds.
KRIS: Is it in a sack? JERRY: Trying desperately to escape.
RYAN: Ugh. God. Another mimic.
I say, whuh (sound of surprise)!
(laughter)
KATE: It's a sack mimic!
AMY: I look at Rosie and I motion to her quarterstaff and I go, poke it.
KATE: Yeah. I poke it.
JERRY: "Ow!"
"Ow!"
KRIS: It knows pain.
RYAN: Yeah. I pull out my sword.
KATE: I'm going to hold my staff in a threatening way, but I stop poking for now.
But I think this person-- entity-- can sense that there's still something about to poke them.
JERRY: Something rod-esque. KATE: Yeah.
KATE: Got my rod out. I say, hey!
RYAN: You and me both. KATE: Who are you?
AMY: (restrained laughter)
JERRY: So you see two hands...
pull it down...
and then you see an older gentleman...
pushing it away and then backing against the inside of the cart.
KATE: Human?
JERRY: Yes.
Just old and small.
KATE: Okay.
AMY: Best kind. RYAN: Yeah.
KATE: I do like old and small.
JERRY: "Did you steal this cart?"
KATE: No!
We got it from Todd Waelvur.
JERRY: "I'm Waelvur."
KATE: Oh. Are you Dad Waelvur?
RYAN: Does your kid like oil rags?
KATE: Yeah, is your kid the guy who works in the shop?
JERRY: "He's obsessed with cleanliness, yes."
KATE: Okay. He said he didn't know where you were. I put my staff down.
JERRY: "Well-- I..."
"about..."
"ten..."
"in the morning..."
"is the first..."
"of many naps..."
AMY/KATE: Mmm. JERRY: "that occur."
JERRY: "This is my napping cart."
KATE: I see.
RYAN: Real quick. So you have other carts?
JERRY: "Uh... Sometimes."
RYAN: Better carts than this?
KRIS: You take a nap in the worst cart.
RYAN: Just for (laughs) free.
JERRY: "Well no... We would never sell this cart."
KATE: Mmm. RYAN: Hmm.
RYAN: But you have access to other carts. This is good info.
KATE: Yeah. RYAN: For later.
KATE: Your son may have pulled a fast one on us.
We definitely got this cart from him, although we did get it from a coupon.
Does that maybe clear things up?
AMY: Oh. I'll show him the thing. RYAN: Show him the thing, yeah.
AMY: And again, I'll put it where it's just out of reach.
And if he goes to touch it, I go-- (sounds of consternation)
(growling) Oh don't touch it!
JERRY: No, as soon as you unfold it and he sees the symbology at the top.
He sees the coupon at the bottom, he's like,
"All right."
"When are you going back to Red Larch?"
AMY: When we're done. KATE: When the raiding ceases.
KATE: Show him the thing again.
AMY: I go... JERRY: It's dark in the cart.
AMY: Oh. Yeah okay.
RYAN: Why don't you use Faerie Fire? Make it brighter. KATE: The raiding must cease.
AMY: I mean, you know. JERRY: Yeah, he gets up.
JERRY: He realizes that touching it is no go.
AMY: Mm-hmm. JERRY: But he gets very, very close...
AMY: That's fine. JERRY: to the document.
JERRY: And assesses it thoroughly.
Seems to wonder if this deal is worth as much trouble as it has been.
And says...
"So Stone Bridge, Beliard, Stone Road..."
"So you won't be back for days."
AMY: I mean, we'll be back as soon as we can get this done.
You know, the more help, the merrier.
Get us back to town quicker.
RYAN: We're doing this for you, man.
JERRY: He scoots back underneath these folds of leather and burlap.
You can hear a glass bottle tink against the base of the cart.
He pulls out a bottle and says,
"Three days is fine."
KATE: What you got in that bottle?
JERRY: "Some for you."
KRIS: Ooh. RYAN: Nice.
AMY: I give him-- JERRY: Gestures back.
KATE: I'm in. I'm going to hop in that cart.
Let's see what kind of poison you brewing.
AMY: When the cart's a rocking-- (laughs)
RYAN: (increasingly louder) What's it take to get to sleep in this place?
KATE: Sleep outside, kid!
RYAN: I was here first!
KATE: The grown-ups are talking!
JERRY: Exactly.
He takes the...
He grabs a few square feet of this material and pulls it over in the manner of a bedsheet.
And extends the bottle out.
KATE: All right. RYAN: We got to get a better cart out of this.
KATE: I hop right in there.
Slide right in.
RYAN: I could sleep through this.
KRIS: (whispering) I'm riding on the roof tomorrow!
(laughter)
RYAN: I say, I could sleep through this no problem.
(laughter) RYAN: Just turn over.
RYAN: Just turn my back to it. JERRY: This is fine.
JERRY: This is fine. This is fine.
It's fine.
AMY: So I was going to take first watch from on top of the cart,
but I'm now going to clamber up the tree and just kind of like watch from up there.
JERRY: Stay with friends. AMY: Yeah.
JERRY: So this-- AMY: Good tree.
JERRY: You don't think that it's just the darkness inside the cart.
You think that this liquid would be jet black even at noon.
KATE: Mmm. AMY: Good shit.
JERRY: You don't-- yeah. This is something someone has made,
and no one has tested it for purity.
But yeah it is like being kicked in the mouth by a horse.
KATE: Dark hooch. JERRY: Yeah.
KATE: I betray no reaction at first. JERRY: Oh, no, no.
KATE: And then I say,
It's woody.
JERRY: "It's made from wood."
KATE: Mmm. I could tell.
RYAN: Good mouth feel.
(laughter)
AMY: That's what they do with old carts.
RYAN: I'm detecting notes of... JERRY: Oaky.
KATE: (laughing) That's what they do with old carts. It's a cart brew.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. Toxic.
KRIS: You do this, and it makes a grinding sound.
(laughter)
RYAN: It's like a rock tumbler.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. KRIS: Ah... !
JERRY: It's just like a jar of marbles.
AMY: Oh my god... JERRY: There's something in there.
JERRY: But as you see so you have just made your peace with this.
RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: Totally fine.
JERRY: It's totally fine. RYAN: I need my eight.
RYAN: Eight and skate.
KRIS: It's me and Coriander then I guess.
KRIS: Oh no, you're up there. Okay so I... AMY: I'm up on the tree.
KRIS: I sleep horse-side tonight.
Because I don't want to be in there.
JERRY: Perfect.
Works fine. The night goes as uneventfully or as eventfully as you choose.
KATE: Never kiss and tell. JERRY: No, no. Absolutely not.
JERRY: What happens in the cart.
And so...
AMY: That's for the fan art to decide.
JERRY: In the morning-- Exactly. We want to see this kind of material in the fan art, channel.
KATE: I burst out. I'm like, boy do I have some stories to tell you guys!
AMY: No... ! RYAN: And I come out and go, oh my god. The stories.
(laughter)
JERRY: He just stumbles out and-- RYAN: Oh god. They were so tiny and wrinkly!
It was like, have you ever seen the movie Critters?
KRIS: At one point I was being used for support!
(laughter)
RYAN: Ugh. JERRY: Leverage!
KRIS: Ugh.
JERRY: You just fall out. Ugh!
And then crawl way. No! No.
RYAN: It was like-- KRIS: No more spirits.
RYAN: It was like two little ball sacks slamming into each other!
JERRY: It was terrible. RYAN: And it wouldn't stop!
KRIS: That's not great.
RYAN: Anyway, I'm great!
KRIS: I got my eight.
KATE: I got my eight! That's all that matters.
RYAN: Got my eight. AMY: Got those spells back.
RYAN: Full HP. JERRY: Exactly.
KATE: Oh yeah! Full rest.
JERRY: Exactly. So this mist-- KRIS: Foul rest.
KATE: Some of us. (clicks tongue) JERRY: Yeah, mist is rising--
JERRY: Oh!
RYAN: I tell my troubles to the horse.
AMY: Wait. Before we get going.
JERRY: Walnut, how can I help? AMY: Because it's a new morning,
AMY: I want to cast Goodberry again.
Each of you now get two more.
So you should have a total of five unless you ate one.
KRIS: Five good berries. RYAN: Mine are in my bag.
AMY: And I give one to little dude.
I'm like, you're going to probably need this more than I do.
JERRY: It's like the classic druid hangover cure.
AMY: Yeah, I'm like-- RYAN: You give everyone one?
AMY: You have five now. RYAN: Oh right. Five.
JERRY: Total. RYAN: I'll eat one for breakfast.
AMY: So now you have four. JERRY: Exactly.
JERRY: It's juicy. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Wait. AMY: Get that HP.
RYAN: I had five.
AMY: Now you have four. &gt;&gt; RYAN: I ate one. KRIS: Now you have four because you ate one.
AMY: (laughing) Bless it. Anyway!
RYAN: So uh... should-- do I roll... ? Or--
JERRY: I'll take it from here, Donaar Blit'zen.
So...
As you awake, you can see--
So this part of the Long Road that goes north,
to the east is the Sumber Hills.
Just these great--
There's many theories about why it's shaped this way.
But it's basically just this range of hills that these roads are designed to get around.
The mist is rising off of these hills as you get your contraption back on the road.
And you think that Waelvur sleeps a lot.
You think that he sleeps like a lot. Like maybe too much.
KATE: He's pretty tired. RYAN: It's Lyme disease.
AMY: (laughing) Okay, Rosie.
KATE: He's pretty worn out.
JERRY: He's exhausted!
KATE: How you doing in there, little pickle?
AMY: (laughing) Little pickle.
JERRY: I wrung this man out!
AMY: He's nursing a crushed pelvis.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. He needs Goodberry! Is what he does.
JERRY: He needs Goodberry-- RYAN: Should I lay on hands?
(laughter)
AMY: Goodberry would do that.
JERRY: Exactly. It's a good Goodberry.
So as I say, you pull back out.
Occasionally you see...
As I say this is the Long Road.
JERRY: Many, many carts like yours. Nicer carts. AMY: Okay.
JERRY: Superior carts. &gt;&gt; KATE: Wow. AMY: Okay don't rub it in.
JERRY: Carts you could be proud to own.
RYAN: Can we... rob them? JERRY: Take to piracy?
RYAN: Yeah. AMY: Oh. Oh, oh, oh. Don't worry.
JERRY: Road pirates. AMY: Don't worry.
JERRY: Road pirates. RYAN: Oh good.
KRIS: What a cool turn for this adventure.
RYAN: Do you got plans? Okay, good. KATE: Walnut?
KATE: You got a little something? AMY: It's okay.
AMY: We just got a contingency plan... JERRY: Thorn Whip?
JERRY: Yeah exactly. AMY: for better carts.
KATE: Thorn Whip a cart!
AMY: I get it. RYAN: Whip the drivers in the face.
JERRY: With cash. That's the whip.
KATE: (laughing) That's right.
JERRY: So as you are...
You entered a very, very nondescript section of road.
You can't quite see Westbridge off in the distance yet.
But you know, in your mind that it's like Rosie GPS,
You know exactly where you are on this map,
and you know that at any moment now you'll be able to see the town of Westbridge cropping up there.
And you know that's where you'll take the east road.
Which is called the Stone Road.
It's all stone shit here.
It's like Westbridge, Stone Road, Stone Bridge, Beliard.
You're not sure who named this stuff, but you know that you could have done better.
KATE: They're not very creative. JERRY: Exactly, right?
JERRY: And so...
But there are on this point of the road going north
there are deep furrows to the left and right.
Almost just these gullies.
So it's almost as if the road has risen up,
but you can't necessarily see all the way down the edges...
of the road on each side.
And it is times like this, party, that we roll perception checks.
AMY: I was getting scared. KATE: I know.
KATE: Thought it'd be initiative. RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: Oh, no. There will be an initiative later. Don't worry.
KATE: Oh boy.
KRIS: Yes boy. Oh that's not bad at all.
AMY: Ooh. KATE: Going to be a ten.
RYAN: 12.
KRIS: (British accent) I got a 20.
RYAN: Nice. KATE: Wow...
AMY: I got a 17 and with my bonus that is a 22.
JERRY: Oh that's very good.
You see...
Really out of the corner of your eye, and every time you try to center it in your vision,
this black shape, orbited by two smaller black shapes,
it's just always shifting, always just out of the edge of your perception.
Off to the right of the cart. And it is keeping pace with the cart.
KRIS/KATE: Mmm. AMY: Mmm okay.
KRIS: What's over there? Is it like low-grass and stuff, or like trees?
JERRY: Oh yeah exactly. Basically imagine that at this point the road has been up and supported,
maybe it was marshy or something underneath,
but the road here has been reinforced
and sitting up on broken rock and gravel.
And then there is a gulley on each side. where it's difficult--
JERRY: Unless you're at the very top looking down. KRIS: I see, I see.
JERRY: It might be difficult to see exactly what it is.
But you are alerted now.
AMY: Okay.
So I'm on top of the cart and I just lean down to Rosie and go,
We got company.
JERRY: Just letting you know. ROSIE: Ugh I always wanted to say that. It's so cool.
KATE: All right.
AMY: Sorry I didn't say it in a cool way.
KATE: That's okay. AMY: But we got it.
JERRY: You hear the horse; you hear Coriander whine.
RYAN: Break out the good china. KATE: Okay.
JERRY: Coriander has not deviated from your direction.
But there is like a high note with each exhalation.
KATE: Okay.
KRIS: Give it a Goodberry.
JERRY: Yeah. RYAN: I can heal it.
KATE: I can do Pass without Trace.
We can try to outstrip it.
AMY: Wow. KATE: Want to try that?
AMY: Can you do everything?
KATE: Just Pass without Trace.
And Darkness, and Silence, and Darkvision, and Minor Illusion. It's not...
AMY: No, I meant can you get everything that we're currently in-- KATE: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
(laughter)
RYAN: Are you the best one ever?
JERRY: Wow. KRIS: Should I just go to sleep again?
KRIS: Can I have sex with the old guy? KATE: Yes.
(laughter)
KATE: I mean, it doesn't hurt.
It actually feels pretty good.
So a veil of shadows and silence radiates from you,
masking you and your companions from detection.
For the duration, each creature you choose within 30 feet of you,
including you, has a plus ten bonus to dexterity
and can't be tracked except by magical means.
And it lasts for an hour.
JERRY: M'kay. AMY: Hmm.
KATE: Shall I?
RYAN: Well you guys are having a little conversation.
Are we aware of this?
KATE: Pass without Trace?
AMY: Yeah, go for it. KATE: All right. Pass without Trace.
KATE: I do it.
AMY: And then I'll lean over because now we can talk freely inside this protective bubble. And go,
Hey, boys. We're being followed, so if you want to...
strap on your armor.
Get ready to go.
RYAN: Followed by what?
AMY: I don't... Listen. It's shadowy.
RYAN: (sighs) AMY: I don't know.
RYAN: Is it a deer? It's always fucking something with you, druid.
KRIS: How soon do you think-- Are they going to catch up with us?
AMY: Three things-- Do I think that they're gaining on us?
JERRY: They appear to be just maintaining...
AMY: They're content to follow us, perhaps, all the way to our destination?
KRIS: Hmm. Okay.
AMY: They're not advancing.
KATE: I know that we're close enough to Westbridge that my Pass without Trace should be able to get us...
JERRY: Probably not all the way there. KATE: Not all the way there. Nope.
KATE: Probably not all the way there. Okay.
But maybe enough to get this thing bored, because it can't see us anymore.
AMY: Okay. Well let's try to see what happens--
AMY: if we continue. KATE: Let's bore it to death.
AMY: Yeah. Let's bore them to death!
(laughter)
JERRY: Okay. RYAN: Exciting!
RYAN: What an exciting adventure! Right folks?
AMY: So this lasts for an hour? KATE: An hour.
AMY: Okay, so... KRIS: Full hour.
AMY: At about 40 minutes can I do a--
RYAN: (laughing) Real time. AMY: perception check to see if they're still following?
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
AMY: All right.
KRIS: Yeah, I don't know what the endgame is.
Like we may want to-- Do we double back on them because then they're like,
Oh! The cart we were going to rob is gone.
And then they just go back the other way?
AMY: I got an 11. Does anyone else want to see if they're still following us?
KRIS: Sure. RYAN: Do we want to fight them?
RYAN: 20! Natural 20! KATE: Nice!
KATE: Nice. I did not get that. JERRY: Real natural 20?
AMY: Real. KRIS: You see all carts.
JERRY: Yeah exactly!
RYAN: I got persuasion.
JERRY: No, it's like you enter the Cart Force!
And you're able to perceive a universe--
RYAN: I'm like, I'll tell you if there were deer or not!
JERRY: This is the crossroads where every cart must one day pass.
KRIS: You know Cerebro where Professor X can see... RYAN: (singing) Welcome to the crossroads!
RYAN: (singing) KRIS: all carts.
JERRY: Exactly. So you... KATE: It's a weird show.
JERRY: So you see, even clearer--
Walnut got the impression--
Always trying to fix her gaze on it,
but was unable to really get any decent definition.
Over the edge you can see...
First, two seeking tentacles that end in diamond shapes.
AMY: (laughing) Kris' face again!
He was like looking away and then he's like,
AMY: Tentacles? JERRY: Tentacles! Whoa, I'm back!
AMY: Sorry.
JERRY: That sort of end in these diamond shapes.
With these lethal looking structures dripping from the bottom.
But it's 100% maintaining parity with the cart.
And then as you see it coming up the lip, up the edge,
you can see that these are attached to something like a...
demonic panther.
KRIS: No...
KRIS: We don't like that! AMY: Ooh!
KATE: I blame you, completely. RYAN: Land-squid.
AMY: Ah! Land-squid.
JERRY: But this is the stranger part.
Is that as it crests that hill, you see a smaller one leap on the larger one's back, and then leap closer to the cart.
And then you see another one leap on to the back,
and then leap close to the cart.
But it trips slightly and has to right itself,
and then keep up with its fellows.
AMY: Nothing I love more than killing whole families.
RYAN: Gotcha. All right. KATE: That's true.
KATE: That's one thing I know about you, for sure.
RYAN: There's a...
KRIS: Metagame. Do we have cause to know what these are or do our characters not know anything about these?
JERRY: This would be a strange-- You might have heard something about them.
KRIS: I think that's actually the extent of my-- Kris' actual knowledge of this animal, so okay.
KATE: I think all I can do is a history check.
KRIS: They're well read. KATE: Do they exist in any--
AMY: Yeah, can I do a survival check too?
KRIS: They're storied creatures.
JERRY: I would like to try stuff like that. I mean it is a mystical creature. I can give you--
RYAN: First I say-- I describe what it is to everyone.
My superior dragon eyes have this figured out, everyone.
KATE: Better than the druid's eyes. For sure. JERRY: Penetrated the mists.
RYAN: I've identified this.
KRIS: What are you guys rolling for to check on this? KATE: I got seven history check.
KRIS: Oh history? Okay.
AMY: Yeah what do you got there? RYAN: Oh I got two on history.
JERRY: If you want to approach it...
KRIS: No, I won't do that. RYAN: Approach the beast?
JERRY: Well no, no. I'm saying if you want to approach it with a skill, and I'll give you information that's associated with--
KRIS: Oh okay. How about investigation?
KRIS: Would that help me? JERRY: Mmm no.
JERRY: Because that would require like if one of them were dead in a room.
JERRY: Then you can come in a choose a light. RYAN: Oh like CSI?
KRIS: How about insight? Would that take me there? JERRY: No.
JERRY: No, I wouldn't think so. KATE: You got some arcana. How about that?
KRIS: History? JERRY: Yeah, we got a history check.
KRIS: "Ar-ca-nah"? All right let's do that. JERRY: Arcana is probably an interesting choice.
KRIS: There we go.
KATE: Oh! KRIS: Ooh it's going to be good. It's a 20.
AMY: Nice. KRIS: All told.
JERRY: Yeah, this is not a natural creature.
This is some kind of aberration.
Who knows its origin?
Magical experimentation. Something like that.
But it has, just as a natural part of it,
it sort of shimmers in place.
It's hard to detect exactly where it is.
Could be a displacer beast.
You have heard about creatures like that.
But there are many creatures that have built-in defense mechanisms of this type.
KRIS: Right. I'm concerned that we are going to rile those-- that mom, if those are cubs.
But those tentacles I feel like would accept a yoke and maybe replace this horse.
(laughter)
KATE: Dungeons and fucking Dragons! KRIS: It would be a rad... Yeah.
RYAN: So wait. We're still invisible right?
KATE: For now yeah. RYAN: Because we're doing this before the spell wears off,
RYAN: but it's still following us?
AMY: Yeah, we got 20 minutes left. KATE: So it's tracking us by magical means apparently.
KRIS: Yeah, I think they're pretty good at this. KATE: Yeah, I think they're pretty magical.
AMY: Hmm.
JERRY: So you see a... KATE: So we-- Are we-- Do you want to--
JERRY: At this point, so you are assessing this situation.
You're saying, we are being hunted by a magical beast.
JERRY: It is at this point, that they begin to lope immediately alongside the cart.
And then she just throws herself at the side of the cart.
AMY: Great. KRIS: Okay.
KATE: The cart disintegrates.
JERRY: Just slams into the cart.
KRIS: Okay. JERRY: And then you hear Waelvur inside go, "Whoa!"
RYAN: I was going to say I was going to grab the old guy.
KRIS: What's our positions again?
KRIS: Am I... Okay wait hold on. You're inside. RYAN: I'm inside.
KRIS: I think I'm inside as well. Yeah. Okay. Yeah, yeah. JERRY: You have been inside before.
JERRY: Rosie's driving.
RYAN: And these two are in front. KRIS: And you're on the roof.
AMY: I'm up on top. KRIS: Okay.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. So let's get initiative now.
RYAN: (Pac-Man sound) Wac-wac. AMY: Boo!
KRIS: (battle music) Duh-duh-duh-duh-duh...
KRIS: Ooh. KATE: 13.
AMY: Ooh.
KRIS: 15. RYAN: Four.
JERRY: Four? AMY: Well you have a modifier too-- Oh.
RYAN: Yes. But a negative.
I went from five to four. Not unlike my Goodberries.
KRIS: Consistent. It's like, ah I've done this when I was--
RYAN: I've done this!
AMY: 22. &gt;&gt; JERRY: Jeez. AMY: Oh I should write my Goodberries down.
JERRY: So you're kicking ass. AMY: Walnut's very motivated. &gt;&gt; KATE: She's on top.
AMY: Which is always horrible because Amy the human never knows what to do first.
JERRY: And then Donaar is in the S-Zone?
AMY: Yeah. RYAN: No, I'm in the--
KRIS: He comes after Waelvur.
RYAN: I'm the tank. Yeah. AMY: Yeah what about Waelvur?
RYAN: Everyone goes twice.
JERRY: Oh I'll handle Waelvur. Don't worry about him. KRIS: He's useless.
AMY: Oh don't worry about him? KRIS: He's no good.
JERRY: Here. I'll put this blank one here for Waelvur.
AMY: You just put it all the way to the side.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. Just put it over here on the left side of the screen.
KRIS: Every turn he's just, ah!
JERRY: No, he's...
Ugh!
(laughter)
KRIS: Abandon cart.
AMY: Okay. Let's see...
KATE: He's got pretty low stamina.
(laughter)
JERRY: All his stamina is all consumed.
KATE: Mm-hmm. KRIS: Oh yeah.
RYAN: Use Forest Friends.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah-- AMY: Oh this is a good time to use Forest Friends.
JERRY: Yeah this is Acquisitions Incorporated... RYAN: I was going to say...
RYAN: I was going to say this before, make a bird, JERRY: Nights!
RYAN: and then talk to the bird and get it to spy around what's around us.
RYAN: But I rolled a 20. AMY: That would have been really good.
KATE: Wow. AMY: But then I saved the day.
RYAN: But then I saved the day. AMY: With my ideas and with my roll.
RYAN: And my rolling.
AMY: This is... Yeah. KATE: Your magical dice.
KRIS: What's happening?
JERRY: Yeah exactly. So, Walnut... AMY: Yes.
JERRY: It has begun to slam itself against the side of the cart.
The cart seems to be holding together now,
but you don't know a hundred percent...
Obviously, you're not like a cart professional.
KATE: Not a Cartographer. AMY: So it's tracking us by magic...
RYAN: I see the monster and I say-- JERRY: Rosie Beestinger! Ladies and gentlemen.
RYAN: I see the big, scary monster and I say,
We're going to need a bigger cart.
KRIS: Ah!
RYAN: Like the movie!
KATE: The movie, Jaws. KRIS: I don't know how you do it.
KRIS: That's the one.
JERRY: Are those the jaws?
RYAN: Yeah. AMY: All right let me just talk this out real quick.
AMY: So I know I have Forest Friends and I'm tempted to use them,
however this thing's tracking us by magical means
so I don't really think I can just like...
throw some meat at it and get it to stop.
JERRY: A snack!
AMY: Yeah. KRIS: Fill the beast with meats!
JERRY: End to end! AMY: Don't fill up on birds.
(laughter)
KATE: What species haven't you eradicated yet?
AMY: I don't know. KATE: Deer?
AMY: So many creatures left to kill!
Pandas. Everybody hates pandas, right?
(laughter)
KRIS: It's the last one. Which you send it into combat!
JERRY: Yeah, it just appear, "Me?"
JERRY: "But I'm a panda." KRIS: You're up, chief.
AMY: Who's got the best chance of doing something here?
RYAN: Did we establish-- AMY: I'm talking about--
AMY: Here's what I think I want to do.
I want to...
(sighs) Rosie's so good at fighting, though.
KATE: Yeah but she's driving.
AMY: She's driving. All right. KATE: And I feel like, yeah this guy needs to be enabled.
AMY: What's your-- I don't know-- Amy doesn't know-- What's your primary stat you use for casting stuff?
KRIS: Oh charisma. AMY: Okay great.
JERRY: Charisma? AMY: So I'm going to...
AMY: I'm going to lean over the side of the cart.
And I'm going to reach in between the bars.
KRIS: Ah! AMY: And I'm just going to touch you right on your cheek.
AMY: Like I'm going to give you one of these.
And do Enhance Ability.
KRIS: Oh! KATE: Oh... !
AMY: And the one I want to do is your charisma.
So that's Eagle's Splendor. The target has advantage on any checks that would be charisma-based.
KATE: Careful with anything eagle-related with this one, though. JERRY: Yeah.
AMY: That's in honor of the eagle you murdered last game.
KRIS: Okay. AMY: Just by--
KRIS: Well I didn't do anything. KATE: Did he really murder it?
AMY: The goop did. And I hold you responsible for all goop.
JERRY: Yeah, it's like you're tied into this goop thing somehow.
KRIS: I don't know how. But I'm going to find out, mister.
AMY: That's it. KRIS: So what do I get? I get advantage?
AMY: You get advantage on any charisma-based checks. KATE: Dang.
KRIS: Oh yeah! KATE: For how long?
AMY: Until I say so! JERRY: 20 days.
KATE: Damn...
KRIS: Touch my cheek more often. AMY: Up to one hour.
KATE: Okay.
KRIS: Eagle's Splendor. Okay. I like that.
KATE: I do like the idea of taming these beasts.
So I'm going to vote for that, but--
KRIS: I'm not built for that.
That's not what's going to come out.
KATE: You talk. You can give him an evil whisper.
KATE: Tentacle whisper. AMY: You'll never get the mom.
RYAN: Yeah. AMY: We're going to have to Bambi this situation.
RYAN: Or yeah, we can tame it with murder.
KATE: Yeah. JERRY: You're going to have to Bambify?
KATE: Show them what's what.
KRIS: Do the cubs appear stout?
Would they work without a mother?
JERRY: No. They're just mewling.
KRIS: I assume that like-- but the mother is smashing itself against-- They're behind...
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, yeah. They're keeping up behind it. KRIS: Okay.
JERRY: And it's almost like they are...
AMY: Like they're learning how to hunt?
JERRY: Yeah. I mean that's a good way of putting it actually.
JERRY: They're being trained. KATE: Walnut recognizes this behavior?
AMY: As having watched all seasons of Planet Earth recently.
JERRY: Well yeah. And also-- KATE: Walnut's a binger.
JERRY: Exactly. And also being taught to hunt by your own mother.
AMY: True. JERRY: I think there's a parallel there.
AMY: Right. KATE: Also elf stuff.
AMY: Also elf stuff. JERRY: Yeah. Also some elven bullshit.
AMY: Sorry. I was just Netflix stuff.
KRIS: You've thrown yourself on a cart. RYAN: Shark Week.
AMY: Yeah it is Shark Week and you're just going to bud.
JERRY: Yeah. So you use your turn to confer a buff on K'thriss Drow'b.
AMY: Yeah and I say,
Listen, we may have to take care of this problem.
Beep.
KATE: Murderer. KRIS: Okay. So that's a "may have."
AMY: Hmm. KRIS: I'm trying to give you deference.
Because I'm not going to just throw a bolt at this guy.
AMY: You can if you want. You can do whatever you want.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. Now, K'thriss Drow'b, it is your turn.
How auspicious.
RYAN: Maybe it's trying to warn us. JERRY: The stars are right.
RYAN: You don't know it's trying to hurt us. KATE: Yeah that's what I'm saying.
KRIS: It's trying to communicate with us. RYAN: Yeah.
RYAN: It's saying, hey there's raiders up there.
KATE: The raidings got to cease. JERRY: It's like Lassie?
RYAN: Yeah. JERRY: It's like the monstrous version of Lassie?
KRIS: All right. KATE (whispering) Tame the creature!
KRIS: I'm going to throw a Hex on him-- her.
Which just occurs.
And what that's going to do...
it's going to take a disadvantage on...
What would that little fella like?
What do you think this creature relies upon?
KATE: Strength? KRIS: Dex... ?
KRIS: It ain't int. Eh it could be.
AMY: I feel like it's got to be strength or dex, right?
KATE: It seems physical. KRIS: Let's do dex.
JERRY: K.
KRIS: And I, personally, if I attack it will deal an extra 1d6 necrotic.
However, for my action...
I am going to cast Phantasmal Force to produce an illusion.
It has to make an intelligence saving throw.
JERRY: Mm-hmm. Unlikely but--
KRIS: Yeah. Seems like a safe bet.
(sighs) What should I create?
AMY/KATE: Ooh.
AMY: Paint me a picture. I want to hear it. KATE: Ooh yeah.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. Tell us. Tell us more, K'thriss Drow'b.
AMY: Yeah!
KRIS: Knowing what I know about this creature and its interests, I...
hold my focus out the side window there,
and I produce an incredible looking cart.
With an even finer horse.
KATE: (whispering) Wow...
JERRY: A juicier horse?
KRIS: Not-- Yes. It's a beautiful stallion.
KATE: It's a low bar. KRIS: Right.
AMY: A delicious looking-- RYAN: No, you want to make it look--
RYAN: Yeah you want to make it look weak!
KATE: But also delicious. RYAN: Animals hunt.
RYAN: They don't go for the strongest in the pack.
KRIS: It's an oblivious, blind horse.
RYAN: There you go.
KRIS: Look our horse is not going to feed those cubs.
You know? You got to bring home the bacon.
I know it's tough these days for displacer beast.
AMY: (laughing) Is there like a ticker on the side of the cart?
(laughter)
KRIS: Not this cart.
And fresh-- Yeah it's a cart loaded with raw meat.
KRIS: I can do that. Let's do that. RYAN: There you go.
KATE: Yeah. Nice. KRIS: That is what I do.
RYAN: A rickety cart. KRIS: That is what I attempt to do.
KATE: Rickety cart, blind... KRIS: Does it fail its saving throw?
RYAN: Rickety cart. Blind, weak horse. KRIS: Do you need my DC?
AMY: Yeah what is it? KRIS: What you need?
RYAN: Lots of meat. KATE: Juicy, meaty horse.
JERRY: Yeah what is your spell DC?
KRIS: 13.
JERRY: No. No, it does not.
So is this cart coming on the opposite side of the road?
KRIS: Is there room for it?
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, yeah. Basically you're on this side and there could be another cart.
KRIS: Yeah let's do that. It's a cart full of meat.
And an oblivious horse.
A specifically obliv--
JERRY: A horse reading a magazine! KRIS: Yeah!
KRIS: As it just walks forward.
JERRY: Exactly.
KRIS: It's always going off the road every once in a while. It's so distracted.
JERRY: Exactly. You see...
Because this thing--
It doesn't have a good sense of where your cart even is.
It's just a good hunter.
KRIS: Right.
JERRY: And so it is slamming itself where it knows there must be something.
This other cart is not like that.
JERRY: This looks like a regular cart. KRIS: Yeah.
JERRY: Coming down the other side of the road.
And as it passes your cart,
you see the two pups sort of shimmer in place,
and then they get distracted by this other cart.
KRIS: Okay. RYAN: Then we kill the mom.
RYAN: And the kids don't know and won't hold it against us.
JERRY: Exactly. RYAN: And we raise them.
JERRY: You raise them as your own.
KATE: Exactly. KRIS: Right.
KATE: They'll never know.
KATE: Someday we'll have to tell them they're adopted. KRIS: We keep them in this cart with the old man.
RYAN: Mm-hmm. Have sex with him!
KRIS: I don't know. That's his thing.
RYAN: I don't know. Dungeons &amp; Dragons.
(laughter)
JERRY: I've never even heard about it.
So this beast is loping alongside the cart.
It's already slammed its body into the side.
It is now...
You can see like serpents, these two tentacles
branch out directly from the shoulder blade
and then curve forward with these strange patterns at the front.
You can see that it has, while it's running along the side,
it's just started to bat at the cart with both of them simultaneously.
KRIS: Oh wow, okay. JERRY: Just reaching out and finding the cart.
AMY: Was that its turn?
JERRY: Yeah, it's going to attack the cart and deal real damage.
AMY: No, that's okay, bud.
KATE: What's the cart's AC?
JERRY: I'll handle it. I'll handle the AC. AMY: Negative three.
JERRY: So the second one, almost like a cobra in a basket,
just waving and trying to bat at something.
The other tentacle connects pretty firmly with the side.
And then knocks out a portion of the side of the cart.
KRIS: Oh in the coach where we're sitting.
KRIS: So it rips more, then. JERRY: Yeah, yeah, so you see it--
RYAN: So it rips the back of the cart open.
JERRY: Just like this! Right along the side.
And you can see it within feet of you.
AMY: Great. &gt;&gt; KRIS: Yeah. Ah. JERRY: This sort of like starving frond inside there.
RYAN: So this is Jaws. It just bit the back of the boat.
JERRY: It's Jaws.
JERRY: All right. Rosie Beestinger. KRIS: (whispering) It's Jaws.
KATE: Question. JERRY: What are you going to do?
KATE: Can this beast actually see us or are we still Passing without Trace?
JERRY: You're still Passing without Trace but it is...
JERRY: It is... AMY: It's got a hint.
JERRY: It's hunted before. KRIS: It's forming a map in its mind.
KATE: Right. So it is tracking us via magical means.
JERRY: Another system. KATE: So if I were to just throw this cart in reverse, it would know.
KATE: It's not just guessing where we are.
JERRY: Right now it's actually struck and hit. KATE: Right.
JERRY: So it knows-- Right now it knows.
JERRY: But you could change that pretty easily. KATE: Okay.
KATE: Yeah that's my instinct is that it paced us, and we did not change our pace.
Therefore they did not change their pace.
JERRY: Oh, ho, ho.
KATE: So my Pass without Trace is on me.
So I'm going to brake Coriander down.
And that's not a problem because she's not a very fast horse.
AMY: Mmm. JERRY: No!
KATE: She stops immediately and I'm going to try to do a--
(clicks tongue) Back her up, girl.
And we're going to try to throw this bad boy in reverse.
JERRY: So you-- RYAN: Aren't they directly behind us?
KATE: I think it's running on the side. RYAN: Oh. All right.
JERRY: So you basically gear-shift the horse down.
KATE: Yeah. Get that clutch.
KATE: (car sounds) Chroom. Beep. Beep. Beep. JERRY: Front is froth.
KATE: Yeah. JERRY: Spittle.
JERRY: I mean this horse has been working. KATE: Oh I thought you were talking about me.
JERRY: No. You're fine.
Please don't do that. Anymore. No, it's fine.
So you start to brake the speed down.
And it is continuing to run.
And it's continuing to wave and bat along the side as you see it, basically, running in front of the cart now.
KATE: Okay.
JERRY: At a greater rate.
KATE: Okay so it believes that we have outpaced it and it's trying to catch up.
JERRY: Yeah as far as you can tell, it's behaving as though the cart is up there.
RYAN: We won.
KATE: We won Dungeons &amp; Dragons.
AMY: Well we got to keep going.
JERRY: The end. Level one million.
(laughter)
Donaar Blit'zen.
RYAN: Ugh now I don't know what to do!
KATE: Hah! Take that! RYAN: I can't fight the thing. The babies ran away.
JERRY: What was your original plan? RYAN: So nap, I guess?
KRIS: Nothing to fight. Nothing to eat.
RYAN: Yeah! KRIS: I don't know what to do!
RYAN: I legit don't know what to do.
So it just runs off into the distance and the babies run behind...
KATE: Waelvur's a good time. RYAN: Encounter over. Yeah.
KRIS: He's good for it. JERRY: Done and dusted.
RYAN: Um...
Yeah. I don't...
JERRY: And you cry. KRIS: What would you do?
KRIS: Like, you're not going to be diplomatic with this beast.
RYAN: No! I was going to go at it crazy. But it just ran away.
It just went doodle-doodle-doo down the road.
KATE: That's true. But it's probably going to be back. So...
KRIS: You can bring it back with that Duel.
KATE: You can-- &gt;&gt; RYAN: Compel Duel? AMY: I think I see what you're doing!
RYAN: After we tricked it and be like,
Hey, dummy! And then, come get some of me! Tough man.
KATE: That is a very Donaar thing to do, though.
KRIS: It is. Hi!
JERRY: You leave this invisibility sphere of protection. Hey!
RYAN: How far away did the babies go? Are they gone?
JERRY: They're not a part of this encounter right now. RYAN: Yeah, so they took off.
JERRY: They followed this mystical meat wagon. AMY: You saved their life.
RYAN: Yeah. KRIS: I think that would make the mother upset.
RYAN: Yeah! Right? KRIS: Once she noticed.
RYAN: Yeah. She's going to double back for them? AMY: She'll find them. She can track.
RYAN: Are we trying to skirt past this thing or are we trying to fight this thing?
KATE: It's up to you. You can just pass your turn if you're--
RYAN: Well that's what I'm saying.
I'm saying if we're trying to be invisible and we're trying to trick it,
then are we trying just get to the town and we don't want to mess with it?
KATE: Okay our combat apparently has not ended, so there is potentially other stuff for you to do.
RYAN: If I cast Bane on it...
KATE: Is it within range? JERRY: Yeah what's the range?
RYAN: 30 feet? How far away did it run?
JERRY: It's probably faster than 30 feet. It's very fast. Just past 30 feet.
RYAN: D'oh.
JERRY: Whatever you want to do, you can do.
KATE: Strike a pose and be like--
RYAN: I don't want to fight it. You have to fight it.
All right I'll fight it. You're not allowed to fight it.
(laughter)
AMY: But you can save any of this for when it does double back.
Like the instant it gets back in range you're like, okay I cast Bane.
KATE: Yeah you can um... What is it? Prepare?
RYAN: Well I mean, if I'm prepping for a fight, who's going to get up in its grill the most?
RYAN: Probably you? Right. KATE: Probably.
RYAN: So I go over to your little old face.
And I palm it.
KATE: Uh huh. JERRY: Like a basketball.
RYAN: Not a gentle like-- I go like-- Yeah. AMY: A lot of face touching in this one.
KATE: Yeah. RYAN: Yeah and I just give you Shield of Faith.
KATE: Nice. Shield of face.
RYAN: Yeah. Shield of face. KRIS: I love the caress...
KRIS: And then that. And he's like, that looks good. RYAN: A shimmering field surrounds the creature of your choice--
RYAN: plus two bonus to AC for duration.
KATE: Plus two bonus. &gt;&gt; JERRY: Plus two AC. AMY: You got it.
JERRY: Now... &gt;&gt; KATE: Thank you. RYAN: Concentration so it's the only one I can do.
JERRY: So Waelvur corks his bottle.
Makes sure that it's firmly wrapped up in some leather.
AMY: Sure. JERRY: Grabs a rough plank off the base of the cart.
JERRY: And tries to hammer it over the hole.
AMY: Oh perfect! KATE: Nice.
KRIS: Nice.
RYAN: Oh I want that hole.
JERRY: And succeeds. KRIS: He knows his carts.
KATE: Succeeds! JERRY: He succeeds.
AMY: Wow.
KATE: The cart's in better shape now than it was before. JERRY: Yeah exactly.
JERRY: A couple more rolls like that and you'll have--
AMY: He also made curtains.
RYAN: Wait till the acid gets a hold of this cart.
Because that's what was coming.
I'm going to spit a blast through that hole!
KRIS: It was like that Nissan Cube for a while.
JERRY: Exactly. KRIS: Now we just have a dumb cart again.
KRIS: And that's too bad. JERRY: Now... !
AMY: Uh oh.
JERRY: Walnut Dankgrass.
AMY: Mmm!
Here's what I'm going to do is I am going to...
KATE: What are you going to do?
AMY: (sighs)
KRIS: I would like-- RYAN: Bear.
KRIS: One of your...
KATE: Finest...
AMY: Well I was wondering if maybe I wanted to get all like--
Because I can like...
basically just web all over the place, and then it's in my web.
KRIS: Oh. KATE: Oh yeah! Web it!
RYAN: Yeah. So we stopped. Right?
KATE: Yeah, we're-- RYAN: Or did we just slow down?
KATE: We stopped, and I got us backing up very slowly.
RYAN: We should just, yeah, build a little trap.
KRIS: (whispering) Yeah.
RYAN: Like dig a hole and then cover it with leaves. KATE: (singing) Built a little trap! Build a little trap!
(laughter)
KATE: Sharpen your toothbrush and put it at the bottom?
KRIS: Oh yeah! AMY: Just one toothbrush?
RYAN: Yeah. My sword, she means.
AMY: Okay so...
Good god... I don't want to...
I really want to wait for it to come back.
JERRY: You can.
AMY: Yeah. Okay, I'm going to-- RYAN: Your little cart move slowed down all the action.
RYAN: Now we're all like, I don't know what to do.
AMY: Well it's just like-- KATE: You're welcome.
AMY: Yeah no, I think it's great.
I'm just thinking maybe we can actually sneak past it.
That it's possible to avoid combat in Dungeons &amp; Dragons.
Believe it or not.
JERRY: Yeah. &gt;&gt; KRIS: You can try. AMY: People do it.
AMY: So I'm going to-- RYAN: When do we cash in our accounts?
RYAN: This is what we were hired to do, though, right?
KATE: No, I don't think-- This is not The Raiding Must Cease.
We haven't even talked to Lord Vizguard...
KATE: Wagon... Cartinwheel. AMY: This is not a one-episode arc.
RYAN: I thought people were confused.
They thought people were being raided but it was actually this monster.
JERRY: Yeah.
KATE: What? He got it right?
JERRY: No. RYAN: Oh.
JERRY: But-- AMY: But it's a theory.
JERRY: I support that 100%.
KRIS: We don't know what this thing is capable of.
It might also be a bandit.
AMY: I'm going to wait to wild shape until it gets within, we'll say 30 feet.
JERRY: Within the wild shape zone?
AMY: Yeah.
Within the zone of my combat anxiety where I'm like,
Okay! Now I got to be an animal.
KATE: Yeah. JERRY: Exactly.
JERRY: Okay now. KATE: Don't make me be an animal.
JERRY: K'thriss Drow'b. &gt;&gt; KRIS: Yes. KATE: Don't let me get my zone.
AMY: Don't let me get my zone... JERRY: What is your action?
KATE: (whispering) Definitely get in my zone.
KRIS: What action shall you take, young man?
Gosh.
If we're just hanging out, kind of want to see what it does.
KATE: Yeah. RYAN: Nap.
KATE: You're just academically curious? AMY: Make a drink.
RYAN: What about the cart?
KATE: You're sketching the displacer beast.
KRIS: Yeah. As my action I compliment Waelvur on his wagonsmanship.
(laughter)
KRIS: It is well built.
Real quick.
Amazingly done.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. He's just absentmindedly just give it a couple quick taps.
Looking at it.
Couple of quick taps.
JERRY: He's a perfectionist, clearly. KRIS: He loves his work. Yeah.
AMY: I really appreciate that you're not afraid to just completely give up a turn and just be like,
See what happens. I don't know.
KRIS: I think that-- AMY: Whatever. Roleplay.
KRIS: It's not-- I have--
The only things I can do is bring that thing back.
If I can even reach it. Well I can reach it.
KATE: I could reach it but I won't--
KRIS: I could kill it, but I won't. RYAN: Yeah, you're controlling the cart, so...
KATE: Yeah.
RYAN: You have to vary our speed if we want to not engage it.
KATE: Do we see-- Has it turned-- So it's turned back. JERRY: Yep. Yeah.
KRIS: This is its turn now. JERRY: It has.
JERRY: It has come back.
It has turned and is--
It's like the traditional jousting set up.
Here is your cart, except you are not visible to it.
And here is this creature coming down the road directly at the cart.
Just sort of sweeping the air in front of it with its tentacles.
JERRY: Just trying to find-- KATE: Trying to find us?
JERRY: Trying to find you.
KRIS: What kind of reach does it have on those--
How long abouts do they look?
JERRY It's pretty substantial.
KRIS: 80 feet. RYAN: Like a linguine noodle.
AMY: Linguine!
JERRY: No. Ten feet. KRIS: Okay.
JERRY: It's-- AMY: Good linguine!
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. It's a lot. It's thick. It's fresh.
KRIS: Wow. KATE: That's-a good linguine.
KRIS: Al dente. JERRY: Dark linguine.
KATE: May it be my turn?
JERRY: It is now Rosie Beestinger's turn, that's great. KATE: Wonderful.
KATE: I would like to cast Minor Illusion.
At its maximum range which is 30 feet.
I would cast it far behind us.
I will stop the cart. Cast it.
And the Minor Illusion will be the sound and image of its baby crying.
KRIS: Ooh yes. KATE: I don't know what that sounds like but I just--
I'm like, whatever the most horrible noise that I can think of--
JERRY: You did hear it. KATE: I did hear it, so I do know what it sounds like.
RYAN: Yeah you heard them mewling. KATE: Mewling!
KATE: Okay I'm going to amp that up so that it sounds like distress.
KATE: So I'm going to cast-- RYAN: Maximum mewl.
KATE: And I'm going to stay super still and hope that it freaks out and we can just book it.
Coriander can go max speed.
AMY: Oh Coriander.
KRIS: Who's been witnessing this entire thing. JERRY: Ugh.
JERRY: No. KRIS: This is an ancient horse.
KATE: That's not a thing? JERRY: That is not good.
JERRY: I had not even have to fudge it for dramatic purposes.
KATE: Uh oh. KRIS: (gasps)
JERRY: It was actually a very bad roll.
So when that sound hits...
just this sort of keen mewl--
like a two-tone mewl.
You see the-- before it's been seeking and like actively looking.
Now they start to writhe...
in midair.
It leaves the road all together.
And sort of casts a wide berth.
And...
(stammering) The actual creature.
You simulated the creature itself, right? Or is it just the sound?
KATE: Both. Yeah. JERRY: Yeah.
JERRY: It leaves the road, still seeking with the fronds,
and just makes a beeline back for this creature.
KATE: Great. JERRY: And it's awful.
JERRY: Because as it gets close--
First of all it can only see one.
KATE: Ah. KRIS: Oh.
JERRY: Then as it brings these tentacles together around it,
passes directly through.
KRIS: (whispering) Oh! No...
KATE: I created a mother's nightmare!
RYAN: Yeah. That was good. JERRY: Donaar.
RYAN: I say, hurry the cart up!
(laughter)
KRIS: As my action I yell at you.
RYAN: As my action I say, good job! Let's go!
KATE: Do you want to jump on and maybe drive the cart?
RYAN: Yeah, I guess. KATE: Yeah, do that.
RYAN: How big am I?
RYAN: Can I get through the cart? KATE: You're very big. You're a big boy.
RYAN: Is there like a barrier to the front?
KRIS: Maybe you can reach through the window and pull the reins.
RYAN: That's what I'm saying. Yeah! AMY: You're like, I won't be outside for this.
RYAN: Just like push my arms through. Hyah!
JERRY: It covers--
The Pass without Trace covers--
JERRY: You can come around back. RYAN: Oh okay yeah.
RYAN: We'll have time. That's right. I keep forgetting about that. All right, yeah.
JERRY: Yeah. So the sound is horrible.
Like the wailing from this creature.
AMY: Great.
JERRY: Yeah. This is the campaign's about, I guess.
RYAN: Yeah, so I get old Coriander going.
JERRY: Yeah. You gun it. RYAN: Giddyup.
RYAN: Yeah. KATE: Maybe Coriander would like a Goodberry.
AMY: Do it.
RYAN: I'm out of actions. KRIS: Not your turn.
RYAN: My action was to go up there and go, hyah.
KATE: All right.
JERRY: We can...
Goodberries can be fed to horses. I mean I want to make sure...
RYAN/KATE: All right. AMY/KATE: Yeah.
AMY: Wait! Are you asking me? JERRY: Yeah, yeah.
KRIS: Lethal to horses.
AMY: (sighs) My god... KRIS: The only animal that cannot eat a Goodberry.
JERRY: It's your turn. AMY: A creature...
JERRY: Yeah. KATE: Nice.
AMY: can use its action to eat one berry.
RYAN: Oh is Coriander a creature? Hmm.
KRIS: Did it roll initiative? (laughter)
JERRY: It's like these creatures eat fruit. I mean you seen--
AMY: Yeah sure.
RYAN: I could lay on hands the thing too.
KRIS: Don't waste it.
JERRY: So you... AMY: Don't waste that.
JERRY: You've instructed this beast...
to move along the road toward Westbridge.
And then you see the displacer beast behind the cart...
AMY: (whispering) It has a name!
JERRY: look back.
And just sort of scanning the area, trying to find you.
And then it has other concerns, apparently, and it sees to them.
AMY: (Final Fantasy VII battle victory music)
KRIS: XP, zero. RYAN: Yeah.
(laughter)
AMY: Aww yeah.
JERRY: No, it's... RYAN: We did it.
JERRY: That's not how it works anymore. AMY: But we experienced... life.
KATE: That's right. AMY: And that's the most important thing.
JERRY: That's not how it works anymore. KATE: The real XP you gained was friendship.
JERRY: So! It's like this...
You enter the town of Westbridge.
And the cart is not in the best shape.
KATE: Was it ever though?
JERRY: No, but it is, arguably, in even worse shape than it was before.
Waelvur knows of a place in town.
KATE: Not Thelorn's though.
JERRY: (stammering) Don't even bring up Thelorn's Safe--
Don't even bring up Thelorn.
KATE: I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
JERRY: As a dungeon master, like out of game,
do not bring up Thelorn with Waelvur.
KATE: I'm sorry. I didn't say it in character. I said it out of character.
JERRY: It's going to be a thing. KATE: I would never mention it. Okay.
JERRY: So...
KRIS: So potent that even out of character he's...
JERRY: Ugh! KRIS: Something!
AMY: The voice is screaming.
JERRY: But he knows of a place called the Harvest Inn.
That's run by what he calls "a strange man."
But the beds are good.
And the food is good.
He says that some of the art is... not good.
JERRY: But... KATE: Hmm...
JERRY: But you know, that's not why you stay at an inn. So...
KATE: Maybe not you. JERRY: Yeah.
(laughter)
KRIS: So deep!
RYAN: Wow! KRIS: Learned a lot.
JERRY: Waelvur agrees to sleep out in the cart.
You think that that's a normal thing for him.
And he busies himself doing some finishing work on the cart so that it can survive the rest of this trip.
KATE: Nice.
KRIS: I just thought he was painting it or something.
JERRY: No. Exactly. So--
KATE: Gilding it.
JERRY: It's near the end of the day.
It's starting to get dark.
You see people are getting to their inns of choice.
Settling in for the evening.
As the...
Hoardsperson...
you should subtract six gold.
KRIS: Okay.
JERRY: It's not the best place, but it's not the worst place.
There's some kind of a premium.
Probably because of where it's situated on the Long Road.
Maybe it's vacation prices.
Who knows?
AMY: Surge pricing on the Harvest Inn? JERRY: Exactly!
JERRY: At the Harvest Inn. You look down at your app.
So you can sort of see what he means.
You decide to take a quick meal downstairs before you retire for the night.
And you can sort of see what Waelvur's talking about in terms of the art.
There's a lot of...
sort of amorphous...
half spheres.
There's definitely a visual theme.
But it's hard to really perceive exactly what they're going for here.
AMY: Hmm...
KRIS: This is art on the walls, or this is actually--
JERRY: These are-- He has some paintings.
But most of what he has are sculptures of different kinds.
KATE: Amorphous half spheres?
JERRY: Yeah. KATE: Like-- Like nuts?
JERRY: Well-- &gt;&gt; KATE: It's not like-- KRIS: Take it easy, Rosie.
JERRY: No, no. &gt;&gt; KATE: (laughing) What? AMY: That's our word.
JERRY: No, no, no. It's odd.
But you hear sort of a--
As your plates come,
JERRY: you hear sort of a hush in the room. KATE: (whispering) Like walnuts. Acorn.
JERRY: And then you can see a man.
Very proud, obviously, of what he is about to do.
He sort of strides by tables.
Touches people on the shoulders.
Says, "Thanks for coming tonight."
KRIS: (laughs)
JERRY: Right? AMY: (sighs)
He approaches in the center of this room are two daises.
One of them is empty.
And then the second one has a sheet of blue silk on it.
And he smiles at the crowd and says,
"You're welcome."
And he pulls off this silk sheet.
And you think it's just a sculpture of an ass.
You think that it is someone's butt.
And when you look at the other pieces...
you think that...
he just has sculpt--
you think that all of his sculptures are just--
(pencil clattering)
JERRY: of butts.
KATE: You laughed at me when-- RYAN: I "apploud laudly".
(laughter)
RYAN: I clap. Say, magnificent!
JERRY: He points at you. He's like...
KRIS: My man! KATE: Donaar finally understands art for the first time in his life.
KATE: I get it!
JERRY: But it's like-- AMY: Well he likes portraits of himself.
RYAN: I'm a prince.
KATE: (laughs) JERRY: Bam!
RYAN: I don't get it. KATE: Falcon swoops in!
JERRY: But it's like halfling ass...
RYAN: Yeah!
JERRY: Elven ass...
Like it's just a panoply of asses.
There's an aasimar ass.
There's a genasi ass.
KRIS: My god! JERRY: It's like...
KATE: Panoply of asses...
JERRY: He is... AMY: Butts all the way down.
JERRY: He is-- Butts from top to bottom.
He is overjoyed at the collection he has managed to...
AMY: Is that the harvest?
JERRY: Yeah. A butt harvest? KATE: An ass harvest.
JERRY: So he... KRIS: Harvest Moon!
JERRY: But there's something that bothers him...
You can tell like this is supposed to be--
Like it's a moment of triumph.
And obviously he's received appreciation from those who with the taste...
JERRY: The curatorial-- RYAN: It's called pomo. All right?
RYAN: Sorry you don't get it.
JERRY: The curatorial tastes to appreciate it.
But you can see his hand sort of like...
wants to slide over the empty dais.
And he gives it a couple quick pats.
And then you can see him turn towards your table,
and you can see a single tear come out. And he just...
He wipes it and just-- (sniffs)
KRIS: (laughs) AMY: What's happening?
KRIS: Oh man!
I don't feel like we need to do persuasion on this.
He's ready to spill on this tale!
JERRY: Do you want to engage him?
KRIS: Friend...
AMY: Everyone's your friend. RYAN: Yeah, everyone's your friend.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, exactly. "Friend."
KRIS: Friend. I couldn't help but notice your emotion.
You've created so many... beautiful figures here. And...
JERRY: "Yes." KRIS: And yet--
JERRY: "Yes." KRIS: And yet!
KATE: And yet...
KRIS: And yet surrounded by beauty, you feel pain.
JERRY: He says...
"The alto."
"The tenor."
"The bass."
"But my soprano..."
And he gestures just weakly, limply at the empty dais.
He says,
"There are shipments that have been going missing."
"On the road east of here."
"One of them included my soprano."
"I think I know who is doing it!"
"I have..."
"Let's say it."
"A competitor in this space."
"A competitor that traffics in profane works."
"Sir!"
"I want to describe for you one of the statues in their collection."
"This is a statue that is sold for more than 400 gold."
"It is a boy..."
"who pees!"
AMY: (laughs)
KATE: That's it?
KRIS: Disgusting.
JERRY: "I think that there is a gulf between the work on display at the Harvest Inn..."
"and the sort of material one might find from a Pragma Cleft."
"Subpar."
"Urine-oriented."
"Not good!"
KRIS: Oh dear. Oh dear! I say.
Dreadful.
Scandalous.
JERRY: "So what brings you to the Harvest Inn?"
"Well, what else?"
KRIS: (laughs)
We actually have been sent on a task to undo the raids on these roads.
KRIS: If we find them-- JERRY: "Is that so?"
KRIS: it might be possible to recover your prized piece.
JERRY: "The soprano..."
KRIS: The very same.
RYAN: (laughs)
JERRY: "You will know it by sight!"
KRIS: I imagine we will.
(laughter)
KATE: No doubt.
JERRY: "It is of a piece with my current theme."
KRIS: Keep an eye out for that.
JERRY: "Were you to return that to me..."
"I am certain..."
"I can find some means of compensation."
KATE: Uh-- KRIS: It is done!
KATE: But-- Well... let's talk brass tacks here.
So what kinds of compensation are we-- No? You know?
KRIS: No, no, no. Yeah, no. Let's do that.
KATE: (laughs)
KRIS: I don't want to over-promise. AMY: I don't want to be-- Yeah, I lean to Donaar and I go,
AMY: I don't want to be compensated with a butt!
(laughter)
RYAN: I don't know.
KATE: I have a feeling-- (laughter)
KATE: I have a feeling it'll be butt-themed. RYAN: I don't know. I feel like he's got good taste.
KATE: And I'd rather have gold.
Or a better cart.
At this juncture.
RYAN: What if we get butt decorations in the cart? KRIS: We get a butt; we sell a butt. It's not a big deal.
AMY: Do you know art dealers? KRIS: Apparently it's in demand.
KATE: Do you know a butt fence?
AMY: Although it may be-- KRIS: There must be many of them in this area.
AMY: It might make our base look more... official.
RYAN: Make our base a home.
RYAN: You know? AMY: It could really tie the room together.
KRIS: Look great on that shelf. AMY: I've come around on this butt thing.
(laughter)
AMY: Walnut doesn't understand the trappings of civilized people.
She's like, I mean it seems good?
KRIS/KATE: This is what they do! KATE/KRIS/AMY: Yes!
AMY: This is like fancy plates on the wall and butts in your house.
JERRY: Exactly. KATE: All right. All right.
KRIS: Yeah, I-- JERRY: So you're like, eh.
(laughter)
KRIS: Yeah are you the only one in our group that would actually take issue?
Because I feel like I'm not from the surface world,
KRIS: so I'm not sure. JERRY: So you're like, "Okay. Butts."
AMY: We're like Ariel with the fork. We're like, okay...
JERRY: It's the dinglehopper, right? AMY: Yeah exactly.
KATE: And Donaar just likes butts.
AMY: And Donaar thinks it's great art, so I'm like... RYAN: I'm a fan of the art.
AMY: Okay. KATE: So I'm the only one who's like...
JERRY: It's like granny. Right?
KATE: Yeah. Yeah. Little old lady. JERRY: Mmm...
KATE: She's like-- (stammering)
Okay. Sure.
If it makes you happy, let's do it.
RYAN: When we get back to the base,
we take that big, old painting of the kids off the mantle
and we put this butt picture there.
KRIS: Yes! JERRY: Done!
JERRY: Clean! AMY: We don't even know if we're getting a butt, but...
RYAN: Now I demand it. I say...
(stammering) There better be butt art!
KATE: The only thing we will accept is butt art.
JERRY: You pay me in any other way...
So...
You scrape the last bits of food from the plates.
Room's comfortable.
Warm. Dry.
Voices begin to die down downstairs.
You wake in the morning.
Waelvur is not awake.
But the cart...
KRIS: Is on fire. JERRY: No.
(laughter)
JERRY: The cart is a heap of ashes.
No. The cart-- You got to say, honestly...
giving it a quick once over,
you think it's in better shape than when you first got it.
RYAN: Eyy.
KATE: Nice. JERRY: It has a little more spring in its step.
KRIS: Waelvur!
JERRY: One of the wheels has been replaced.
You don't know where the wheel came from.
RYAN: Syphon gas from another cart.
(laughter) JERRY: Right?
But you are now ready to leave Westbridge
via the Stone Road and head toward where the "raids..."
are currently going on but must cease...
if you are to satisfy the letter of the law of your requirements.
AMY: Three of your berries expire.
RYAN: Oh!
JERRY: They expire berries?
RYAN: Wait I had four. Now how many do I have?
KRIS: What if I eat it anyway? What would happen? AMY: You keep track. I'm telling you--
KATE: The ones you made the first day. So we made them, we ate one, so two?
AMY: So two expire. KATE: Okay.
KATE: Everything from the first day. AMY: I replace them with two, so your math is fine.
KATE: Okay. AMY: And then I'm going to give one to Coriander.
KATE: Nice, nice. AMY: And keep the rest for myself.
JERRY: All right. KATE: Okay.
JERRY: Right. So...
Like I say, Waelvur tip-tapped apparently through the night.
Gentleman's tuckered.
AMY: Oh I give him one too.
Whoops.
Humans!
JERRY: You just put it on his lips.
RYAN: Pry it out of the horse's mouth.
(laughter) JERRY: No! No.
RYAN: Yeah. AMY: I split it like an apple. No, I don't do that.
RYAN: Then put it in his mouth. And then you hold his mouth shut and rub his throat.
(laughter)
What is happening?
JERRY: You get the-- (warbling sounds)
RYAN: I fix the cart -- (warbling sounds)
KATE: Coriander's shoulders just like slumped.
She was like, so close.
AMY: No, I fed her. I fed her. JERRY: Yeah, she's fed.
KRIS: K good.
JERRY: So you head out in the bustle of the morning town.
You head out the east road there.
KATE: Are there any shops with provisions we might want to stop in before we head out?
JERRY: East from Westbridge--
Yeah, yeah. Typically at the edges of towns like this you can always find something. What are you looking for?
KATE: I don't know. Raiding must cease.
So we got any kind of healing herbs or potions?
KATE: Or other things we might stock up on? KRIS: We got Goodberries aplenty.
KATE: Well Goodberry heals one hit point.
KATE: I'm not saying it's not enough. RYAN: Oh really? Oh.
KATE: I'm just saying... AMY: It is just one HP.
RYAN: I thought it was like a senzu bean.
AMY: No. KATE: It's like a little edamame.
KRIS: An amuse-bouche.
AMY: (laughing) It is an amuse-bouche.
No and I took off any other healing spells that I might have because I just assumed--
Originally when we made this party, Ryan said at one point, I could have heals.
RYAN: I do have heals!
KATE: He has heals. AMY: Then there we go!
RYAN: Not a lot of them!
KATE: Right. AMY: Well we're only level three.
AMY: There's only so many HP to lose and gain.
RYAN: That's true.
KATE: Famous last words. I will still pick up some potions.
JERRY: Okay. KATE: I have some gold that I picked up off a dead guy...
KATE: that we killed once, so I'll spend some of that. JERRY: Okay cool.
JERRY: How much are you looking to spend?
KATE: I got six gold.
JERRY: Mm-hmm. KRIS: This is interesting.
KRIS: It's like a little-- Like I hear that little pan music. RYAN: If I had my other cards. I want to swap out--
KRIS: The shop theme in my head. KATE: Yeah?
AMY: Oh you don't have your whole deck with you?
RYAN: No it's over at Elyssa's desk.
JERRY: Mm-hmm. AMY: Oh no.
KRIS: That is over-budget for us. I'm sorry, but we cannot-- KATE: (laughs)
RYAN: I hope I need Command. AMY: Yeah. Oh...
JERRY: Yeah, the stuff that you're seeing at these shops here,
six gold isn't going to get you much.
KATE: Okay. What about-- Hoardsman?
JERRY: Yeah you can get healing herbs.
KATE: Yeah. Okay. JERRY: Absolutely.
JERRY: But in terms of a healing potion, something like that you'd need a few "sa-shays" of quasi... you know.
KATE: And a healing herb is something you just go-- (eating sounds)
We don't have to have an alchemist in the party to do--
JERRY: What it will do is it will help you with medicine checks.
KRIS: Oh. KATE: Interesting.
RYAN: I'm rich and cool.
KATE: Okay. Well buy us some potions, moneybags.
KRIS: What's it going to cost per potion then? KATE: Fancy-boy.
JERRY: You find a shop run by a person with exceedingly shifty eyes.
A cart right on the edge of town...
that will sell you three potions of healing...
for 30 gold.
RYAN: (sighs) KATE: I'm going to haggle.
AMY: Yeah.
KATE: I think we could probably-- Let's say...
We're unloading these potions.
You look like you got places to be.
Why don't we say all three for...
15 gold?
JERRY: "25 gold."
He looks over your shoulder like he's expecting someone that he doesn't want to see.
KATE. Right. Well let's-- You know. Let's um...
KATE: Let's take our time. JERRY: "25 gold!"
KATE: Let's take our time. 17 gold.
JERRY: "25 gold!"
KATE: (sucks in breath) 18 gold.
JERRY: "20 gold!"
KATE: 20 gold it is.
JERRY: He's reaching his hand out, just...
(laughter) (clapping)
KRIS: I love this dice-less interaction! It's amazing!
RYAN: Should we test these potions?
KATE: Not important. RYAN: Okay.
KATE: Hand over the cash. AMY: It's sugar water.
KRIS: What do you got there? Got coin on you? KATE: 20 gold?
RYAN: Yeah, I got it. AMY: Oh my god!
RYAN: I'm royalty! JERRY: He's rich.
AMY: I-- but here's the thing is that Walnut-- anytime he keeps saying he's a prince-- is just like...
JERRY: All right. Now who is going to hold these potions?
KATE/AMY: Hoardsman. JERRY: Individual?
RYAN: Oh I was going to give one to everyone.
JERRY: There's only three. KATE: Oh sure.
RYAN: Yeah sorry. One to everyone else.
KATE: Not you. You can heal yourself. RYAN: Because I have lay on hands.
RYAN: I can heal myself, worst case scenario.
JERRY: K. One, two, three.
RYAN: I mean if we get split up, I'll just--
(sounds of pleasure) I feel better already.
KRIS: Let's go ahead and just do that. RYAN: Oh it feels so good!
KATE: Okay, okay. So now we each have a health potion. AMY: Health potion.
JERRY: Yeah. A "health potion." &gt;&gt; KRIS: So well done. AMY: I'm going to make a little inventory right here.
KRIS: I enjoy that.
AMY: Jerry! RYAN: "Health potion" in quotes?
AMY: Okay. KRIS: Yeah.
KATE: Or is it?
RYAN: Can we test? Can anyone test it?
KATE: I didn't bring my pH strips. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Can we smell it? JERRY: Is that a good idea? I don't know.
JERRY: Put in them strips!
No. It's like this...
RYAN: These are all health mimics.
KRIS: This potion has agreed to die. JERRY: So you are...
JERRY: You grab your potions. You were able to haggle down.
You feel good about what you were able to deliver there.
Grandma-style. You know what I mean?
We're talking about those...
swap meet talents.
Over a hundred years of swap meet values.
KATE: Town champ swap meets. JERRY: You brought it home-- Yeah, yeah, yeah. Oh yeah.
KATE: Had trophies. JERRY: GOTY. Right?
KATE: They don't even give trophies for that, but they gave them to me.
JERRY: No, exactly. And you had to haggle for it!
JERRY: Like that's how it works! KATE: Had to haggle.
JERRY: And so as you load up, distribute them, he's just drumming his hands on the surface.
You get in your cart. You start rolling out on the Stone Road.
And then just when the town is at the edge of your vision,
you look back and you see what you think is the town guard.
You see a tall hat.
You see them just descend on the cart like locusts.
(laughter)
KATE: Hmm.
AMY: Did we just smuggle drugs out of town?
AMY: Great. KATE: Mm-hmm.
JERRY: All right. AMY: Can't wait to drink this!
JERRY: It's the sub-quest.
AMY: Yeah. KATE: Yeah. Be careful.
RYAN: This has turned into GTA.
KATE: Mental note.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. But you have three stars!
AMY: When you said that we were going to another town, I got Skyrim quest anxiety.
Where it's like, we're going to pick up more quests!
And I can't deal with it.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. No, it's okay. I'll handle it.
I mean right now, how many quests do you really have?
AMY: Five.
JERRY: You got butts...
KRIS: You got butt one. KATE: Butts. &gt;&gt; RYAN: The butt quest.
AMY: Butt quest. Cart quest. KRIS: That's stuff later though.
AMY: Onyx quest.
JERRY: Oh! You're thinking about the chicken.
AMY: I'm the Documancer! RYAN: Yeah, so the chicken quest--
RYAN: and then the to-be-determined party security quest.
RYAN: What's the 5th one? JERRY: Exactly. Oh yeah that's true.
AMY: A dark quest. No one needs to know about.
(whispering) I miscounted!
A dark quest!
JERRY: But that's what I like. So you've internalized this Documancer business.
Like all the way in there.
AMY: I have a Google spreadsheet of our quests.
AMY: For real. JERRY: Exactly.
AMY: But a magic one!
JERRY: So as you progress east along this road...
there aren't quite as many carts as you saw going north and south on the Long Road.
This is a place people go to seasonally.
It isn't quite as busy as that north-south passage.
You know that in the great distance the Stone Bridge...
A beautiful-- Basically a cathedral of stonework that has been the site of famous battles.
That's a substantial period of time away from here.
But it's basically like cathedral-level geometric beauty that people just ride carts over.
Like it's a note-worthy piece.
Not far. Maybe four and half, five hours into your trip going east on the Stone Road.
You come across what you hope won't be the first ruined cart.
So...
It is off the road. Perhaps... 50, 60 feet?
Just sort of dragged off.
The horses are apparently completely decoupled from it.
But you-- As I say, this could be the first evidence of this.
There could be other information.
Ryan may have another interpretation of these events.
RYAN: (laughs) JERRY: You know?
RYAN: Well we should check it out.
KRIS: No, that's no-- KATE: Yeah? You want to hop out?
RYAN: Yeah. KATE: All right. I'll stop the cart.
KRIS: Okay. KATE: You want to get out there?
KATE: I'll keep an eye on this cart.
RYAN: All right.
Yeah I mean, could be a trap. Yeah.
KATE: Go on, Donaar.
KATE: What do you see? What do your... KRIS: Who's going to stop for a ruined--
JERRY: Yeah. What do your dragonborn eyes see? KATE: What do your dragon eyes see?
RYAN: Yeah.
KRIS: What you looking at?
RYAN: I don't know. Should I roll? What do I see?
JERRY: So you jump out of the back? RYAN: Hmm.
JERRY: And then your feed hit the ground.
And then you hear two more feet hit the ground right behind you.
Waelvur is apparently interested in this as well.
RYAN: Oh. AMY: Oh for spare parts.
RYAN: Yeah, I want to loot the cart. KATE: Cart enthusiast!
JERRY: Yeah. So he has brought his bottle with him.
You don't know to what extent that is going to affect his assessment of these proceedings.
But your experience, Rosie, is that he knows how to drink.
KATE: He does. JERRY: He's gone pro-tier.
AMY: Among other things. KATE: His expertise goes up after he's drinking.
JERRY: This is what you see pulled over.
As I said, the bridle-- the entire front of it is a wreck.
As though it's been-- the horses had been cut free.
And then the tines that project from the front of the cart are actually dug into the ground in front of it.
As though it moved for a time and then was stopped.
You see here what looks to be a carriage that held prisoners.
AMY: K. RYAN: Ooh.
JERRY: So the carriage body is of very sturdy construction.
It's not comfortable in any way.
It is meant to carry criminals from place to place.
But it is very practical and pragmatic in its manufacture.
Up where you would tie the reins off, you see an owl.
A small carving of an owl that has a strip of leather wrapped around one of its metal feet.
There is also, as you open up the back, you can see that it has part of--
basically the armature and some of the mechanism of a small catapult.
And this one also has...
What you would-- for a lack of a better term, a cool spoiler.
RYAN: Nice.
KATE: Cool? JERRY: Yeah.
RYAN: It's a cool spoiler. JERRY: It has a sweeping darkwood edge on the back.
KATE: We're definitely going to want that.
JERRY: So these are the parts from here.
Waelvur's pretty deep into this bottle.
You wonder if he has more in there or if this is another bottle.
But that's the situation.
He's creeping around this cart carcass with some interest.
RYAN: Hmm.
KRIS: Guy knows his carts. AMY: Grab that owl.
RYAN: I snatch that bottle from him. I say,
Focus on what's at hand here, buddy!
Had enough out of you.
JERRY: He reaches into a back pocket and gets a flask.
RYAN: All right.
(laughter)
I put the bottle in my pack.
KATE: Add it to your inventory kit.
RYAN: Hmm. Waelvur's bottle.
JERRY: So as I said. It's a sturdy, if boxy, prisoner carriage.
Cool darkwood spoiler.
Part of a catapult mechanism?
And an owl statue to tie off--
RYAN: So we just did a little pass-around.
JERRY: Exactly. RYAN: Like I'm...
KATE: Are you out there too?
KRIS: Yeah. I'm going out. RYAN: hollering to make sure, is anyone in there?
RYAN: Is this... is anyone around?
KRIS: Yeah is the compartment shattered open?
Or is it like solid and shut?
JERRY: It's odd. So the actual door on the back that would be released by the person who is bringing the prisoners--
The lock on it is broken.
And you see near or around the lock, you see bite marks.
KRIS: Hmm.
AMY: My favorite kind of marks for a thing we're tracking.
KATE: Are you out there too?
AMY: I would like to jump down.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. It's all there for you.
So those are our things.
And he's looking back at your cart and he's looking at this cart...
AMY: Can I do a survival check real quick on these bite marks?
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, yeah. Sure.
AMY: I just want to see if I know anything about them.
I want to see if I know anything about bite marks.
Ooh. Maybe I do. 12 plus five. 17?
JERRY: They're not animal marks.
KRIS: Ugh. RYAN: Hmm.
AMY: Ew. Gross. Ugh.
KATE: Walnut's not interested anymore!
(laughter) JERRY: Now it's gross!
(laughter)
AMY: She immediately goes like, people bit this.
KATE: (laughs)
RYAN: So I yell and no one's in there, and no one's around, right?
JERRY: No, no, no. Whatever-- RYAN: I say, hey. Okay.
RYAN: Whatever's in proximity.
JERRY: Whatever happened here, happened already. RYAN: Okay.
RYAN: Then I grab drunkee and I say,
What do you think? Should we--
Anything you can take to salvage our cart?
Or should we switch carts? What's your professional opinion?
JERRY: He takes a deep swig.
RYAN: I'm going to take that fucking bottle, dude.
JERRY: Then he takes a second, even deeper swig.
KRIS: Looking at you in the eye. RYAN: I know.
JERRY: Then he holds it up and looks at it.
And then shakes it a little bit and gets some in his eye.
And then he's like-- (grunting)
RYAN: I say, give me the bottle! And I take this one too.
KATE: I'm going to yell from the cart,
Don't knock it till you try it!
JERRY: Try what, Rosie?
JERRY: So-- RYAN: Throw this one off in the distance.
RYAN: I don't keep this one.
JERRY: He's like, "Well what do you want?"
KRIS: He's doing good by us.
RYAN: Cart analysis! Here.
JERRY: "I can take that and put it over there."
"Take that. I can remove this."
"What do you want?"
KATE: Let's Mad Max our cart. RYAN: I want to combine these carts!
KATE: Yes. RYAN: You drunk little fool.
(laughter)
KATE: So angry.
RYAN: I know! I got no patience for this guy.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah.
So he looks to you and he says,
"Can you bring that cart..."
"over here?"
KATE: (laughs) RYAN: Oh my god.
(laughter)
AMY: I see the rage building in Donaar, and I'm just like, okay.
JERRY: Now he's going to cover him in acid.
AMY: And I want to just like lead Coriander and try and like get the cart--
KRIS: Get the carts together? AMY: Get the carts closer.
RYAN: We got new horses. Coriander's probably going to be dinner.
KATE: I'm going to-- RYAN: Cori-dinner.
KATE: I'm going to hop of this cart because it seems like no one has actually tried to open these doors yet.
I'm going to stick my quarterstaff in the bars of the prison cart and just kind of nudge around in there.
KATE: See if there's anything soft.
JERRY: No, there's nothing soft or moist.
KATE: K. JERRY: Or flaky.
KATE: Okay. RYAN: All right.
KRIS: Or buttery.
JERRY: (laughing) Yeah you can open the back of this cart. (laughter)
You can open the back of the cart if you want to.
This has been passed over pretty substantially in here.
There's a couple old swords?
Longswords.
But there are not any-- There's no coin.
You can see something that might have been a secret compartment underneath one of the benches.
Where you can see the chain link.
But it's empty. It's been gone through.
KATE: Okay.
AMY: Can we salvage one of these-- Yeah.
AMY: Yeah get this guy to salvage these parts. RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: Go ahead and drive the process.
RYAN: I want to take that...
KATE: Cool spoiler. Yeah. RYAN: that cool-ass spoiler.
KRIS: It's coming. RYAN: And I want that owl.
JERRY: Cool spoiler. RYAN: I want them swords.
JERRY: Hey now, I was going to say, this owl is...
KRIS: I was going to say, let's look at this owl.
AMY: Yeah it said it had leather around its...
KATE: Its foot? AMY: Its foot.
KRIS: Hmm. KATE: The foot.
AMY: Is there a secret missive in there? KATE: Yeah should we do some checks on this?
KATE: See if it has some significance? JERRY: Absolutely.
AMY: Everybody, look at this owl!
(laughter) KATE: Druids!
JERRY: No. Dude. Dude. KATE: Concentrate!
KATE: I'll do a history check...
Which is a ten.
KRIS: Can I investigate this owl? JERRY: Arcana-- Absolutely. Arcana is good.
KRIS: Oh arcana. Imma do it. Okay.
KRIS: I'm actually-- RYAN: What about athletics?
KATE: Rosie does a history check, and she's like,
I've never read a book about any owls.
JERRY: Period. KATE: I've never read a book with an owl in it.
JERRY: Not because I haven't been able to. Because I don't like them.
KATE: I don't like them. RYAN: I got 18 on history.
KRIS: Hmm. KATE: Wow.
RYAN: I know a lot about owls.
KATE: Tell me one thing about owls.
RYAN: They go hoot.
KRIS: Bet you didn't know.
RYAN: Yeah bet you didn't know. The more you know. KRIS: 13 arcana.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. They're symbols of wisdom and protection.
They're commonly adorned on carts.
You...
It would take more investigation on your part.
You'd have to come back and approach this later.
But it's not just a statue of an owl.
KRIS: Oh yuck.
KRIS: We going to-- RYAN: It's like your owl's owl.
KRIS: No. We're going to keep this owl with us.
JERRY: Yeah. Bring it with.
Continue to spend quality time with it.
KATE: You're like, that's my owl. JERRY: So yeah.
JERRY: So what are you trying to get off of this thing?
AMY: Spoiler. JERRY: Cool spoiler!
RYAN: The spoiler, the owl, the swords...
AMY: Really? Is there like a spare wheel in here? KRIS: See something good? &gt;&gt; RYAN: Sell them!
KATE: And their toothbrush.
RYAN: Look if this was Skyrim, I'm "take all."
KRIS: How long are all these modifications going to take?
KATE: Mugs. Cheese. What do we got? KRIS: How well we in for?
KRIS: How long are we on the road while he cobbles together a super-cart?
JERRY: We'll see. We'll see. There's--
AMY: We're getting a good cart out of this!
RYAN: Like there's lumber. I feel like we can reinforce, right?
KATE: Yeah and there's also parts of a small catapult. RYAN: He obviously knows his stuff.
KATE: Which I feel might be useful for us if that displacer beast comes back.
RYAN: Take the catapult, and just reinforce... JERRY: So...
JERRY: And there's also the carriage itself on the back.
I mean you could choose to just go that way.
RYAN: Take that cart? KATE: Yeah.
JERRY: And modify the rest. AMY: It looks way more sturdy.
KATE: And it was a prison cart so I feel like we can keep stuff out.
AMY: Yeah is there anything from our cart that we would want?
JERRY: Yeah. That's the question, right?
RYAN: So we're just stealing someone's cart now?
KRIS: It's an old cart. It's a busted cart. AMY: We're not stealing it!
RYAN: Why are we doing this mission?
All right. We got our reward. The end. We go back?
KRIS: No, we have to get that ass!
AMY: We want the ass and we want the 200 gold.
RYAN: Oh we do want the ass statue. Shit.
JERRY: The cart is not the payment. RYAN: Goddamn it.
AMY: Also the other thing is-- RYAN: Sprinkle that MacGuffin in there.
AMY: The other thing is I point to the missive that has the, you know.
And I'm like, I want to report to Head Office that we did something this week.
JERRY: (laughs)
AMY: I want a good Q1! KRIS: This cart was just something for us to the job with.
JERRY: Q-motherfucking-1.
KATE: Consider this...
We take both carts.
Two carts...
AMY: But how do we pull it? RYAN: Split the party.
KATE: Donaar pulls the second one.
JERRY: Split the "carty." AMY: He'll never do that.
RYAN: No, I thought there were horses there.
AMY: No, no the horses-- KATE: The horses are gone.
RYAN: Oh they were gone. Uncoupled. KATE: You're going to have to pull the cart.
RYAN: That ain't happening. You know what else can probably pull a cart? A bear.
AMY: (laughing) That's true. KATE: That's even better. (laughs)
RYAN: That's true, I don't see a bear.
Guess we only get one cart.
RYAN: Wac-wac. KRIS: Shoot.
AMY: We don't need the crummy one.
AMY: All right we can take the-- KATE: Let's transfer.
AMY: We can take the all-weather canvas.
The leather.
KATE: The S-hooks. AMY: The S-hooks.
JERRY: Love it. KRIS: All that junk in the back.
AMY: All the nail. JERRY: Junk in the trunk!
RYAN: Yeah. KATE: Whatever Waelvur needs.
AMY: And then let's-- Can we like...
Can somebody strong peel just a couple of loose boards out of there?
Just so we have like a cart repair kit.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. AMY: Like a first aid kit.
AMY: You know, you keep it in the trunk in case... KATE: Muscles. You want to peel some boards off?
RYAN: You know what's strong? A bear.
(laughter)
JERRY: Waelvur is picking up what you're putting down.
He is over at the cart.
And you see him-- he removes a couple key...
JERRY: A couple key posts. KRIS: (laughs)
JERRY: And then jumps back. AMY: (laughs)
JERRY: As it basically devolves into a wagon kit.
KRIS: Yeah. AMY: Amazing.
JERRY: So he's able to grab a few planks...
AMY: And the wheels.
JERRY: to bring along. You don't want those wheels.
AMY: Not even one wheel?
JERRY: Maybe the one wheel he stole from Westbridge. AMY: I want one wheel.
JERRY: That might be a good plan. KRIS: I want to wear it.
AMY: I want one wheel.
KATE: Like a necklace. AMY: Actually, I like this idea...
AMY: Because if we get the people who are responsible for raiding
and we don't want to murder them we can bring them back in the thing.
KRIS: Or their bodies. KATE: An anti-murder campaign from Walnut. How surprising!
KRIS: You can go in there with them.
AMY: You guys get on me for murdering stuff!
You get on me for not murdering stuff!
KRIS: We did a great job with the displacer beast. AMY: You're the kid sister of the group.
KATE: We got to tease you.
AMY: Sure.
KRIS: Okay. We got what we need.
RYAN: Make me a comfy bed in there.
JERRY: So you're going to roll out. So you're going to keep a hold on the catapult...
KATE: Yeah. Right. JERRY: armature?
JERRY: They're in the back?
KATE: Is it usable?
JERRY: You could ask.
KATE: I'm going to-- Yeah. I'll ask Waelvur.
Does this look functional to you? Do we need to repair it in order to make this a catapult situation again?
JERRY: I'll have him take a look at it.
K'thriss, he's staring at it for a long time.
You're not sure he's going to stop staring at it.
AMY: Oh no.
KRIS: (stammering) Okay can I rouse him?
Can I just shake him on the shoulder?
KRIS: Friend? The catapult? RYAN: Did he say, arouse him?
KRIS: I arouse him. Yeah.
RYAN: Twist his nipples. KRIS: If this doesn't work...
RYAN: Say, hey! Focus, buddy!
KRIS: If this don't work, he's lost.
JERRY: Exactly. KRIS: I leave him here by the side of the road.
KRIS: Jeez. Can I perceive him?
JERRY: You don't have to perceive him! KATE: Something about that catapult.
JERRY: No, yeah, yeah. yeah. He's just like,
"I just really like it."
KRIS: (laughs)
It could be ours.
KATE: My dude. You got to focus up. (laughs)
KRIS: It's a good cart. JERRY: You see him go out and examine the side.
JERRY: And you can sort of see some diagram just unfolding in his mind.
You see his eyes just flitting from place to place.
And he says,
"I would need some time."
KATE: How much time? JERRY: "But I can roll with that?"
JERRY: "If we got a big fire, I could probably do it overnight."
KRIS: Siege horse!
KATE: I think it's worth it.
I think having an extra ballistic--
AMY: What time of day is it?
KRIS: It's afternoon, I think.
RYAN: Can I sleep in the cart as he works on the cart?
JERRY: Yeah. KATE: Yes!
RYAN: Okay, then yeah. Let's do that.
Yeah. JERRY: It'd be loud.
KATE: Can we build a big fire? You got a big fire in you?
KRIS: We got a wagon we can set on fire. We can have a huge fire.
KATE: That's true.
JERRY: It is not time to shut down just yet.
AMY: So why don't we keep going and then we'll-- JERRY: Yep, yep.
KATE: Okay.
AMY: When it's time we can work on it. KATE: Got it, okay. Yes. Great.
JERRY: Exactly.
So you roll back in.
You can see Waelvur is inside just...
running his hand along the edge of this catapult armature.
Very, very excited about the possibilities.
AMY: He's just very a sensual man.
JERRY: He is! KRIS: Yeah, I look at Rosie and say,
KRIS: (whispering) Is that what it was like?
(laughter)
Just curious.
JERRY: Yeah you hear-- AMY: He's just into intimacy in general.
JERRY: You hear...
Waelvur doesn't look back at you,
but he looks down at the catapult and he says,
"She's a weapon."
(laughter) AMY: Whoa.
RYAN: And I say, it was nothing like that!
(laughter)
JERRY/AMY: I was there! RYAN: I was there.
RYAN: I lived it. I will never stop living it.
(laughter)
JERRY: I can see it now!
So you continue.
Starting to become similar to the Sumber Hills that you drove through before.
You're starting to reach an area where hills like that are rising up on both sides, before the Stone Bridge.
And this is where you find the second cart.
KRIS: Hmm. AMY: Huzzah.
AMY: What's it look like?
JERRY: This other cart has...
It's maybe received a little bit more of a rougher ride.
But you think it just might be because the prisoner carriage is so well manufactured.
This is almost like Gothic in its look.
It almost looks like a cart from a story.
AMY: Shit! Took the wrong cart.
JERRY: It has a-- RYAN: Is this the rest of the game now?
KRIS: We each get a cart! RYAN: We just jump from cart to cart?
JERRY: It has a spacious interior.
RYAN: Ooh.
JERRY: On one side is sort of a U-shape of velvet couches.
RYAN: Oh... AMY: (laughing) We got to take this cart.
RYAN: I want this cart. KRIS: It's sumptuously appointed.
JERRY: In the back it's almost like the way a boat or a ship has to be clever about a constrained space.
There's different sorts of tables.
Small workspaces that can fold out from the inside there in the back.
Where you would tie the reins around on this,
is a small statuette of a cat.
There's also an array--
Sort of tied together by straps of black leather, tightly,
is what looks to be a bunch of cigar boxes.
But the closer you look...
you peer inside the box you can see that it's just rows of wands.
KATE: Oh... RYAN: Mmm.
JERRY: So it's almost like-- RYAN: Take that.
JERRY: It's almost like a two by four set of cigar box-like wand cases.
KRIS: And where was this found?
JERRY: This is in this sort of Gothic... KRIS: Oh inside.
JERRY: blackwood, red velvet interior.
There is also underneath this cart--
It's sort of tipped on its side, like one wheel is kind of up on a ridge of stone.
If it were darker it would be easier to see.
But examining the undercarriage, you can see a glass chamber.
And you can recognize it. It's filled with Dancing Lights.
KRIS: Oh. Okay.
Light source?
KRIS: It's still active? KATE: So it actually has ground effects?
JERRY: Yeah. KATE: Nice.
RYAN: Hmm.
AMY: I mean I know that, meta, you're annoyed that we just keep switching carts; but I feel like...
KATE: I think that Donaar might prefer this cart. RYAN: No, I like this. It's real velour!
JERRY: Yeah. No, it is nice!
You run your soft palm against it.
KRIS: I don't like it.
AMY: You don't like a goth cart? KRIS: It rubs me the wrong way.
KRIS: Oh I like the look of it. I don't care for that velvet. I'd rip that out.
RYAN: No. The velvet stays.
We add more velvet.
JERRY: (laughs) Actually we put velvet outside. RYAN: Yeah.
KRIS: That's where I want it.
Waelvur.
(laughter)
KRIS: Upholster this cart. JERRY: Snap, snap!
KATE: Would we recognize any logos on those wand boxes?
Is there a manufacturer?
AMY: Yeah what brand are these?
RYAN/KATE: Yeah.
AMY: I don't want these fly-by-night knockoffs. RYAN: Generic?
JERRY: Yeah, exactly. Exactly. KATE: Yeah.
RYAN: Costco-assed wands. Get out of here. KRIS: Yeah. Bulk.
KATE: Costco's got really high-quality goods.
RYAN: Gucci wands.
KRIS: I want to do-- AMY: This episode brought to you by Costco.
JERRY: In an attractive, swooping script, it says, "Percival's."
KRIS: Ah... RYAN: Hey, like my toothbrush.
KRIS: Hey! AMY: The very same.
AMY: You look at all these-- KRIS: (growls)
AMY: Your toothbrush was a wand? KATE: Toothbrush wands?
RYAN: Yeah, I start brushing my teeth with a wand.
My toothbrush was a wand the whole time!
What the-- What?
KRIS: Wha--!
RYAN: I'm a real wizard!
KRIS: Ah... And you fly away.
JERRY: In the morning and at night.
RYAN: Yeah. JERRY: Right?
KRIS: I want to do another arcana check on this cat.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. Examine it. KRIS: Let me examine it.
KRIS: Do I got anything good-- Oh! I'm going to use advantage on this.
JERRY: You should.
AMY: Somebody likes you.
KRIS: Don't need to. 20!
JERRY: You could do another roll again. Because it's good to do that.
AMY: Let's just see. KRIS: You want me to? All right.
KRIS: I'll do it. I just want to see what my-- Where the heck is it? I just want to see what my modifier was.
KRIS: They're both excellent. JERRY: Oh jeez.
KRIS: 23 is going to be my number.
KRIS: Ar-ca-nah! JERRY: Yeah, yeah.
JERRY: So you think that this little statuette,
when installed on to the cart--
the cart of your choosing, obviously--
confers a Silence spell on the wheels.
KATE: Oh! &gt;&gt; KRIS: Ah... RYAN: Stealth cart.
AMY: These are awesome. But then maybe the owl does something too! We can swap them out.
JERRY: Yeah. Take a look.
KRIS: May I? Shall I? JERRY: Take a look. Yeah, yeah. It's--
JERRY: A bunch of time has passed.
KRIS: Is it within enough of my-- Okay. JERRY: Yeah, yeah. The refractory period is over.
KRIS: I'm so good at arcana, you guys.
AMY: Are you? KRIS: Nope!
KATE: Wow!
KRIS: I don't know what this bird-thing is.
JERRY: You don't even recognize it as a bird.
JERRY: You like hold it upside down. RYAN: That's a funny looking cat.
KRIS: I try to gnaw on it.
JERRY: This cat's fucked up you guys. KRIS: Yeah.
KRIS: We got a good cat and a yuck cat.
JERRY: But that's the situation we have in terms of...
For the true cart enthusiast there are options available.
KRIS: This is carts aplenty! KATE: So speaking of cart enthusiasts...
Does Waelvur-- I know he is lit. But...
JERRY: Oh yeah. Perpetually.
KATE: Can he maybe--
If we tell him like with this cat casts a Silence spell,
what is your best guess about what an owl statuette might bestow upon a cart?
JERRY: Your guess is that he...
Your guess-- I mean it didn't come up, obviously, that night.
But there are other topics discussed.
None of them had to do with arcane statuettes.
Honestly the person to ask would be the guy that runs the Harvest Inn.
He's the one with the statue fetish.
KATE: Yeah he's kind of butt-focused, though. KRIS: What do those confer?
JERRY: It's a very specific sub-genre.
KATE: Any owl butts?
KATE: I guess... RYAN: Why does he keep those statues?
KATE: I mean I guess we can use our brains.
Owls are a symbol of wisdom.
AMY: Which is somewhat of a misnomer actually...
KATE: Right you told me owls are wicked dumb. AMY: that owls are a smart bird of prey.
KATE: You told me that for years.
AMY: Sorry. 20 years. KATE: Every time we bring up owls.
AMY: I just want everyone to know!
Stop owl propaganda!
KATE: Okay. So owls are stupid.
JERRY: Yeah! KRIS: Owls suck.
JERRY: They're bad and dumb.
AMY: But perhaps it confers one of those ones...
Isn't there one that's an owl? Maybe there's not one that's an owl.
No I'm thinking of Eagle's Splendor. No! Owl's Wisdom.
(laughing) Maybe it gives us advantage to wisdom checks.
KATE: It's a very wise cart.
KRIS: Do we really want this cart?
And to stop up and have a cool cart?
Or we like our cart?
AMY: I would like to say that as official members of Acquisitions Incorporated wouldn't it really be...
detriment to the brand to not have the nicest looking cart that we possibly could?
KRIS: But if we have a fancy cart, as opposed to this business cart,
people are like, oh they're here to prance around instead of get work done.
AMY: But the lock is broken on our prisoner's cart,
and this one seemed like it was, as you said, very good construction.
JERRY: It's very good construction. Obviously, it doesn't have the pragmatism of the prisoner barge.
AMY: Sure. &gt;&gt; JERRY: But... KRIS: Can I Mend that lock?
JERRY: It's not bullshit. KRIS: I'm not going to do it, but could I Mend the lock?
JERRY: We can investigate it.
KRIS: All right. So whatever. KATE: What do you think?
KATE: I believe that the practical route is best.
I am a fan of the prison cart.
I believe that the Gothic cart is ostentatious to a fault.
I think the ground effects are gaudy.
KRIS: (sighs) We need a decision. KATE: However...
AMY: I'm so happy that things turned out the way they did!
KATE: However I do believe that this Percival fella probably wants his shipment of wands.
KATE: So we should at least take that with us. KRIS: Oh yeah, I already took them.
KATE: As a little side quest.
KRIS: Oh I wasn't even--
KATE: Oh you didn't even bother saying it. It goes without saying.
AMY: I listen to that and I go, hmm interesting. And just very calmly go, Donaar?
(laughter)
RYAN: I like the velvet.
KATE: Well he is the Decisionist. RYAN: (clapping)
AMY: That's three votes for this monstrosity. KATE: Three votes, yeah.
KATE: Look how that turned out for you.
You were so worried about it.
AMY: I'm like writing it, I'm like-- I actually keep a very detailed documentation of what we do everyday.
And it starts with like, dear Omin...
And it's like, today we found a very good-looking cart.
I'm sure it'll make you proud.
(laughter)
KATE: Can't wait to meet you, dad-- I mean, Omin. RYAN: The ground effects.
JERRY: So just to verify.
We now have a Gothic cart.
You have in your possession an owl statuette.
KRIS: Yeah. RYAN: That does question mark.
JERRY: Exactly. A cat.
You have catapult mechanism.
AMY: That's coming.
JERRY: And you have the Dancing Lights.
Now is the spoiler staying back here?
JERRY: Are we going to take the spoiler? RYAN: No, take the spoiler. We'll put a spoiler on it.
KRIS: Oh that's gauche.
We're not going to put a spoiler on this beautiful cart.
KATE: At this point?
(laughter)
KRIS: Come on! RYAN: That's gauche.
KATE: Don't gild the lily, folks!
(laughter) RYAN: That's a hat on a hat.
JERRY: Oh man! There's all-- Oh! I'm not going to say anything. I'm not one of the players.
KATE: (laughs)
JERRY: I'm not one of the players. KRIS: So excited. All right.
KRIS: Yeah okay. Yeah you can do it.
AMY: But the spoiler-- I mean, why-- Meta.
Why would this human, who's sitting behind this thing, describe a spoiler to us if it wasn't--
I don't know! There's got to be something!
Why would you go through the trouble of saying there's a spoiler!
KATE: It's tight as hell! JERRY: I just want to make sure--
JERRY: I'm just putting content in front of you...
JERRY: and I want to make sure that-- RYAN: It paints a funny visual.
KRIS: It's a couple nails. You can throw it on there. It's fine. I'm not going to fight this battle.
AMY: What time is it? RYAN: It makes us go faster.
AMY: Yeah. It's true it makes us go faster.
What time of day is it? Is it time where we could stop and do this whole...
KRIS: It's not cart o' clock.
JERRY: Yeah you think... RYAN: Just about to say that!
JERRY: It's cart o' clock.
No. You think that there's definitely more travel to do today.
And then you can wrap it up.
KATE: Waelvur. What's your opinion of the spoiler?
JERRY: "Sweet."
KATE: Same. RYAN: Nice.
RYAN: I high five him.
JERRY: He's way down here, but you kind of go down.
RYAN: I push him into the ground.
JERRY: You just grind him.
All right. So now I understand.
You have a Gothic cart with a cool spoiler.
And chambers full of Dancing Lights beneath.
You have the owl and cat hood ornament.
And you have a catapult armature.
JERRY: All right. You continue on to the east. RYAN: What cart will we see next?
AMY: Yeah you got to update your sketch.
JERRY: If only you knew.
Yeah. The cart sketch is going to be updated each time.
KRIS: I'm glad I didn't start drawing that other one.
KRIS: Waste of time. KATE: Augmented. Yeah.
JERRY: Very near to the Stone Bridge.
It is now plainly visible in the distance.
You can see a cart cruising very quickly across this bridge.
And then out of sight.
And then on the left side of the road,
you can see a third cart,
with one of the wheels actually still spinning,
tipped over on the front right.
KATE: How far away is this escaping cart from us?
JERRY: It is on the other edge of the Stone Bridge.
You think it would be challenging to keep up with that.
They clearly did not want to be here anymore.
KATE: How big is the Stone Bridge?
JERRY: The Stone Bridge is massive.
KATE: Okay. Golden Gate Bridge in size.
JERRY: It's very, very big.
This cart looks like a cart from a story.
It is mostly...
It is basically-- Yes, exactly.
If you were to transform a pumpkin into a cart...
But it has certain advantages.
Insofar as it is completely round.
Windows placed, evenly spaced around it.
It has where you would tie off the rope,
it has a crystal ball...
AMY: I ain't grabbing that.
JERRY: in the center.
KRIS: Are we stopping for the cart?
I guess we're not going to make--
JERRY: I'm just going to let you know--
There is a-- I'm just going to let you know what you see on here.
There is a chamber underneath the rear carriage,
that you poke it a little bit and it sprays something slick.
Some slick fluid.
RYAN: Some Spy Hunter stuff. JERRY: Right?
KRIS: Yeah.
JERRY: And so you get back. Obviously it's disgusting.
Inside this cart...
as I say there's a central table,
and then there are different workspaces around the central piece.
On opposite corners you got two quarter circle couches.
And then you have something that looks like an alchemical station. Titration. Things of that kind.
A small library in this section.
And... It's not quite as-- Like the construction is opulent.
There is also a minibar.
But near the front where you would communicate with the driver,
you can see a small skull...
that is sort of mumbling and muttering to itself.
It has a little ring of metal...
attaching its upper teeth and its lower teeth.
So it's trying to communicate,
but there is this ring that is preventing it from speaking.
AMY: We got to pull on that ring.
KRIS: Got to tug that ring.
KATE: Free those mandibles up.
RYAN: I want to examine that crystal ball.
AMY: Yeah let's do that-- Wait any there any people in here?
JERRY: Mm-mmm. AMY: Oh they're-- it's gone.
KATE: Just a skull trying to talk to us?
KRIS: This skull's part of the cart.
KRIS: It's like a feature of the cart. JERRY: Yeah.
JERRY: Yeah but it could be removed, you think. KRIS: Oh okay.
AMY: What would look better on a goth cart than a chattering skull?
KRIS: This is dope! I love this cart! RYAN: Take that minibar.
KATE: Oh my god. KRIS: MTV's Carts.
(laughter)
KRIS: I'm going to go ahead and pull that ring.
KATE: Yeah, I want to talk to that skull.
JERRY: It starts to sing very loud.
RYAN: Oh it's a radio. Nice!
KRIS: What's it singing?
JERRY: It is singing... KRIS: Anything that we know?
JERRY: Yeah it is singing a...
elven birthday song.
RYAN: (singing) Friday, Friday...
(laughter)
AMY: Party bus. KRIS: They're always born on a Friday.
KATE: Is it your birthday?
AMY: Not today.
KRIS: How me make ring go back on?
(laughter)
JERRY: So it's just-- (incomprehensible singing sounds)
You're just like...
KRIS: Yeah. (grunt) Okay.
JERRY: Then I guess it's just-- (humming)
KRIS: It's just back to business.
Let's look at this crystal ball.
So that's notable.
JERRY: Go ahead. RYAN: Yeah.
KRIS: Arcana again... AMY: Who doesn't want to take that?
KRIS: (blows raspberry) Trash.
JERRY: You don't know. You don't even know what balls are.
KATE: Should I check out the library?
JERRY: Yes absolutely.
KATE: Tell me about the library.
RYAN: Just take it all with us.
JERRY: The library has a number of books on history.
A couple tasteful, you would describe it as almost curatorial selections of poetry from different regions.
KRIS: Hmm.
KATE: Okay.
You've mentioned that the last two carts that there are workspaces.
KATE: Can you describe what that means exactly? JERRY: Yeah, yeah, exactly.
JERRY: So one of the corners is entirely given over to goofy-looking magical bullshit.
KATE: Nice.
JERRY: Potion manufacture. Basically magical cooking.
And then this library area also has a stenographer's setup for duplication, transcription, things like that.
KATE: Okay. Does it seem above board? Or is there evidence of illegal goings-on?
JERRY: It doesn't seem illegal.
KATE: Okay. Okay. RYAN: This is like a Breaking Bad RV?
JERRY: (laughing) Yeah. KATE: Exactly. Exactly.
KATE: Okay.
Seems cool.
No blood? No evidence of violence?
JERRY: You don't see anything like that in this cart.
RYAN: Can you see any logos?
KRIS: Yeah. I wonder if this was targeted. JERRY: The McDonald's logo.
RYAN: Yeah. KATE: McDonald's logo.
JERRY: (laughing) No, no. Don't write that down.
KATE: (laughing) It's too late.
JERRY: There's nothing--
RYAN: Like the Percival-- Anymore of that Percival logo anywhere?
JERRY: No, no, no. Nothing like that. KATE: No, this is not Percival's cart.
KATE/AMY: Okay.
KRIS: Hmm.
KATE: Okay and you tried to do something with the crystal ball.
KATE: Nothing. KRIS: Couldn't figure it out.
JERRY: It was too dumb. KATE: Okay.
KRIS: We're going to take it with us though. KATE: Can I try a perception check on it?
JERRY: Yeah sure. KATE: Okay.
KATE: 18?
JERRY: Yeah so you can-- As you're looking through it,
you know that people use devices like this the same way that K'thriss uses his focus.
I mean you know that there's different scales of interaction with this type of thing.
But even just looking through it,
you can see all outside the cart.
Like just at the base level.
KRIS: Like a backup cam!
KATE: Yeah. RYAN: Backup cam. Nice.
RYAN: I thought it was going to be GPS.
JERRY: You're not even trained to use it.
And you can look at it and get a sense.
You can turn around and be looking outside the cart from each perspective.
KATE: That's extremely tight.
KRIS: Does it transfer to other carts?
KRIS: Or is it just this cart? KATE: Yeah can we take it?
JERRY: Try. KATE: And move it? Okay.
KATE: I'll pick it up. JERRY: You break it.
RYAN: Oh. &gt;&gt; KATE: Sorry. JERRY: No.
(laughter)
AMY: I was so upset! RYAN: The house is on fire!
AMY: I was like, son of a...
JERRY: No, it's fine.
There's a bolt on each side,
but you think you can remove them
JERRY: and withdraw the device. KATE: Okay.
AMY: Take it. These are slottable buffs. KATE: I'll do that, yeah.
JERRY: You break it.
KATE: For real? JERRY: No.
(laughter)
AMY: God every time! KATE: Damn it, Jerry!
JERRY: It's fine. No, no. You're able to withdraw it.
You think that that crystal ball could be mounted very easily where you would wrap the...
RYAN: Presents.
JERRY: the tethers around.
AMY: At the gift wrapping station in our goth cart. RYAN: In our goth cart yeah.
JERRY: At the gift wrapping station at the mall. KATE: So you guys are still into goth cart.
JERRY: You're still gothing.
RYAN: Like, yeah! We're just going to take the cool stuff from this one--
KRIS: I'm in the-- KATE: This one's even cooler than the goth cart.
AMY: In what way? &gt;&gt; RYAN: How so? KATE: It's bigger.
KATE: There's an alchemical station. We can make potions. There's magical cooking. There's a library!
KATE: There's like a stenographer's-- JERRY: This is my fantasy!
(laughter)
KATE: Arguing the merits of carts! KRIS: Cart fight!
AMY: I am tantalized by the stenographer's station.
AMY: As I have my bagful of documancy. KATE: Documancer.
AMY: I'm like-- (sound of consternation)
RYAN: This is like a Cinderella pumpkin cart though?
KRIS: I'm already taking some of the alcohol from the minibar to return to our friend.
Because he's been good to us.
JERRY: He's working hard. AMY: He's been good and dry.
KATE/KRIS: Yeah.
KRIS: I don't want to metagame. AMY: I'm fine.
AMY: I think our black cart's very cool.
KATE: (sighs) All right well we're going to vote.
AMY: Yeah okay. Let's vote.
It matches the horse.
KRIS: Is that going to work? RYAN: All right.
KATE: This new cart's way better.
RYAN: All right. Put it to a vote. KATE: And bigger.
KATE: And better and fits more couches. The gothic one only has one couch.
KATE: This has two couches! RYAN: Are we going to vote or are we going to talk?
KATE: Okay.
All right. I want the library cart.
KRIS: I want the gothic cart. I don't care. KATE: Oh my god.
RYAN: I vote prisoner cart. No.
(laughter)
RYAN: We're going to go back and we're going to get the prisoner cart. I changed my mind.
KRIS: I'm going to live here in this cart.
JERRY: Exactly. All right.
I think I understand what your intentions are.
Here very near the geometric heap of the Stone Bridge.
You can see evidence that people do park by here.
Not just to make out. They rest here.
KATE: Really? &gt;&gt; JERRY: Yeah. AMY: But also to make out.
JERRY: But also-- Yeah. Making out is a possibility.
That's how we started this adventure. We can wrap it up that way as well.
KATE: This is our horniest adventure yet.
JERRY: Oh yeah. Hey listen. From here on out, just fuckfest.
RYAN: Yeah, our app is in a park and ride in the high weeds?
JERRY: Oh yeah this is just-- RYAN: Bad things.
JERRY: Yeah there's no party like a Holkins party.
And so you're able to break camp.
Waelvur immediately-- fully empowered by the minibar.
KRIS: (robot activating sounds)
JERRY: Yeah, he has reached his-- RYAN: Engorged.
JERRY: He has reached his final form.
He's going bat-shit out there.
In terms of the...
You're interested in which of these weapon devices?
RYAN: I say, pick it clean. Take what we can take.
JERRY: Yeah. And you want him to try and install these things on there?
RYAN/AMY: Yeah.
JERRY: And he's like looking at all this junk that you have piled up.
And he's like...
"Am I installing the wands?"
KRIS/RYAN/AMY: No. RYAN: What, are you an idiot?
AMY: (laughing) Smack him. RYAN: I smack him.
KRIS: I want the wands as the spokes of the wheels.
(laughter)
I just want spells firing off as we roll.
JERRY: Chain gun? AMY: It's like a Roman candle.
KATE: I want to fashion stilts so I'm taller than everybody.
(laughter)
KRIS: We can get a pogo wand.
JERRY: He's like, "No? No wands?"
AMY: No. No wands.
RYAN: No. We're just going to keep them all in the box.
JERRY: "All right well I just-- Because they could..." KRIS: Oh, no. That's good.
AMY: Wait, wait, wait. They could what? RYAN: No, that was a great question.
JERRY: He's like... On the side he's like...
RYAN: You're going to panel the cart in wands?
KRIS: Yeah how-- RYAN: Why I ought to...
AMY: Make the AI logo out of wands.
JERRY: He shrugs, "It's fine. I got plenty of work."
"It's fine for me."
AMY: Do we want the spoiler? Or do we want the catapult?
KATE: We want the chamber in the rear with the slick fluid that sprays us.
We want the ground...
JERRY/RYAN: Ground effects.
KATE: from... Yeah we got that one.
JERRY: Is the skull staying or going?
KATE: It's definitely staying. RYAN: Staying!
KATE: Can you communicate with it psychically and see if it has any useful knowledge?
KRIS: Oh that's a great idea. RYAN: Eh we'll figure it out later.
KRIS: If I do... what the heck is it called? Is it intelligent? AMY: It's not making any noise. Just bring it.
KRIS: Does it know a language? Can I communicate with it? RYAN: You can change the station!
KATE: If for some reason that those mandibular ring...
if that pops off and he just starts singing,
he's going to give us away from a mile away.
KRIS: Yeah can I communicate with the skull? KATE: He's very loud.
KATE: Psychically. JERRY: You can try to.
KRIS: Skull.
I address with you.
AMY: Friend. RYAN: Friend. Yeah, call it friend.
KRIS: Friend. RYAN: Friend skull.
KRIS: Friend-- What was probably a friend.
I pop that ring out.
What other songs do you know?
JERRY: "What is your request?"
KATE: (gasps) It takes requests! KRIS: Oh.
AMY: Oh my god it can vamp-- RYAN: All Along The Watchtower!
KRIS: Do you know Silence?
JERRY: He opens up his mouth...
AMY: (laughing) That was-- KRIS: Fam, we good to go!
(laughter) KRIS: We're taking this skull with us.
RYAN: Put the clamp on him, just to be safe.
KRIS: Yeah, we'll go ahead and just tuck that in.
KRIS: All right that's-- JERRY: It's like a duckbill, like...
(laughter)
JERRY: It's just open.
KRIS: Do you know John Cage's 4'33"? KATE: Hang him from the rearview mirror.
JERRY: Exactly. AMY: Yeah hang him from the rearview mirror.
JERRY: So while you're interacting with this skull,
which is happy to be there,
Waelvur is using some of the boards that he had secured previously
to create something like a support for the catapult that fits on the side.
So there is on the right side of the Gothic cart...
AMY: It's like a camper. JERRY: Yeah.
JERRY: He's like, "Something like this?"
KRIS: I love it.
KRIS: Love what you done with the-- RYAN: Trails behind?
JERRY: No. It's like a sidecar.
RYAN: Oh okay. Better. Yes.
KRIS: This is a wacky cart! RYAN: Yeah.
AMY: Which is great. JERRY: Wacky Races.
RYAN: This is like the Wacky Races cart, yeah!
JERRY: Exactly, exactly. RYAN: A hodgepodge nonsense car.
JERRY: It's a heap. It's a heap of crazy nonsense.
AMY: It's fine. We'll soup it up as we go.
RYAN: Can we put it on the top?
JERRY: So it's been installed? AMY: No. Spoiler goes on top.
JERRY: It's been installed on the side.
There's a gentle glow beneath the cart.
Grease canister installed in the back. Tastefully.
KRIS: Yeah. JERRY: Hidden.
AMY/KRIS: Sure.
JERRY: You know, underneath. RYAN: How do we engage that?
JERRY: Exactly. KRIS: I don't know.
JERRY: He's definitely gauging it out.
RYAN: But how do you turn it on?
JERRY: This is a fantasy for him. KRIS: He'll solve it.
AMY: There will be like a pulley inside. RYAN: Is there like a button?
KATE: Waelvur will let us know. KRIS: Let him do it.
RYAN: Okay. I hit him! Because everyone's giving me crap.
(laughter) AMY: I take out all my--
JERRY: People are fucking with me about this shit all the time.
So you're able to put all this stuff together.
He doesn't seem to need a whole lot of sleep.
Waelvur. I think he does most of his best sleeping during the day.
KRIS: Yeah. KATE: (clicks tongue)
AMY: (whispering) Goddamn Rosie.
JERRY: So you... KRIS: Rosie let them in.
JERRY: As you wake up...
you wake up to the sound of a cart...
rolling over the Stone Bridge.
And let's get some perception checks.
KATE: Yes, sir. RYAN: I am not perceptive.
KRIS: Whoa. Did it count? KATE: Whoa. Hey there.
RYAN: Three. So... KATE: That's a nat 20.
KATE: I'm going to count that for you. KRIS: Okay.
AMY: I was about to say I got an 11. KATE: I got 21.
AMY: Oh yeah. He got it.
JERRY: 21? KATE: Mm-hmm.
RYAN: I got a three. So I see like no...
JERRY: So you're taking a look at it...
You can see the cart. You can see sort of a...
It's early morning.
They clearly got an early start to the day.
Very, very stiff body. Probably the cold morning.
You can see that there are...
there's one set of reins that goes to the driver.
And another set of reins that go inside the cart.
KRIS: Wow. RYAN: Nice.
JERRY: That is the end of our adventure for today.
KATE: What? RYAN: Nice cart!
JERRY: Mm-hmm. It's true. It's true. KATE: Oh my god.
JERRY: Hey! We're going to run a little thingamajig.
And then we're going to come back for Table Talk right after that.
So come back and see us.
AMY: Bye, everybody!