JERRY: Hello.
I'm Jerry Holkins. I'm also Tycho Brahe and I'm also Omin Dran.
But today I am Jerry Holkins, Dungeon Master of the "C" Team.
It is my great pleasure to introduce the players.
To my right, Ryan Hartman as Donaar Blit'zen.  RYAN: (claps heartily)
JERRY: Which, I'm offended. No-- That's-- None of that.
RYAN: Oh.
JERRY: You're already in character?
KRIS: Solemn, solemn.
JERRY: No, don't. No. No, not yet. It's not time. RYAN: Ten? Oh.
JERRY: Amy Falcone as Walnut Dankgrass.
Which might be Dank-Grass.
JERRY: That's-- we'll investigate it. AMY: Mm mmm. &gt;&gt; KATE: The K is silent.
JERRY: Kate Welch as Rosie Beestinger.
The most dangerous grandmother in the Forgotten Realms.
Kris Straub as his OC character headcanon fan insert, K'thriss Drow'b.
KRIS: Yeah. The real deal.
JERRY: The actual-- Exactly. RYAN: Slashfic.
KRIS: With myself. RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: All right. Well hey, motherfuckers, are we ready to play some Dungeons &amp; Dragons?
KATE: Ready motherfucker. &gt;&gt; KRIS: Yes. JERRY: All right, let's do it, let's do it.
JERRY: Now, there is something of a surprise that greets you.
You have obviously-- you have your own reasons
for wanting to become a licensor of Acquisitions Incorporated.
The fastest growing adventuring company in Faerûn.
But the license that you get back has a couple conditions that you weren't expecting.
And it also comes with a strange object. So what you learn, as fully 40 pages of documentation return to you,
is that the license that you have purchased, perhaps the only license that is available,
is for 25% of one license.
AMY: Uh... JERRY: Yeah.
JERRY: You're going over it, you're going over it. Everything seems like it's okay. Very, very, small text
on the back of the last page, on the bottom, says that licenses of Acquisitions Incorporated
in the Dessarin Valley, which is the region you'll be operating in, are sold in tranches of 25%.
Something like a medieval dating service, they will choose three other licensors and build you into a
company designed for maximum mission effectiveness based on your--
RYAN: It's like a timeshare? JERRY: Exactly.
JERRY: It's like a timeshare but for adventuring--
RYAN: Okay.
JERRY: in this particular region. KATE: Wow.
JERRY: It also comes with one other thing. It comes with an acorn.
JERRY: Obviously that gets you cranked up.  AMY: (scoffs) Whoo!
JERRY: Yeah. Good stuff right?
AMY: (excited growl) RYAN: Her name's Walnut.
JERRY: Fucking reel it in, okay?
AMY: Sorry. Pornographic. JERRY: We can't have the whole game...
JERRY: just beads of sweat.
Each of these acorns has had the cap dipped in gold, and there is a note that accompanies it that says that
you are to enter an inn called the Dran &amp; Courtier noon the next day. So there is a very, very short timeline...
for you to even achieve this objective. Luckily, you're all well within that range. It will not be a difficult process.
You are to meet there at noon, and the cap-- the acorn must be with you.
K'thriss Drow'b. You were dropped off in this town via the Acquisitions Incorporated airship.
KRIS: I don't remember.
JERRY: You don't a hundred percent remember any of this. The fact of the matter is--
is that your Dungeons &amp; Dragons career-- the very first roll that you ever made was a one. And that was in the
process of you contacting another plane for advice. And what happened instead was that your entire
consciousness became transmuted into a kind of madness that made everything absolutely hilarious.
And the amount of hilarity was connected directly to how bad things are.
KRIS: Right.
JERRY: It's been a huge problem.
You awaken in a filthy alley.
RYAN: Naked.
JERRY: Na-- No. I'm going to run this.
KRIS: I take my clothes off. JERRY: Goddamn it!
JERRY: Listen! RYAN: Finally.
JERRY: Do you see this? Do you see this screen?
It's like this... You awaken with this note, written in your own hand.
Your focus, which is a chunk of a dark altar that you found in the Underdark.
As a warlock you have the capacity-- the Eyes of the Runekeeper allow you to read any language,
but there were symbols on this altar that you couldn't perceive. And because you could not perceive them
they became almost fetishistic for you. It's not normal for you. As soon as you see a piece of text,
no matter where or when it's from, you can perceive it, but these symbols eluded you.
You were able to carve a chunk of it out and you focus your warlock powers through it.
It is burning hot in your hand. This note is in your other hand, written in your own handwriting.
KRIS: Ink? JERRY: Yes.
KRIS: Okay. JERRY: Yeah. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Phew.
KATE: You sound disappointed.
(laughter)
JERRY: Your forehead is also hot.
There is a raised welt on it that you can feel with the back of your hand.
KRIS: Oh I don't like it. Okay.
JERRY: The only thing that you know right now is that I had to take your 9th level character sheet away.
You now have this shit-eater 3rd level character--
KRIS: This mess. KATE: Six levels...
JERRY: (laughs) version of the same character.
KRIS: Where's the rest of it?
JERRY: It's all gone, it's all gone.
KRIS: It just started. JERRY: It's true.
JERRY: But you're now scrubbing it with the rest of them.
And you know that you are in the town of Red Larch, where you're supposed to be, but there are many, many
other things that you do not know; up to and including the incredible sorceries that you developed
JERRY: over the last six years.  KRIS: Right.
AMY: (laughs) That stinks. JERRY: Yeah.
KATE: That super sucks, dude. RYAN: Everyone's writing stuff down.
JERRY: Exactly. AMY: Don't worry about it.
JERRY: You steady yourself against-- KATE: We're the brains.
JERRY: the stone wall of this-- KRIS: The least filthy wall.
JERRY: Yeah, the least filthy wall you can find. KRIS: I check.
JERRY: Here, percep-- No, we're not going to do it.
KRIS: You stick your hand right through. JERRY: Minimally, "Aw it's gross, it's the worst."
JERRY: Then you step in something. You don't like that either.
KRIS: Naw!
JERRY: You steady yourself against the edge of a wall, and as you come around the corner, you can see a sign
that hangs in front of the building, that reads, "The Dran &amp; Courtier."
KRIS: Oh, this is ideal.
JERRY: Yeah, this is an optimal scenario for you. Everything turned out great.
Walnut Dankgrass.
You are approaching Red Larch from the wood to the north, near the base of the Sword Mountains.
A place that's often been known for druidic goings-on. Your type of shit.
RYAN: Maybe I'll write stuff too.
JERRY: You can sense-- Yeah, you can be a part of this team as well.
Be sure to open that up. Draw funny pictures.
RYAN: Oh.
JERRY: Whatever feels good to you at the time.
Walnut, you know even just walking across the soil on the Long Road that cuts right through the middle of
Red Larch, you know that a forest was cut down for this.
AMY: Okay. JERRY: You just-- You know. You can tell from the soil...
Even your feet on the soil on the way to the town, you know that this was a beautiful red larch forest
that the people of this town had the audacity to name it after. There is nothing here-- There is nothing even
remotely larchian about the awful place that they have manufactured here.
AMY: I am internalizing all of this.
JERRY: Exactly. It's all going to go into your journal.
AMY: (repressed grunt) Yep. JERRY: Right?
JERRY: There's going to be a poem.
JERRY: And you accept that. Right? AMY: Mmhmm. yes.
JERRY: But as you cross straight down through-- obviously your mode of dress is distinctive.
But the Long Road through Red Larch that goes from Mirabar in the north and Waterdeep in the south
brings all kinds through this village. No one's too surprised by this particular raiment.
You have directions that will take you to the Dran &amp; Courtier. It's not quite on the main drag. It's off a bit.
You see wagon shops... places that you make a note to hate in the future.
AMY: Just internally making that shit list.
JERRY: Exactly, exactly.
And as you turn the corner... you can see the sign of the Dran &amp; Coutier and you can also see a drow
in blue raiment supporting himself against the front if it. You don't know if he's been here all night.
You don't know if he's trying to get back in after a night of drinking. But he clearly is having a difficult time
supporting himself in an upright, bipedal way.
AMY: I make a snap judgement.
(laughter)
KRIS: As is your right.
AMY: Okay.
JERRY: Yeah so you're welcome to interact or I can continue with the situation.
AMY: I think Walnut's there for, you know-- I'm just here for my own things I don't need to--
AMY: get involved in whatever that is. KRIS: A door you don't want to open.
AMY: That's not something I want to mess with.
KRIS: Right.
JERRY: You just let that happen. AMY: Yeah.
JERRY: Donaar Blit'zen.
Your dragonborn village is on the eastern ridge of the Sword Mountains. The secrets of that town are held in a
cavern high up that you are familiar with from your own rite of passage that we'll get into later in this campaign.
RYAN: Oh ho...
JERRY: But there's no walking for you. As a relatively highborn person in that-- there is a cart that drives you
basically to the gate of Red Larch.
AMY: Of course... RYAN: (laughs)
RYAN: What are you shaking your head for?
JERRY: You step off and the cart raises, substantially, as you've been deposited.
You get the nod from the front and they roll away.
You cross much the same path that Walnut did on the way in. You curve over to the left first.
You see other shops, you see the town waking up and getting ready for the day. And you approach a...
You approach the Dran &amp; Courtier from the north. You can see what is clearly a druid in like a warlike raiment.
It isn't the classic robes, there's nobody getting any mistletoe at midnight here. This is a this is a druid that...
It's not your father's druid essentially. This is a druid that protects the natural world via another mechanism.
You can see her face furrowed with anger and rage at a drow in front of an inn called the Dran &amp; Courtier.
RYAN: Okay.
Which is where I am supposed to be going.
JERRY: Indeed. That's the document that you have.
RYAN: All right. And you're a mess.
KRIS: Don't look great. RYAN: All right.
RYAN: So I flip him a coin and I say, "Here you go, vagrant." And then I walk into the inn.
KATE: Are you naked?
KRIS: No, I think I... I mean vagrant doesn't imply nudity.
KRIS: I think that it's probably-- RYAN: I don't think-- It wasn't my intention.
KRIS: No, no, no.
RYAN: But I mean, pleasant coincidence... KRIS: I don't have any... &gt;&gt; AMY: Not yet...
KRIS: I wanted to explain. RYAN: I would've given you more coin.
JERRY: "No, nope. Actually, no I'm great."
KRIS: But all I can muster is, "Thank you, friend."
(laughter)
KRIS: (kissing sound) Mwah.
JERRY: Is it-- do you even catch it? Does it just hit you in the chest?
RYAN: It just bounces off your head. KRIS: It hits me right there.
RYAN: Right in the welt. AMY: Right in the welt.
JERRY: But you still have the presence of mind, "Oh great, yeah."
KRIS: Right. "Thank you."
JERRY: "I love those. I remember what those are for. Those are great."
"I want to get a bunch of those if I can."
RYAN: All without looking at him. Without eye contact.
KRIS: I was talking to the coin. JERRY: Yeah exactly.
JERRY: "Good job!" KRIS: "Oh you again, yes."
JERRY: "I love how round you are. I love all of this."
JERRY: So Rosie, you are approaching town from the south. Not quite-- Waterdeep is a week south.
You were actually in this area for other business already and so getting over here is is an easy jaunt for you.
You can see what you believe to be Red Larch, certainly the map would communicate that to you.
You can see it in sort of the middle distance there. You know you'll be there soon, when from a copse of trees
you see three young men intersect your path on your way to Red Larch.
KATE: Do these young men look... savory?
KATE: Or not so much? JERRY: Well here,
JERRY: let's grab some intuition and I am going to apply disadvantage to that. The channel has been kind enough
to provide me with bad rolls for players and I'm going to put them to fucking work.
KATE: Wonderful, wonderful. Okay so I'm going to roll a d20 with perception?
KATE: My perception check? What is it. JERRY: Let's see...
RYAN: Ooh. Nice. KATE: What do you got me doing here?
RYAN: I didn't know that were dice in this game. JERRY: No, insight. &gt;&gt; KATE: Insight? Okay.
JERRY: Yeah so roll two of them and take the lowest. KATE: Okay.
JERRY: I actually have your character sheet. KRIS: Mine might be the lowest, but--
KATE: I got a nine.
KATE: Okay and then I also got an eight and I have plus two wisdom?
Does that bonus apply?
JERRY: It does not in this case. KATE: All right, so eight.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. RYAN: I have plus three strength. Does that help?
(laughter)
KRIS: I confer some of my strength... no.
JERRY: So, one sidles into the middle of the road in front of you and the other two edge their way...
JERRY: just try to get behind in the periphery. KATE: Mmhmm.
JERRY: And you can see-- I mean, it doesn't require much sophistication to determine that a grandmother
walking this road... walking the Long Road outside of a town might represent something like
a bunch of juicy grapes hanging off of a vine.
KATE: She is juicy.
JERRY: Yeah, oh yeah. Every aspect of Rosie Beestinger to them communicates an easy mark.
KATE: Okay.
So there's one in front of me?
JERRY: One in front and two are edging around behind...
RYAN: Grapples. JERRY: And you can hear--
JERRY: You can hear behind you and to the right, you can hear the twang of a hand crossbow being loaded.
KATE: Hmm! Okay.
JERRY: So the young gentleman in front says,
"Good morning, grandmother."
KATE: "Good morning. Can you help escort me on my way to town?"
JERRY: (laughs) "This...?"
"You'll be on your way very quickly."
KATE: "Oh good." JERRY: "The transaction we have in mind"
JERRY: "shouldn't take more than a couple minutes."
KATE: "Wonderful." JERRY: "If you're smart."
KATE: "Oh I think I can be. How can I help you today?"
JERRY: "Anything you have, "
KATE: "Hmm..." JERRY: "that a shop would want..."
JERRY: "you're going to give it to us."
KATE: "I see." JERRY: "And then you're going to continue on. Upright."
KATE: "Hmm." JERRY: "There's another way it goes."
KATE: "Okay." JERRY: "Right?"
JERRY: He directs--
You think he might have had this speech before. You think that he might have leveraged this one.
Maybe practiced it on his mates.
He says, "There's not a lot of you to hide."
"It's five minutes work."
KATE: "Mmhmm. Interesting." RYAN: (laughs)
KATE: "Well--" JERRY: Are you pleased with yourself?
RYAN: Yeah that was good! I liked that.
KATE: "I don't have much that I can offer you. So I'm not sure I can be of help to you today."
"If you wouldn't mind just letting me on my way. I'm just here to do some business in town."
JERRY: "No. No, no, no. That's... Grandmother, that's not how this story ends at all."
KATE: "Hmmm."
JERRY: "That's not how this story ends at all" KATE: "Okay."
AMY: This is the most pleasant mugging I have ever seen!
JERRY: It's pleasant for now.
KATE: So I think I would like to try to intimidate this young gentleman.
JERRY: Now, Rosie, don't forget. You might be able to intimidate quite well with the assistance of your friends.
KATE: Oh that's so true!
JERRY: Of your vast network. Your social network...
KRIS: The social network. JERRY: has conferred--
JERRY: the Stingers, have conferred upon you a certain level of capacity in this.
KATE: My little beehive mmmm.
JERRY: Yeah, so the hive. So don't... KATE: Wonderful.
JERRY: Don't wait. I mean definitely put them to work.
KATE: Okay. I would love to use one of my special dice. My stinger bees.
JERRY: Yeah let's do it. All right. Let's see this intimidation. I have a copy of your character sheet here.
Let's-- oh shit! Oh wow, so you're a total motherfucker on this sort of thing. Even though you're a tiny grandma
you like to intimidate a motherfucker.
KATE: It's just a pastime.
JERRY: Well here listen, so advantage for you, Rosie Beestinger, means that you roll the d20 twice
and you add four to each of those rolls and you take the best of the two.
KATE: Goodness.
JERRY: So let's get to work. KATE: Okay.
AMY: Big money.
JERRY: Holy fucking... RYAN: Oh wow.
JERRY: All right that is a crit. KATE: That's a nat 20, folks.
JERRY: Let's see what the other one is just for kicks. KRIS: Oh my god.
KATE: Could be a 21. Never know. JERRY: Yeah, I was going say,
JERRY: let's see if there's another dice in there.
RYAN: A one. JERRY: That's a one.
KRIS: Does that cancel out?
JERRY: No. It doesn't cancel it out. So listen, obviously this 20--
This 20, it would let you cut this man in half just with a glance, but what does Rosie Beestinger do in this case?
KATE: I think Rosie Beestinger would like to-- Excuse me.
I would like to give this young man a very cuttingly perceptive look and say,
"Don't I know your grandmother? Haven't we gone to some kind of party together?"
"Perhaps I've seen her around town? Isn't that someone that I might have encountered before?"
JERRY: You can see his hand sort of do this like a leaf in the wind, and he reaches for the dagger.
KATE: Mmhmm.
JERRY: and he unsnaps the top of it and he pulls out the dagger and the dagger falls on the ground.
Now, different people are reacting to this situation in different ways. The fellows behind are not in the
gruesome cone of the intimidation that you have laid out. And one of them, you think it might be on accident,
pulls the trigger of the crossbow.
KATE: Oh. RYAN: Hmm.
JERRY: So let's get some initiative going. KATE: Okay.
AMY: Watching K'thriss puke at the bar is like-- JERRY: That's a total shithole.
KATE: That's a ten, plus three. 13. JERRY: Yeah that's way better than me.
JERRY: Now don't be intimidated by the tiny vampire mouths. This is not a vampire.
KATE: Thank goodness. KRIS: Yet...
JERRY: It would be a very different-- (laughter)
RYAN: I've heard that before! JERRY: Yeah.
KRIS: Let the blood moon rises... JERRY: Yeah exactly, there's--
KRIS: Crossbow turns into fangs.
RYAN: It turns into a bat midflight.
RYAN &amp; JERRY: (bat squeaks and screeches noises)
JERRY: No no, so Rosie is going go first but that first attack is a surprising scenario,
JERRY: and so it's going to happen right away. KATE: Okay.
JERRY: Is your... AC 16, grandmother?
KATE: No, it is 15. JERRY: Okay.
JERRY: The crossbow bolt sails through the air.
KATE: I would like to deflect missile.
JERRY: Would you? KATE: I would.
JERRY: How does it work?
KATE: I roll a...
I believe I have the power to grab anything that is being deflected at me-- or sorry-- to deflect anything that's
being shot at me. I also roll a 1d6 plus-- 1d10 plus six, and if that is higher than the damage that would have
KATE: been dealt to me, I can grab the item in the air.  JERRY: Okay. Well...
JERRY: It is three points of damage so let's go ahead and get that dice roll,
but I'm pretty sure this is going to end with you holding...
KATE: That's a nine. JERRY: Yeah.
JERRY: It comes, and in a moment, in a moment... just a fluid shift, and you catch it over your shoulder.
KATE: I'm going to-- I do have the ability to then use this to throw, but I think that these young men are just a little
bit mislead. They've gone down the wrong path. So I'm going to simply hold that crossbow, turn,
look over my shoulder, and say, "Did you drop something?"
AMY: (whispers) Oh my god. RYAN: Yep bite it.
KATE: (laughs)
JERRY: He is scooting back. He is scooting way back, as far back as he can go, to the extent that he falls
down, and then continues to try to move back even though he's mostly on the ground. When you turn back
to look in front of you, there is-- the young man is now hiding in the bushes he was going to put your body in.
The third young man is nowhere to be seen. You see a tiny shape just running back down the Long Road.
It could be him.
KATE: I am going to continue on my way, unobstructed.
JERRY: You keep it as a souvenir? KATE: Absolutely.
JERRY: Perfect.
KRIS: I'm so tickled, I'm so tickled. KATE: I always keep them as a trophy.
JERRY: Exactly, it's just nice. It's nice. KATE: it's just nice.
KATE: Can I add that to my inventory?
JERRY: Yeah exactly. Absolutely. One crossbow bolt.
KATE: One... crossbow... bolt. AMY: A little souvenir.
JERRY: Exactly, exactly, so-- KATE: I put a smiley face next to it.
JERRY: Exactly.
You enter the town of Red Larch from the south and just off the first curve on the right, you can see loosely
swinging in the wind is the sign for the place that you are meant to go.
KATE: I assume I see this sad sack.
JERRY: Well you see one sad sack drow still sort of vibrating in place.
JERRY: You see... RYAN: Now a little richer.
JERRY: Exactly.
KRIS: Just still (kissing sound). Admiring it. JERRY: Indeed, you see...
JERRY: You see an intimidatingly garbed druid alongside. You're not sure what's going on there.
JERRY: And you've already gone inside, correct? RYAN: Yeah.
AMY: So as soon as I see Rosie looking my way, I immediately look like I've been caught being in trouble,
and I look to this drow who is, you know, I'm a wood elf out of my element, I see that this is a drow out of his
element, and I walk up to him-- not too close?
JERRY: Not too close. AMY: Like not within like...
KRIS: You don't want-- there might be a scent. AMY: like projectile range, yeah. Yeah that.
KATE: They not looking too fresh. AMY: There's kind of barf situation?
JERRY: Yeah exactly, a cone weapon, obviously. AMY: Away from that.
AMY: But I say,
"Hello, fellow outsider. Can I help you get to where you're going? Can I help you inside?"
KRIS: "Ugh. Yeah you can--" AMY: "Get you some fluids..."
JERRY: Hydration. KATE: Rosie's like, "Isn't that sweet? Aren't you a dear."
ROSIE: "What a nice young elf." AMY: "Hello, ma'am."
KRIS: "I would love that, I would love it if we could wait until the sun was not out."
"So I could go inside without being destroyed by those beams."
KATE: "The sun is pretty much at its highest point right now."
KATE: "It's going to be a little while." KRIS: "Oh!. That's the worst thing you could say to me."
KRIS: "I'm just going to-- I was just going to pop inside, and collect myself. Hope they have a washroom."
AMY: "Okay." KRIS: "I appreciate it. "
KRIS: "Actually didn't fare too badly."
"Maybe I'll take up this occupation. I already got a coin out of it today."
(laughter)
"And I was deep in the alley, I didn't think anybody could see me."
AMY: "That's great."
KRIS: "So imagine how much better it could be if I'm on the stoop in front."
AMY: "I'm happy for you. That is super validating for you."
JERRY: Yeah exactly, you know. Internalize that.
KRIS: "But nonetheless I appreciate it." AMY: "Sure."
KATE: So are you just talking about why you're not going inside?
KRIS: No, I am going to go inside. KATE: Okay.
KATE: After the monologue. KRIS: There's no running water out here.
KATE: I see, okay, okay.
KRIS: I'm a dirty man. I mean it could help with the act, with the panhandling.
But I'm just going to go ahead and go inside.
AMY: "All right well I'll hold the door for both of you." And then I hold the door.
KRIS: "I do appreciate though that a wood elf would stop for a drow."
KRIS: "Because usually I get..." AMY: "Well."
KRIS: "It ain't the best, on the surface." KATE: "That's very inspiring, very inspiring."
AMY: "Well, we're not all in our element here."'
KATE: "I am." I go inside.
AMY: I say, "After you. Ma'am."
JERRY: Exactly. Now as you enter the Dran &amp; Courtier, there's a-- you feel a slight pressure change.
There's a temperature change from outside to inside.
In your inner ear you feel a little pressure momentarily, and then it's gone.
As you enter it, this seems like a perfectly serviceable opportunity to get fed,
make acquaintances, stay the night.
There's nothing remarkable about it, really at all.
Except that it is almost annoyingly... themed. It's like a theme restaurant.
AMY: Mmm.
KATE: Oh I love these. JERRY: Yeah, right?
JERRY: Over the...
To your right, you can see three chairs that you think might have been had the edges cut out of a cauldron.
So imagine it has sort of a high back and side placed on a stool.
They're radiating warmth from the fire in that corner.
Over the fireplace, which is itself near a very small stage, is a portrait.
A lavish, almost like gold leaf edged, portrait of a wizard in a high purple cape with a skull clasp.
And you recognize this person instantaneously.
JERRY: Not a week ago... KRIS: Right.
JERRY: Not a week ago, you were in the company of this sorcerer of some renown.
He's known-- he has power, but he's known to be a showman.
KRIS: Right.
JERRY: His name is Jim Darkmagic.
JERRY: And...
KATE: (whispers) I'm going to write that down. JERRY: But that theme...
(laughter)
JERRY: I mean terribly, awfully, not evilly, but annoyingly, cloyingly, extends even to the staff.
So even the staff here are adorned in a way that marks them as acolytes of some kind to this sorcerer.
They have an easier to wear, easier to wash version of his raiment. That cape-- the neck isn't quite as high.
KRIS: Right.
JERRY: Some of them have a wig that communicates that long black hair.
But the place is full of revelers, the bar is open, and the Dran &amp; Courtier is available for business.
KRIS: "Ah jeez. I think this is a cult."
(laughter)
KRIS: "I have great misgivings now about this." AMY: I've done it again.
KRIS: "I thought..."
KATE: Wouldn't you be excited about cults?
KRIS: Not this one. AMY: Not this kind.
(laughter)
KRIS: It's very lively and fun and, it's like (non-commital sound)
JERRY: I want a cult that has cool clothes. KRIS: Yeah.
JERRY: Optimally some kind of evil pact.
KRIS: Sure. No flair. JERRY: Right?
KRIS: I don't need that. KATE: I was just saying, does anybody wear flair here?
KATE: Are there pieces of flair?
JERRY: Some have apparently collected different kinds of skulls. Maybe there are seasonally available skulls.
KATE: Mmhmm.
JERRY: They all seem-- RYAN: I hate Mondays skull.
JERRY: They all seem very excited.
You see a young woman-- a young halfling woman take the stool on the small stage near the fireplace,
tune the lute very quickly and then sing a song that is entirely about Jim Darkmagic.
KATE: "He sounds great!"
JERRY: From end to end the lyrics are,
"Jim, there is only him."
"I serve his every whim."
KATE: Jim...
(laughter)
AMY: J. I. M. &gt;&gt; KRIS: Him, whim, got it.  RYAN: Am I writing enough?
JERRY: But there is a booth near the back of this... establishment with availability.
KRIS: Now, as I-- I'm going to make my way toward that booth being-- I'm imagining it's the only open one.
JERRY: Yes. KRIS: And then I notice...
KRIS: Would you already be seated, actually?
RYAN: I was at the bar. KRIS: You were at the bar? Okay.
JERRY: Yeah, and you came in earlier. RYAN: Yeah.
KATE: I spot-- RYAN: And then I see you and I say,
RYAN: "I-- I don't have any more. Guy. "
RYAN: "I already-- I'm sorry." AMY: "I don't need any."
KATE: I've identified you as rich, and so I am at the bar next to you just trying to get you to buy me a drink.
JERRY: His golden scales just shimmering in the light inside.
KATE: Yes. Beautiful.
KRIS: I make sure it's not actually a scale.
KRIS: Because that might be worth something. RYAN: It was! That was the trick!
RYAN: I'm not rich at all. That's the game.
JERRY: That's how I do it. KRIS: Well played.
(laughter)
KRIS: No, I make my way to the booth and... I assume you do the same?
Like we notice we're traveling in the same direction.
AMY: Yeah so at this point... the social awkwardness of I ushered you in and now I feel kind of responsible
because I might have let in a person that's not great.
JERRY: You might be responsible for hauling him out later.
AMY: But I look with pleading eyes at the matriarchal figure of Rosie leaving me.
AMY: I'm just like, "Ah." KATE: I lean over to Donaar and say,
KATE: "I'd like a Jim and Tonic."
JERRY: It's literally-- RYAN: Nice.
JERRY: It is literally on the menu. KATE: Yes! Yes!
KRIS: Incredible.
RYAN: And I'll say, "Two Jim and Tonics please for me and the lady."
And then I say, "What do you know about... 25% ownership of..."
(laughter)
KRIS: You just lay is out. RYAN: Just lay it out there. "By the way."
KRIS: "So I don't know you but I got this uh--"
RYAN: "I don't know you. Never met you. You're just a bartender. What do you know about this?"
AMY: I got this magical nut. RYAN: Yeah.
RYAN: "I got this magical nut." KATE: "Oh!"
KATE: Rosie brings out her magical nut, "I got one too!"
RYAN: "Well then you and I should talk." KATE: "What do you know?"
JERRY: The person behind the bar in the middle of mixing the Jim and Tonics...
says, "Oh yeah, people often meet up. People often meet their Acquisitions Incorporated contacts here."
"Sometimes it's even Jim Darkmagic!" RYAN: (clicks tongue)
AMY: (gasp) Jim Darkmagic (murmuring as an excited crowd)
RYAN: "Who is that?" KATE: "I've heard that name..."
JERRY: "Jim Dar--" RYAN: "Who is that?" &gt;&gt; KATE: "Yeah...?"
JERRY: "Jim?"
He points over toward the fireplace.
JERRY: "Over the top, over the top." RYAN: "Ah okay."
JERRY: "Not the--" KRIS: He's fire. &gt;&gt; RYAN: "So he's made of fire?"
JERRY: "No, no, no." RYAN: "Oh."
JERRY: "No, no. You've never heard of Jim Darkmagic?"
RYAN: "No, I can't say that I have."
JERRY: "Hang around here a little bit." RYAN: "Yeah?"
JERRY: "Yeah. Yeah, yeah."
JERRY: "You're going to learn a lot today." RYAN: "Anyway...ETA on these Jim and Tonics, buddy?"
(laughter)
JERRY: "You're going to learn a lot tonight-- Oh! Oh! Oh. Yeah, yeah, yeah."
He puts them together. Pushes them out.
You can hear him humming the same song that the halfling is singing on the bench.
KATE: I'm also singing it now. It's really stuck in my head.
RYAN: "Do you know this guy?" &gt;&gt; KATE: Total earworm. RYAN:"Have you heard of this dude?"
KATE: "No. Never! No, but he sounds great! Look at all these people dressed like him! He must be..."
RYAN: "The drink's named after him taste... tastes all right."
KATE: "It's a good drink!" RYAN: "He's got that going for him. I guess."
RYAN: And I'm just casually flipping around my gold nut like, doop-a-doo.
JERRY: Yeah. KATE: Yeah okay so--
KRIS: No idea about what its import is. RYAN: No... like the importance is entirely lost on me.
KATE: We're visibly-- Can you guys maybe see us
KATE: like having that nut conversation? KRIS: Yeah, I see you flipping that around and I'm like,
KRIS: "Oh," I think, "how many other people have this?"
AMY: And then I go... KATE: I thought it was special.
AMY: "This is a Magical Day." And I pull mine out.
(laughter)
KRIS: "I don't know what that means but..."
AMY: And I go, "Even I know what that means."
KATE: Do you uh, would you say you... busted your nut out?
KRIS: Lame. &gt;&gt; RYAN: There we go. Yeah. JERRY: This is a family show!
KRIS: Lame! JERRY: Rosie Beestinger!
AMY: But I liked it!
(laughter)
KRIS: "I think I'm going to go see what that's about." And I go to the bar. I approach the both of you...
RYAN: "Dude. I said I don't got any more money, I don't know how much clearer I can be." (slurps)
AMY: I'm like in the back, "Uh..."
JERRY: Uh ah. &gt;&gt; AMY: This guy. JERRY: Ugh.
KATE: "I have some money." KRIS: "Are you here about the--"
KRIS: "Oh really? Hold on a second."
(laughter)
AMY: Campaign derailed!
KRIS: "I could use a little coin. No, are both  of you here about the franchising opportunity as well?"
KATE: "Yes, as a matter of fact."
AMY: I hear franchise and I am immediately up over, looking just very glower but...
AMY: listening intently. KATE: "This nice young dragonman"
KATE: "bought me a Jim and Tonic" RYAN: "I did that."
KATE: "Would you guys like a Jim and Tonic as well?"
RYAN: (slurps) "No. I'm good. No more." (laughter)
JERRY: Flat. RYAN: Yeah, yeah. &gt;&gt; KRIS: yeah.
RYAN: "I don't know how much more I have to give this dude in one day but I draw the line."
KRIS: "I don't--" RYAN: Out of coin and stepping over him.
KRIS: "I don't want to drink anything named after a necrotizing man."
(laughter)
KRIS: "So I'm good, I'm complete."
JERRY: You're starting to see people... groups of people are beginning to leave the establishment.
They're not being replaced.
You can see outside the window, it has begin to darken what you would describe as unseasonably.
KATE: What time of day is it?
KRIS: Apparently it was noon. KATE: It was noon.
JERRY: You came in here about noon. RYAN: It's about seven pm.
KATE: Okay. JERRY: It's already begun to...
JERRY: the shafts of light that are coming through the window have already begun to dim precipitously.
The bartender says, "Were you supposed to meet someone here? What does it say in your...?"
RYAN: "Uh..." (unfurls scroll sound)
"I don't think so." (rolls up scroll sound)
AMY: What's it say in your nut, boy? KATE: "Mine says, 'Enter the Dran &amp; Courtier at noon.'"
KATE: "But there's no other details besides that except for this curious little nut."
JERRY: "Hmm." But he says,
"The closest Acquisitions Incorporated franchise is in Waterdeep."
"And I understand that the roads from Waterdeep are springtime roads right now."
"Which is to say that you could swim through part of them."
"Um."
"We don't have rooms here tonight but it may be a situation where you need to wait in town"
"for your contact to arrive."
RYAN: "Okay?" JERRY: "I would rent you a room."
JERRY: "But I don't have them. They're already rented."
RYAN: "Right..."
KATE: "Do you know of anywhere that might rent us rooms?"
JERRY: "If you head out to the main path, worst case scenario there might be somebody at the--"
"Allfaiths Shrine to take you in. But it's not a super busy time of year because of the roads. It should be okay."
KATE: "Super busy for you apparently, though. That's pretty nice for you."
JERRY: "Well, we have a reputation."
KATE: "I'll say."
JERRY: Absolutely.
A cat... perhaps the cat of this establishment-- probably not the owner.
You feel a cat sort of curl around your right leg and look up to you.
AMY: Well. I look down and I'm immediately pleased to see...
AMY: something not humanoid. JERRY: Some sign of life?
KATE: You're like way more excited to see the cat than any of us.
AMY: Yeah well now that I know we're not getting a room...
So I'll kneel down and look at the cat and, you know... offer it a hand like, "Can I pet?"
JERRY: Oh yeah, yeah, yeah. It's the full meal deal. Right along the side, it goes right for that cheek.
JERRY: Goes for the other cheek. KRIS: Oh yeah.
JERRY: People are not paying this cat the kind of attention it deserves!
RYAN: It's a good cat. KATE: (whispers) Cat. Good cat.
JERRY: This is a premium cat. Can I get a perception roll from you, Rosie Beestinger?
KATE: Sure.
KRIS: That's not a bad cat. RYAN: You're like...  (laughs) &gt;&gt; AMY: I'm ready.
KATE: I got a one. I'm not very perceptive about this cat. RYAN: Wow... You step on the cat.
JERRY: You know what?
KRIS: You cannot see a cat. KATE: Yeah? All right, let's do it.
JERRY: I would use your advantage. KATE: Okay.
AMY: Summon your friends.
KATE: 18. RYAN: That's quite different.
KRIS: What is going on with your rolls? JERRY: Now what do you got there on your percep?
KATE: On my perception...
JERRY: On your wis. KATE: I got plus two wis.
JERRY: All right. That's marvelous. You notice something odd. The chandelier in the middle of
the Dran &amp; Courtier... the pattern of candles in it are a celestial pattern.
KATE: Ooh. Is it a celestial pattern that I recognize?
JERRY: Yes. You absolutely recognize it. It is called the Homeward Star. And it literally forms a kind of triangle
and the candle nearest the door in this configuration is sort of guttering a little bit.
KATE: Okay.
JERRY: Might need to replace that. Something to consider. Something to consider
Something else that's strange is that you're used to a certain level of recognition and notoriety from halflings,
and that is not being paid to you here. You're trying not to be offended by it...
KATE: Trying to move past that. JERRY: You're trying to move past it but it's not...
JERRY: It's...
JERRY: It's uncommon. KATE: Okay. Okay.
KATE: How many halflings are in this joint?
JERRY: There are three. There is the performer and then there are two at a small table playing what looks to be
like a chess or checkers-type game.
KATE: Mmm. Playing game, Okay.
JERRY: K'thriss, I would like to get a perception roll from you as well.
KRIS: I'd love to give you that. I'm going to go ahead and...
KRIS: pop one of mine as well. JERRY: Use your juice?
JERRY: Love it. KRIS: Why not?
KRIS: So let's see that's a... RYAN: Heavy.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. No, it's serious. KRIS: Oh that, that's going to be a 16...
KRIS: plus a... so it's 18.
JERRY: Okay.
You're drinking from the glass, and as you drain it, you notice a strange inscription...
through the base of the glass.
KRIS: Hmm. AMY: (laughs)
AMY: This place is like just lousy with like, I don't know...
KRIS: Those secrets. AMY: secrets.
JERRY: No. RYAN: I want to Detect Magic but I don't have it.
JERRY: It's bizarre. The...
(laughing)
the symbology at the base of it, has the Acquisitions Incorporated logo. The sigil that adorns all the papers,
all the paperwork that you have.
It says, Acquisitions Incorporated Test Market. All Rights Reserved.
KRIS: Is it symmetrical around the...
AMY: Hmm. KRIS: Hmm.
KRIS: Why conceal this?
RYAN: Are you asking me?
KRIS: No that's in my head. RYAN: Oh, okay.
KRIS: Otherwise I would say, "I said it..."
(laughter)
KATE: Test Market. AMY: Can I cast Speak with Animals, talk to this cat?
JERRY: Yeah. AMY: Assuming it's still spending time with me.
JERRY: Oh, it's right here. AMY: Okay.
AMY: I would like to do that. So I got ten minutes of quality face time with this cat.
(laughter)
JERRY: Exactly. You're going to have a positive experience with the cat.
KATE: A paws... AMY: Stop!
JERRY: Paws-itive experience.
JERRY: I want to see this gif.
AMY: Ugh. RYAN: Yeah... &gt;&gt; KATE: Jiff?
RYAN: Love it. KRIS: It is.
AMY: No. KATE: No.
AMY: That's for another time. I'm going to focus on this good, good cat.
(laughter)
AMY: Oh it hurts me. JERRY: This jood, jood cat.
RYAN: Yeah, animated gif. AMY: Ajree to disajree.
AMY: So I look at this cat and I go... I'm like, "Hello, my good feline friend."
"Tell me about this place. This is a strange place for such a good cat to be in."
JERRY: The cat says, "This is no way to become friends." And it dotters off.
Through legs, between tables, under chairs, to the edge of the room.
AMY: I'm crushed.
KATE: You just got big timed by a cat. RYAN: Yeah.
AMY: I did. It can't make time for me. KRIS: Yikes.
JERRY: It winds its way back... AMY: Mmm?
JERRY: with a mouse.
KRIS: Ah...
RYAN: Talk to the mouse! KATE: You're so lucky!
RYAN: Talk to the mouse! Can you Talk to Dead? AMY: Oh, in it's mouth or like with him?
JERRY: In its mouth. &gt;&gt; AMY: Gotcha. KRIS: It knows more.
JERRY: No, not together. This is not like a... a folk act... that includes a cat and a mouse. This is a gift.
A gift of meat.
RYAN: Jift? AMY: Oh my goodness.
JERRY: Shut up! AMY: Jift?
(laughter) RYAN: (self five)
AMY: So I reach in my pocket for something...
RYAN: A mouse! Your own mouse. AMY: But I don't have anything a cat would want.
RYAN: You give him the mouse as well.
AMY: Oh I pull out a feather and I do the little twist thing so it might be like tantalizing for a cat.
JERRY: Oh the mouse is dropped!
AMY: Great. I make this exchange and I take this dead mouse... just put it in my pocket for later.
JERRY: Put it in your mouse pouch? AMY: I give it a sniff. Oh yeah.
AMY: Is that a mouse in your pocket? Yeah. So it is in my pocket. And I say, "Thank you, friend."
JERRY: "Thank you."
It's...
AMY: It's just batting?
KATE: I am watching this whole exchange and nothing about it is striking me as strange.
JERRY: It's fine!
KATE: It's wonderful. AMY: Becoming a cat--
RYAN: I'm watching this and everything is strange and I'm getting more and more irritated.
(laughter)
RYAN: Because i don't know what's going on. KRIS: I'm watching it and I lean over and I say,
KRIS: "Are you going to finish that mouse?"
(laughter)
"You bring enough to... share?"
AMY: "Um..." JERRY: Extra mice?
KATE: You still smell terrible don't you?
KRIS: I probably do. AMY: So I press again with the cat
AMY: because, you know, I only have so many minutes--
JERRY: Right. "Actually cat, listen, there's not much time!"
AMY: There's not much time! No, no no. JERRY: You've got the paws.
AMY: Just holding his little paws. JERRY: Come on!
AMY: And I say,
"Friend, is there anything you can tell me about the strange people who inhabit this place?"
JERRY: "I will tell you what I know."
AMY: It's going to be a cat thing, but go ahead.
(laughter)
JERRY: "Whenever I go to the mousehole..."
"the food place..."
AMY: "The good place."
JERRY: "there is always a mouse."
AMY: "Hmm."
AMY: Okay. JERRY: "I have no complaint!"
AMY: "Well I'm happy to hear about your pest problem."
JERRY: "Every time. I could get you another mouse now. That would contravene... the rules of our friendship,"
"but I could get another mouse very easily."
AMY: "Let me ask you one more thing."
"Is it always a different mouse?"
JERRY: "I've never considered it."
Winds its way over... Winds its way back, mouse firmly attached to the craw. Drops it out.
AMY: Okay. I am now examining both dead mice. So...
JERRY: So at the bar! Let's be very clear about what's happening here.
At the bar you have a dead, crushed mouse,
RYAN: She just...
JERRY: in each hand.
RYAN: You're staring at the ceiling.
JERRY: There's a very distinct--
KRIS: I'm getting hungrier by the second. RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: there's a very distinct brown marking pattern, sort of on the haunch.
AMY: Sure. JERRY: On both of them.
AMY: Okay.
Could I do perception to gain more insight here?
AMY: Or is that all I need to know? JERRY: Yeah go right ahead.
RYAN: You're really drilling down on these mice. AMY: I...
KRIS: I'm going to cast Determine Similar Mouse.
(laughter)
JERRY: It's a, it's a 7th-level warlock ability. KRIS: Yeah.
RYAN: (laughing) Detect Mouse.
AMY: Oh no. It was a 13.
JERRY: Now, now Walnut, you actually have advantage.
KATE: Quite a few. KRIS: Yeah.
AMY: Oh I would like to use one of Walnut's nuts.
RYAN: So you're going to waste advantage on examining a fucking dead mouse?
AMY: I want to-- RYAN: I want to use all three advantages.
I'm going to really want to dig deep on these mice.
AMY: Now Ryan... RYAN: I look in their mouth.
AMY: Now I know that you might be a little newer to D&amp;D but this is the kind of stuff that you do
when one is presented with two potentially identical dead mice, you give it a look.
RYAN: I'm growing more and more irritated as this happens.
KATE: In real life? Or...?
RYAN: Both. This is D&amp;D?
RYAN: This hasn't been explained to me. AMY: That's fine. I do want to use advantage.
JERRY: Exactly. AMY: So what do I-- do I get to roll it again?
JERRY: No, no you're good. AMY: Okay.
JERRY: Brown markings.
AMY: They're not in like the shape of a skull or anything?
JERRY: No, no no. AMY: Okay.
RYAN: They say, "Open the backdoor."
JERRY: But both of these mice are missing the same tooth as well.
AMY: Gotcha.
KATE: This is just the same ass mouse. JERRY: This is incredibly weird.
JERRY: This is just weird stuff. It's 100% weird stuff.
You feel a...
a set of claws on your shoulder. Nothing strange. It's not like a hellhound or something. It's typical.
There's a dragonborn. You see a green dragonborn hand sort of come around your shoulder,
and you hear a whisper in your ear.
RYAN: Okay.
RYAN: What do I hear?
JERRY: In your own language you hear a dragonborn woman's voice say,
"I have a room in this inn."
RYAN: "Oh!" JERRY: "Do you know why?"
RYAN: "Do I know why?" JERRY: "Do you know why?"
RYAN: "No, I would like to know why."
JERRY: "Sometimes... they say Jim Darkmagic comes here."
JERRY: "And I want to be ready." RYAN: "I heard about that guy."
AMY: She just wants to tell him this.  RYAN: Yeah.
KATE: I think you can get it.
RYAN: Yeah... KRIS: I'm Jim Darkmagic.
(laughter)
RYAN: That's me! AMY: Why that's my name.
JERRY: T'is I.
RYAN: All right, I turn around and I look. JERRY: Yeah.
RYAN: and there's actually a person there, right? JERRY: Oh yeah.
JERRY: Absolutely. RYAN: Okay.
RYAN: Got to make sure. A lot of kooky stuff going on in here. And I say, "Look, lady." And I unfurl my little scroll.
"I was told to be here at noon to meet some dude!"
And all of this weird crap's going on, and I want know who I have to meet!"
"Here's my nut."
And I go like this, in her face.
And I say, "Someone tell me what's going on!"
JERRY: The barman rings a bell for last call.
KATE: Oh god.
RYAN: And I say, "Hey! What's that supposed to mean?"
(laughter)
RYAN: I'm just getting more and more angry. KRIS: That was a bell code.
KRIS: How many times... RYAN: "Is that more magic in here?"
JERRY: She-- RYAN: And I say...
JERRY: She is like scooting away from you, like navigating the tables and chairs.
RYAN: And I say-- KRIS: Hurrying back to your room.
RYAN: I say, "Wait, where are you going? Hold a minute. Wait a minute."
JERRY: "It's-- it's fine."
And then once she gets to the bottom of the stairs, the rest of it's a run.
(laughter)
KATE: Oh.
JERRY: The halfling that was playing is no longer here.
KATE: Okay. JERRY: This place is thinning out big time.
KATE: And people are not being replaced because it's closing time.
JERRY: Yes. &gt;&gt; KATE: Is that what we presume? AMY &amp; RYAN: It's closing time at noon?
JERRY: That's your guess.
KRIS: Well something's happening. AMY: That wasn't a change of lunch shift or something?
JERRY: Outside it is much darker than you think is appropriate for noon.
KATE: Rosie's had some pretty-- I've had some pretty interesting observations.
I'd like to approach the two halflings that are playing the game and have a conversation with them.
And I'm going to speak to them in Halfling to determine if they are actually halflings,
or if they are some kind of weird... fiction. JERRY: How will you do that?
JERRY: This is-- I am fascinated by this attempt.
KATE: Okay. AMY: Could be full of dead mice...
JERRY: How will you do this? Yeah! It's just a big pile of dead mice.
AMY: It's mice all the way down. RYAN: And you just keep using rolls to look.
RYAN: Whoa no. KATE: Yeah.
KRIS: The grain on the bar, peculiar wood. JERRY: She'll be here all day.
KATE: Well, I speak Draconic so I heard that RYAN: CSI: Mice.
KATE: craziness that that lady said to you.
And I watched those two mice and they had real similar butts.
KATE: And you were like-- JERRY: Oh their butts were crazy.
KATE: and you were like really into these mice.
RYAN: Mice butts. KATE: And this guy's doing whatever he's doing.
KRIS: I notice everybody leave and I'm going... (sniffs) KATE: But I've got suspicions, yeah.
KATE: So... JERRY: Filth!
KATE: I'd like to-- I'm going to walk slowly and with a hobble with my quarterstaff, leaning heavily on it,
and come over to thes young halflings and ask them in Halfling,
JERRY: Yeah I was going to say.
KATE: "Tell me about this game you're playing."
JERRY: One looks up at you, furrows his brow, and then looks back down to the table.
KATE: Hmm.
Uh... Okay.
There's some, I guess, I'm just confirming there's whack shit going on, I don't know what I learned from that.
(laughter)
Can I figure out what game they are playing? Is that something that's relevant information?
JERRY: It is not a halfling game. I mean there's nothing specifically halfling about it.
There's nothing to indicate that it is anything in particular.
RYAN: What game is it? AMY: Squeeze game.
JERRY: You're welcome to watch them play for a little while.
KATE: Sure, I mean I don't know maybe... I don't know if I'm much into games. I'm 120 years old.
JERRY: But you were a child once. KATE: That was a long time ago.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. Well, you're welcome to watch.
KATE: I would like to talk more about the Homeward Star actually.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. Exactly.
KATE: So I found this constellation in the chandelier.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. This is an important constellation to you.
This was the second constellation that your parents taught you.
KATE: Oh... snap! JERRY: So this is like...
JERRY: This is a fundamental...
This is a fundamental, astronomical piece of information.
KATE: Okay.
JERRY: It's baseline vital. KATE: Yeah. Okay.
JERRY: If you're not able to get home with the first one they taught you,
if it's obscured, this fallback is always available.
KATE: So is that particular constellation something that everyone-- it's general knowledge?
Or is this something that's maybe only my parents taught me?
JERRY: Like I say, it would be hard to know, because you were not there for the astronomical instruction
that other halfling children received from their parents.
JERRY: But...
it's a little inside baseball. It's not, like I say, it's not the first technique you'd learn.
KATE: Interesting. Okay.
KATE: So...
Rosie is suspicious as hell. Things are whack. Whackadoodle.
JERRY: Here can you toss me a perception real quick? KATE: Yeah sure.
JERRY: So they're down here playing, you're up here looking at this. Observing it. Trying to absorb it.
KATE: Okay that's a 16. KRIS: That's pretty high.
AMY: Nice.
JERRY: They are literally moving the same two pieces back and forth.
AMY: Mmm. KATE: Huh.
KATE: Okay. This is some kind of just, magic. I'm going to--
JERRY: Yeah, at this point...
JERRY: they fold the board in half, KATE: Great.
JERRY: and begin to leave. KATE: Okay.
KATE: So my theory, that I'm going to announce to you--
JERRY: It's Westworld! AMY: We're the only people left.
RYAN: They're all robots. KATE: It's literally Westworld.
AMY: Doesn't look like anything to me. RYAN: Two timelines.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. I've been waiting to use it. RYAN: Two timelines.
KATE: Yeah. I think they're all just mouse-structures. No I think, I think--
JERRY: Heaps of mice. Heaps of mice and glue. AMY: I knew it.
RYAN: Just burlap sacks full of mice. KRIS: So that's why.
KATE: Walnut tosses the mice. I knew it! JERRY: Yeah, exactly.
KATE: I think all of this is being conjured by someone. I think that these are all hollow constructs.
And that we need to get the F out of this inn ASAP.
AMY: If only someone had prepared Detect Magic. KATE: PDQ.
AMY: What an oversight that was.
JERRY: Dun, dun, dun! Word. KATE: Yeah. Yeah.
KATE: But you got all kinds of magic. KRIS: No, that's one of the ones I did not take.
AMY: We both did not do it. RYAN: Yeah we both didn't. I can detect...
KATE: Well I can tell this is going to be a long and fruitful business relationship.
(laughter)
RYAN: Divine sense. I can see if there are any fiends. AMY: Are we the only ones left?
JERRY: Yeah. Ain't it them fiends. AMY: Are we the only ones left?
JERRY: Walnut. It is you and an increasingly agitated bartender.
RYAN: I can Intimidate the guy.
AMY: Yeah, let's find out what's going on. RYAN: I'm going to go shake this guy down.
KATE: He's the only one that's not in the mirror. Okay. RYAN: Or should I persuade him?
RYAN: Should I go good cop or bad cop? You want to tag team him?
AMY: Yes. &gt;&gt; RYAN: All right. Yeah. JERRY: It's Dungeons &amp; Dragons, motherfucker.
JERRY: How you want to do it?
AMY: All right. RYAN: We'll go after-- we'll go at him.
KATE: Who's good cop, who's bad cop?
RYAN: We should decide this ahead of time. JERRY: Yeah yeah, work out the situation.
RYAN: "Hey, mouse girl. Let's go get this guy." JERRY: You don't want like two lukewarm cops.
AMY: "Oh." KRIS: Two identical cops.
RYAN: "Hey, Mousey."
JERRY: Hey we're police. KRIS: Yeah. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Yeah.
AMY: Yeah I look up and I see what Donaar is trying to do
and like walk over to the bar with my look at the bartender and I go...
RYAN: Mice still in hand. AMY: Mice still in hand and I go, "Sir,"
JERRY: "Ugh." AMY: "explain these mice!"
AMY: "Something's going on with these mice."
JERRY: "They're mice. You were playing with the cat. The cat gets mice. I don't-- have you ever seen a cat?"
AMY: "These are the same mice."
AMY: "What do you say about that?" RYAN: Then I yell. I say, (shouting) "Hey buddy!"
RYAN: (shouting) "You tell her what she needs to know or I'm going to go fricking crazy in here!"
JERRY: "I'm not a mouse-- I'm not like a mouse expert. I don't..."
JERRY: "spend a lot of time thinking about mice." RYAN: You got to hold me back. You got to be the good cop here.
AMY: I put the mice down on the bar, but just I want him to know they're--
JERRY: "Ah!" AMY: I just want him to know they're still there.
AMY: Then I look at Donaar and I go, "Oh let's not-- let's not scare him."
AMY: "Let's not scare this nice man who's--" RYAN: I go, (growl)
AMY: "let us stay here after last call."
KRIS: Cool off. RYAN: (deep breath) Yeah.
AMY: "Take a beat, take a beat."
AMY: "Sir. I'm sorry about my friend. Very sorry."
"But..." and I cast Charm Person?
You attempt to charm a humanoid you can see within range.
It must make a wisdom saving throw and does so with advantage if you or your companions are fighting it.
AMY: Just kidding. Doesn't have advantage. JERRY: Yeah.
AMY: Yes. KRIS: Never.
AMY: Okay. KRIS: Always hits. Auto-hit.
AMY: I want to do it. Auto-hit.
RYAN: You win the game?
JERRY: You cast the spell. AMY: Mmm.
JERRY: And you've cast this spell before. You've practiced it in your own Enclave.
It's an early spell. You may have been taught this spell by your own mother.
AMY: She was charming. JERRY: There are...
JERRY: When you cast it you reach toward a mind.
You cannot find...
You cannot find a mind to manipulate.
AMY: The color drains from my face.
KRIS: I hold my-- the cup I was holding aloft. With a whirl of my cloak I yell to the bar,
(shouting) "The jig is up!"
And I just wait.
KATE: Ooh. This is interesting. KRIS: And I hope that, I hope that
KRIS: the mastermind reveals him or herself.
AMY: Brilliant. KATE: Yeah. Okay.
JERRY: Now, he is now cowering behind the bar. He's got a bar full of witches. He's got dragons.
He's got grandmothers that seem nice but there's something fucked up about them.
KATE: In fact I'm going to... I'm trying to climb up and examine the chandelier more closely.
Potentially dangle from it.
RYAN: While we're screaming at a bartender,
RYAN: climbing on it. KATE: Because that is the directive that I've been given.
AMY: We're throwing dead animals at him.
JERRY: You reach up and try to hang on-- RYAN: Slapping dead animals around.
JERRY: Hold on a second.
So you've been given a chandelier-oriented directive.
KATE: Correct.
JERRY: From Patrick Rothfuss? KATE: Correct.
JERRY: Who plays Viari. KATE: Correct.
JERRY: Okay, so I should never have put any chandeliers in here.
KATE: Yeah. No. RYAN: Thought that was interesting.
JERRY: So his chandelier disease...
AMY: It's contagious. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Yeah. KRIS: It's a common fixture.
JERRY: is now spreading? RYAN: Incepted.
KATE: I don't have control over these things. That's just how it is.
JERRY: That's fine. You...
RYAN: He wrote The Name of the Wind, he ought to know something.
JERRY: You get up on top of the table.
JERRY:You quick jump, grab it, and it collapses on you. KATE: Okay.
RYAN: You're dead. No. JERRY: No. You're not.
JERRY: You're not dead. AMY: Nice knowing you.
JERRY: You take three points of damage and you're covered with hot wax.
RYAN: (laughs)
AMY: Nice. KATE: Thanks, Patrick Rothfuss.
JERRY: Yeah, Patrick Rothfuss, you want to fuck with my game.
RYAN: That's funny. JERRY: Only torment awaits you.
KATE: I'm covered in (shouting) hot wax? RYAN: (laughing) Love it.
KATE: Jeez. JERRY: Yeah now you're all waxy.
AMY: Is it beeswax? JERRY: Yeah. &gt;&gt; KATE: (gasps)
RYAN: Now you look at the ground. Does it form a new constellation?
JERRY: No, no, no.
(laughter)
JERRY: It's some Dan Brown shit. KRIS: Or it spells a message.
RYAN: Yeah! JERRY: Yeah exactly.
AMY: It's the Illuminati. JERRY: Exactly. The bartender says,
"I can provide you with rooms tomorrow! It's closed. We're closed now."
AMY: And I say-- JERRY: (shouting) "We're closed!"
AMY: "Donaar, wouldn't it be great if we had rooms tonight?"
RYAN: I just pick up a stool and I throw it over his head. It smashes above his head.
I say, (shouting) "It'd be great!"
(laughter)
KRIS: Oh my god. This is violent!
RYAN: This is how I intimidate people. I don't know how to intimidate someone!
KRIS: You could use the mechanics of the game. RYAN: Is this working?
RYAN: No, it's better this way. KRIS: All right. Well...
KATE: Can I try to Intimidate now that I'm all wax? RYAN: I start whipping the dead mice around.
KATE: I got some intimidation, I could just ask him really nicely, but like scary, you know?
JERRY: All right, he makes a break for the door. KATE: Okay I'm next to the door.
JERRY: It's true. KATE: I'm going to stop him.
JERRY: Yeah exactly.
JERRY: So let's have a contested roll. KATE: Okay what is that? Tell me.
JERRY: That is going to be you and me...
It's going to be him trying to get out and you trying to grab him.
JERRY: So for you that is going to be a strength test... KATE: Okay.
JERRY: against my dexterity test and I am going to give you disadvantage on your roll, heh heh heh.
KATE: You are a turd. KRIS: Ugh. Punitive.
JERRY: I'm the worst.
KATE: Okay. That's a nine. Sorry,
RYAN: You have another-- you have more advantage for once.
KRIS: Yeah you can enjoy an advantage. AMY: Yeah burn them.
KATE: But can I-- JERRY: Not on this one. No, no.
KATE: Yeah we can't do battling. JERRY: Yeah, it's not going to work like that.
KATE: So that's going to be... AMY: Well then I don't like this.
JERRY: Yeah it's garbage.
KATE: Nine plus two... No,  I got a nine.
JERRY: Okay. I have a 14.
So he...
he's under the bar and then he's crawling out from the side of the bar.
And then he's pushing his way out of the door. You reach-- you grab the hem of his shirt,
tear a little bit of it off, he pushes open the door and it is solid black, and he disappears into it.
KATE: Hmm &gt;&gt; RYAN: Hmm AMY: Delightful.
KATE: I did get a little bit of shirt though.
KATE: I'm going to smell it. RYAN: We can't leave?
JERRY: You can try. KRIS: I watch as it happens and I say,
KRIS: "Computer, end program."
JERRY: It doesn't--
KRIS: That doesn't work? JERRY: No. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Nothing happens
KRIS: Okay what I actually say is,
JERRY: You can examine all this stuff.
KRIS: "I think this is a new kind of franchising opportunity."
"I think this is a popup inn."
RYAN: Yeah?
KRIS: "That is solely magic..."
"and..."
AMY: Go on.
KRIS: "I think we have to fight the dragon woman for the last room."
(laughter)
RYAN: Yeah. Is the whole town fake or just this building?
JERRY: You feel a cold wind blow in from the door.
AMY: Oh no. RYAN: Okay.
RYAN: Go look out it.
KRIS: It's true, may I try to peek out? JERRY: Absolutely.
AMY: You love the darkness. RYAN: Yeah you love the darkness.
KRIS: I love dark.
KRIS: And I love magic. KATE: You have darkvision right?
KRIS: Yeah I have very good darkvision RYAN: I hate the dark and I hate magic.
KRIS: 120 feet. What's that get me? Nothing? KATE: Dang. Woof.
AMY: Spicy. KRIS: Still right at the door?
JERRY: It is-- I mean you're welcome to examine it with your skills and spells and--
KRIS: Oh I will. I'm going to-- let me try arcana.
AMY: Get witchy. JERRY: Yeah, get witchy with it.
KRIS: Me me take that.
And I've-- Ah... I'm going to hang onto that.
JERRY: You can. It's up to you. KRIS: Let's see how I do without it.
RYAN: These are like potions in RPGs.
JERRY: Yeah yeah yeah. RYAN: Afraid to use them.
KATE: Save it? &gt;&gt; RYAN: Stack of them. JERRY: But yeah don't be so afraid.
JERRY: They've given you two. Don't be afraid.
KRIS: All this magic is clouding... If it is magic, the darkness. I got a 12.
JERRY: 12? KRIS: Yeah.
JERRY: Yeah it is not a door in the classic sense.
But it is not solid.
KRIS: Oh. Then I proceed.
I'm going to exit this establishment.
JERRY: As you walk through, you feel another cold snap.
You feel that pressure change on your inner ear.
Give me a perception roll.
KRIS: Now I am going to take it.
(laughter)
KRIS: Yeah I'm going to want that. That was an eight. KATE: Good thing.
AMY: Yeah that was good.
KRIS: Oh god. All right, uh... KATE: Was that even worse?
JERRY: Yep.
JERRY: Add up your perception. Add up your stats. KRIS: All right, 14.
JERRY: You walk through, and you enter... what appears to be the Dran &amp; Courtier,
except there is no one in it on this side and in your pocket you feel that the acorn is gone.
AMY: You're in the Upsidedown.
KRIS: I see. And what do I see the other direction?
JERRY: You see a solid wall.
KRIS: Ah okay.
RYAN: We have no idea this worked.
AMY: Bye.
RYAN: We assumed you died. KRIS: Can I can I bang on it and go, "I got it!"
KRIS: "I figured it out!"
JERRY: You hear a...
the sound of like a distant drum...
AMY: "We'll he's dying." JERRY: from the door.
KRIS: He's being consumed. RYAN: That's his...
RYAN: his death rattle. Yeah. AMY: That's his death rattle.
JERRY: That's his heart.
He's dying now.
KATE: "I'm not very attached to him." KRIS: How could you be?
KATE: I don't... AMY: I...
RYAN: "Although there's nothing left in this room for us, right?"
AMY: "Also he came with an acorn."
KATE: "That's true. And he wasn't made of total magic bullshit so..."
KRIS: So you're assuming that maybe out there there's a free acorn...
KRIS: that I dropped as I disintegrated. JERRY: Yeah, exactly. Oh man.
AMY: So that mean's there's another 25% for Walnut. KRIS: You could have two of them.
JERRY: Exactly right. We are talking about a 50% stake. KATE: Make that paper girl. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Nice.
AMY: And I say-- but I don't say that out loud.
What I say is... I say,
"We should, in all good conscience, go help our fellow acorn-adorned friend in whatever trouble"
AMY: "he may be going through right now." JERRY: Our fellow acorn enthusiast. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Yeah.
KRIS: Yeah. AMY: Mmm. Fellow nut enthusiast.
KATE: Mmhmm. AMY: Know I love them.
JERRY: Nut fans unite?
AMY: And then I look at Donaar and I go, "Big guy." RYAN: "Yo."
AMY: "Want the honor of the first step here?"
RYAN: "Ah, I don't like this magic stuff."
AMY: "I know, nobody does."
AMY: "Nobody does." &gt;&gt; JERRY: No one's a fan. RYAN: All right.
RYAN: I say, "Fine. I got to get the hell out of here."
So I step through.
JERRY: You bump into K'thriss Drow'b.
RYAN: "Buddy, I got no more money for you."
(laughter)
KRIS: "Everywhere? Again?"
JERRY: This is becoming a thing. RYAN: Yeah. &gt;&gt; KRIS: Yeah.
RYAN: And I look around. AMY: I look at Rosie and I go, "After you."
KATE: "Sure thing!"
AMY: And then I go through.
JERRY: You pop through. Now there is literally no room.
It is you and then Donaar and then K'thriss Drow'b in a kind of conscious brick.
That has accreted like a pearl on the inside of the door.
KRIS: I was going to say, did we like telefrag each other? RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: No. KRIS: Like are we within?
JERRY: No, there's nothing like that. AMY: We're clipping into each other.
JERRY: There's nothing like that. KRIS: Okay.
KATE: Are our nuts gone?
JERRY: Your nuts are gone. KATE: Okay.
KATE: "Get over here and your nut'll be gone."
KRIS: No they're all in.
RYAN: Yeah, we're all here. KRIS: I think you were the last one.
KRIS: Or, no wait. You were. So you're all in. Yeah. AMY &amp; KATE: We're all in.
KRIS: You all followed. KATE: Nuts are gone.
AMY: I'm disgruntled about that. JERRY: That's right.
JERRY: Now this version of the inn that you see, this version of the Dran &amp; Courtier...
looks identical to the existing one. There are simply no revelers, no bartender.
RYAN: Is the chandelier on the ground?
JERRY: No, no. The chandelier has been replaced.
JERRY: It is the Homewar-- it is the Homeward Star. KATE: Homeward Star. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Homeward Star.
RYAN: I wrote that down. &gt;&gt; AMY: Me too. JERRY: The candle... nice!
JERRY: That's Dungeons and Dragons!
RYAN: I did it, I did it guys! AMY: You got it! You got it.
RYAN: Homework, done. JERRY: The candle nearest the door is
JERRY: guttering just-- KATE: Guttering again?
JERRY: Just as the last one did.
RYAN: What about the cat? He anywhere? AMY: I love time loops.
KRIS: Mouse count? &gt;&gt; JERRY: Yeah, exactly. RYAN: Oh yeah. &gt;&gt; AMY: Mouse count.
KRIS: Quick mouse count. RYAN: How many dead mice?
JERRY: Mouse situation?
AMY: (smacks lips) Not enough dead mice.
JERRY: No, yeah, exactly, no that's not for me.
We're going to go back to the other place.
JERRY: They had a... No... AMY: Bang on the wall.
JERRY: Because it's a situation where it's like, if you go to Red Robin there's like...
RYAN: dead mice in your food? JERRY: No, no. That's rare.
JERRY: No, but it's like bottomless fries, that's like bottomless mice.
And that was great times.
JERRY: Obviously if you are a cat, that's a great situation for you.
AMY: True. RYAN: Yeah.
KATE: So the cat existed somehow outside the time loop? It sounds like?
AMY: We're not confirmed it's a time loop, I just said time loop because I love time loops.
RYAN: I feel like it's another dimension.
JERRY: Listen there's plenty of opportunities for us to execute some time loop scenarios.
AMY: I do love it. KRIS: I'm assuming I lost the glass.
RYAN: (singing Beastie Boy's Intergalactic) Another dimension, another dimension.
JERRY: There's no glass. KRIS: My keepsake.
JERRY: No, no exactly, exactly yeah exactly it's like a-- KRIS: Juice tumbler.
JERRY: Well no, it comes with every drink. Obviously you get the novel glass.
JERRY: So this-- as I've said, this place is identical except it is empty of life.
RYAN: And we're not being... Why did we bump all into each other?
KRIS: I raise my empty hand aloft and I say, "The jig is up!"
AMY: Just keep trying it. KATE: "You know there might be rooms in this one."
AMY: "Oh yeah no one's here so..."
KATE: "Yeah, yeah, I bet they got some empty rooms." RYAN: Yeah. Can we just loudly ask if anyone's there?
RYAN: Say, "Anyone here?"
"Hello?" (like an echo) hello, hello...
JERRY: No. It just bounces back off of the wood panels.
AMY: "Well we can't keep at this forever." JERRY: No, no you can explore.
KATE: God... RYAN: Can we go over to the front door of this place?
KATE: Yeah. JERRY: You can play Dungeons &amp; Dragons.
JERRY: The only distinction between this inn and the last one is that where the door was is completely flat.
KATE: Pat Rothfuss has texted me again and said... JERRY: What does he say now? More bullshit?
KATE: He said-- &gt;&gt; JERRY: Listen, I can hurt you. RYAN: Do the opposite of what he said.
JERRY: I've got 2 disadvantage.
KATE: He says, obviously it's *this* chandelier that is the one you need to swing on.
JERRY: Listen, you-- KRIS: It's like a fetish.
JERRY: Yeah, exactly.
KATE: All right. JERRY: This is Chandelierianism.
RYAN: So what is the exact layout of this room? So it's a tavern; a bar, tables all over the place, a fireplace.
JERRY: Exactly, Fireplace on the right. RYAN: Stairs? Loft?
JERRY: Exactly, stairs over to the right. So over on your right; cauldron chairs, fireplace,
there is no painting of Jim Darkmagic in this version.
AMY &amp; RYAN: Ah... KATE: What?
JERRY: Up the stairs, you can see that there are--
there's an upper landing that have sort of a half circle of rooms that goes around the top.
RYAN: Doors? JERRY: Mmhmm.
RYAN: I'm going to head up there. AMY: I would love to follow.
RYAN: I want to go check out them doors. JERRY: Yeah, yeah. &gt;&gt; AMY: Yes.
JERRY: Tell me more.
RYAN: How many doors? JERRY: Around this arc we have a total of eight doors.
RYAN: Eight doors.
RYAN: I say, "Hey--" JERRY: Is that an auspicious number?
JERRY: Should you write it down?
RYAN: Whoa, whoa, hey. Eight doors... JERRY: No, no.
KATE: Nobody write it, nobody write it.
RYAN: Eight divided by four means that... KRIS: One for every door...
RYAN: I dunno.
KATE: Two... bees have two wings... &gt;&gt; RYAN: Amy, roll. AMY: I can't do this under pressure.
KRIS: Roll for the right maths.
KRIS: Roll for eight minus four.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. WALNUT &amp; RYAN: Okay.
RYAN: Anyone else coming up there with me? AMY: Yes.
RYAN: Me and you? AMY: Yes.
JERRY: Walnut's ready to go. RYAN: All right.
KRIS: Let's stick together.
RYAN: Check out these doors. KATE: Don't split the party. I'm with you all.
AMY: Let's split the party first session. RYAN: Yeah, split the party first.
JERRY: Exactly, yeah definitely.
KATE: That's what they say. RYAN: I specifically say, "Don't follow me."
JERRY: You know about this.
JERRY: You know about Dungeons &amp; Dragons? RYAN: You don't want to see what I'm going to do.
JERRY: Definitely don't all do the same thing.
Don't stack damage on enemies. You know, definitely don't do that.
AMY: Don't buff each other. Don't buff each other. JERRY: Yeah, yeah so please.
AMY: Go ahead. You're leading this charge. RYAN: Umm...
RYAN: Yeah, I open the first door.
JERRY: Okay. So you reach down-- RYAN: The very first door at the top of the steps.
JERRY: You see him reach for the handle, and as he does so the door... the handle opens slightly,
and you can see a ring of sharp teeth...
that clamps down on Donaar's hand. And you see the entire door flop forward.
JERRY: Imagine a big thick, like Fruit Roll-Up. AMY: Oh yeah.
JERRY: Imagine that the flesh of the door-- KRIS: Just goes on?
JERRY: just holds him like this,
and then begins to sort of roll him around near the top of the stairs. Let's get some initiative going.
RYAN: Going to fight some doors!
JERRY: Ladies and gents. AMY: So wanted to...
AMY: Should've cast something. KRIS: I'm excited by that door.
AMY: (blows raspberry)
RYAN: Eight. JERRY: Ugh that's a...
AMY: Did you add your mod-- Oh...
RYAN: Yeah. AMY: (laughs) You add you negative modifier.
JERRY: Yeah. You add your negative modifier. RYAN: Eight.
JERRY: All right, you got eight? KRIS: You ain't last.
AMY: Walnut got a ten.
JERRY: Okay.
RYAN: I'm not last? KATE: Rosie's 15.
KRIS: In keeping with my enjoying watching others die,
JERRY: Yeah. KRIS: Five.
JERRY: Believe it or not...
this creature...
AMY: Which also has vampire teeth. JERRY: Yeah yeah yeah.
JERRY: Yeah, this creature goes last.
KRIS: Hmm!
JERRY: Even though he did a great job... sneaking up...
AMY: I love this. This is so helpful. JERRY: Yeah yeah yeah.
JERRY: Yeah this is old school. This is how we do's it. AMY: That was good.
JERRY: All right, Rosie. So you are on the lower part of the landing I assume?
You see this slab, this like curtain of flesh...
just slam down on Donaar, bring him to the ground, and start rolling him around.
KATE: Okay. Am I within striking distance? JERRY: You can get there.
JERRY: You can get there however you like. There's a railing that goes up...
RYAN: Chandelier?
KATE: Is there a chandelier up there? JERRY: (sighs) There's a chandelier...
RYAN &amp; AMY: Don't do it, don't do it! KRIS: It's going to eat you.
KRIS: Everything in here is that thing! JERRY: (laughs) Yes, yes...
RYAN: Yeah that's true. Don't touch anything.
Rule number one! I yell from the...
RYAN: (muffled) "Nobody touch anything!" KATE: "Don't touch anything!"
RYAN: "The doors are Fruit Roll-Ups!" KATE: "You'll have to pay for it."
KRIS: I put my hand on the least mouthlike part of the chandelier, so that I may find-- No, I'm good.
(laughter)
RYAN: I do a perception check for teeth. KRIS: Yeah.
KATE: Okay, so there's a railing, and...
JERRY: Exactly. Railing. Staircase. KATE: Okay.
KATE: I believe that I am going to climb the railing like a tiny little monkey.
JERRY: Like straight up? KATE: Surprisingly dexterous. Yes. Shockingly so.
JERRY: I'm not surprised in the least.  KATE: You're not, but you guys are.
JERRY: Yeah yeah yeah, you're like, "Hey!" KATE: Right?
JERRY: This isn't your grandma's grandma. KATE: You're like, "Hey, look at that granny go!"
AMY: "She's so spry!" KRIS: "That must be some kinda railing!"
JERRY: Goddamn! KRIS: "Wow!"
RYAN: Just attribute everything to what's around like, "Wow, that's got to be the shoes!"
KRIS: "Yeah."
JERRY: You got them pumped up?
KATE: And to get within striking distance of this Fruit Roll-Up door.
And can I also make an attack? Or is that my whole action?
JERRY: Yeah absolutely, you can move there and you can attack.
JERRY: But he is currently-- RYAN: (muffled) "I said don't touch me!"
JERRY: He is currently sort of wrapped up in this, you know, almost amorphous...
KRIS: Let him have it! JERRY: grabber. &gt;&gt; KATE: Right.
JERRY: So some of that may come through onto your new friend.
JERRY: Let's see how it goes. KATE: Okay.
KATE: The amorphous grabber. I'm going to try to strike the non-dragon part of whatever this blob is.
JERRY: I'm going to strike the least draconic part. KATE: Yeah.
RYAN: I appreciate that. That is appreciated by me. KATE: Whatever looks least draconic to me.
JERRY: I want to register my satisfaction. RYAN: Yeah.
KATE: Okay. RYAN: I cheer you on.
AMY &amp; KATE: (muffled) Yay!
KRIS: I will not be doing you that kindness.
KATE: I got a 24. JERRY: Jeez.
AMY: Woo! KRIS: Mamma mia.
KATE: Apizza. JERRY: Yeah that's real good.
JERRY: Hit it! KATE: Okay.
KATE: So then I got a d8. KRIS: Which one are you doing?
KATE: I'm going to do, well I'm doing-- KRIS: Just a quarterstaff?
JERRY: You're going to whack it with the quarterstaff? KATE: I'm whacking it with my,
KATE: I get up there with my quarterstaff and I'm just going to go, "Wah-pah!"
KATE:  Right in it, which is a... JERRY: Just with the back!
KATE: Seven.
And then also, because I am fluent in martial arts...
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. In the martialest. KRIS: In the language of the quarterstaff.
KATE: Yes, in the language of the quarterstaff.
JERRY: The dialectic!
KATE: As a bonus action I can take an unarmed strike.
JERRY: Woo! KRIS: Oh, nice!
KATE: And in addition to that, I'm just going to go-- let's just go all in, folks.
RYAN: I'm glad I'm giving you the chance to show off with my incompetence of grabbing doors.
RYAN: I asked for this. KATE: I can also...
KATE: I'm going to spend a ki point and engage my flurry of blows.
Which means that I can go,  "Wah-pah," with the quarterstaff
and then with my two little feet, go "Chop chop!"
AMY: Chop with the feet? &gt;&gt; KATE: Yeah, yeah. JERRY: Oh, nice! &gt;&gt;  KRIS: Oh, like a cat!
RYAN: A foot chop?! KATE: Yeah yeah, it's a foot chop, it's a foot chop.
AMY: That's how you know she's good. KATE: It's a monk thing.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, you wouldn't know about it. KATE: Yeah yeah, it's a big deal.
RYAN: Your little toes bend like... KATE: So that's a six.
KATE: And... JERRY: Jeez.
KATE: a five.
KATE: So total of... KRIS: Wow.
KRIS: You're dead!  JERRY: 18.
KATE: 18, okay. (laughter)
AMY: That's what happens when you buy her a drink. KATE: On all the non-dragony parts.
JERRY: Brutal. RYAN: (muffled) "I owe you another drink!"
KATE: I haven't even started breathing hard, RYAN: "As many Jim &amp; Tonics..."
KATE: I'm just like, "Chop chop!"
I'm just like waiting to see--
KRIS: Right, you do it with the same-- RYAN: Surgical precision.
KRIS: the same motion that you used to climb the banister.
AMY: (laughs) Oh god!
KRIS: It just rolls immediately into those moves! KATE: (laughs) &gt;&gt; JERRY: Yeah, yeah!
KRIS: They're indistinguishable. JERRY: It's one thing.
JERRY: All three of these hits is like within a second and a half.
KRIS: Right. JERRY: Right?
JERRY: Absolutely. That is an incredible debut from this dangerous grandmother.
Next up is Walnut Dankgrass.
AMY: Hmm. RYAN: It's not dead yet?
JERRY: No! &gt;&gt; AMY: So... KRIS: It's got a good grip.
RYAN: Ugh. AMY: (sighs)
AMY: Hoo boo booey...
What do I want to do.
KATE: "Hoo boo booey," is a great battle cry, by the way. JERRY: Yeah yeah yeah!
RYAN: Yeah! JERRY: Write it down, obviously.
JERRY: Yeah, we're still building the brand, you know...
KRIS: It's going to be on all the shirts. KATE: Yep! Got to get those at--
AMY: I... RYAN: "Hubba booey."
AMY: would like to-- just because I don't feel...
comfortable in my ability to, like... pull you out of this?
This happens right in front of me, and I look at this like, "So much is happening right now."
So I would like to touch Donaar and use Barkskin?
KRIS: Hmm!   KATE: Hmm!
AMY: So I touch a willing creature--  We'll just... assume. KATE: He's willing. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: You reach under for his... RYAN: (shouting) "Who's touching me?!"
RYAN: (shouting) "I don't agree to this!" JERRY: his foot!
KRIS: "No touch!"
RYAN: "No-no touch!" AMY: Just real quick.
AMY: Until the spell ends, target's skin has a rough, bark-like appearance-- so scales,
and the target's AC can't be less than 16 regardless of what kind of armor it's wearing.
KRIS: Hmm! KATE: Nice.
JERRY: Oh, wow! &gt;&gt; AMY: So.. KRIS: The bark sloughs off...
KRIS: with a gnash of the teeth!   AMY: I think that maybe doesn't do anything for you...
RYAN: My AC's 18. &gt;&gt; AMY: Oh. Well... KATE: That's all this door needs.
AMY: So you look like bark. KRIS: It just loves bark! &gt;&gt; JERRY: Exactly!
KRIS: It's its favorite flavor. RYAN: I look like bark wearing stronger armor than bark.
AMY: I made you hideous and you're getting eaten by a door.
KRIS: (yells in horror)
RYAN: (shouting) "Nobody look at me!"
JERRY: So here's what's happened... AMY: Thank you.
JERRY: You are a young druid... and sometimes you get excited.
AMY: It happens to a lot of people! JERRY: Yeah, exactly, happens to a lot!
JERRY: So you confer upon Donaar an effect that makes his flesh like armor inside of his...
armor, which is also armor.
KATE: I'm going to give you two thumbs up. I loved it.
AMY: And then I would like to use my move action to just...
JERRY: To be ashamed!
AMY: just back up and ashamed a little bit!
(laughter)
RYAN: I just start turning into bark and say,
RYAN: "What is happening? Who is it?" JERRY: "Why?"
RYAN: "Is this the door? Is the door doing this?" KRIS: Right!
JERRY: You don't even know! KRIS: "Itchy! Flaking! Ah, ah..."
JERRY: All right. Donaar Blit'zen!
Welcome to your very first ever combat in Dungeons &amp; Dragons!
KATE: (gasps) Aww!
RYAN: The one where I died via door. JERRY: That's right.
KRIS: Well, you didn't have to grab it.
JERRY: No, it's like this-- RYAN: I didn't have to grab a door? Wha...
JERRY: You fucked up!
RYAN: I'm going to slow every game down from now on,
where I meticulously check to make sure it's not a monster.
AMY: That is the game! KATE: That's the game!
KRIS: That's what people do! KATE: That's Dungeons &amp; Dragons!
KRIS: That knob was its genitals.
(laughter)
KATE: You'd bite you too! KRIS: And it's so angry!
RYAN: I'm so perturbed with this room. JERRY: No, it's not angry.
JERRY: Like that is a positive experience. AMY, KATE, &amp; KRIS: Oh...
KATE: Oh, this is a mating ritual. JERRY: You're going to have to marry this door!
RYAN: Well I'm okay with that! KATE: Mazel tov!
KRIS: It wasn't the grasp, it was the turn. RYAN: What's the dowry like from a door?
JERRY: So you marry... &gt;&gt; KATE: A doory? JERRY: It's just hinges. It's like it's easy.
AMY: Skeleton keys. JERRY: It's a huge timesaver for you.
RYAN: Yeah, no that's fine! JERRY: It's like if you were to try to marry...
JERRY: a dragonborn woman... Very complicated! RYAN: Yeah.
KRIS: No, no, no!  RYAN: Yeah, I don't want to go through that.
JERRY: No, no.
KATE: Hassle. KRIS: If you carry the door over the threshold
KRIS: (clicks tongue) that's your door!
KATE: There it is. &gt;&gt; KRIS: In your house. JERRY: Just install it!
KRIS: It's just done. RYAN: Carry a door through a door, that's...
KRIS: It's a great door. &gt;&gt; RYAN: that isn't good. AMY: Is this a bit, or is this guy marrying a door?
JERRY: No, exactly! So, as a-- KRIS: Fast forward! &gt;&gt; RYAN: Yeah.
RYAN: That's Dungeons and Dragons!
JERRY: As your basic action for this turn...  RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: You can marry this-- No. (laughter)
RYAN: Roll to propose! AMY: Ah.
JERRY: No, no, exactly! You do.  KRIS: Right.
JERRY: So your charisma's very high.
JERRY: The fact of the matter is, RYAN: It is!
JERRY: you could probably fucking marry a door, and no one would bat an eye.
JERRY: So, Donaar, KATE: I can officiate.
JERRY: She's ready to go.
Donaar Blit'zen. You are grappled by this door.
Well it's more of a liquid creature now.
RYAN: A fruit leather door. JERRY: Exactly.
JERRY: So a grappled creature's speed becomes zero, you can't really move around.
You can't get bonuses to your speed...
But basically you need to use your own strength
to sort of peel-- again, the Fruit Roll-Up metaphor is continuing to be strong.
RYAN: "It's quite the sticky situation!"
KATE: God! We can't hear you! AMY: (blows raspberry)
JERRY: So peel it off. KATE: You're covered in-- &gt;&gt; RYAN: I say it to the door.
KRIS: It's to himself. RYAN: The door hears me. (laughter)
KRIS: The door chuckles. RYAN: And it's smitten! It loves me more!
JERRY: (muffled sounds)
JERRY: So your beak is just like rasping against the side of this thing.
RYAN: I'm just saying tons of funny shit and this door is loving it.
KRIS: All my good material is getting absorbed by this damn door!
JERRY: Yeah, so before you can-- RYAN: I make a note to say it later.
JERRY: Before you can do much, you want to get the fuck away from this door.
RYAN: Yes, I do. I want to... withdraw myself. JERRY: Right? So there's a couple things.
JERRY: Checks. This specific type of creature is extra hard to escape,
you get disadvantage trying to get away from it.
But you could very easily leverage your advantage to make it a straight roll.
RYAN: Yeah, I will do such a thing. JERRY: Now, is this the sort of thing that
JERRY: systemically brings you around? RYAN: Yes.
RYAN: Now, what do I have to do to... What am I rolling, strength?
JERRY: Exactly. So this is basically an ability check.  RYAN: Yeah. Okay...
JERRY: So you're looking for a DC 13...
JERRY: Here's your strength. RYAN: Yep. 16, with a plus three modifier.
JERRY: Exactly. So you roll a dice, you get a plus three, these are good times!
KRIS: See what you get.
RYAN: What am I rolling? d20?
JERRY: Oh yeah. Yeah, yeah! d20!
KRIS: Yeah, we love them.
JERRY: Most of the-- if I ever ask you for a check--
RYAN: 11. JERRY: No!
KATE: No!
JERRY: If I ever ask you for a check...
RYAN: It's always 20? All right.
JERRY: Grab that 20. RYAN: I got another one, can I do it again?
JERRY: No, not right now. So that's your action for this turn is trying to get the fuck away.
KRIS: You're getting an embrace of the door. KATE: You got to add a bunch of stuff to that, right?
KATE: Add all kinds of stuff! JERRY: Yeah!
RYAN: 14!
JERRY: 14 is one over what you need. AMY: Mmm. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Oh!
JERRY: So you sort of reach inside, you push out just far enough, and then you just remove it like a heavy cloak.
You just peel it off and snap it like a towel. And throw it a few feet down the hall...
JERRY: And then stand up like, "It's cool." RYAN: And then I say...
RYAN: "That was a sticky situation!"
JERRY: (laughing) I've been saying it the whole time!
RYAN: "Yeah! Guys. Did you see that?"
KATE: "I love it, I love it, I love the joke." KRIS: I'm like, "I heard it, those three times you said it."
KATE: "I didn't." KRIS: "And you intonated differently each time."
RYAN &amp; KATE: Yeah! AMY: Just workshopping it.
KATE: You heard it because of your excellent hearing.
RYAN: And then I make a point to thank Rosie... KRIS: I have dark hearing.
KATE: Yeah. RYAN: And...
AMY: That's a bonus action. RYAN: I look at Walnut...
RYAN: and I just don't say anything. KATE &amp; KRIS: Yeah.
RYAN: I don't admonish, and I don't thank. AMY: "Is that a butterfly?"
KATE: Just a long stare... RYAN: And I just scratch my barky skin.
JERRY: Yeah, it's just neutral. No, no, it's like birch!
It's just you're peeling off sheets of it... AMY: Ew. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: All right, K'thriss Drow'b. AMY: "Exfoliating, whatever."
JERRY: Yeah, exactly! Exactly. AMY: "You're welcome."
JERRY: You're revealing skin's freshest layer!
All right. Take it away, K'thriss Drow'b.
KRIS: I'm going to nail this door. And I'm going to take aim at all the other doors.
Show them a lesson. We're going to--
KRIS: "No shit from you," RYAN: You're going to beat it up,
KRIS: "the seven of you!" RYAN: "This is for the rest of you doors!"
KATE: Oh, there's seven other doors!
KRIS: I am going to... JERRY: So where are you physically in this scenario?
JERRY: Because you and Rosie were sort of down on the lower landing.
KRIS: Oh okay, yeah. I take my time carefully up the stairs.
Although I am dextrous, no need to put myself out.
RYAN: (laughs) AMY: Not a showboater.
KRIS: So that puts me... I guess furthest in the back.
Oh, no! You advanced on this thing.
KATE: Mmhmm.  KRIS: You were basically on top of it. Okay.
KRIS: Where are the two of you? Yeah, we're-- So down the hallway...
JERRY: Mmhmm. KRIS: we're now situated here...
JERRY: Just half-circle, up the stairs, KRIS: and they've been thrown--
JERRY: they are farther up, they're about in the middle of this ring here.
She has already approached and has interacted with these creatures.
KRIS: Okay.
JERRY: But it is now a couple feet past them around this ring.
KRIS: All right. I just want to get close enough to get line of sight so I can Eldritch Blast them.
So let's do that.
JERRY: So you want to blast them in an eldritch way?
KRIS: Yes. JERRY: Okay.
KRIS: It's the preferred method of my people. JERRY: Prove it. Now how does that work?
JERRY: So your focus is this chunk of this altar that you carved out.
KRIS: I reach into my cloak and thank the gods I still have it.
KRIS: I didn't take that over my acorn. I don't care about that!
KATE: Which gods do you thank?
KRIS: Oh... I only say that as a nicety. I only believe in the real, actual one.
KRIS: The darkest, sub-one. RYAN: "I say it as a nicety."
KRIS: Yeah. People say, oh you're atheist but then why do you say thank god?
Because everybody says it! It's part of our language.
(laughter)
AMY: Ugh!
KRIS: I give it a little (kissing sound) mwah-mwah kiss, as is traditional,
that I've discovered enhances its power.
JERRY: Yeah, exactly, a moistening.
KRIS: Yeah, yeah. It requires saliva to function.
And then I lower one arm at this flopping thing.
AMY: I'm so transported.
KRIS: (straining) Ah... Ho! What's that?
JERRY: Do you know about numbers? KRIS: That's nothing!
KRIS: No, no, that's pretty good. KATE: Bringing your shitty little game....
KRIS: That's going to be a... 15! KATE: to my table.
JERRY: Yep, yep. KATE: Mmm!
JERRY: So these... razor sharp...
KRIS: (hisses)
JERRY: bursts of eldritch power leap out of the stone.
What kind of damage are we talking about, K'thriss Drow'b?
KRIS: We're talking about a tender, choice, juicy 1d10.
(laughter)
KRIS: It's like a filet mignon junior! RYAN: Roll a ten!
KRIS: A four.
KRIS: A four. KATE: Oh, just four damage, huh?
KRIS: Just four. JERRY: Yep. &gt;&gt; KATE: Mmm.
KRIS: It don't do so much at level three.
(laughter)
JERRY: It impacts this, sort of meaty shroud...
KRIS: (sound like damp cloth being vacuumed) "phthlm!"
JERRY: but is largely absorbed by the creature.
Next up, this beast begins to slither and writhe along the ground and next it's going to leap up...
onto Walnut Dankgrass.
AMY: Okay. Cool.
AMY: Learned my lesson. RYAN: Yeah.
KATE: Mmhmm. AMY: About being squishy.
JERRY: Right. So as it comes up, you can see the mass sort of slithering toward you.
It sort of grows in height the closer it gets. Never quite becoming humanoid.
But it's surprising, because as it approaches a pseudopod lashes out from an unexpected arc.
AMY: Great! Okay... JERRY: It has no shape of any kind.
AMY: That's how I like my pseudopods?
JERRY: (laughs) "I like my pseudopods like I like my other things."
KATE: Without form. JERRY: Amorphous!
KRIS: My ears perk up. JERRY &amp; KRIS: (noises of interest)
JERRY: Nine, I assume, is not your...
AMY: Oh, no. JERRY: Yeah.
AMY: I dust it off. JERRY: Yeah, exactly.
KATE: Phew AMY: "Nice try."
JERRY: Yeah. It tries, you just easily come underneath it.
JERRY: We're back on to Rosie Beestinger. KATE: Okay.
JERRY: So Rosie Beestinger has been the greatest contributor of damage thus far in this scenario.
KATE: It's not too late. JERRY: Yeah!
KATE: Okay.... Rosie is... she has followed this thing as it has slithered across the floor...
KATE: She's got-- JERRY: Just tracking it?
KATE: Yeah yeah, she's like, "Just move!" JERRY: Just the rod out?
KATE: "Just try something right now."
She's got her stick out and she's waiting for everybody else to do their thing.
And then she's just going to go at it again. She's got no trust for this thing,
It went after her dragon friend who bought her a Jim &amp; Tonic.
And she's just like,
"If there's one thing in this life that you can trust, it's someone who buys you a goddamn drink."
So that's why she is all about--
JERRY: She's about it. &gt;&gt; AMY: Wise beyond her years. KATE: ridding the world of this...
RYAN: We're best friends! JERRY: Well, pretty old. &gt;&gt; AMY: But not beyond.
JERRY: Wise at exactly the right amount for her age. AMY: (laughs) Yeah!
JERRY: So you come up, classic technique. KATE: Yeah.
JERRY: You've known this for... 80 years.
KATE: Yeah, it's not-- It's like breathing. It's like water.
And it's going to be...
a... AMY: (whistles)
KATE: Hmm that's an 11 to attack?
AMY: Well, not quite like breathing... KATE: (whimpers)
JERRY: You can see that it's lashed out with its pseudopod at Walnut. You time your strike perfectly and
as immediately as you put it through, it makes a void.
KRIS: Mmm. &gt;&gt; KATE: Ah.  AMY: Ooh. &gt;&gt; KATE: The void.
JERRY: Goes through. You withdraw it. KATE: Void's stuffed. Okay.
KATE: Then I don't know that I can do much about that.
I can do-- I can take a bonus action of kicking...
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. You should always KATE: As I always do.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, exactly.
AMY: Why wouldn't you? JERRY: Let's having kicking be your thing.
JERRY: Because you know, everybody has to have a thing, like maybe your thing will be kicking monsters.
RYAN: Oh, are we doing things?
KATE: Yeah, yeah. My thing will-- JERRY: Everybody work out their thing!
KRIS: Choose your thing! JERRY: No, when I come to your turn
RYAN: I spit acid. JERRY: you better have your thing worked out.
AMY: Okay. KATE: It creates that void, and I'm like,
KATE: "Oh yeah, you can't do it twice! You can't do it in two places!"
Oh, sorry, I rolled the wrong thing.
JERRY: You get excited by the damage! You're like-- KATE: (grunting) I just--
JERRY: "I want to roll it again!" Hey, no real quick, KATE: I already did it!
JERRY: Don't forget so next time... on an attack... people watching the show, they want you to succeed...
KATE: Yeah. Sorry. Yes. I'm very-- I'm in it! I'm in that place.
JERRY: But that connects. That's a gruesome hit. KATE: Oh yeah, that's a 21.
KATE: Okay. And that is going to be...
a... five damage with my foot. With my little granny foot.
JERRY: So it looks from your perspective, this looks completely planned. She's fired the quarterstaff in.
It's made the space, and it's thickened it over here, for the direct blade kick right along the side of the foot.
More damage from Rosie, now it's back to Walnut Dankgrass.
AMY: This situation is unbearable.
JERRY: Yeah!   KATE: Oh no...! JERRY: Oh no!
KRIS: (victory airhorn noises) KATE: It's happening! &gt;&gt; RYAN: (quacks)
AMY: So I use wildshape to turn myself into a brown bear.
RYAN: Oh. I thought you were going to say, "into a dire wolf."
AMY: No, there's different puns for every... thing!  KATE &amp; KRIS: (growls)
JERRY: Now we worked this out.
AMY: Yes. JERRY: There's cool phrases for each beast.
JERRY: Right? "Unbearable". Love it. What's next?
AMY: Okay. So I can start out by giving it giving it a chomp. Giving it a bite.
JERRY: Yeah yeah. So you you become a bear.
AMY: I become-- Oh sorry! I am now a brown bear.  JERRY: Yeah.
KATE: Is there any pomp and circumstance to it?
Or are you just like one minute you're-- It's just a blink-- like, I'm just a bear now!
AMY: I mean she looks angry and then she hulks out. Yeah there's a cutscene. This is theater of the mind!
KATE: Roleplay this shit for me right now.
JERRY: Altered beast. AMY: (growling)
(laughter)
(laughter) KRIS: It's more like... (growls)
AMY: Or it's almost the closeup shot of the hand like getting all gross.
RYAN: Stretching and reforming, yeah. JERRY: All the hair...
KRIS: An American Bear in Paris. RYAN: An American Werewolf... Yeah there you go.
JERRY: So it sounds like Walnut Dankgrass is just cracking her knuckles...
It sounds like she's just cracking her knuckles, but she is transformed into a gigantic, starving bear.
AMY: I would also...
JERRY: Starving ass bear! AMY: Starving ass bear!
AMY: I want to do a bite, but I don't want to mess around because I really want to redeem myself
because Walnut, and maybe the human playing Walnut, are very embarrassed about that first attack.
JERRY: Hey! Worse things have happened. So you're saying you want to dump one of your dice into there?
AMY: I want to dump one of my special dice.
AMY: Thanks guys  JERRY: So two rolls, and choose your best.
RYAN: There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
AMY: Okay, 11... JERRY: Em-bear-assed about? (laughs)
(laughter)
JERRY: All right. RYAN: I say that really loud.
AMY: Seven... Okay, so with an 11...plus I get a plus six?
JERRY: Mmhmm, yeah. 17. AMY: So, 17.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, yeah. So this is the bite?
Yeah, so you just transform and then you just lope...
AMY: Lope! Okay!    JERRY: down, right down the middle,
JERRY: I mean, you guys have to make way. There's not enough room for you guys and the bear.
RYAN: You don't just make curds... you make whey. JERRY: No, no, no, no. &gt;&gt; KATE: I just let her go over me.
JERRY: Yeah, exactly, you just...
KRIS: Curd jokes. Love it.
JERRY: And then you just-- you close your jaws down around the thickest part of this thing.
AMY: I sure do. We'll see how much it hurts.
JERRY: Jeez! AMY: Yep! Plus four so 11.
KRIS: Oh! That's tangy! JERRY: (high pitched scream)
AMY: But because I'm a bear-- a special thing about bears...
JERRY: You know there's something  special about bears y'all.
RYAN: Hold up everyone, bear facts.
AMY: Nature facts time. Bears have multiattack so I also get to get him with my claws.
KRIS: I get to roll for each tooth!
KRIS: Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang! AMY: It's going to be a long night, folks.
AMY: Okay, so I get to do the claws now.
AMY: Ah! Oh! 19! JERRY: Whoa! &gt;&gt; KATE: Dang...
AMY: Which actually would be a 25 but... KRIS: Who cares?
AMY: It's fine, I don't want to show off.
JERRY: Yeah, we're not comparing numbers, obviously. RYAN: It's got keen smell.
KRIS: Bears can't count! AMY: Keen smell? That's not going to help me here.
AMY: Okay so I get to do 2d6 plus four of slashing... So that's a three... plus four. Seven.
JERRY: So it's 18 total? KATE: Rosie's impressed.
RYAN: That bear's got some crazy stats. JERRY: Jeez.
JERRY: Right, so you have grabbed it and then as those jaws clamp down, it's trying to do its shit.
It has a canned response when it has been seized. You know what I mean? It's trying to flow out and the jaw is
just right down on it. And then you take that opportunity while it's there, pinned down, just to shred whatever its
midsection equivalent would be. Yeah, it has begun to weep a black fluid.
AMY: My favorite.  JERRY: Yeah, so flavorful.
JERRY: Donaar.
RYAN: This thing's not dead yet? So is it in her mouth?
JERRY: Right now it is, but it's slowly flowing out.
RYAN: Yeah, I don't know. If I go at it am I going to hit it?
AMY: Who cares? Right? I made you ugly. JERRY: No, no, this is not that type of situation.
RYAN: Okay, all right. Then I'll go at it with my greatsword.
JERRY: Let's see it.  RYAN: All right, so...
JERRY: That's going to be d20 for you.  RYAN: Yeah, plus five on it. Right?
AMY &amp; JERRY: Mmhmm.
RYAN: 15.
JERRY: 15, yeah. That connects.
JERRY: Let's see some damage. RYAN: 2d6 plus three.
JERRY: Ho ho...
RYAN: 2d6 plus three slashing.
KRIS: Oh yeah, this thing is so slashable.
AMY: Ooh... RYAN: 13!
JERRY: Jeez! &gt;&gt; KATE: Ooh! That's a big hit. KRIS: That's some sword.
JERRY: Wow that is... KRIS: That's a great sword!
RYAN: Thanks.
JERRY: That is exactly its level of hit points.
RYAN: Hey! I killed it. AMY: What line do you say when you kill it?
AMY: You've got to say something cool! JERRY: Do you have a greatsword line that's...?
RYAN: A greatsword line? I thought I needed a door line.
AMY: Whatever. RYAN: Oh.
RYAN: I don't know, I got nothing. I start-- I panic. And I start weeping.
(laughing) RYAN: (whiny crying sounds)
RYAN: "Is it dead? Oh no!"
And then I feel real guilty because we had something for a minute.
RYAN: I was halfway to marrying the thing a minute ago. KRIS: Not my door wife!
RYAN: "Oh! I a-door you!" (fake crying)
(all fake crying)
JERRY: Tears.
So basically, as soon as it's trying to get away from this grip and these claws, as soon as it tries to slide away
you slice it like a cake. The two halves try to go their disparate ways. They are not able to. A foot or so away,
in each case, they just stop and then reduce into puddles.
It is at this time that two of the cauldron chairs begin to begin to lope their way up the stairs.
AMY: Is it Beauty and the Beast in here? God!
JERRY: Beauty and the motherfucking Beast, you all.
So they are on their way up right now. And if I understand this situation correctly...
AMY: This Fantasia... JERRY: Yeah, exactly.
KATE: Are they coming to help?
JERRY: No! You're not their guest.
We have Donaar, Walnut, Rosie, and then K'thriss.
KRIS: I'm in the back. JERRY: You are in the back.
JERRY: And that's great. KRIS: And I'm presenting....
JERRY: Yeah exactly (laughing) KRIS: for these cauldrons.
KRIS: Here they come. JERRY: No, no, so you just hear the ringing of the...
JERRY: of the heavy metal-- KRIS: Of the shell? &gt;&gt; JERRY: of the shell.
JERRY: And you see the legs of the stools just running up. You see two of them skittering up the up the stairs
behind you and they are coming to get you.
KRIS: (grunts)
JERRY: Let's see what we're talking about in terms of your armor.
KRIS: You're going to love it. JERRY: 13?
KRIS: Oh it's a push. So it, yeah, it hits me. JERRY: Oh I love it. This is great news.
KRIS: Bites me right on the tail. Ah! Do drow have tails?
JERRY: Exactly, no no. So... AMY: I don't think so. Maybe.
JERRY: before pseudopods were whipping out, this you see it come up and then you see around the base and
bowl of the cauldron you see the teeth emerge.
KRIS: Oh the whole seat becomes the mouth?
JERRY: And then it sort of jumps and tries to catch you in midair.
KRIS: (groans in pain) JERRY: They are starving.
JERRY: They think that-- AMY: They want some of that sweet, sweet drow!
JERRY: Oh yeah, they have heard about it, and this is a bucket list item for them. You know what I mean?
KATE: It's a delicacy. AMY: Get it because they're bucket seats? I don't...
JERRY: Oh it's so good. &gt;&gt; KRIS: It's a choice meat. KATE: I liked it. I liked it.
JERRY: It's so good. &gt;&gt; KRIS: High grade. RYAN: Maybe I shouldn't have yelled at the bartender.
JERRY: That's nine points. KRIS: Rancher's Reserve... All right.
KATE: Ooh nine points. KRIS: Yeah
RYAN: I yell out an apology for yelling at the bartender earlier.
JERRY: "It was wrong!" RYAN: I say, "Was it...? I'm sorry!"
JERRY: "It was wrong, the whole thing was wrong!" AMY: That's not how we talk about our feelings.
RYAN: Does anything happen?
JERRY: Oh yeah, he gets-- KATE: He gets a big old bite. &gt;&gt; KRIS: It hurts me a lot.
RYAN: It bites you hard (laughs) JERRY: He gets his ass bit... what kinda hit points
JERRY: do you have left over there? RYAN: It detects the weakness of the apology.
KRIS: It takes me to 12. JERRY: Yeah, okay...
KATE: Rosie says, "That's a big mouth."
JERRY: Yeah, there's a lot. There's a lot of mouth. But there's another one coming.
KRIS: (munching sounds) JERRY: Ugh! That's even higher.
KRIS: Oh no. Oh but it doesn't beat my armor class, though.
JERRY: No, it does. It really, really does.
KRIS: I have armor class 13 and then 15 and up.
KRIS: You've got to roll a 14. JERRY: Oh it's a range. Nice.
JERRY: No it doesn't work that way, warlock.
KATE: That'd be great. JERRY: That is another seven points.
KRIS: Oh mamma mia. It's not looking good.
JERRY: Nope. And then we move right back up to the top for Rosie.
KATE: Okay.
JERRY: So the situation has been altered substantially. The one that you were striking cleverly was a large
floppy thing, and these are smaller, more agile cauldron beasts.
KATE: Okay.
KRIS: And right now I'm like pressed up against a wall bleeding my own blood...
(laughter)
KRIS: that's now painting... JERRY: This is new.
KRIS: Yeah. A new sensation for me... Yeah. JERRY: This is a new sensation... Yeah.
KATE: Umm so... I... I can't help you.
JERRY: Fuck you.
KATE: Yep. "Fuck you," says grand... KRIS: I turn my...
KRIS: I get a drink. (laughter)
JERRY: It would just come straight out... like... KRIS: Yeah. (laughs)
JERRY: You would not even be able to absorb it. So what do you got there, Rosie?
KATE: Rosie is just going to go at-- take a-- sigh heavily because she was not expecting this day to go like this.
KATE: And take it out on the-- JERRY: It was supposed to be a day of filling out forms.
KATE: It was, it was purely-- Like first day on the job they don't put you to work. You fill out all the HR shit. But she
is actually getting stuff done. So she's like, "All right,  well I guess I'm just going to continue on my merry
quarterstaff way." Try to attack whatever is attacking him, because he seems cool and he had a nut.
KRIS: There's, there's two of them so you've just got to pick one, I guess.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, take your pick. KATE: Yeah, I'll pick the one that's most--
KATE: Oh I see. They're both aggro on you. KRIS: Yeah.
KATE: I'll take the one on the left. JERRY: I can track that.
KRIS: Ooh... KATE: That's a 24.
KRIS: You're a performer. JERRY: Damn!
KATE: Thanks, gentlemen. JERRY: That's all right.
AMY: I guess we can just go home. You got this right? RYAN: Goo goo gooo!
RYAN: Hey I killed the door! JERRY: So let's see it.
KATE: All right.
RYAN: (softly) I did a thing...
KATE: So that's going to be five bludgeoning, and then my bonus action will be my martial arts.
And I will.... do another hit on that...
KATE: Which is going to be... oh!  KRIS: Aww...
KATE: Oh no! But it's okay because I have this lucky ability. I can reroll a natural one.
JERRY: WOW! Let's see it &gt;&gt; KRIS: What? RYAN: Nice! &gt;&gt; KATE: I'm a lucky little halfling.
KATE: Okay. That's not much better... That's a ten.
JERRY: No. That does not do it. &gt;&gt; KATE: Okay... KRIS: Shoot &gt;&gt; AMY: Oh no...
KATE: But I did the five points of damage anyway. JERRY: So you whack...
JERRY: straight over the top, I mean everything that would lead you to believe that you're going to hear a
ring of metal, and it's just-- it's like training against a dummy full of straw. Like it's just this sort of hollow
thick sound. And then you kick straight in and it just opens its mouth and your foot goes into that void
expanse. You withdraw. You're not able to deliver any damage on that one.
Walnut Dankgrass!
AMY: Umm... RYAN: Still a bear.
AMY: Still a bear.
JERRY: Still pro-bear. AMY: Uhh... (laugh)
AMY: Very pro-bear platform here.
So seeing this, I would like to...
and I don't want to use this word...
but I can't think of any other word for it, but just like barrel through the hallway...
KRIS: (fake laugh) AMY: Nope. It was not appropriate. &gt;&gt; RYAN: (snorts)
KRIS: Because bears always hide in barrels. I get it. RYAN: Yep! Yeah.
AMY: Yeah! Exactly.
KRIS: Because that's what they balance on top of at the circus!
JERRY: I will, I will turn this game around! (laughter)
(laughter)
JERRY: Let's see what you've got-- AMY: I don't have all these two dollar words Jerry!
JERRY: Let's see what you've got, Walnut.
AMY: Okay. So I would like to go for the one that's not getting quarterstaffed.
JERRY: Exactly. So you're going to go for the fresh one? So this is the situation, obviously your parents went
away for a week's vacation. They left the keys to-- No. That's not what happened. So she has connected
with one on one side. You're basically just very surprised.
KRIS: Yeah.
JERRY: You're trying to make yourself as thin as possible. To your right, is a halfling ninja monk.
To your left, squeezing you against the right side of the railing...
AMY: Oh, yeah.  KRIS: Then that hot musk rising.
JERRY: is a gigantic, angry bear.
AMY: Yeah it's like when they're trying to get in the tree.
KRIS: With the like prehensile like... the mouth. JERRY: Yeah, yeah (growling)
JERRY: Yeah, exactly. AMY: So yeah, I want to go for a bite if I can...
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, do it, absolutely. RYAN &amp; KATE: (in unison) Do a bite!
KRIS: Do a bite! JERRY: Do a bite but remember you got juice.
JERRY: You have juice from the channel too. AMY: That's right I do have juice!
AMY: Mmm... I would like to juice. JERRY: Up to you.
JERRY: Yeah yeah. So this is for your bite attack? RYAN: We have to save Kris, he's pretty much dead.
AMY: For my bite attack, yes. &gt;&gt; JERRY: He's fucked. KRIS: I'm a dead body, it's what I've always wanted.
RYAN: It's what he always wanted. K'thriss actually jumped into the cauldron. AMY: Thank you, friends of Walnut.
JERRY: Hit it! AMY: I'm doing an attack here!
JERRY: Yeah. KRIS: Have some reverence.
JERRY: I-- I'm in command AMY: Silence, please.
AMY: It is my turn! No, I'm joking.
RYAN: Here comes the one.
AMY: I get to do it twice though!
RYAN: 19! AMY: Oh nice!
AMY: I mean, it's not going to get better than that but is it?
AMY: It didn't. JERRY: It could... it could!
AMY: So 25?
JERRY: Oh yeah, yeah. &gt;&gt; AMY: Okay so lets get...  KRIS: You hit all cauldrons ever made.
AMY: I hit him and its parents. I... (laughs)
KRIS: You hit a cauldron factory!
JERRY: Somewhere a cauldron factory catches flame!
(laughter)
AM: Okay, so that is... 13 piercing. JERRY: Jeez!
JERRY: Gosh... &gt;&gt; RYAN: You going to multi? AMY: And then, if I can, get a little claw in there.
JERRY: Yeah, absolutely. So, this is a thing where it's exposed its fangs through the false kettle. And you just
connect it with the top. You have bitten the top of it. Shaken it a couple times. And now you're ready, now
that you have it you're going to go to work with the claw.
AMY: Well we'll see. RYAN: They wanted us to sit in these things...
KRIS:  I know... &gt;&gt; RYAN: Can you believe that? JERRY: Think about that!
JERRY: Get OSHA in here. AMY: 17? 17?
JERRY: 17 to hit? Yes absolutely. AMY: Yeah, is that going to do it?
AMY: Great. KRIS: Sure.
AMY: (laughs) Thanks, Kris. KRIS: Oh, no it hits. Yes please. More hits!
AMY: Ummm... (mumbling) 11?
JERRY: I love it. I love that set. God I love that set. AMY: Good, it's very nice.
JERRY: So good. I feel like it's making me a better dungeon master to have these rad dice on the table.
AMY: It feels good. JERRY: Donaar Blit'zen!
JERRY: So you're fresh off your greatsword... RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: Has been hefted back up onto the shoulder.
RYAN: I guess I should go after the weak one, right?
JERRY: Cull the weak! RYAN: Yeah. I mean, we've got to take...
AMY: Dealer's choice.
RYAN: Yeah, let's go to the one that was just weakened. JERRY: Savaged?
RYAN: Yeah, so I'll go at him with the greatsword again. AMY: Finish him off.
JERRY: Yeah, exactly. The premium sword experience. RYAN: Yeah.
KATE: Hey could you just do a little roleplay?
RYAN: Huh?
KRIS: Yeah, give us something. AMY: Give us some flavor!
KATE: Give us some spice. JERRY: Yeah. Give us some flavor!
RYAN: I uh... KRIS: You loose it off your shoulder--
RYAN: I pull my sword over, and then I walk over to the cauldron, and then I go...
KRIS: You do the sword move that you see in games. RYAN: I do the... yeah. &gt;&gt; JERRY: Yeah, exactly.
KRIS: I want to send dark souls when you have the... RYAN: I don't know... uhhh. All right.
JERRY: And I... and I confer... KATE: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
JERRY: I confer disadvantage on this roll.
RYAN: I drag... I use mine to counter-- KRIS: No, you can't. &gt;&gt; AMY: You can't.
JERRY: It's too late. RYAN: I thought I could counter yours!
KRIS: No... KATE: He won't let us. I tried.
RYAN: Oh... All right. JERRY: Next time. Next time, we'll try it.
JERRY: This time we're learning. RYAN: So conferring disadvantage means?
JERRY: You roll two dice and you take the shitty one.
RYAN: Ah, shit, all right. AMY: You got it! &gt;&gt; KATE: It's okay, you got this!
KRIS: Roll the same number twice-- KATE: We believe in you.
KRIS: that's all you got to do. Defeat him! RYAN: Okay.
RYAN: 12... JERRY: 12.
KRIS: Okay... KATE: Not bad, not bad.
KRIS: Not showing off, but... AMY: But it would be... you still get the plus.
RYAN: Five. &gt;&gt; AMY: Oh, all right. (disappointed noises from all)
RYAN: So I've got to take the five...  KRIS: So I put my sword back on my shoulder.
RYAN: So that's ten. JERRY: All right, so....
JERRY: That's not able to do it. So Walnut has it in the fangs. Shakes it, claws it, and then flings it in the
manner of a wild beast, up in the air for that second snatch. You try to come down with the greatsword…
it just misses.
JERRY: K'thriss Drow'b! AMY: Okay good.
AMY: I was waiting for the, "And then it hits Walnut." RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: Yeah yeah. And then you die! RYAN: And then you lop off her paw...
JERRY: Exactly. So K'thriss Drow'b, what do you got? KRIS: I can only...
RYAN: Oh I was going to do a smite and shit... KRIS: I'm just torn up... near death.
JERRY: No you're savaged. But the dark robe is doing you a lot of favors here.
KRIS: Oh yeah. JERRY: I mean you still look great.
KATE: Slimming. RYAN: The mud hides a lot.
RYAN: Still got the mud on you. JERRY: Obviously the abdomen-- KRIS: Wrinklefree.
JERRY: Larvae. You know what I mean? KRIS: Yeah. Exactly.
KRIS: I can only wonder at how much I've disappointed this god by going from level nine to three.
But I know that that might be responsible that-- that even at his most eldritch-- it was just a measly--
couldn't even take a door out.
So I'm going to look at the more damaged of the cauldrons
and I'm going to cast Dissonant Whispers upon it.
KATE: What does Dissonant Whispers do? JERRY: Yeah!
KRIS: I'mma tell you 'bout it.
JERRY: Dude you got to dish up this RP for me, man. KRIS: Yeah, exactly.
RYAN: He pulls out a book? JERRY: (shouts) What the fuck?
JERRY: Oh that's a premium experience!
JERRY: It'd be like you brought out like a veggie tray.
KRIS: Yeah. For all!
JERRY: Hungry? KRIS: What a party!
KRIS: I don't need the book description. You can get that for the damage.
It's not so much a dissonant whisper at the cauldron, but more of a prayer to the sigil which I'm still clutching.
And hopefully this cauldron will overhear it.
JERRY: Now, hold on a second, there's an attack roll? KRIS: I don't care if there's damage.
KRIS: I'm sorry. That's incredibly important. This is a wisdom saving throw.
JERRY: Perfect, yeah that's vital. So you don't need to throw.
KRIS: For this creature.
KRIS: You're right. JERRY: Yeah. You ready?
KRIS: That's critical. JERRY: K.
RYAN: How smart is this cauldron?
JERRY: I was just going to say, it's not-- There are... KRIS: It's a wise cauldron...
KRIS: It's not the most smart. RYAN: Yeah, beyond it's years. It's seen a lot of butts.
JERRY: There are smarter cauldrons. 13?
KRIS: Uh, let's see against mine? JERRY: Yeah.
KRIS: Oh, no you don't get it.
JERRY: Okay, no I'm... Listen-- RYAN: Mine's a million.
RYAN: I'm super smart. JERRY: I'm eldritch as shit so...
KRIS: Me real smart.
JERRY: Yeah yeah, so dish it up.
KRIS: All right, so then it becomes a 3d6 psychic damage.
KRIS: And what a mind he's got on him. KATE: (gasps) Oh my god.
KRIS: That's eight and it must immediately use its reaction to escape my presence.
The presence of these whispers.
JERRY: Yeah, exactly. So this evil prayer, maybe the first prayer you learned,
the first revelation of this chunk that you carved out.
As soon as the whispers hit it like a physical wave. And you see it tip back over the edge of the top stair.
And then halfway through that process it just bursts into like a pustulant liquid and runs down the stairs.
KRIS: As a bonus action I go, "Yah yay. That's what you get."
(laughing)
RYAN: All bleeding like, "Aagh."
KRIS: The other one is still very much in my way. RYAN: It's like right in your face.
RYAN: "I'm the best. Ow..."
JERRY: The other one is going to chomp chomp chomp at Rosie Beestinger.
KATE: Come at me.
RYAN: What are we going to fight next a fireplace? JERRY: Ooh 18?
KATE: Yes. KRIS: That was a hot hit.
JERRY: 18.  KATE: Yes. &gt;&gt; AMY: Oh no...
JERRY: Now, it delivers unto you six points of damage...
JERRY: and uh... AMY: This level it's a lot.
JERRY: an additional six. So as it bites, it slavers into the wound an acidic spittle...
AMY: (gags) Disgusting.
KATE: No. Okay, so... JERRY: It's true, I'm sorry.
KRIS: Right in that hole. JERRY: It's not my fault.
KATE: That's another six points of damage? JERRY: Yeah, it's 12 total.
KATE: Okay.
JERRY: So that's down, and we are back to Rosie. So you have an opportunity to respond with immediacy.
AMY: Yeah. KATE: Okay.
AMY: Get them, granny! KRIS: We're both, like not hot over here.
KATE: Yeah if you guys got some of those good heals...
KATE: we could probably use some of that. AMY: Not as a bear.
KATE: Not as a bear, great. Good, good, good. JERRY: (bear noises)
JERRY: Just a big shrug. Like the biggest shrug! KRIS: Yeah.
AMY: Though truly. KATE: Okay.
KATE: I'm going to use one of my juicy die.
JERRY: I was going to say, you have a heap of dice.
KATE: Yeah I do. I have a pool. JERRY: So put them to work.
KATE: And I'm just going to... AMY: Oh, Rosie!
KATE: I'm going to keep attacking. JERRY: Yeah we got the Rosie fans in the channel!
AMY: I guess she's really cool. KATE: She's got...
KATE: I mean she's not a berserker, she can't enter a berserker rage but if she could she'd be doing it now.
KATE: She's just angry at this point. KRIS: It's so polite.
JERRY: Bless your heart. KATE: That's a bless your heart kind of anger.
KATE: Okay so the then plus five is 15 to attack. Okay. JERRY: Yep.
JERRY: That connects. KATE: Great.
KATE: So then I'm going to do... AMY: Do work.
KATE: Oh yeah, ten plus... I'm going to use my bonus and a ki point for flurry of blows.
KATE: So... JERRY: So you're going to come at him twice?
KATE: Mmhmm. Two kicks. My signature move...
JERRY: (snorts) RYAN: Chop chop.
KRIS: Mmhmm! KATE: So that's a 17...
JERRY &amp; KRIS: Mmhmm!
KRIS: Mmhmm! KATE: Which gives me another six...
KATE: And... a 13. AMY: Oof, you almost had it.
KRIS: Yeah, almost had it. KATE: 13? AC? &gt;&gt; JERRY: Yeah!
KATE: That's a hit? Okay, good. JERRY: Yeah. Jeez, Rosie.
KATE: And that's a 4.
RYAN: Wow. JERRY: All right. So this is what it looks like.
AMY: Granny came to play! RYAN: Yeah, seriously.
JERRY: This is what it looks like. The first strike just goes into its gullet.
And she uses that to lever it and flip it up behind and then there are two kicks behind her in midair.
It crashes through the railing and hits the ground and becomes a pool.
RYAN: Okay, and the other one's running away from you.
JERRY: No. They are they are dead! KRIS: No, they're obliterated.
RYAN: Oh! &gt;&gt; KRIS:  it also did the same thing. KATE: Yeah, no they're dead. They're out.
JERRY: No! There is a there is a slippery... RYAN: Oh. Thought they ran away.
JERRY: non-OSHA-approved stairway...
RYAN: Nice.
JERRY: on the way down.
RYAN: All right KATE: We're bleeding out. So...
RYAN: Uh... I say...
RYAN: "Nobody touch anything," I say, "I don't know if you guys noticed, but everything's alive."
JERRY: Yeah!
RYAN: All right... In the moment to breathe... KATE: As we're all covered in goo.
RYAN: I will-- since you're still a bear... I guess I'm the only one who has healing stuff.
So I'll have to lay on hands individually on you guys. What are you at?
KRIS: I'm at five. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Out of? KATE: Six.
KRIS: 21. KATE: Same.
KRIS: And she's at six out of 21, so... KATE: Yeah.
RYAN: All right.
KRIS: We're both not... super hot. &gt;&gt; RYAN: All right so... AMY: Who do you like better?
RYAN: I don't have enough.  KRIS: I was going to say, who's an asset to the team?
RYAN: Well I have 15 I can divvy amongst the both of you.
KATE: "Well I'm I'm quite old. It's my time."
AMY: Oh my god! KRIS: "But I want to die!"
AMY: That's true!  KATE: We can fight over who gets to die!
KRIS: "Don't take this from me, old woman!"
RYAN: I can give you eight and you seven. And then you both...
KATE: Oh yeah, that'd be great. KRIS: (sighs) Fine.
RYAN: I'd have to do them individually, but we're not in combat so it doesn't matter.
RYAN: So I'll do that. KRIS: Back from that sweet brink.
RYAN: And I'm out of healing points now. KATE: Okay great. &gt;&gt; JERRY: For now.
JERRY: So this is how it works. As you are healing them...
RYAN: Mhmm. Backrub.
JERRY: Yeah yeah yeah, it's the full... RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: This is... It's incredible.
KRIS: Yeah, not just laying on hands, but technique! JERRY: No, no, no. Like, this is Palms Plus.
EVERYONE: Mmm.
JERRY: This is a real-- it's *deep*.
AMY: Deep tissue.
JERRY: Deep tissue.
RYAN: And I say, "Remember when I bought you that drink, and remember when I gave you that money?"
KRIS: I'm weeping! &gt;&gt; AMY: All he does is give! RYAN: And I just, "All I do is give."
RYAN: (whispers) "All I do is give, guys." KATE: "Yeah." &gt;&gt; KRIS: "This feels so right! So right."
JERRY: As you're as you're doing this, the wall in front of the house... you can see the boards-- the slats of the
boards, "flip, flip, flip," and the door that you recognize from before is there.
RYAN: Hmm. KRIS: (sighs)
KATE: Your wife? Different door? JERRY: Ha! It could be!
KRIS: But the sweet memory! RYAN: I saunter over and I say, "Hey."
(laughing)
AMY: What's a good looking door like you-- RYAN: "What's a pretty door like you doing in a place like this?"
KRIS: "I'm newly widowed... Just wondering if you, uh..."
RYAN: Are we going to have to fight the room now, what's happening?
JERRY: You have-- but now you have PTSD.
RYAN: I know, and now I don't trust anything! JERRY: The D is for Door. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Yeah!
JERRY: Right? &gt;&gt; KRIS: Yeah. RYAN: Dis-door-der.
KATE: Got hurt by one door, you're never going to trust.
KRIS: Yeah. JERRY: Yeah, exactly.
JERRY: But there is a door. RYAN: Oh, someone else go first.
RYAN: I'll tell you that much! KATE: I'm not it. &gt;&gt; AMY: I-- Okay um...
KRIS: Just throw the bear through! RYAN: Yeah!
KRIS: Just press on it. KATE: Can you bite the door?
AMY: I go, (growling grunt) and I lumber towards the door. And I like...
RYAN: Keen Smell?
AMY: It's not going to help through a portal! RYAN: Smell it!
JERRY: Hey so you're still the bear... RYAN: See what you can smell.
JERRY: you're like (bear groans) AMY: Yeah! &gt;&gt; KATE: (laughing) Yeah!
AMY: Well, because I can't-- and for those that don't know,
I cannot now communicate with any of my party members.
JERRY: Human mouths. &gt;&gt; AMY: Yeah. KRIS: So, but let me clarify this
KRIS: As a bear, you do not possess even the language you once had?
AMY: Nope.
KRIS: Because I could telepath to you... AMY: I now have--
KRIS: but you have nothing.   JERRY: Telepathic is fine.
AMY: Telepathic is fine. That's to the discretion of the DM, and the DM wants to let me do it?
JERRY: So she has her mental stats. KRIS: Yes. Okay. &gt;&gt;  KATE: Nice.
JERRY: But she doesn't have a human mouth. RYAN: Mentats.
KRIS: "Ah... it hurts so bad, go through the door please."
RYAN: You're fine! KATE: Real useful message.
RYAN: I just gave you... KRIS: I could send that all day. I can talk to it all day!
KRIS: I don't get a one time. AMY: Bear. Hey, bear. Bear.
EVERYONE: Bear. Bear. Bear. Bear. JERRY: "Brbrbrbrbrbr"
AMY: All right, I want to, uh...
So wait is it like that black void thing again?
JERRY: It is. AMY: Okay, so I will...
AMY: lumber on through. But like, you know, I'm ready.
AMY: I'm ready for whatever's on the other side. JERRY: You go through like (growl)
KRIS: I was going to say--
AMY: I'd be like, "I'll mess up all the doors!" But not saying anything.
KRIS: The mass of a gilded acorn is removed from your body.
JERRY:  Yeah. Exactly.
AMY: (yelps)
KRIS: And it turns out gold is a dense metal.
JERRY: A delicious part... KRIS: So you lose...
JERRY: A delicious part of you. The most delicious part. KRIS: Just your heart is gone.
RYAN: Sweetbreads.   JERRY: No, just one valve! &gt;&gt; KRIS: Yeah!
AMY: Gross! &gt;&gt; JERRY: Just one valve.  KRIS: The rest of you is good.
AMY: But what really happens?
JERRY: No, you're fine. As soon the bear head pokes through, the rest of her disappears.
RYAN: Snaps shut. KATE: Rosie's a little worried.
JERRY: Yeah, it just closes. She's viciously sectioned.
RYAN: And then the bear head goes into a new room and it's shown mounted on a wall.
KRIS: Right it's just a portal to a bear capture device. RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: That is not...! &gt;&gt; KRIS: Auto-mount. Yeah. AMY: That was the puzzle.
AMY: We need to feed it a bear. JERRY: Everybody else won.
KRIS: Now we all get 33%. RYAN: We had to trick her into becoming a bear!
(laughing) KRIS: (claps)
KRIS: He hates bears. Who knew? RYAN: Yeah.
KATE: I'm going to go last because I'm worried that we're going to enter the same time loop
and have to fight that damn door again. So I'm going to keep an eye on things from--
RYAN: No one's going last other than me, when it comes to doors anymore, all right?
KATE: All right, we can hold hands and go through together.
JERRY: There's a goddamn system!
RYAN: Yeah!
JERRY: Absolutely. So you pop through. You don't like it. It's like as you're walking through, you're looking over at
the door on the hinge and you're like, "I'm onto you."
You see those hinges, even the hinge...even the squeak of the hinge is terror. But you pass through. You enter a
a dark room, but there is an arc of light in front of you.
AMY: Does it say, "Congratulations, you did it!"?
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, yeah. There's a big banner, and there's a--
RYAN: There's a cake. JERRY: And there's a cake.
AMY: And my family's there. JERRY: No!
AMY: Oh, okay.
RYAN: Dad! KATE: Aww.
RYAN: They're telling me they're proud of me.
RYAN: I'm playing baseball and they're watching.  KRIS: Yeah. &gt;&gt; AMY: Okay.
AMY: So I see an arc of light. JERRY: You do. You see an arc of light.
JERRY: Sort of-- it looks a rough-hewn around the edge, but from here that's what you can see.
AMY: Okay. Um.
So, I like scratch at the wall as if like, "Hey, guys. This is the signal, like come through."
JERRY &amp; KATE: Yeah. KRIS: We're all going to go now...
AMY: Okay we're all over. KRIS: I think we're cool, yeah.
JERRY: They've committed. &gt;&gt; AMY: Oh! JERRY: They have committed already.
KATE: We don't have... AMY: They're all here!
JERRY: Yeah, exactly. AMY: Then I'm just going to be at the ready.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. It's a musty scent here in this dark corner that you've emerged into. The arc itself, as I said,
looks sort of like rough-hewn stone? But the closer you get to it, I mean even in your bear guise, you know
exactly what it is. Two things. One, you smell prey. You *smell* prey.
AMY: Keen Smell. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Nice. JERRY: And it requires your...
JERRY: It requires your elven intellect to tamp down that desire.
It smells like a nest of some kind.
And this arch is not worked stone at all. You can actually see that it's gnawed.
The entire arc of it around is gnawed wood, up into a sort of portal-- Not of the mystical variety, obviously.
AMY: Right. JERRY: Or the video game variety.
AMY: Right.
JERRY: But then you can see out there it's just a vast expanse.
AMY: Oh my god, well I'm like completely tantalized by this.
JERRY: Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. There is something delicious.
KATE: Is the deliciousness through that portal?
JERRY: You would not describe it as delicious. You would describe it as smelling primarily like musk and
urine. It's not, you do not...
KRIS: So I'm-- so I start salivating.
JERRY: This does not turn your crank. This is not something grandmothers...
This is like "One Trick that Grandmothers Hate."
KATE: One Weird Trick. &gt;&gt; AMY: One Weird Trick. JERRY: One Weird Trick. &gt;&gt; KATE: Yeah, okay.
JERRY: Coat things in urine. Right?
KATE: Yeah we do hate that. JERRY: So obviously-- and you're getting wild.
JERRY: You're like, "More filth!" RYAN: Something to eat?
KRIS: Yeah, I'm fiending, I'm-- The bear's got to hold me back!
JERRY: Let's continue to absorb it!
Donaar.
RYAN: Um...
RYAN: Urine front? AMY: Mmhmm.
RYAN: I'll just follow behind you. KATE: I heard it.
JERRY: Smooth. KATE: Yeah. Yeah, it's good.
AMY: I'mma keep going. What's this? JERRY: Absolutely.
JERRY: So this, the expanse out here, as I said is massive. Vast. It looks like an immense plain, and the
ground recalls desert ground that is baked after a rain.
AMY: Okay. JERRY: There are long furrows.
JERRY: The difference between this and the desert ground is that they're all completely uniform.
These furrows in the ground go out in sort of great rectangles out as far as you can see.
But they're deep. I mean they would need to be stepped over in a pronounced way.
They're not-- It's not obvious, it's not safe to travel around on these.
They need to be jumped over individually.
AMY: Okay, well then I'm going to release myself from this bear-prison I'm in.
JERRY: (laughs)
AMY: Transform back into the Walnut you all know and love.
JERRY: Yeah, the Classic Walnut. Walnut Classic! AMY: Classic! Classic Walnut.
JERRY: Walnut Classic. KATE: There's no nothing wrong with Classic Walnut.
JERRY: Absolutely.
But this is-- I mean you are an expert in natural environments.
AMY: I am. JERRY: Surviving.
JERRY: You have-- as a basic obvious capacity for Walnut, you can feed five people.
AMY: I was just about to say. JERRY: Straight out of your wisdom and knowledge.
JERRY: You think you would have to customize your approach to this place.
There's a lot about it that does not mirror the natural world.
KATE: What's the sky look like?
JERRY: I'm so glad that you asked.
You are an expert, obviously, we've gone over it.
You have a uncanny capacity for identifying star patterns.
You always, obsessively-- and there's a reason for it, right?
You obsessively know where you are at all times. And you always know how to get home.
There is only one constellation in the sky.
And that is the Homeward Star.
KATE: And based on that constellation. What is it telling me as far as my orientation to my home?
JERRY: The star that is at the point is blinking weakly.
KATE: Does it usually blink? Or is that unusual? JERRY: No.
JERRY: That is quite unusual. KATE: Okay.
KATE: Okay.
KATE: Hmm... AMY: (laughs)
JERRY: But you should be able to orient.
JERRY: You should be able to orient the party from that. KATE: Great. I can do that.
KATE: So based on the orientation of that constellation, am I inclined to go through the portal?
JERRY: Through this gateway? &gt;&gt; KATE: Mmhmm. JERRY: Absolutely.
JERRY: My presumption is that you've already moved somewhat past that to examine this space.
KATE: Okay... okay... So we are in the portal, we're in this new space.
JERRY: You've passed through this new doorway. KATE: All we see are the desert furrows--
KATE: and this particular constellation?
JERRY: Exactly. In the distance you can see what you assume are trunks of trees, canopies of various kinds...
But this is a bizarre natural environment, like I said.
KATE: Okay. I can-- so I will route us. I explain to you guys--
JERRY: So do you want to collaborate with Walnut? KATE: Sure. Yeah.
KATE: Yeah! So, I know star stuff. That star is acting whack.
And I think I know exactly where we need to go, based on it.
AMY: Well I trust you.
KATE: Can you get us safely through this environment with these two treasured companions of ours?
AMY: Yes, I will do my best.
KATE: We're going to go... this way! AMY: Don't want to disappoint.
RYAN: Am I still bark?:
JERRY &amp; AMY: (whispers) No. KRIS: Oh, no.
JERRY: It was a phase! RYAN: Oh, phew!
JERRY: Right? It was just like your second album!
You were trying bark!
AMY: Don't worry my bark's worse than my bite.
JERRY: (wheezing laugh) KATE: Oh my gosh!
RYAN: We got there everyone, we did it. Streams over! KATE: Beautiful. Yep.
RYAN: Thanks everyone! Goodnight! This was great. Thanks everyone.
JERRY: No we're hanging it up.
JERRY: All right, no! KATE: And the party wipes!
JERRY: No, exactly-- no, we're fine. RYAN: You get swallowed in a dune. The end.
JERRY: So like I say. You're able to guide the party over these furrows.
AMY: Okay.
JERRY: But it is at about this point that you're starting to get hungry and thirsty.
AMY: Mmm okay. Okay...
Well I can enable five companions to live off the land, but you said I would have maybe trouble doing that?
AMY: Can I roll to see if that's possible? JERRY: Absolutely. Absolutely.
JERRY: You have a mystic dice if you'd like to employ it, but you can also hold onto it.
AMY: I mean..
I don't know, I feel like Walnut would be-- wouldn't want to be distrustful of nature
AMY: like not giving her what she wants?   JERRY: Yeah. I like it. I like it. &gt;&gt; KRIS: Wow.
AMY: I don't think that this-- KRIS: That's RP!
JERRY: That's 100%. AMY: That's deep roleplaying.
JERRY: Yeah exactly!  AMY: All right, so would this be like a survial?
JERRY: Yep exactly. AMY: Okay.
AMY: Big money.
(groans)
Uh... 12.
Well we said we'd have trouble!
JERRY: Exactly! I was going to say. You're not able to 100% map it.
You feel like you may have to travel for a bit and get a better sense of this environment.
KRIS: I ask-- and I say, "I don't want to be rude."
"So I don't know the ways of the druid. But we all-- I think we're all getting a little bit hungry."
"Is it possible to assume bear form, let us cleave off a little bit of that meat. grill it up."
"And then, but not take you to zero health, and then you just come on back to regular Walnut stance."
KRIS: "We just eat some of those bear cuts." KATE: Bear steak.
RYAN: I think that's tough but fair. I weigh in, "Tough but bear."
JERRY: (snorts and laughs)
KRIS: "I don't know if that's like, if you get asked that a lot. So I mean I apologize…"
KATE: Rosie is very... RYAN: Is that rude to ask?
AMY: "Your drow humor is strange to me."
KATE: I'm going to say that's a no.
JERRY: Could be a no.
RYAN: So we die of starvation then? That's your answer? Just so I'm clear? Okay.
AMY: I mean how dire is it?
JERRY: Yeah, it's not quite there yet.
RYAN: So are you going to turn into a wolf? No? Like is this your setup?
AMY: Bury the lede! They don't know what my forms are!
KRIS: Bear-y...
KATE: I have-- RYAN: Bear-y! She's going to turn into a...?
KATE: All I have to offer is a bag of sand.
But I offer it anyway just in case anyone's gotten to that point of hunger.
JERRY: To eat sand. KATE: Yeah.
KATE: It's all I have but I really don't like-- I'm a grandmother. I don't like it when people are going
hungry. I want to offer anything I've got and it's all I've got. I also have paper.
RYAN: I have toothbrush.
KATE: You brought a toothbrush?
RYAN: Yeah I bring a toothbrush everywhere. KATE: Wow.
KRIS: I guess that's smart.
RYAN: Yeah I got a toothbrush and floss. AMY: Oh my...
KATE: I'm a nasty granny. I didn't bring a toothbrush. JERRY: And floss? &gt;&gt; AMY: Toothbrush and floss.
RYAN: I got acid breath, all right! And I got to keep-- take care of them pearly whites!
JERRY: I got to maintain it.
RYAN: Don't neglect your gums, are you crazy? KATE: That's why that dragonborn lady was after you.
RYAN: If you could spit acid you'd be brushing your teeth all the time.
RYAN: Don't judge me! KATE: You can spit acid?
RYAN: I just met you people! Don't judge me!
JERRY: Just even while you're talking to people. It's just... listen...
RYAN: In fact now that we got a little downtime, I pull that bad boy out.
JERRY: You're going to get use to this, it's fine.
RYAN: I call my toothbrush Percival.
RYAN: I go (brushing noises), "Me and you, Percival. Forget these three."
KRIS: Back at work, Percy.
KATE: So you have almost married a door and you're obsessively brushing your teeth.
JERRY: So Walnut your hope is that if you get near-- AMY: That's what I'm saying.
JERRY: one of these trunks.
JERRY: Some of this canopy. AMY: Scrape out some bugs.
JERRY: You may be able to find something going on down there.
AMY: I feel a lot of social pressure to provide...
KATE: Yeah! AMY: for these people that I'm with.
AMY: Okay so can we travel a little bit more. Can I try again?
JERRY: Absolutely, yeah, yeah! I'd love to see some of that survival.
AMY: And now Walnut feels betrayed...
AMY: by the natural world. JERRY: By the natures?
AMY: Looks up and just whispers... Iike... uh... you know... I want to use one of my mystical dice, basically.
KRIS: Come on! Come on plants!
AMY: "Please. Please, I have always been your champion. Give me something!"
JERRY: "I druid nonstop. I'm always doing it."
AMY: 100% on my grind. Everyday. Everyday!
AMY: One's a 15. Hang on.
And another one's a 15. So 20.
JERRY: 20? Oh that's marvelous. You guide the party toward...
AMY: Pizza.
JERRY: These structures. RYAN: (laughs) Pizza tree.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. To a food truck. KRIS: Hot n' Ready. Little Caesars. Oh boy.
JERRY: They got the square pizza. They got the bread sticks!
No! That doesn't exist yet! That hasn't been invented and it won't be invented for several thousand years.
So... I'm sorry. That's how it is.
Your guess is that if you can sort of approach this loose copse over here,
you'll be able to provide something for them but you don't actually know.
JERRY: Right, you're trying to-- AMY: Best guess?
JERRY: Yeah exactly you're trying to apply your knowledge of this space to this.
And as you approach it, these... are not trees.
Like the closer you get to them, there's no--
AMY: I feel very betrayed!
JERRY: There's no bark of any kind that surrounds them. They are wood! But they are not bark in any case.
Near the base of them, though. This is the strange thing.
JERRY: Near the base of them-- AMY: This is the strange thing.
JERRY: Yeah exactly, this is actually the weirdest part.
Umm... are...
How do I even describe this?
JERRY: They are-- AMY: That's how you know it's bad.
JERRY: No, no, no.
Maybe... basketball sized...
hunks of crusty bread.
KATE: Take it. AMY: Hmm.
KRIS: Hmm!
AMY: Wow! KATE: Do they smell good?
AMY: I just want to like-- JERRY: It's not new, but you could definitely eat it.
AMY: Having a flashback to when I said,
"Do I need to make a card for Purify Food and Water? I never will use that ever!"
RYAN: I did the same thing, I passed on it.
AMY: I said, "That's stupid who care's about eating?" KRIS: Is this-- are these at the base of every tree?
JERRY: Yeah! Yeah, yeah! Near the-- KRIS: Or every tree-like object.
JERRY: Yeah, exactly! Exactly! KRIS: Huh.
KATE: Okay so they're not new. I am proficient in history. Can I determine how old they are?
AMY: Is that a history check?
JERRY: No! Culinary history? Food Network? RYAN: Can I intimidate?
JERRY: No. I would love to get some perception rolls from the party please.
RYAN: My perception ain't great. AMY: I want to perceive!
AMY: 20! JERRY: Jeez!
KRIS: Yeah that one beats all. I was going to say 16.
JERRY: Yeah! what's this? It's garbage! RYAN: 13.
(laughter)
JERRY: It's filth! So, here's the thing. So your ears perk up. Your elven ears perk up instantaneously.
What's more! At the 20 you're not even surprised by what it is. You know exactly what it is.
It is the sound of claws on wood.
And then edging out from behind these tall wooden pillars...
you can see...
what appear to be gigantic mice.
(chuckling)
RYAN: You love those. AMY: I told you!
AMY: It was nothing but mice! (laughs) KATE: She did tell us.
AMY: Okay gigantic mice. Like how big? For like..
AMY: I mean like bear size? Or car size? Or bus size? KRIS: Like classical "gigantic"?
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, yeah. I would say like a bear. AMY: Godzilla size? Okay.
KRIS: Big mouse. RYAN: That is a big mouse.
AMY: Okay so how far off? RYAN: I wonder...
JERRY: From here they're maybe 50 feet... 50 to 60 feet away. There are several of them that you can hear.
Because it was a 20 I'm going to say this is information that you got.
And you can see right now it's like--
Your sense is that they're not hostile but you can't imagine what you must look like.
KATE: Yeah so Rosie will lean over... AMY: Mmhmm. Okay so I'm pointing this out.
KATE:  Yeah, yeah. I'm going to say, "Tell them I said, 'What's up?'"
AMY: I go, "I can only do that once per day."
KATE: "Ah we need a short rest.
AMY: "It's not unlimited." KATE: Oh okay.
AMY: I can tell these creatures that we mean them no harm. Or I can attempt to if they're not so smart.
AMY: But do we want to risk going that close? JERRY: How would you do it?
JERRY: How would you do that, roleplayer?
AMY: With Animal Friendship but I would have to approach by 20 feet and signal to them...
JERRY: Interesting!
AMY: It is a beast. KRIS: And do a classic-- like a mouse...
AMY: "Whoa! Whoa, girl!" KRIS: gesture!
JERRY: Do the classic-- do the classic mouse...
KRIS: You got to get up high like that. AMY: Walnut, Tamer of Mice.
JERRY: The classic mouse sign of friendship. AMY: All right,  let me try it.
KATE: Yeah because I want to get on that bread.
AMY: So I want to intervene for the party so they can grab at that bread.
And I want to get within 30 feet of these mice.
AMY: It must see and hear me. JERRY: Do you have bread with you?
AMY: Do I have bread with me?
JERRY: Yeah I want to make sure I understand who's got what, where they are--
AMY: I do not have any food items on me when I approach these gigantic beasts.
KRIS: Same.
AMY: I'm in my cheese suit-- No!
(laughter)
JERRY: Head to toe. It's come in handy! AMY: Head to toe.
AMY: Chedder! So if the intelligence is less than--
KRIS: Your Fro-mage Armor.
(laughter)
KATE: She's trying to do a-- &gt;&gt; AMY: I hate it! JERRY: You're a monster!
AMY: It was good enough to sneak in. It's okay to interrupt me for those good jokes.
KRIS: I'm sorry.
AMY: If the beast's intelligence is four or higher the spell fails.
Otherwise it must succeed on an wisdom saving throw or be charmed by you.
But if one of you guys hurt it the spell ends. Please don't.
KATE: Okay
JERRY: So you're going to try it?
AMY: Try it, yes. JERRY: Okay.
AMY: So is it... is it real smart?
JERRY: No. It's a mouse. AMY: Okay. Well I didn't know if this was like some like--
AMY: psionic... ability...
JERRY: Mage rats!
AMY: I don't know! It's D&amp;D!
KRIS: It rises up on its two-- AMY: Big mouse, big brain, right?
KATE: It's just a mouse. AMY: Okay, so I want to...
AMY: All right now that I've convinced it, you know like, steadying the beast!
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, exactly.
AMY: We mean you no harm. We are simply here to get nourishment and pass through.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. You see a couple more mice peeking out.
AMY: "Get the bread guys!"
"It is imperative that you now get your food and we be on our way."
KATE: Rosie suddenly realizes we're in a Honey, I Shrunk The Kids situation.
KRIS: Yeah. &gt;&gt; KATE: Okay. AMY: And with no Antie.
KRIS: I was taking a break to see when it was appropriate to interrupt with that.
But I'm that glad more than one person came to this.
KATE: I see, I see. Wonderful. Okay! So you said, "What's up?" to the mouse?
AMY: I said, "What's up?" to the mice and I look at over my shoulder at you and say,
"Please get your food so we can continue."
KATE: Okay I'm going to run in there, grab as much bread as I can,
but also tear half of it off and throw it to the mice.
KATE: And run back. AMY: Great. Aggro the mice.
JERRY: Yeah! &gt;&gt; AMY: Thank you. KATE: They love bread!
JERRY: They're into it.
KRIS: It's bread! RYAN: Hey don't fill up on it though!
JERRY: Optimally you don't fill up on the bread. RYAN: Don't fill up on bread.
JERRY: So you grab that hunk. And you sort of underhand it out into the area.
Three mice go for the same piece.
KATE: Mmhmm. AMY: Oh no.
AMY: Do not feed the animals!
KATE: Maybe you all could go get some and help me--
KATE: and put some crumbs out there.  RYAN: I am lumbering and slow.
KRIS: Are you really? Oh yeah you took a little less speed. All right I'll run through as best as I can.
As far from the mice as I can. And I'll get a crumb.
AMY: A basketball sized crumb. KRIS: It's like this! &gt;&gt; JERRY: Yeah. This big.
KATE: It's like this? &gt;&gt; KRIS: Yeah. JERRY: There is this process of her...
JERRY: maintaining the diplomacy with the mice. KATE &amp; KRIS: Jurassic World!
JERRY: Maintaining mouse diplomacy. AMY: Very cool!
JERRY: While you guys are cycling back and forth grabbing as many crumbs.
JERRY: Watching a dwindling supply-- AMY: Much like mice.
JERRY: Watching a dwindling supply of their own food.
You've pitched it out and then...
ultimately, once they have been satisfied, the largest of the mice comes over to you, Walnut,
and just gives you the maximum sniff.
AMY: I stand tall and remain calm. JERRY: Maximum sniff.
AMY: Very calm. JERRY: These whiskers... they're all over.
JERRY: This situation is very tickley.
KRIS: It's like Percival.
JERRY: It's dry!
RYAN: That's my toothbrush! KRIS: Toothbrush. I remember.
AMY: Okay it isn't a wet sniff. JERRY: This is not a wet sniff.
JERRY: The nose very cold.
At this point after this sniff is thoroughly sniffed,
when he leaves, the rest leave with him.
You're thinking it might be time for something along the lines of a long rest.
AMY: Okay. JERRY: It might be time to get your bearings.
JERRY: Try to get some food together. Put together a fire situation.
KATE: We feel like the mice are cool with us being here?
AMY: I feel that they're okay. KRIS: It's a test!
JERRY: Your read is good. KATE: Okay.
AMY: I think we should make camp here. RYAN: Make camp?
KRIS: I think we should make camp further from the rug.
(laughter)
Not in sight of a rug in the establishment.
KATE: Let's do it here where the solid floor. KRIS: Yeah.
KATE: Is there a mouse hole that we can go into? Can we follow them into like a cave?
RYAN: No, I don't want to do that. AMY: I can't talk to them yet.
RYAN: Never follow a mouse to a second location. That's rule number one.
(laughing)
JERRY: Is that mice wisdom? RYAN: Oh yeah.
KRIS: Oh yeah. JERRY: Exactly. Big book of mice wisdom. All right!
JERRY: So yeah. It's a situation where you're thinking with your survival approach
that you should be able to shave off hunks of these pillars
and try to build yourself a small fire underneath this canopy.
Which you now tihnk is probably not a canopy at all.
AMY: All right. Okay. RYAN: We're super tiny.
AMY: So I guess we got to get to sir with the greatsword.
Can we shave off some stuff? Get a fire going. You want to help me?
RYAN: Uh... Yeah I got a big old sword.   AMY: Come on, big guy.
JERRY: It's going to take some doing. RYAN: Yeah, I can do that.
KRIS: Is this hemp rug? By chance?
KATE: This table legs? I tihnk those are table legs. KRIS: Okay, that's possible. Yeah.
JERRY: You got it. All right. So!
AMY: Oh my god! And the lighbulb comes on!
Kris: Finally. AMY: It was like phew phew phew! The whole itme!
JERRY: So this is how it goes: you're able to, with the edge of it, shave of slivers.
Enough slivers of wood for you to build a fire. Put it together.
There's enough bits of cheese and meat and bread that have collected down in these furrows.
KRIS: Charcuterie. Filthy. JERRY: For you to go to work!
JERRY: Right? AMY: You love it!
JERRY: It's like this, so long rest. You regain your hit points.
KATE: Yes! Phew.
AMY: And all your spells. I mean I only needed a short rest.
JERRY: No. RYAN: Yeah no, I didn't got all my spells.
KATE: Rosie gives all her cheese and meat to Donaar.
RYAN: Aww. No you don't have to do that.    KATE: She's a monk, it's bread and water.
RYAN:I insist! KATE: Ah you know. I'm 120. I weigh 28 pounds.
KATE: I'm all about the bread and water. It's fine.
JERRY: About halfway through the night...
AMY: Uh oh.
RYAN: Ugh.
JERRY: No, it's okay. It's all right.
AMY: Ah... We didn't do watch. JERRY: Exactly.
JERRY: Everyone else is resting. It's your turn.
KRIS: Oh wait a minute, hold on though. Halfway through the night, I only am in a trance.
JERRY: It takes four hours for you?
KRIS: It's four hours, yeah. AMY: Same.
JERRY: Yep, yep. &gt;&gt; KRIS: Okay. AMY: Elfs. (raspberry)
JERRY: High five on that. &gt;&gt; AMY: Yeah, well... KRIS: I'll take second trance.
KRIS: You take first, I'll take second. JERRY: Smooth. Perfect.
JERRY: So there's a period there in the middle where you're both awake. You just pass each other.
JERRY: I'm done! AMY: Ships in the night.
JERRY: But Donaar I would like to get a perception roll from you.
RYAN: (groans) My perception sucks. JERRY: That's great! I'm glad it does.
KRIS: You're sleeping. RYAN: 14!
RYAN: 14. I get nothing on wisdom. JERRY: You get no juice?
RYAN: No. I'm flat. So just 14.
JERRY: It's not as much of a sound as just as a sense.
Just a dull vibration that you can feel sort of in the panels of the ground.
You're not able to place it. And you're not able to identify the source of it.
RYAN: Am I the only one who feels it?
JERRY: Yeah at this point. RYAN: Okay.
JERRY: The morning occurs.
You can see light coming through the shafts of what you now realize are the windows.
The celestial configuration of the chandelier, still useful, still directing.
But you know that it might be more than a day at this scale to get to where you're trying to go.
JERRY: It is at this point when you guys are collecting your gear and putting your equipment back together,
that another diplomatic group of mice...
(laughter)
JERRY: approach the group. AMY: And I'm ready for them.
AMY: So I look at these mice and I use Speak with Animals.
JERRY: Speak with Animals?
AMY: You say, surprised!
JERRY: What's that? What's that, Walnut Dankgrass!
AMY: So anyway. I got another ten minutes with these mice and I say...
JERRY: They come up and it's all noses.  Except this time all four of them come up--
AMY: And I'm sniffing back. JERRY: Direct nose contact.
JERRY: Exactly right. AMY: Ah four of them.
AMY: And I say to them-- I say,
"Good mice friends. Thank you for letting us stay in your realm."
"My companions and I are trying to make it through. I was wondering if you could--"
JERRY: Before you finish your sentence...
there's a moment where you realize that the largest mouse that you saw is not there anymore.
And the one that rubbed noses last says, "Our queen is dead."
AMY: And I look back and I go, "Ah..."
JERRY: "We have stories of far mice."
"Mice from the hole that come through from time to time and help us with great tasks."
AMY: Mmhmm.
Oh!
"We are your far mice... today."
JERRY: Yeah and he looks like, "I fucking told you these were far mice."
AMY: And then I look back at these guys, I'm like, "We got a mouse quest situation."
JERRY: Situation we got to fucking deal with!
AMY: I go, "But I think we can curry favor with these mice if we do them their small task."
"How much could it be?"
RYAN: Can we ride them? &gt;&gt; KATE: They're mice. AMY: Maybe after we help them.
AMY: Oh actually, I say, "Mice, of course we're here to help you. We are far mice."
"Can you take us to the problem so that we might help you?"
JERRY: "The problem may come to us."
AMY: "What-- Did you see what killed your queen?"
JERRY: "What *ate* our queen."
KATE: Your old friend.
AMY: We don't know that! We don't know that!
KRIS: I think you might know that. KATE: I think we might know. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Yeah.
KRIS: We seem to know that here. KATE: We all know it. Walnut's in denial.
JERRY: Yeah yeah. And then the whispers from the other mice--
behind the one that you're having the parlay with-- say, (whispers) "Onyx. Onyx."
KATE: (gasps)
AMY: Hmm. So I have a sinking feeling. But I say...
"Well..."
God!
AMY: Um... (laughter)
I don't know what I say!
Walnut's like, (sucks in breath) "Oh...!"
(everyone makes nervous noises)
KATE: Do you want to like life line to us? Like let us know what's going on?
AMY: Yeah I go, "Let me speak to my companions." JERRY: Hey listen, I know some people.
KATE: Talk to the other far mice. AMY: "The other far mice. Hold. hold please."
AMY: And I look back and I say, "So... I don't know if you would remember but,"
"I met the acquaintance of a cat."
KATE: Rosie is way into it. "Yes, I remember."
KRIS: "We've been in this room for like two days now. I remember everything!"
RYAN: "I'll never, ever forget this."
JERRY: It's not possible.
RYAN: "You're talking about the cat who delivered the identical mice you stared at for 25 minutes?"
AMY: "Right, right, right." RYAN: "Yeah I remember that."
AMY: "I believe that that is their queen." KRIS: "Yeah it kind of stayed with me."
KATE: "The dead mouse that Onyx was killing?" AMY: "I believe that was their queen."
RYAN: "Twice."
AMY: "Listen it doesn't matter how many times! It just happened! Whatever happened it happened!"
"And I think we can get these mice to help carry us but we... I don't know."
KATE: "It sounds like they want us to kill Onyx."
RYAN: "Does every franchisee have to go through this?" AMY: "Is this just hazing?"
RYAN: "Yeah what did we do wrong? What did we do to make them so mad?"
KATE: Hey! Consider this! Consider that the nuts, the acorns were sent by these mice..."
That they're the ones who summoned us.
JERRY: Yeah the Acquisitions Incorporated-- KATE: This is the job, ladies and gentlemen!
JERRY: Acquisitions Incorporated is operated-- owned and operated by mice!
RYAN: By mice people behind the scenes. Holy shit. AMY: That was the secret purpose. It's been revealed.
AMY: "Well I don't feel comfortable murdering a cat that I've become friends with."
KRIS: "So your going to sit this one--" RYAN: "I murdered a door that I became 'friends' with."
(laughing)
AMY: Uh... RYAN: My betrothed!
(laughter)
JERRY: I interacted with a door in a way unbecoming a gentleman!
AMY: "If we can get the cat here now, I could talk to him. But it would have to be now. We have to act quickly."
KRIS: "All right we'll just act delicious then."
RYAN: Yeah I was going to say, "Look tasty?" KRIS: "She's just going to come around."
KATE: Yeah. JERRY: You had a suggestion about riding, is that..?
RYAN: Oh... Yeah. KATE: Can they carry us to where Onyx hangs out?
KRIS: Yeah bring us closer, or are they willing?
AMY: Yeah or hear me out. Just an alternate idea.
AMY: We tell them-- JERRY: This is the sequel.
AMY: their queen is gone they must find another queen. If they come with us-- also maybe we're riding them.
KRIS: Wow. You're just going to lie to them. RYAN: Wow.
KRIS: Instead of kill a cat you're just going to lie to them. RYAN: Are you going to offer to be queen of the mice?
KRIS: The queen's actually fine! AMY: I didn't use Animal Friendship!
AMY: I used Speak with Animals! I don't owe them anything.
KATE: Yeah! that's right! Let's lie to these mice! AMY: They could be magic mice!
RYAN: I got no problem lying to a mouse. KATE: It's fine.
KRIS: Honestly, I don't either. Lie to the mouse. Kill the cat. I'm game.
JERRY: That's not against my personal morality. KRIS: Anything we need to do.
KATE: Yeah, what if we tell them that Onyx hangs out at the door. Ride them there. And then so long, suckers!
AMY: Oh, well no I didn't mean that. KATE: Peace out. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Yeah.
AMY: I mean their best chance of survival is getting away from the cat and finding a new queen.
JERRY: I'm having the best time! RYAN: Who cares?
JERRY: This is what I wanted! RYAN: These are mice! It's not Steven Hawking!
AMY: I'm a druid!
KRIS: You don't deserve to be a franchisee-- Okay...!
RYAN: Yeah! You know what? I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
JERRY: Okay, all right. It got heated Let's table this for now.
RYAN: Yeah. KRIS: Sorry.
AMY: Okay. All right I just want to see how the mice feel about this. I look back at the mice and I go,
"Your queen is dead. It is no longer safe for you here."
JERRY: You just see their-- You just see... just a wave of fur like just back-- like they just react to that.
Just physically you just see it roll over their backs.
They're just looking at each other like, "These are the far mice? Really?"
KATE: Uh oh.
JERRY: No, no. Do your shit. I'm just giving you information.
AMY: No, no. I know. RYAN: All right.
AMY: "If you wish to seek a new home, and a new queen, and a new--" What do mice live in? "Hole."
JERRY: Fucking mouse shit. AMY: Whatever.
AMY: "We can guide-- We can give you safe passage if you come with us to the far lands over there."
JERRY: Yeah. Yeah. KATE: And carry us on your backs.
JERRY: They chatter. I mean they all sort of chitter to each other. It's like,
"Well the last far mice went back on their promise."
RYAN: So will we!
JERRY: You got some persuade?
JERRY: Let's see what we're talking about. KATE: Mouse liars. &gt;&gt; AMY: I... really...
RYAN: I say, (whisper) "We won't do that. (loudly) Yes we will."
"Oh, I said the loud part quiet, and the quiet part loud."
KATE: The mice can't talk to us! RYAN: Yeah I know. I can insult them to their face.
AMY: Walnut genuinely wants to-- JERRY: Make your case and let's see how it goes, right?
JERRY: I mean you got... you got time.
AMY: Oh man, I would love if someone could just like, I don't know, like guide me here.
JERRY: Well here-- We can have-- He can-- He's got sick charisma.
AMY: Okay. RYAN: I can't talk to mice.
JERRY: No but you can try to cut a deal. You can try to...
RYAN: I can say, but use you as the proxy. Be like here's what...
KATE: Say it just like this. RYAN: Yeah here's what you say.
RYAN: I've got to be your Cyrano de-- AMY: Cyrano de Bergerac.
RYAN: Cyrano de Mice! Cyrano de Whiskers. JERRY: You all occupy some position in their culture.
JERRY: This is weird stuff.  You know what I mean?
JERRY: But, you're welcome to-- AMY: Sure...
JERRY: but you can confer with your friend, your ally. RYAN, KATE &amp; KRIS: Yeah.
AMY: "Friends" is... "Friends" is... RYAN: Yeah. "Friends." We just met.
KRIS: Do you have Guidance? If you want Guidance I also have Guidance.
RYAN: Yeah.
KATE: I can also do somebody. KRIS: If you just want to go rogue, again.
RYAN: I can Intimidate. KATE: I'm terrifying.
AMY: If you've got good charisma, let's go for it.   JERRY: Yeah, yeah.
RYAN: I have good charisma. JERRY: Go ahead and just--
RYAN: What's our sticking point here?
JERRY: Just build the case, you're just trying to build--
KRIS: You got to convince the mice. JERRY: Build rapport with the mice.
JERRY: And then you'll roll Guidance? KRIS: Yeah.
JERRY: So roll a d4.
KRIS: Yeah let me give you some of that.
KRIS: Where's the color... It's black! JERRY: It's the evil pyramid.
KRIS: Tough to see. RYAN: We got one minute. &gt;&gt; AMY: It's okay.
KRIS: It's a trash roll.
JERRY: It's a one. All right. KRIS: You're going to enjoy a one.
AMY: Okay. RYAN: What am I rolling?
KRIS: A very confident one. AMY: You're rolling your--
JERRY: You don't have to roll but you need to tell me if you want to help her.
You need to tell me what you're conferring to her.
RYAN: All right. I will use my charisma and knowledge of mice abounds. So you talk to the mice and you said...
You made the case that their queen was gone and they didn't like that.
KRIS: That case doesn't need to be made.
RYAN: And they're not down with taking us across to the far lands?
JERRY: We don't know. She's trying to make the case. AMY: They're worried...
AMY: They're worried that we're going to go back on their promise, and I have to tell you...
I do feel obligated to help them in some way, and part of me does feel like this is a way to help.
RYAN: All right. Maybe you should go to Kris first because all I want to do is lie to them.
JERRY: No, no, no. Lies are good. Guidance is going to help on the roll.
You communicate it to her and she'll do the roll.
JERRY: What's the case? KRIS: You don't...
KRIS: Oh okay. If you're still working, all right. KATE: Let's hear the pitch.
RYAN: Ah I thought that was a good pitch before. KRIS: Let me jump in there.
KRIS: You don't want to kill this cat. RYAN: Yeah.
AMY: I don't want to kill the cat. KRIS: How do you feel about--
KRIS: driving it irretrievably insane?
(laughing)
KRIS: It's still a cat. AMY: Well, it's a cat. &gt;&gt; RYAN: I like that.
KRIS: Still lives. RYAN: Still breathing.
RYAN: How do you feel about lobotomies?
AMY: The cat was my friend. I can't in good conscience--
KATE: You can't be friends with every animal. KRIS: That cat is anybody's friend.
RYAN: Here's the thing... KRIS: That cat is anybody's friend.
RYAN: There's a thing called the Food Chain? This cat aint going to buddy up with these mice.
KATE: I like that Walnut's like, "I can't be friends with every animal?"
KRIS: I know it's tough. JERRY: Let's see the persuade roll.
AMY: Okay. That's you.
RYAN: I need to persuade you! AMY: Right?
RYAN: To be okay with lying to these mice. AMY: I'll do it but...
KRIS: This is tense guys! &gt;&gt; JERRY: Go ahead. AMY: I will make sure that they get help.
RYAN: What do I roll a 20? KRIS: Roll that die!
KATE: We'll help them later. RYAN: Natural 20. &gt;&gt; AMY: 20!
JERRY: Natural 20. KATE: Holy cow!
JERRY: You, out of nowhere, you spin an incredible tale of mysticism, magic.
You are ready to deliver maximum loyalty. And it is so potent, in fact, that they bow...
RYAN: Ooh. Nice!
JERRY: to the party.
AMY: Now I'm uncomfortable.
JERRY: They'll allow you to mount the mice. They rise up...
KATE: Yes!
JERRY: and then begin running toward the end of the Homeward Star.
KATE: Yes. RYAN: Nice.
JERRY: We're going to pick it up next week.
RYAN: Yay!  KATE: Yes.
JERRY: Thanks for playing everybody!
RYAN: Watership down! KATE: Mouse mounts!
KRIS: My god. RYAN: Nice.
Subtitles provided by volunteers @CTeamUpdate @Heyyley @catie_cat_3183 @Bekkablair &amp; @lvl14druid. Edited and re-synced by @AtomicRoboTesla Thank you!  For more information, visit: reddit.com/r/thecteam