turn at the enemy the past attracts the
fastest weapon you wouldn't make it past
a second and that the question play a
brash and reckless to choose a car
solution you saw was prudent poker poker
to don't become a putrid it's that well
said I pursue in no mountain to speak
but don't in too deep to spend
expendable marks up to the top of the
peak of belief they see me become a
shark to it while I swim in that money
bill by Carl Barks ruin essential
national parks do it I'll send him home
in a natural box the post time most of
the parks included save your breath for
a cleric confessor that there's a lesson
and life is at any profession but if you
speak in my official advice sign on the
dotted line and listen with twice hello
everyone
the show is starting now so I'll turn
this game around not like this hello
like this
hello I am taiko Riya Penny Arcade
impacts
I'm also Jerry Hawkins I'm going to hear
played a game of my friend and then a
moment also looking done with T referred
[ __ ] crap no juror for creams is only
for a table talk
that's my persona that I manifest in
kill alright Jack Ryan hard this is a
good running bit yeah legit always
forget I got it yes Dragonborn
narcissist dinar Blitzen right you are
not obligated I want to make sure
everyone at this table knows all right
I'll always do it I want this might be
less face yet environment we know you do
not have to direct any energy of any
kind you legitimately don't I direct
enough for myself towards myself you're
applauding for me this is distracting me
yes it from my applauding myself yeah
well not Don grass a druid we might
recall her stylings ah you know crypt
garden for us represent Wow what's
Optimus yeah exactly exactly I don't let
her get into that and Rosie V singer not
your gravis grandma I got ya and
character most styles yeah the reality
is that it's entirely possible I can be
your grandma's grandpa hi Greg
Emma it's real Katrice grab this cloud
emerge from or submerge it doesn't even
matter alright it doesn't even matter
both yeah here here nope before we go
into like the last time on you know last
we saw our heroes there is an incredible
organization that improves our packs
shows substantially called the cookie
brigade well yeah right now they'll roll
freedom of that and I'll give you a
cookie for it donation a cookie Brigade
actually dropped off some cookies for
the C team today these are chicken chip
cookies that's come I like that yeah you
would it's the the onyx special cookie
so it's like a waffle but it has chicken
in it so here so what's a classic common
end but not a get a whole here's one
grandma used to make this one and then I
always grandma no no this was our
Heaven's Gate moment yeah everyone take
a big bite on maple mmm got that got
that chicken
no no just gonna say it how big it's not
like a take the biggest but you can yeah
to it up real good
I'm gonna tell me what you think's in it
interesting that you're not you're
wondering yeah yeah what's that once
told the part of the cookie that I had
on there and okay they're sweet that's
very good actually it is really good no
no no they got crazy ass like reviews
but anyway so now that now that you are
eating on Mike exactly a now that you
are mid snack from Rome oh god I'm in
love come here damn laughs your goal
lightly indeed when last we saw our
heroes they had emerged from the cavern
that was left behind in the wake of a
beast that acquisitions incorporated CEO
what minister Tara were drawn calls the
wandering Crypt and in the wake was this
glass carved cavern strange symbols sort
of resting inside the glass
the party went there because they were
directed to find out more about this
wandering crypt I am doing in addition
in the roost of a deep crow the deepest
crow there was it oh hell yeah did you
see my sister Dina crane there's deep
crow and in this deeper crow and then
it's the deepest crow oh yeah yeah yeah
so in a mask secured as foodstuffs for a
clutch of wriggling eggs you found a new
friend Devine eighty fling from the city
of memos ear to the north in the crypt
garden for us now novel interesting
useful incredibly coincidental
the very next job for a positions
incorporated northern branch deaths are
in Valley housed in the drawn and
quarter was a job to go north and deal
with a surplus of rats the job was
placed by one mayor Fran Elsa Gore and
upon arriving in town having met him
definitely in the coop continuum has a
lot of dad jokes at the ready which is
to his credit I mean that's I've got the
premium material there for my people you
began to move around the town directed
on your map to two distinct zones the
first a hassling in one of the few
bright places when a few cheery places
in NEMA's eared ironbark and I believe
it was
oh-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho well it is indeed the
ironbark in and you noticed because it
would be impossible not to notice that
rosy be stinger has a reputation that
needs her in some quarters but the rat
infestation was in the baseball the
party split quite conveniently for
davines purpose because the moment that
the foe had been crushed Devine took
that opportunity to Lance cthe wrist
route with searing cold moonlight and
basically pressure basically put right
into the ground
against which there is no possible
Constitution safe no I don't need
impossible special this material also
Makati Russian reference oh yeah exactly
what yeah one love upset Aaron but what
occurred at this point cut wrist Robin
made note of a strange rodent creature
here in the basement that the brain
itself exposed light being cast from
this realm after putting self-insert is
open 38% whole the whole campaign is a
self insert six months yeah the rat is
not my avatar okay what you want thing
to a friend yeah zoom out on this thing
else is your body yes I didn't shave
your face and refusing repose
yeah but having emerged from this base
mom Devine violent criminal demean took
this opportunity to cast alt herself and
get those you know that raiment which is
required for her task so she is now
looking as one cthe risk drought and the
role of Devine which last week was
played by a lumber who had made a
generous donation to child's play
and earned that earned that seed us to
be the role of Devine this week will be
played by Chris trout or Chris Stroud
and where does one end and the other
begin by the same person it's a secret
though you get this beautiful [ __ ]
self inserts kiss reception you know you
need to look over here and a great
number one the best one somebody's like
drought I don't have dark hair where you
color the top of his head shut your
mouth oh that that's precise he does
color is how them said yeah exactly it's
just for men no know what I mean just
put it in there it's like Helen can tell
just for men Zubrin and that was way
[ __ ] inside baseball different thank
you now and your guys's Devine you have
received a rare daytime summons to frown
you have received a rare daytime summons
to the high house that rests in on the
mound in the center of Nana's ear
I mean are we going listen I'm sorry we
can talk to each other stable right here
we go so summoned up this is a
hand-cranked lift don't like me yeah so
speak right on the edge up high you can
see the city itself you can see it's
strange whirls and it's odd construction
broaden even greater relief by the
altitude you have been here before but
as I said never never in the day that is
not when the daughters of MELAS do their
work in this town or indeed any other
town so as you as you approach the high
house it knows you well by now and
allows you access
through the main doors and is a strange
place within peopled by rafts of unseen
servants that move silently purposefully
around the compound you know precisely
how to enter the inner chambers there is
a bust on a shelf in a sitting room and
when you turn the head of this bust away
from the secret door it reveals itself
passing through their door closing
behind you inside you can see an orrery
in a immaculate beautiful wood paneled
study and you know only to will how it
must be configured celestially to allow
entree into the second the deeper secret
of this house and the moment you have
done that as you're shifting the planet
surrounding us already the gentle light
that they cast is pushing strange
shadows in the corners farther and
farther away and you can tell that
they're not moving the way that they
should when the light moves they should
cede their space that's that's the
ancient law and what is happening is
instead is its reticent to leave some of
these corners as the secret door opens
just a black mist pours through the
crevice and it draws these errant
shadows into itself and generally
speaking this entity is kept well in
hand you've heard stories of other
daughters that have fallen to it simply
in the prosecution of their normal
duties and it's draws itself close to
you and sniffs your neck
and it is at that moment that you hear a
voice from beyond the door pushing the
door open
it says Prince where are our manners you
can see it flatten itself out and draw
itself back into some dark place beneath
a chair a table partitioning is itself
as necessary to occupy the space and
this is this voice the voice of your
mentor who you have known most of your
adult life says you are precious to me
you may enter waves you into the back
room a holy place a sanctified place for
that is where the black altar of MELAS
rests Carthoris Trobe Himself would
recognize this a device of this
construction having found it half buried
in the Underdark and a momentary
exchanger that changed the course of his
life you see this only during the
highest rituals and he issues his edicts
which you know is law he says to the
south and the sombre Hills there is a
cavern which bears the mark of our
mother the rightful heir to this forest
you were to go there and determine what
power it may hold and then you know you
know the altar to be a solid thing the
physical thing a single thing but when
he sweeps his hand through the top it's
like a well it's like the water of a
wishing well
and then as he dips his hand down into
its depths when it emerges it has a
black dagger that has that symbol which
is most precious to you that of the
betrayer maelys and he grants you this
knife and you Lee
- hi house and booked passage south
through West bridge through red larch
and into the hills where you know where
to find this cavern yeah cutscene
cutscenes in Dungeons &amp; Dragons they're
back and bring it back yeah so cook it
so ya know Devine / Caprice drought you
have now having taken that raiment which
is required you have emerged your dagger
kept secret and safe inside your robes
you are now outside the ironbark Ian
this is picking up immediately after it
is indeed yeah yeah so that was back
story right now okay have I have I rated
qataris yeah then included the quartet
just at this point yes okay you you have
a starry cloak okay you have it's not a
focus that a focus that you recognize
but you can feel as you carry the focus
you can feel the dagger drawn deeply to
it you can feel the dagger where you've
kept it that it wants to be together
with the focus they want to be in the
same place Yeager's hmm hikers island
yeah so he came up the steps asked my
walked out the door from the the
basement okay yeah what would I've seen
a rat free to wrapper a situation that
I've seen a walnut oh yeah did you about
the back already go have those because
you hadn't you hadn't come back in yeah
Randy Allen exactly okay my mind rally
and the yeah into the basement in the
same route it is indeed okay so you have
you have emerged and there you see a few
howling dogs still vacating the the
alley those dogs that can jump
up on boxes you know summer some are
choosing dead to hide but most of them
have just fled away and you can see a
shaken walnut dawn grass and a woman on
the ground so what's left what's left of
their meal is on the ground what's
something else then something strange
happens immediately you can see you can
both see this plainly even in the dark
of the alley you can see the hand that
holds the dagger that she has sort of
lifting and raising around and in an
animated way and then when the dagger
points at you cos risk grab one take
four points of damage from that just
nicely right on your sheet does that
kill you
well he she was at three when she left
the basement though a short rest vagina
does a little health portion laws down
loosen pass yourself up so work on the
drug the dagger the dagger strikes the
back of your hand and then goes through
the wound and joins the focus stabbed
into it is absorbed by absorbed by it
okay it's actually gone it goes from the
corpse into his focus was the way in
which it was animatedly moving because
of the death grip yes it was magnified
yeah okay it was it and I did indeed an
adequate dancing yeah
knife and me who is that one salt last I
checked I was still in my wolf form is
that cool you can wolf it on Adam you
recognize the wolf form you seen it
um so I'm just gonna I poached slowly
I'm growling just look like a very low
growling oh no I know exactly what that
growl is I also found out wolf stone
park so I'm ending my previous well you
will have good smell
yeah I know I will get there okay I'm
just growing right before I came up I
rub myself all over countries oh that's
really smart
yes like it all around the design I
inspire just like I'm walking dead rotor
motor red yeah just putting in trails
I'm fine
no I am really clutch I thought your
growling I'm approaching yeah like that
um
I'm approaching the body is what I'm
putting between me and oh yeah corpse
I'm like over the body
Oh eating on yeah yeah you're eating a
snack oh yeah we're snacking on oh yeah
oh yeah bullying problems thank you um
it's been a rough couple days right here
her eyes are clearly eating it you just
had a dagger a male Jagger which I wrote
myself and no like pick up the knife now
clearly you have it yes inside your
focus so yeah I'm growling at this point
I I want to try to like I guess I can't
send anything out with long beaky I was
going to saying like what I know because
I can't do all we can find with I say
that's the thing like when you try to
reach out with your brain well you know
it usually comes from yeah usually in
our conference yeah yeah man yeah yeah
party line um growing and if he gets
within you tell me when you get what
happened yeah wall-eyed there yet return
to your normal form though the enemies
clearly down um and my eyes are
transfixed not on his eyes but on his
focus okay um I mean can you really tell
we got cold dead eyes
yeah gentle friends Rosie and dinar have
heard its birthday party like we're yeah
out so no like when the hell yeah cuz
yes come on wrist said yeah you wouldn't
yeah we're out gave a warning before he
was betrayed yeah no no okay we're
outside too
all right I would see this seen
everybody cool out where's the bean
yes try to make it a thing yeah
everybody cool out yeah TM Wow yes is
that Devine on the ground
where's the bean oh all I see yeah yeah
yeah right I'm like I don't know who
this course is where where are the rat
the rats are done with but to be
attacked me down there when she ran off
a struck her with a tentacle lash cuz I
could do that yeah as a warlock that's
true that if you do love that let's try
to a lot of that we are to make one you
as a rock we know this is he gave chase
but it were turning meantime he's a good
boy I had a familiar
well nothing to see here looks like we
got another job done we established the
pattern that like whenever we meet
ourselves we ask a question only they
would marry Ocasek you got to tell me if
you're a cop that's the rule the law
from now and it's going to be you gonna
tell me if you're a being is a
shape-shifting laugh right away well I
know why I like it I can tell you - yes
woods but they wouldn't have caused to
know that though I want to know as a
meat
all I know is there was five of us
another's for the cake as a cake
it ain't indefinite hey yeah alright
horrified look you'll see yeah
thank you for your Polyjuice potion Matt
I'm doing exactly um yeah
okay so yeah snake got away and the man
attacked you and ran off yes your story
and who's this this they flung a knife
at me as they died mmm I'm just like
longship you know when a dog's there
like it like that mohawk the hackle oh
yeah tails like completely straight out
yeah and just like like I balding at at
is focused like oh am i eating and table
talk this or it's like I won like
wouldn't say anything because then she
had to reveal the whole yes thing about
Mela that's right oh wow talk about me
laughter I mean every other words I just
miss my phone nights going yes exactly I
wouldn't do that well I think it's like
MELAS club you know you can talk about
Oklahoma um a rule I mean yeah so yeah
just transfixed on that's okay Wow
what's her deal
why is she freaking out of you yeah hey
document sir I don't know completed the
rat job in her inner wolf form she might
sense some of the stink of the moon
about me oh that makes a lot of sense
you know I did smell moon yeah yeah like
ozoni like starting up like lightning
after storm foam yeah kind of like home
she's getting over that okay so uh Rosie
is afraid I really feral yeah but she's
gonna go check walnut come back to us
it's not too late and then I want to do
how closely to me like explain explain
feet or so yeah I'm like Janice Stan
d'emilia and dangerous it is
yeah I'm not that I wanna go we go like
I'm going towards you okay do you let me
get all the way to yeah yeah and then I
want to body block you from the brick
and then white you're still stearic
address okay alright that's interesting
mmm-hmm continues to be doing strange
things it's all work Renu Oh basically
Fennell I think that since we got here
you want to pop out and talk with your
human voice or no you good you good girl
Shelley what can you use her Granger can
we talk okay alright okay so she's just
like she's just a well this is like a
this is like a fear like she gave in her
most issue you know her human self is
like super squishy so
like when she's threatened like our
animal form the only thing that's going
to give her any kind of theft shielding
okay okay oh you got goose as a humans
got nice
so like HP's like super loads okay okay
alright you need to use your mental
powers we need to talk her down yeah
actually
obviously messed up can you can you hair
it's too it's drained from the fight
with the beam down there and then her
and how magic stuff we're a mile in the
to feral at this point I don't think it
would work
can I do a [ __ ] check on this
statement yeah yeah is basically a
perception or yeah what I decided will
be more of an insight check insight okay
help sing out to nine yeah that's not
going to it okay you can tell he's a
very good boy it's a very good while off
boy
yeah there's a person we've always known
forever you can tell that he's a idiot
right now he's delivering a premium war
life experience okay oh nice pop not
yeah I strap in
if they just excited to cut about it and
I'm nursing my my injury and them like
that be honest this isn't a kind of
reception I expected from after
dispatching that that flow well perhaps
I should be thanking you since you this
one might have been coming for me to uh
when you like make any motion away from
yourselves just like snaps there I know
this sounds like oh okay I'd like prema
dog aggression okay uh what happened
down there yeah I don't have a way he's
around you're crazy
calm you down um I'm sorry
yeah nothing I got that uh Keith command
uh you know are you cool is that I could
attempt to calm you down but I don't
know Jenna but I can't get so alright
mhm
refractory period no that's not the
problem might be actually but this is
different there's a different constraint
yeah a play okay I'm gonna use command
and I'm going to say down okay so you
have to succeed if you want to try you
can exceed on wisdom saving throw okay
my BP is falling searching i'm relation
I'm never yeah that's hard yeah I look
sleep I think 14 no I don't know 12 12
yeah I'm gonna give you a disadvantage
on that role
yeah you would okay so that's a 14 no I
got esteemed babes okay okay I'm like
okay and I'm inching towards you please
anyone if anyone wants to stop me
mentally yet still going closer uh yeah
I'm not going to let you fight our
friends and I would just plant thinking
something's wrong with your Wilshire
right okay we killed all the rabid yeah
we need to write it down let me get a
grabber or something like your strong
wave Standefer let me get a DM let me
get DM ruling this is terrible charm
person on a humanoid there's a count can
I do a wolf yeah and I'm gonna do that
let's see make a wisdom saving throw
this is so forth do this and I use my
advantage
Oh - good I'm I use tentacular
technology yeah I shred your movie actor
so you're using advantage on that yes
yeah she actually said that oh well so
two dice two guys okay
wisdom saving throw you know what I
don't know actually
what there's no there's no us oh here it
is you're trying to beat this team okay
well I got it I was having a job so that
you know so it if you say out where we
hand okay so make sure you're good to go
luckily I'm eliminating what you
wouldn't have had to do the advantage
anyway because it says you do so with
advantage if you or your companions or
fighting okay you're not fighting not
yet okay so I can happen by DZ and I did
and I got at one and you did okay
there's there's nothing under it really
which it's just
mcjohn so itself so I I go wanted to
meet tres and I the cardinal sin I'm
reaching out to my pet you okay oh wait
did you have something I was gonna are
going to see if term person is a spell
that warlocks can use if I know that
because he has you ever have you ever
used a term person spell before but I
use it maybe you got us confused because
we're like so films maybe but I know a
lot look okay guys well I don't know do
when I do again when I do charm person
and I like charm person I hear my friend
you know that right
it's V and s yeah yeah but my V was a
good girl I'm your friend
look if you guys already reached out I'm
gonna do about hopefully you know what
you got when you got to do a bike she
kind of do like let's get the manager
tell him we did a good job killing a rat
no one want to go to the next location
and kill the rats were here to kill rat
I would like to do bite on a cutter is
who's reaching out at me okay okay
goodbye my hand um let's see
well not good no seven nothing seems but
you're gonna snap close at me right what
are the hands like right there like you
take off the to take off your arm from
the elbow if it were a fitted babe I had
been drawn are smart and I would be like
I'm not touching that okay yeah you're
just like look I learned my lesson the
last time when we were in the cave what
I've mostly invested in both of my
friends yeah so I'm like and so I'm
really back off Todd I'm like what is
going on I told her I don't know I think
the wolf form has gone wrong somehow
maybe it's the city she's been weird
ever since we got here I have no idea
what's going on I can't make her stop it
so we need to get you inside and keep
her outside until she calms down can you
just go back in the in just yeah
absolutely
yeah sure no I don't want a letterman
look I make any attempt to stop them you
know they had that's something yeah go
on and on you should come with me
lets me and you go inside and we'll talk
to the manager come we did a job well
done that's something we can work
started going to the next location to
get these rats we're here to do a job
the job has killed two records act
what's most not want you I mean if
they're still standing next to each
other than like
jump past in our bill I want to lunge it
the focus but I know it's going to look
like I'm wondering for like his neck
yeah yeah that okay
so obvious I go to leave yeah I mean
I've already like I'm covering it up
it's never like on display how's that
you obviously got rabies from the rats
and you're crazy yeah that's true yeah
which is exactly what Rossum I know like
a lot of stuff happened down there while
we were eating bullish one day yes a
leap and was really wonderful I miss the
party yeah so I want to lunge it to
purses everything looks good inside yeah
okay okay I don't want to try and barrel
round good I'm gonna hit you I'm sorry
I'm fine I'm gonna try
so she's lunging for Chris and I'm just
gonna go just to try to like bunker
where I was the line of attack no I mean
I that's my react okay okay you gotta go
for it
but also block me out of you you
adjudicate this yeah totally here so
well I just like to see the attack roles
from both of you let's see if I get
garbage again that's Jack 16 the cool
jacked up now no pizza 1414 is that here
Oh where we doing farmer yeah oh you're
freaking yeah with them okay so you
connect him and would you deliver wait a
minute no if I rated Catherine no it
does not hit me if I'm wearing a garment
that you know so and then you deliver a
16 what's your AC as your host as
Wolfman hmm not that 42 oh I was
actually need to yeah exactly so so she
just takes to the air push us off the
ground and goes right for Chris's throat
and then you use your opportunity no
doubt a sort of water oriented technique
just to absorb the absorb it and then
just guide her to the other side of the
alley just manipulate her own momentum
around and I'm now going to stand over
you with my staff and try to block you
from attacking because risk again and
I'm going to I'm sorry I'm really sorry
this is I do not understand what's going
on we're going to figure this out but I
don't think you yourself right now and
you need to not kill our friends
something happened in that basement we
had a teammate our new friend betray us
and leave apparently they both went
crazy right
like can I try an intimidation yeah I
mean everybody keeps dumping their
skills on you yeah yeah it's worth it I
got it you guys with her yeah alright
another another crit okay tell me I'm
standing over you you're still not
you're probably not pleased with me cuz
I just like pushed you out of this line
of reasoning I say walnut grass you and
I don't know each other very well yet
but we're about to if you don't back off
sit down and be a good girl well he goes
inside and we figure this out listen to
me
just do it trust me so then I guess like
tail between the legs and then I don't
know so like still making that but
uneasy like the dogs across around me
uneasy noise like this yeah I understand
we're gonna get to about of this okay
don't know inside yet more you go inside
back inside you
hey let's go Denar yeah hi bud go inside
and look for the manager you're just
like roared where's the Lord yeah we're
doing job I have no reason to think
anything otherwise
okay yeah alright everyone this is
terrifying yeah this is [ __ ] low tell
me why you so we're like walking through
the restaurant looking for the manager I
guess so Devine betrayal when he
attacked you huh no you see you see the
see Marvin who operates the place you
see as it staircase wit not good all
right yeah he's watching the party come
in and it's just like and each person
from the party that enters the door is
like just another like slap to the face
until he finally sees Rosie's and just
couldn't let's just winch a couple times
tries to take it out and he knows that
he's not he knows that he's in trouble
I'm still outside with walnut okay okay
no yeah I just report in like yeah we
take job well done killed all your rats
because I could my understanding is that
the the job was for two locations I
certainly it's it's being paid for by
the city it's nothing it's nothing the
ironbark ian is going to be taken care
of all right do you have to sign off on
us you want to check our work
I don't just going to take my word for
this I'll go down I will go down to the
basement some of my companions and if
ours if all is well then I'll have to
marry or see what hi thank our
documentary oh she's a document sir yeah
uh for the contract yeah everyone knows
our documentaries right back me out here
right absolutely
see you're the one who's weird not us I
mean my friend
we're not anyway I'm sure there's
something you want to sign I don't
really adduce do you think do you think
Rosie do you think Rosie B singer will
be joining us again this evening oh I'm
sure of it
yeah she's mad at you she told me to
tell you that this Sunday's were
low-quality you know cool yeah tonight I
believe look I'm with you man I'm not
going on comms going on here it's shiny
some Sundays and kill some rent so check
the thing so I mean out here I know
right right it's crazy this is a wacky
world we live in backing up that's
absurd yeah the next time we speak for
Rosie your voice would have not heard
you're going down
all right here so no you're like I hate
them yeah this is the worst Roger
alright six for the road yeah yeah the
camera returns to the the alleyway where
two friends are attempting to resolve
their differences via a unique dialectic
that is thus far involved sticks and
teeth let's see where it goes from here
my my staff is down by my side now and
I'm petting
I'm petting me gently can you please
come back to wellness all set
um this is the dishes so this is the
best game DN it's the bet only now why
break the how much fun we've had so far
more yeah great thanks so much thank you
extraneous 18 I was I want to do it come
back here um I'm gonna talk to you
all right so if there's anyone other
than burns me but what waiting craving a
maternal for years exact right now we
are now more than ever come so I would
turn back into all that but like it says
it's like some of her wolf self hasn't
left her a little bit so just one here
this is like a lot of hair yeah
Italian sense it's just a like foaming
like if a person could bristle you know
like her hair whatever but like she's
got hackles yeah she's yes extremely
she's like huh and she's looking at you
like she wants a like I want to talk to
you um but that would mean revealing
like too much and she's just looking and
she's like there's something wrong with
Karissa's symbol how do you mean uh
there's I have Sheila she's just like
beside self and she's looking at
retention like I have to destroy it
she's like we have to get rid of it I
have to get rid of it oh okay so you you
are attacking the symbol you are not
attacking good threat alright sure okay
alright just making sure it seem like
you're trying to kill him and that was
not your maybe have to go to but right
now we got to focus on that symbol okay
uh okay well and she's like yeah okay
yeah I mean we can go talk to him that I
don't think it's gonna give it up easy
but we can certainly go talk to him I
want to talk to him okay who's going to
do it alright we're just going to just
do this thing but it has been the source
of a lot of problems for us yeah yeah
yeah it's like
I've been saying that for we have now
yeah I look at her and I'm like Rosie I
need you to just trust me on this one
this trust you she trusts you just try
it why can't the Frank I'm only dreaming
in right now because because wilmut came
out of wolf nut which was a voluntary
act
Rosie is like you trusted me I trust you
let's do this great let's get in there
cool looking real quick on motion all do
you right yeah
I'm just before we go in there I want to
UM cast first good berries hold up
tempers and I love um you know I want to
touch Rosie's shoulder and give her
advantage on Constitution checks and
game 2d6
temporary hit points okay let me do that
real quick this is enhanced ability so
one of the four and A to C get six extra
HP I love you Mike okay I got my guys so
I do I get advantage on Khan rules non
Connor will be okay
doesn't if anyone's princess Moonbeam
anyone okay oh so small role is it could
be on another thing yeah she just had to
pick a set she picked all that spare
it's random random it's really gotta
earn those bus so you so who's coming in
the iron Birkin first me yeah a resident
so you you push your way open you can
see Marvin is having a conversation with
mostly with the narvik-a therus is also
there by constantly casting looks back
toward the door and then the thing he
was fearing finally happened and you see
him you seen sort of bouncing play right
but I broke but I play it off and I go
oh she does look mad okay and he do he
busies himself immediately swiping
something and it goes into the back I am
in the middle of something right now but
I'm gonna have words
yeah Marvin okay um so good risk a
it seems like there has been some
shenanigans and before we move on to our
next rat killing mission I would just
really love to get a look at your focus
hanover assume it's the rock with us in
milano give us a rock Wow are you Rick
I'm the diplomat we'll need you two
talking please rock throughout beautiful
Silas I would let you look at it but I I
mean it's actually very precious to me
uh sure okay um yeah we'll take that
just like hold it out so that we can get
a really good look at I'd love to see it
for the one hand like going on three
yelling I'm like the exes do do you spin
it actually I'd love to see you do some
David Bowie yeah yeah what's the coolest
you can hold it um yeah that's it and
really enough to see it in the light and
I my eyes aren't too good so I you know
so old could you could you bring that
closer as close as you can I really like
take a look just real close just real
close
yeah the closest of course if I must hi
I guess
Genaro look like what is this about what
is this business women am i right yeah
and then I was mice as strong as I can
around it I do show it to you close to
my body but yeah okay
I mean it's attached to me by a chain
but yeah it's chained to you yeah oh I
didn't realize okay like a wallet chain
situation very tiny a really great
change you know very cool was anything
happening when he holds it does it
because it usually reacts and weird ways
when I order oh yeah like if someone
else held it like if the beam holds it
does it do anything different yeah yeah
is that Carly I don't think okay my gosh
um light a piece of rock ooh I hate
hostess are we satisfied I want to do I
because it's so close I want to do an
unarmed attack and just try to knock it
out of hand but this trust I know I know
it's a like I'm doing I'm doing what
well
needs and I'm like okay it's going to
happen yes you're standing over a human
corpse we're in me okay
well that's what I was trying to guess
to investigate like what was this about
it is gravity yeah and now we're looking
at me like I did something we're out
there with it we're going to leave that
corpse later
don't worry about it okay so unarmed
attack against just the focus so yeah
I'm gonna hand - okay here we go
I'm trying to see if the 20 I've done
anything going on right I'm gonna do it
oh wait against the focus what does
focus is armor class that well know what
kind of what would I have to be basic
come on no it's at this point now it's
going to be a strength check oh you know
let go my strength is trash yeah not
great so let's find out I'm just trying
to beat that roll
yeah advantage I take the damage though
but I take it though I didn't know I had
it mom thank you know Custer's has it
remained in that show that's true that's
true so trying to beat a 15 with one
roll didn't do it okay
I must show you so basically basically
like that it's like dad like and then
you just like pop it yeah and then lock
it hoping hoping that you're about to
yeah some some just grab it out of the
air [ __ ] or whatever you want to destroy
it I'm giving you the opportunity I'm
going to lay up
it's in the air cool uh so I want to UM
just be so mad I know I know I know
how mad is the fact that you're not
really reacting this violence banal
that's okay I don't think she's crazy
mad so you just pop it yep right I'm
shocked obviously I'm not shocked I want
I want to me to look
oh it's distance damn it never mind
that's just stupid spell why do I even
have that I just want to try and grab it
just a regular old rap bill Dex yeah
just Dex okay and I got nothing to help
me um first the weasel just we can swoop
in and catch it my rock
why wouldn't why not he might be yeah it
pops up you're able to snatch it of
course it is jeiza rock okay it is still
chained around his neck
yeah but now I'm like holding it yeah
it's like cut cut the back of my head
when you grab it now it's come back down
but I get over you I'm sorry but you can
re yeah but you can see you can see the
symbol that you saw in the deep one of
the symbols that you saw in the cavern
indeed at the Black Gate that was in the
wandering crypt but every now and then
in the right light you can see the hated
symbol of Malin Duckett recipe comes
back I'm sorry okay um so okay so I have
it in my hand and I'm looking at Kipp
dress and and I don't see anything weird
it just looks like a dress right sure
yeah okay
what's the meaning of this what is the
meaning as I'm outraged as Chris Brown
yeah I would take your back here a
little bit like weird in our way this
yeah Pharaoh
what did I'm for doing tell me what
happened down there
someone might come eat your ice cream
I don't care the whole time and I'm very
confused
you had confused dad no time a little
designer ready
oh yeah my moms like very strong
apparently um yeah not that no um
actually probably strong engine are not
enough my routes right so I just want to
give it a gimme things I actually talked
to her yep any struggling cuz is this oh
it's an area oh man um so I have it and
I'm looking here and I'm like I'm gonna
give you one chance you tell me why that
knife went in here that's my focus it
protects me no that's not what happened
outside and then when I say that I want
to do turn reduce flame and a flickering
flame appears in your hand the flame
remains there for the duration and harms
neither me or my equipment you're doing
flames sheds bright green line ah Thank
You relic oh it's a great plane you say
oh yeah I took this also thank you
pretty green frame light wink it's a
grand slam
it's a Graham flag Randall
it's a Grand Slam yeah okay someone over
my hammy okay so normally I would say
that I have to so I might like on my
next turn I would be able to hurl it but
I'm just threatening you and it's like
everything around the [ __ ] yeah
everything is like table side like you
on Bay yeah yeah I just wanted like yeah
it's right in your face there's flame
and so then on my next will we can maybe
we can fund a little bit my next action
would be like I could hurl it but I
guess that would be when I would do
damage on it okay I just wanna make it
cool I'm writing a face and threatening
you what are you gonna do else are you
cooking it I think step back okay yes
I'm just getting really bad yeah going
on so this you have to pause here is
because I'm trying to figure out what we
can do not knowing this yeah yeah how he
would react oh no absolutely that's true
so I don't know how I would react I'm
gonna try and I'm gonna try and yank it
back although that's a fireball you're
gonna pull the fireball toward your son
yes I'm gonna grab it in a mine big down
so I bellow it where's the one I want
you each to roll a strength check and
add your bonus it's not a good bonus
wait but here's the thing I'm trying to
figure out whether or not I had
something that can boost it because
apparently sorcerers have a bunch of
weird spell mod business they've all
kinds of rich [ __ ] yeah green I don't
know I don't know that I have that no no
oh yeah that's true well it's dad's on
first checks - all right check this
analemma syringe yes yeah Sokka Sokka
thrist gathers the chain that's it me
just hitting the old hot chain and you
can see that you can see his hand sort
of gather the chain up and then try to
pull it back they don't have it you have
it directly in your clutch you never
break the turn nope you got me and if
you don't love me no no no it's like
it's like if you can't live me at at
Devine yeah you know desert vehicles
right on the edge of users because
that's incredible thanks for yeah that's
what I'm telling you
merchandise okay so then if you didn't
break away
don't break away it's just a spirited
effort but I don't do it cool then I
want to blast it in your face
Wow watch the whole bit geez I start the
dark cymbal occultists trying to kill me
or don't
okay yeah you saw Lisa oh it's gonna be
okay yeah I'm just like as Chris I'm
like wow but as yeah yeah okay cool okay
so yeah was it make a range spell attack
so I roll thing and then I'm going to
know what my um okay see Marvin is essa'
it's just at the periphery of this event
with a bucket of water
yeah like ready to extinguish it kind of
neat so oh no and like there are patrons
at the bar though yeah we're doing this
on a busy Applebee's right the TGI
Fridays and there's no triple training
there listen we good good
what is that I turn to Marvin Marvin if
I want your help you'll know okay so
when I'm doing a range of all attack do
I use my spell attack modifier yeah yeah
okay we'll see all right oh and plants
late july 2019 yeah okay
Yeah right behind me what does that
didn't so um so since it wasn't it I
don't get to roll doubles dice for
damage for this do I who was a natural
20 on an attack I think you just make I
thought that's rated of all the bonuses
like double the dice no that so it's a
to d8 we can see double down so you're
taking this funny thing a nice face yeah
yeah I'm hitting it guys like myself in
return that was the bad memories yeah I
know you but I did the wrong days try
this is the dice
oh so six same couple I wasn't worried
to the part all right six damage to me
your Reeves in green flames well gran
flame your hair tears fire um you look
great yeah L I'm so sorry I'm not doing
a very good job of this yeah
the nails are coming out of the green
off now okay for a moment I just want to
talk and know his reactions to you even
being near the focus is nothing like how
I win when I tried to get him out of the
cave when he was just like I got near
him and his eyes were like [ __ ] he
attacked me twice yeah energy attack
like this is not I know I know I'm
metagaming this a little bit but this is
not good the rest is all right that's
right I could tell something was wrong
with walnut even when we walked into the
city later she had a little lunar I get
anyone's perceptive about people's
emotions I think it's racing I'm an
impact I think an hour just like item I
know like it takes your share yeah way
okay that yeah Devine wouldn't have that
background right that I would that just
goes nuts rain do something with it
really touches on you okay so I'm
suspicious at this point of what
whatever the [ __ ] going on here this
is out of character forest but I don't
know what I like what conclusion I would
draw about that right I just know
there's something very very amiss
taking his thing lighting on fire and
smushy shows his face I feel like Ali
yeah I feel like I was like side with
him though I feel like that's kind of
messed up I feel like that's there okay
can I ask you a question that's sort of
an tied to being Carol I think it bears
saying because I
what I want to do yeah like this the
focus is basically a hunk of obsidian
yeah right that's been heated it has
this carving on a superheated yeah am I
going to end up like you know tote from
eating of the Jones and I got it seared
into me here or here yeah and if there
happens does it have an effect on me
being a mammoth person i I like all this
stuff so basically you superheated this
rock it has a symbol on maybe earth so
much I should marry yeah I think hey I
have an idea
cool we're still early but I ate on our
leaf yeah I hear one more Sunday night
right yeah I buy this by this point your
that your hand is covered in symbols
just from different like trying
different ways to grasp it the hot chain
is seared on the right hand on your
cheek symbols of the ER and MELAS have
sort of come in gold in a massive sort
of scarification I like that on the left
side okay very tight shame to meet your
real body yeah
did you add your PIN well I like this
with video do this
I'm coming yet another huh teammates
attacking I'm just trying to get
everything cool I don't attack them so I
go everybody cool out again really bad
like I got a jerk on ik entitlement
so I go to iconic entitlement alright
real a night are you entitling nice and
nice so I say okay alright and I just
like your chronic entitlements this week
nice okay can't this does make sense I'm
coming I hear from oh it's good though
so but yeah so I just go everybody cool
out man
man apologize to everyone in the
restaurant i bellow this I say I've
everyone enjoy your meals I'm sorry
you to me stop just go downstairs get
out of everyone's hair I will figure
this out it's quiet and private and
let's just talk this out
yes I think we should I also think we
should because I suggested it right and
you're entitled I'm entitled to yeah
yeah why don't you should yeah well I
think you're entitled give them a sing
bag looks like English it I had ten
minutes of that fellow anyway short rest
but I get everything I'm like alright
give me a house yeah alright okay so
having noticed the oddness of his
reaction can I do any kind of reception
to notice anything that might different
like go downstairs
well like the highlights Pablo's words
like what's different about this picture
versus that picture where you kind of
initial job and while we go we can talk
about it but we have one more rat nest
to clear out and then we can leave I
think we need to address this now I
angry you know if he doesn't want to go
I think we are dressed down let's just
get this over with
all right everyone stop it I'm just
going to cage magic down there yeah we
might we're going around what are you
doing
there's a rapper yeah it's quiet I don't
I don't like that you guys are doing
this in the middle of a restaurant okay
I don't think that I want yeah hey I
would come into a city that they have to
do a job and have a public fight in the
street yeah I don't like public displays
on how I you don't know what brave I get
it you're right I can go down I've been
trying to find a reason that you have
their delectably half-hour I'm in the
game now fine let's go down there yes
let's all go down there we'll work it
out
I don't know okay get strapped in a
basement yeah yeah okay okay we all
walked out there's John - okay okay
first what do we see you say roles for
singers Cal naked in a Christian body I
think you guys are going first because
you're being ushered down by Bernard
yeah you gotta bear behind me yeah and I
just kind of like yeah my professor here
and I say to Marvin don't whatever you
hear come out of basement don't disturb
us and for Sunday's are yes grandma call
now now you probably already read about
this but like
I hide the buying be foolish not to let
me go over sled but yeah yeah let's
let's go proceed because there's a
reason why I can't do that did you have
any when I was stripping it naked did I
hide income or something no I don't
think so
no stage making so in you okay
serpent taking the exam I call that I
would youth you've seen it you can use
them as you enter this as you enter this
realm you can see there's like this was
a hard packed earth of the cellar it
sort of crumbled and broken screens
right where they're exactly where the
rats had emerged you can also see if
you're careful you can see the Rings
where these rings of moonlight have sort
of been dragged around in Donbass yeah
exactly yeah but there is no body here
look that's what you're looking for I
don't know why you would met a gamer
split this is where she we just want you
to describe a safer yeah that's all this
is where she attacked us I'm not the not
here yes connection right here and here
in the level of dice trade see where she
assaulted me where did she go how did
she get out
yeah how'd it come out in here she
didn't go out the alley and she didn't
go past us yeah she go I don't know I
was down here trying to recover and
finish off the rats handle and
understand she was helping you finish
off the rats when I was down there yes
she she I'm doing all the work when I
was down there so she attacked you fled
you killed the rats
job well done and then cable sticks of
course there else was I gonna go good
work in I point I want to just be like
okay Walter you gotta want to do this
maybe um where she goes uh you had it
under control I went into the alley both
of you saw me leave at which point I was
attacked by a cultist
of some kind this is what we should be
talking about that was the body of it
right and then when you came out your
focus summoned the knife into itself and
absorbed it Solent a dead bodies knife
flew out of its hands and went into your
focus
- the focus product of listening yeah
okay
you didn't go into the focus I pull out
the other dagger that is mine oh my god
it merely retrieved it for me hmm
someone looks like that's not true I I
saw it going to the focus I look at my
family you have to trust me here to
dress me I think this will be invaluable
for my for my studies and this dagger is
the same one that has the symbol the
hated symbol on it right oh yeah yeah
did it did it like reflect yeah yeah on
there yeah three on the knife and then I
I look at it for this point and I look
at that symbol and I go I go I can't
explain now but you need to know that
that symbol means that he's I don't know
what's going on with him but he's not
with us I had that vibe since the cave
next to know what yeah on this we may
reach agree yeah
that cave whether your rough situation
yeah no she really what do we do oh yeah
like do better
yes getting it giving it you're sorry
it's like a whole map of what I should
have done from the whole jurisdiction
okay okay
so at this point that accusation your
support of it about the cave and my
observation that he was reacting very
weirdly to his focus makes me want to
bust out some grandma man see hmm yeah
and ascertain some [ __ ] truth yeah
that sound good to you he okay I'm gonna
do it
nothing it's not truthful what do you
say RP it uh well okay so grown man seat
is up in the air is exactly but but we
talked about it before the game and you
like the idea as do i that rosie has
just a capacity from hundreds of years
of gret of grandmother thousands exactly
just to like auger right into someone
right and figure out a secret about them
yeah okay
this is going to be very useful for us
to gosh alright
let's see how quickly I can ascertain an
actual secret well you have do you get
to determine the secret or does the risk
being ordinarily in ordinarily you
wouldn't be using this on a party member
you know what I mean yeah we even show
you a lot of [ __ ] on each other no exact
today's accident and I'm told that
doesn't happen there being my first
foray into D&amp;D I'm like this is all
normal
yeah emails like don't now I like this
with different groups
yeah paradigm but no in this case a
ordinarily this is going to be used
against NPC right and but right now
right now this is a player character
okay while you determine I suppose the
secret that you're going to tell me I
will be some build another Lane yos vamp
uh give me a moment guys good there's
drought yeah uh what what is going on
how what is this focus what is your deal
I I want to know tell me exactly why
everything has happened the way it has
I'm trying to learn that myself my focus
works in ways that I don't necessarily
understand where did it come from
thank you you see what she she would
have no way to know
I'll let she had some insight though I
it was a part of an altar that I am an
altar yes we're a destroyed altar in the
Underdark obviously hmm interesting
this sound like [ __ ] to me a lot of
weird stuff goes on yeah but Devine
would have seen this shape on her altar
indeed so that's probably where all that
out very specific yes okay alright and
what does this symbol mean that I don't
know either but that's good time it's my
task in life to figure it out I'm pretty
sure he's told us the name before the
earth yeah
I think he said that out loud before I
don't think that I want to put it I
think I wouldn't had cause to say it all
right okay no we just know I say it all
the time okay yeah same I sleep yeah
okay
speakable I won't say its name in this
filthy cellar mmm sure
some respect for me what I've been
through
tell me all what all we really know is
that wallet has acted very strangely
since we've got here
that is the precipitating factor through
all of this and I'm being set of blades
and being brought back down in this
rathole I I don't understand I've gone
through so much today I understand I
just just one more question there's
there's there's something that I just
said hey you don't mind I hear is excuse
me yeah yeah hey Mason I get it I you
and I entire conversation before where
we we've had we've compared certain
aspects of our childhood to each other
you remember that conversation but
because that that to me is how I know I
trust you because we were able to to
connect on this level you remember what
that was rough one
hmm to roleplay good because she
wouldn't know there was having some
trust issues
right yeah you guys about ten seconds no
that's fine um a conversation of what we
experienced as children there are much
more pressing matters at hand here no
yeah by the way ello said go nuts
so how's that we're waiting on oh really
yeah yeah no um Rosie's not buying it
because because they both know about
this particular conversation yeah and it
matters very much to but it happened
live that happen if this happened to be
able directly yeah this was just
something that was it was this about the
stalactites oh yeah they're really cool
I was really a sense of intellect and
and her Star constellation so Rose
he is ready an attack he likes yeah it's
not looking good hmm this is that well
yeah a situation he might have been
taken over by this earth is focused I'm
not because I don't know that weird but
you know that the focus the symbol
there's there something you know not
right here yeah I'm not sold on on what
happened I'm not everyone's kind of like
glossed over the fact had our teammate
momentary teammate but teenagers the
betray doesn't bounce she's she's a
sorcerer so I'm willing to like her that
she might have like blinked out well
they didn't like snake go there what
specific sweet snake boy and a beautiful
sweet sneaking your snake sweet like a
patty the guy biscotti okay yeah so
we're in in terms of that like I don't
trust them well how much time is passed
oh you're well within the oil scale I
know that I know that I'm just asking do
I have time to cast a chromatic orbit
well on Rosie did what we're going to do
is we're actually going to roll we're
just in a roll initiative if this is
going like that yeah then we're gonna
roll up that's a great you know it's
funny we're going to roll initiative has
managed this is fun obviously shadow
counsel I invoke your blessing upon
these proceedings but by we're going to
do an initiative kind of go that has no
monster marker 22 nice I got a Levin how
doing it you go before I do I'm eighteen
woo hey Tyler angry red inner five and
always liked it alright what's that well
not done grass I can't decide if I'd
want to give our record an hour
hold on I'm texting Ella I'm saying how
do I defeat the entire C team I'll let
me know what she says okay yes follow it
away I guess and you've already taken a
little bit of day mostly par today yeah
yeah we're not lost thing I'm not almost
died yes I guess oh wow you know what
what I'm a bygone
I didn't put a whole well the Beast I
was going to turn into I don't have my
card for so easy
referring to a weasel and turn inside
out senators forward me um I'm gonna try
and just born with you actually we're
going to do with you have to come down
and murder we're gonna try it with him
right in the eye mister killing ain't
done in this sooner you're going to whip
them and then say remember when that
happened
missed one grab a little a little little
spell attack making me lie spell attack
against the target I'm gonna roll which
I do
oh it's not good it wasn't 11 that's in
the [ __ ] so I don't do that's a
Scooby bad have you ever connected with
song widow but it's going great when I
do I was going to be so whipping and
back yeah I'd agree
you just you just hear the snap right by
your ear Rilke throughout okay it is
actually your turn to throughout all
right I'm going to set this up so you
know because if you don't know no I am
going to go ahead and throw a chromatic
orbit well it's a freemium or yeah it's
a hot colored orb and you know love it
oh yeah I'm just gonna get kind of disco
down here yeah I'm gonna okay so I hurl
a 4-inch diameter sphere of energy inch
sucks and a creature you can see within
range and it's gonna be Rosie yeah mute
you choose acid cold fire lightning
poison forth with the Thunder well the
type of or be create I don't know I
guess I'm going to do we like Thunder I
guess thunders good the great horse it's
a classic Ord and a range spell attack
against you so here we go arranging it
good luck
no that's no good everybody's like that
enough
I bring your mouth yeah you bite it's a
fruit you orbit subjects is not gonna do
it close your mouth and you burp and I
read yeah no it's acid um
fire Thunder mango yeah
you know drink and wouldn't think okay
so I've and you but I have my bonus
action I do
expeditious retreat now this allows me
to move in an incredible pace lasts for
10 minutes on a bone at a bonus action
after each of my turns until spell and I
can - so Nene - oh that's an action that
wasn't it I can't take it he doesn't
actually disengage or any noise I just
go no it's me get go but I got a speed
of 30 okay let me handle that yeah
check this out yeah enjoy my retreat we
can turn around upstairs of course what
else matter I'm gonna have to one pass
me yeah good let's see it yeah now you
get close alone what else am I gonna try
yeah sonars just like what it I'm a
blighted farewell we are in a halfling
cellar so I'm like tonight way yeah I'm
like the hard Doria yeah that make sense
to me but if you're if you're legit like
trying to like beat feet out of here
people get to swing on you yeah I get it
it's your chance I mean walnut walnut
was not able to connect all right it's
what I'm doing yeah yeah what's my route
with the chromatic or videos there and
if you're Lou nice you have to you know
you're going to have to run out of here
your your compatriots are going to have
an opportunity to to stop you from doing
that
let's go your oh but everybody gets the
wrong gift to tear even though you've
gone yeah really
alright to keep your in the but it's
loud thunder horribly active brothers
run wheelchair so exciting exactly the
second but I would say that I would say
that Rosie you should try to stop this
no problem and do it okay alright argue
so you're trying to you're trying to
beat feet yeah I'm trying to leave it's
just my regular attack you'll 18 yeah
okay that's going to connect now don't
remit no I want to make sure you you
filed us away yeah the staff of the
master when it hits any melee attack
that you do that round yeah is a d8
instead of a d4 right and so on turns
where you dump a key point in mhm
you just to do this flurry like that's a
lot 3d 8 plus for each time I'm just
saying it's something to consider
okay I felt I felt bad like I hadn't
explained it and so I just want to make
sure you know you have that in your I'm
going to do it I'm going to give her all
kinds of punches and kicks okay so
strikes with the core stuff which is
going to be a nine and then I will do
two on arm strikes that's two anyway I'm
going to I'm going to go for the backs
of the knees
Wow try to hamstring a little bit that
is a hit and that's another seven and
that's I it sticking forward to me you
don't you need yeah below zero let me
know yeah yum yum yum I'm a minus one
yeah the staff of the master whips out
he's defending and made a murder correct
anyway is Chris right I was your friend
and I don't think you had that few hit
points like you're good with something
have a few this is the first around
behind yeah we only do that I didn't
mean Oh live and once he loses
consciousness what happens to the
shape-shifting I think that I think that
there's probably different ways to
interpret the end result of that what I
am going to say is that as soon as
Devine loses consciousness
you see Chris's black hair sort of like
burst out in the back and change color
you see horns erupt from the sides of
the skull right on the stairs just like
falling forward is completely out and
unconscious and you can see that you can
see the focus on the chain like pulling
itself on the ground
mm-hmm like like putting like and it
drags the body on it ragdoll physics
yeah like like she goes down and then
immediately it starts to crawl I imagine
like a truck
attached to something with a hitch right
like this thing is crawling and rolling
dragging her around like slicks yes hmm
and it pulls over to the rough soil at
the edge of the rats had previously sort
of pushed through and you can see it
like almost like scraping and scratching
at the dirt oh [ __ ] hmm all right the
focus being your oh you're okay good
fine yeah run over and say that would
drive you crazy right like the hood that
thinks they're swarming around yeah I'm
going to start digging in the dirt and
encouraging our please yeah come help me
so we're dig like yeah yeah there's no
PT Paul he doesn't actually enter grab
grab it off her body yes so you're
eating whatever you always know whenever
you reach down for it it's always blade
first go grab it
uh-uh like really slow and purposely and
like gritting my teeth and I grab it I'm
assuming I was pleased and damaged
longer yes three fingers you can yeah
yeah exactly
yeah you just lost it yeah go ahead yeah
yeah that's for the emotional damages
but it's a good imagine if you'd imagine
that it's like a sort of a weeble type
scenario like no matter which way you're
reaching for it it's always pointed at
you with anger
that's the weevil reference is a
difference yeah every episode we can go
card exactly it's like clean Irish
Prince of bel-air we believe you're
gonna go your own way yeah exactly so
you so you you grabbed it and it just it
doesn't it doesn't want to be held by
you it's like holding a snake like it
just it doesn't want to be near you
okay what's with you guys can continue
your stuff and I'll just as a magistrate
I'm I'm still working inside I'm not
making much progress cuz I battle and my
hands are small yeah but you probably
hear me turn it so I'll just yeah you
getting all that dirt you're digging
through it what do you find our opinion
digging I know what I find you find you
find the
it's soil soil soil then you connect
with something then you brush it away
and you can just see a dark foot hmm
dark blue foot I go uh found Chris and I
start pulling them out I hope he's not
naked and it's going on the dirt is
receding and it there's no clothes yet
and I'm like I just like make of it
naked time like I want to see where I'm
going
yes your feet actually in character yeah
like all of it
ah see you know thank your mangled husk
and you don't know what you are like
done you're forced intended like that
remembers no it's like an elephant it's
just it's like every monkey bread yeah
it's like a mash of that yeah like what
it's like this it's like the bottom part
of a squid yes just right no none of
this is true I'll just say this was not
canon can I check the OL I like my dad
yes yeah regular I gave it a roll up on
a dick perception like I want to really
get in there nice exciting no is he he's
alive dead no he's asleep as you told
him it's like a little baby Jesus no no
he's actually snoring now you pulled him
out you sand and just as death and then
lay in the recess behind after lunch
well it is you pew is you you pull him
through you can hear frenzied shrieks
and squeaking just beyond the dirt of
this wall hmm and there's actually a
glow cast from the back of that and then
as you as you withdraw Keturah strobe
the last bits of the earthen and a sand
sort of fall and close off the passage
hmm wake up you said you killed the rest
for good even you Devine is that it yes
I wake up
why do they keep up on the tables
you want music you're living is for I'm
over the body nobody saying it doesn't
was anywhere yeah yeah it does that
rouse me out of it oh yeah it or does he
need a healing really cool like you
probably know well no no no no he got a
long rest
wow I not know notice the the process
that you think you don't you don't know
why he he doesn't look like he's
sustained substantial magic injuries
he's stronger than he was before
Wow yeah you you have your own trouble
right going on when this might yet be
nothing I got to do that more often
yeah so he did forget about could be
disease yeah I'm like super suspicious
yeah I was suspicious at the very start
we were in a in and it never went away
and now it's only going up and up and
now you can any of you could be anyone
else with any moment can't open doors no
I'm just like my paranoia is reaching
like logically it's gotten ranked up but
you see you know your your cloak yeah I
mean you you are basically all of your
best coolest garb everything that's
associated with your IP is draped orient
is draped around to Devine I cover
yourself up ice ice cream because I
remember suddenly ah the night-sun Oh
ah no dinar my name Waldo you've met the
moon why are you sleeping in dirt you're
supposed to be killing Rhett I don't
know alright fair enough it's just this
no it's her thank you
and so so that it is able it rolls the
focus twists and rolls itself over the
horns yeah and then like a faithful dog
um roles roles to your foot and begins
to snake its way up there naked right
yeah there's usually a phrase like all
three guys you're guilty but really
nothing he is it is just Chris Brown
with me altogether this is like this is
like one of the shots from the Capri
strobe under dark after dark calendar
and also he's murdered with just what
the earth is like 30 it goes around my
waist
and then just as a fig leaf yeah yeah
yeah I think I felt like jab dagger does
not yeah why are y'all road hog and it
can't be apart from the focus so it's
trying to go it is trying to pull itself
out and so you are anything and it is in
midair and you are continuing to hold it
imagine that it's almost like it wants
like you want it to be stationary
doesn't but you have to almost like
you're pulling a rope but it's just a
single dagger and I'm in the mid air I
mean are you continuing to hold like
come on wall what the hell is this why
what is it so I want out like uh are you
continuing yeah I mean okay go ahead
yeah given the dam again and I'll tell
you what I'm gonna do that's three so
you were wrestling with this thing in
midair one my old my process is not
feeling good guy um and so then I look
at Katara's and I don't want to say
anything but I want out like can I at
least help it like can I chill to the
edge of so that he could see the because
it's mirrored so you'd see the symbol
that's on it also I can see that yeah
you can even try to hold it so that he
sees the icon of my lips yeah for like
one second and once he sees that knee
makes that face I let it go shot oh yeah
ah yeah and it get get flies right at
you and go straight in well actually
straight in at your great Adi level
right I don't actually a knife going
right at your junk is it a Dean whatever
it a knife feel I mean not a Diago
Skippy know that I'm saying like SAP
into a knife at me no no no to lumber
hands no no this this a night this these
mainland daggers okay they can't be
apart from it Oh from the focus like I'm
AG bouquet it's like with the dead body
in the hole in the Elias I think and
they're going inside the focus somehow
they are we're actually saying I hit
they strike it and then are drawn in
okay so they've both gone in and I go
home look for blood yeah no mine is the
what is going on it's all like that why
I'm saying that it's all intact all you
it's eating together she attacked me
where were you guys
I mean I'd like to do my cologne way I'm
already like taking the clothes I go
thing yeah what's going on okay yeah
well I'm sure Nega nebulous that
register game it takes a few seconds
right like Oh God oh well I'm what I'm
seeing your nan dragon father shuns me
why are you with your nipples at the
table talk thing yeah she might have put
on the necklace - not knowing where was
yeah but I didn't want that to be the
easy TV yeah um no okay that was like
the first thing I thought it I am
rotating or picking over the body of
Devine to try to figure out what if
anything if it's any clues as to why
destroy stuff like appeared in betrayed
us out of nowhere don't find anything
but I mean the only like the real
standout item the the main point of
commonality is that that she had exactly
the same dagger as this ally assassin
okay but I don't know about the ally
assassin only walnut' knows what the
Elliots asymptoting yeah so you're the
only one who can draw that particular
yeah nothin of truth together okay I
said look right and I guess it's true
saying I'm gonna call you over actually
okay like what
all right take a look at this I always
talk about police like it is formed oh
it's was learn it okay so he's the only
one that saw it yeah um and so it gets
observed in my girl that's the same
knife the cultists head I got my
absorbing to the air before another your
focus it sucked up to blows Cultus
daggers now what does it say oh my god
you guys there's still rats back there -
okay I'll put the cause of it on this
conspiracy and go kill up some rat yeah
you know what blow off some steam
yeah rat bean dip okay so I I turn
around and I've got I put my cloak back
on but I haven't put anything else yeah
let's just focus
and the clothing-less but what would
what would those knives want with my
focus I like I can't hear any of it what
the dadgum mystery I'm just standing up
like your crotch oh yeah yeah oh yeah
everything oh and so I and then I looked
at like Oh brushing dirt off that's why
I know how my god
so I look at this person I say um I say
I think it had one of those dark Strauss
symbols on it and like I'm obviously
trying to cover this up yeah yeah it's
private because it's about it's relating
to a personal conversation okay we
talked about it when you try to scribble
it on my document right I know you know
about that's innamal at the drummer
named one I go yes this thing sent this
one I start to drive and then I go yep
you got it and then I actually I don't
roam it out with my with my hair but
what I had I do with my foot yeah okay
yes because they're all bloody yeah aw
yeah yeah that's just hygiene which so
what did she know about your nowait I
don't know anything about you I know
about it you don't know that it made me
uncomfortable and I knew and then I knew
I'm glad to talk about and I'm going to
rip a piece off of davines clothes start
to bind your hands while you two-thirds
of that I like why you need to do this
and then this for the fans I start to
tie you up a little bit Oh
because everybody no no no we're getting
these we're getting that type of action
you know we go we got to give him the
moments they need it has room we don't
you do it
urgent and then a winding brain rad
crawls out how binds me I'm shared a
traitor too she came in here you know
what it looks like a Thai person up for
some banish your hand oh that's what you
meant I thought you're trying to prevent
her from attacking me more no she don't
like your show on his bleeding no I know
I was agreeing so make sure if you want
to bind Devine because she's not that
did want to stab her with her right
night but she's not that negative one
yeah 97 not a lie I know I have been
back here managing all this okay all
right so I I do think I should we should
tie her up just in case you're gonna
watch as her I'm granny's where I need
rope
I'm still not 100% clear on what
happened it's high right I
any of us you have my closer to the
puzzle so I'm like better safe than
sorry
hi everyone else let's all tie ourselves
up we spend the next hour explaining
everything that just happened to
describe the particular pattern I used
to tie a suit
there's actually a very unique now is a
fisherman Ottoman sailor's knot yes
I'm extremely facing you you are going
to tie
devine up with grandma's rope I am
flying up with the Rope I'm going with
can't can't miss on an unconscious body
right well the women compared next so
yeah so I'm dressed now I'll do that ah
hmm and then I go over there look at the
baby I trusted you
this I will never trust another tiefling
again the whole species yeah one pruned
it right there with you now write down
your character sheet yeah just anyways
yeah any a yen's any a yen's none
dragons yeah I'm not surprised he's
right idea yeah I've been telling you
yeah I've been done said it so where's
you will snake boy they say comparison
of moving huh
Oh God Scottie no look at it I'm gonna
go to Scottie I cannot bring Emma back
uh
so don't let me interrogate her alright
we should interrogate her but I want to
say that I can vigilant I won pretty
good yeah yeah okay
you have to resurrect your interrogator
oh wow okay just put it in the hole it
was like chili and Terry oh yes you did
boom just go up yeah let's get those
rats on you I'm just like rap we know we
can you heal her a little bit
yep you and I can't Euler back like this
yeah can't heal her soul back to my dad
right okay um I don't have any other
Bible let's try that further ahead now
we're doing me are you gonna shake it a
couple times to the last gettable
eyeballs out of there I work well
because it settles right you need to
know that
oh yeah do you have any like olive oil
yeah you're freakin back from the dead
no we can't but is there a way to talk
to her soul like that yeah yeah okay
ready
any you just apologizing for doing a bad
job yes so I'm like I said I think
there's some metagaming going on cuz I
think I did a great job you know I
forget to do huh
so no I have no skills that would let me
do stuff with my dad I would love to
thank you okay I would love to interact
with the bail in a number of there
beyond my reach if I know is it so what
I'm talking about I notice that she's
pretty much dead right oh yeah do this
I'm like this is pointless okay and I
want to go halfway
yes and tonight I start undoing it and I
I want to you know like um make it look
like I'm untying her and then just like
whisper in her dead ear um say what you
get for following the betrayer
hi Claire got betrayed me you just
cursed the dead yeah sick person darkest
druid like we're gonna meet someone
someday that we don't kill and that day
is in a weird day yeah I haven't killed
Marvin yet not yet but you know I look
at my watch showing around a stick talk
yeah five o'clock somewhere stab I
pointed a devine and I go I think we
should put her in the crystal do it
Katherine hold up that rathole and
should we kill the rumors while I die
like let me do it i dragging her by the
horns over to that hole right to the
hole and twisting and jerking the neck
like I know and I whisper I said no
you're driving a car said I'm not used
these horns for drinking glasses if they
don't think it's too weird I start to
cut them off and they give me a weird
look then I'm just gonna I'm gonna not
do that I'm not gonna give you a look
okay we say that really loud like
they're pretty loud saying really loud
and I go it's super weird I give you
like a thumbs up that's very weird
I guess I got my own we're comfortable I
just don't we go into a wholesaler
decision is life is weird
I know experience weird AF it's super
weird
yeah I'm the Paladin I'm the moral
compass the group well now I it's really
funny you think you're trying to stuff
her into this yeah and indica twistle
you but about the time that you would be
done you know you're like is it worth
much effort it's like the 95th like the
90/10 thing yeah it's like you know how
much more do I really want to do this
yeah um there's it's because there's a
jerk and she gets me fooled
just like halfway in and then there's
another jerk and she's just gone know me
cool she will get res and become a thing
of nightmares later well we don't have
to laugh and she's covered residuals I
prefer to believe that she till is
killing the rest of the rats for us yeah
dragged to hell we should tell the
proprietors
probably not this is another job well
done far as I'm concerned write it up
let's go okay send only witnesses there
are no oh yeah all right yeah we have
one more to do unless that those Reds
are gone because this was a bunch of BS
only one way to find out yeah we're
going to do a job keep wearing it you're
actually you yeah who's going to betray
us in the next is it you is it you is it
you home game yeah if you fire almost
good stuff coming I don't like nothing
but it's so good I know
yeah no this is great no for real it was
like an hour in real time yeah how did
you figure out that it was what how did
you figure it out she just attacked you
down here well on the body
oh I mean you found me I do I did it I
did you stood him did you guys come
looking for me I dug you out you guys
came looking for me and we're being
attacked you while you were down here
how didn't even see that she had that
symbol on her face as long as this might
think she took my symbols yeah I lit it
on fire and then I shoved it in her face
what are you a vampire the rock I like
I'm looking at it now like just smell it
in never was on her but yeah the rock
the circumstance we took but not
everything's fine you got your preacher
of nice rock it's fine
you got your cool now right like your
your rock is not fine
Sean's rock it's not a high percent fine
I'm checking the rock out there smell is
definitely that of the smells new smell
there's an idiot you have that you have
that we have a new focus smell but
that's you're like a Cajun little Irish
yeah it was a 20 I can't count it I
think I could count no 12 almost 20 it
has it has a smell
it's commingled with the original sort
of primeval must right um a whole new
smell yeah exactly yeah anyone else
would hate it if now if now commingled
with like the scent of wet leaves wet
leaves you say hmm yeah and there is
there is actually another symbol light
soil of it law on it yeah it's visible
at all times it is visible at all times
but it's still very dim it's only when
it catches the light that you can see it
but it is the mark is clearly upon the
focus what is it it is the icon of
Mahlon yeah those are how I'm little
refresher this guy
sea turtles the whispering I are on a 11
yes evil exact thing exactly but but so
you've seen it and this the focus is
sequestering these daggers somehow like
it's let's not shoot them out at us way
yeah it's collecting them the focus has
changed that smell is one of the things
that like reminded me of the under
darken head and that night when I found
it yeah I think isn't weird are you over
to you focus focus
under spike
two boys are you assuming you're
connected from the arena
yeah you can you can I'm searching for
the words okay well so while you're
doing that and I go listen I don't know
why you can understand what that you
know he's going to recognize this symbol
but you should know that it's bad and
it's wrong we got to get rid of it I
don't know what this is but thank you
because this would happen otherwise you
may have brought me a little bit closer
to a truth oh come on screws you're
welcome and you remember last session
like I said what was the second person
right but that's well yeah I think it's
heartfelt but I'm like you you might
have brought me closer to unleashing
whatever this is well my guess along
looks just like it realizes that what
she's saying is just like not piercing
the same reality that like if you're not
living in the same thing I wouldn't
leave Leo alone and I'm looking at it
looking at the new symbol like I think
that's cool I get used to that this
scent is important now before it was
just a one piece of the puzzle and it
started to draw the token itself into
itself and actually two-in-one this one
it's waving to the right I got to give
it two kisses every time now
No so you don't think that lucky Rock
did your symbol I don't know what its
aim is yet but if that's something that
it that it needed I was going to give it
that space I think at this point on the
grill a little bit of a I think at this
point she might actually reveal like
pretty-pretty what her context is for it
not in so much debt so I can't write the
symbol can you say the name no you can
say to me okay if you want to maybe it
would have been anything but I think
that's and all another way if you call
it like the hated machine who betrayed
you okay I was like that's a mobile on
sushi who betrays like unless
serve she betrays that's not your symbol
here that because that symbol that's
what it does it it gets places that it
shouldn't be and it shouldn't ever be
written
well now you hear you with you always I
don't like that less I don't hate it
though no I like it I like it less
that's originally picking up some what's
going down here yeah so this symbol is a
something that I can see it doesn't bug
me
can I perceive it the shapen again on
the on one of the sort of impossible
indescribable phases of this geometry
it's plain as day okay have I seen it
anywhere else in the city since we've
been here
no maybe you're like like I got like
graffiti or something like that sure
Nelson no no like carving me with rules
yeah yeah yeah um is it something that I
was canoeing history check on you be
familiar with her no this is this is not
human history I'm not human yeah yeah
this is not this is not the type of
story people tell um all right and same
boat
well like when refresh my memory so when
we were down in the cave and you were
going crazy the symbols were appearing
on the gate did we see some others it
just he seen uh no use you can see it
though there so they're very visual but
the difference right is that he can see
a symbol and know what it means
yeah yeah right so the entire cave was
lousy with all kinds of symbols but I
knew my symbol and then you knew that
symbol but all I know of it is that it
bothered you for writing to bother you
that around you're correct and now you
have some curve but but no but now you
have some more context for it right now
you know it's correlated in some way
with DES Riddick lore right yeah
well sir the difference okay all right
yeah can we yeah let's get let's just
like complete our mission and get the
hell out of their city location - yeah
yes but I don't ever as we're walking
littke thrissoor find me okay that's
fair vocally tell them I hate in every
stand differences Isaac I want
five you like I think that's wise
absolutely so it's plain as day on your
scroll document sir you know precisely
where the next venue is I do it is north
so beneath this great mound that exists
in the center of this town you can see
almost like a way out that train tunnel
might be carved there is a main road
that exists that travels through the
center of it but even even inside this
it isn't it's all useful space there are
little shops hammocks
there's zero hammocks around your
hammock district okay I mean right here
in TripAdvisor it says you're visiting
NEMA's are you gotta go I'm gonna kill
anybody on a deep Candida it says 2-0
does it not give it to me cuz I might
exhibit a needed but he does not like to
be separated from sight I might need to
be put I might need to put it in your
esophagus later I thought oh good yeah
there aren't any hammocks feelings but
you can see that this stone has worked
and they've sort of carved shops and
serve it right to make this this block
as useful as possible and I hate this
store and I think I just don't like that
or would not enter into that stores
loyalty program having a punch card of
this store you analyst souvenir shop
exactly to make meaning Amazon all I got
was a super-special all dude this is I'm
telling you the merchants a Lords
murderer can't write it so exactly so
actually I'm sorry any merchants and
merchandise I will have to burn yes he
actually made me less merchandise I
burned it exactly it was a huge loss
yeah so what you see that it's sort of
the northeastern corner of this you can
see that the walls the exterior walls of
the city itself
sort of join up near the north of the
city but sort of nestled in that little
crook there near the top is a
tower that has the face of a clock on it
so a clock tower
exactly you don't think it it doesn't
you're not you don't think that's a time
that is on there it is referencing the
real time times it is outside it has
like half of one hand okay and like it
hasn't service it's not an operation
they didn't photograph you can be reps
we could be rats who knows rat hate time
exactly but this is the they're the
enemies who is their natural enemy yeah
kind of the enemy of the past I think
he's the fastest time and I reckon
you're this whole campaign is going to
be about the song exactly Oh amazing
predictable thought was prudent hegemony
was know Karl Marx Marx is raised very
like that big bad boss at the end all
right he's at the top of large Benjamin
here it could be so it's like I'm
allergic Benjamin this this site I hate
you can we tell some rest please
I love it go get this rat killed by
Benjamin so this clock tower if you will
yes there's a name today plenty of ice
okay all right Marge Benjamin QQ don't
[ __ ] don't encourage me favor ISM
don't it Kersey's Beast
all right this very special story of
guys I want here's no no no but this
tower is the property of Hallie OTT
chief who is a Dragonborn
finally thank God who a dragonborn
alchemist who currently operates this
place not a not a sorcerer another
wizard not a warlock Graham supplies the
town with lotions and potions so
Knightly speaking i Jed and then Bethel
beyond exactly it's like yeah it knows
it is beyond beds and baths yeah mmm but
but yeah there's a wide sort of almost
barn door Dumbledore shape at the base
let's go inside them yes store there we
go we got wet yellow go in looking for
rats see we're looking for ya over the
podcast but I took it out of in our
family wait did you did you guys do this
place already that's why it took so long
for you to come get me because you
cleaned this one first and then you came
Oh sweetie we now know we we hello
birthday party for dinner let's not talk
about it oh you're alive he's dead what
what do you want 'god as you as you
approach the idea first a double doris
you see a window higher up in the
rickety structure thrown open and you
see a platinum scaled Dragonborn high up
he's thrown over the window and he says
rat rat yeah we're here about the rat is
it hey finally god damn i like this guy
he's yeah we're here to get a man he
gets it he gets a descent an eyeful of
dinar Blitzen scrunches of his fate
recognized everywhere you feel right now
he closes this window and the doors at
the base open and allow you access you
know it look like you like you very much
doors open isn't it you love me how
could you not and we go so that you you
feel like the lower floors sort of you
can see some rough shelving and things
like that you feel like rats have
started at the bottom of this tower
another here yeah they started from the
bottom now the whole town [ __ ] here
correct but you can tell that they have
they have had their way with virtually
every had every edible thing down here
hmm
sure you know I'm talking about mm-hmm
deep breath
yeah yeah the rest hey so um but you can
be any Brad chakra difference is the
first we never apologize very bad so
these these stairs in the same way that
coriander is barely a horse like these
barely constitute anything that you
would want to walk on by choice
rats have gone nuts on these as well you
pass up through the the middle tier of
this and you see various alchemical
apparatus
many of them broken vials without
stoppers throwing us thrown to the side
I just note to myself there's got to be
some kind of health code violation I'm
wondering that reform for yeah it's
almost perfect
almost certainly workers comp together
so I'm a little like thanks for saving
this place for me yeah it didn't heaven
over here like this yeah you you
approach the third and final tier of the
venue and these things appear to be this
appears to be a functional laboratory
you can see that that you know beyond
all you know all that the lower floors
would indicate many of these jars and
flasks contain liquids which you feel
like is going to be the baseline for any
alchemist
you know what I mean like this is this
is where an alchemist would do some
[ __ ] alchemy [ __ ] oh yeah 100% wall to
wall it's the idea least eight different
pests it's the IKEA of alchemy you can
see a lot of a lot of materials there
and you get and you can see how as you
can see Hallie act moving around kata ya
know you can you can see a Hallie AK
sort of moving around from bigger to
beaker making mild adjustments in terms
of temperature
whispering occasionally to them he has a
process and he likes it and then without
without even looking back
kiss-kiss yeah he says every kind of
wild jung-min how came you by this cloak
this one um why does it smell like I was
feeling a little bit at the moment I get
I can get it he snorts he says I've seen
it's like but not this make oh
interesting this was found a in a
feeding goblins cart hmm he three turns
around he applies a stopper with a six
some blocks overlooks this just never
like this never like this out of order
he says generally they show the Stars as
we see them
tell me about it interesting it's weird
right
it is weird is playing data no yeah it
is weird it's weird aberrant apparent
becomes not bare ever how but how brant
friends well as you saying this is a
knockoff I couldn't tell you the red
stars a ring of red stars oh this is not
it's a special feature exact Chua Lee it
could be I can't imagine what would the
book of stars is a classic I can tell
you I'm just wearing it I haven't seen
any like it I just assumed that this was
a part and parcel would go oh get up if
he would bought it somewhere I would say
you should take it back modifications
like this never go well oh that's a
choice of phrase that I'm grateful for
because I thought
fashion he says I should I should give
you some information before things go
too much further well we love
information did you you you must have
seen the status of the first and second
floors looking rough that's real
functional though that's good Dragonborn
engineering right there can either
perception both sure are you sure can
you sure can has one where is it there
it is I'm gonna roll jack-jack it's not
a deliberate all right well fine
all right right that was worse that's
the one yeah got a nice slappy eight
something's bugging you but you don't
know what it is okay cool um can I use
try something's bugging me like
intelligence oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
just even you've taken in a lot of data
and it's not something that not yes it's
been a weird day right I don't wanna see
sighs yeah yeah it's the witching hour
um he says he says the second floor
especially sustained profound damage at
the hands of the rat infestation and I
need to make it absolutely clear to you
it would be malpractice on my part if I
did not communicate this with full force
I know it's my discretion that's on the
line here these rats may have drunk
several potions what's that a piece kind
of yeah what do you make it Rosie and
walnuts and Ian isn't ahead well I have
certain potions for which I am well
known and such a good price here in
Nana's ear and it's dude they're dragon
board potions I guarantee they're
amazing right yeah right guy we know it
needs Wow do they just glares at me
yesterday Michael no
Dragonborn and we're the best right yeah
right right
business shorthand writing a roleplay
yeah there's no Jenny Warren
yeah just read from that card yeah it's
just janar need i say more so your
course ugly that is not yes what of it
yeah Wow god I'm good yeah yeah janar
but his name isn't his infan our it is
tennis but he called Yujin are well
that's a member of the clan people don't
know that
no I didn't know there are platinum
princess Oh called you - it is okay a
lot of helping yeah like it before
yeah earthly yeah he says thank you all
right well Norris
he's let's get into it I have a potion
of haste great i brewing great batches
hmm
incredible for cleaning the tower huh
yeah yeah yeah exactly you know yeah
also drank some before yeah exactly
there is a lightening potion that I make
that does add a drink
sure and you won't like that and also a
potion of giant strength mmm very the
lead on this one yeah you you'll know
which you'll know which one that is
you'll definitely wheeler one cannot
obey or was that there's smoke there
more you'll get a sense of which rat
might have had the the giant potion do
they have like an expiration on them
should we come back after that yeah like
like a last we're 10 minutes per round
per caster level or something they had a
lot and I thought it would be over by
now so those are good potions do you
have any of those good potions ready
right now
that good good potions is like I lost
my entire stock I'm in the process of
making more now how long will it be like
five minutes ten minutes he goes back
and starts looking at all the potions
and just gets completely lost him
so longer than ten minutes just doesn't
begin he's doing some kind of math on
his claws we see this with a lot of
clients I mean you should have called us
on the first sip
yeah it's awaited you know we're gonna
music they like yeah hi Piper this
something gonna cost extra you waited a
long time wheat Jim's I'm paying them
here in the we're paying the town I may
be able to I may be able to ease your
way somewhat when I finish this batch
it'd be great okay can I take out I one
of my health potions you're wondering if
it's different than the other ones and
I'm wondering if he could and I look at
a girl needs me like the help myself
especially I look I'm going to go what
do you make of this it takes it and it's
like I almost saw my a please water yeah
exactly
either bouquet cork off fresh-cut garden
hose
quick pass hmm not Natalie exactly two
quick passes got good legs if you could
tip if this is thicker than a health
potion generally is I'm not sure that
any of the ingredients in this potion
would be shared with a health potion
mmm-hmm I think this is not a health
potion you know what it might be well
grab a rat and of course they do Rasmus
is portion of incident rat yes exactly
so you see um you're not gonna let him
take it he's not trying to drink it okay
my god no no try to find out okay you
get the impressions this is not someone
to get by on their own some warriors
building up a resistance hierarchy so I
okay powder exactly know
he brings it over to his his array and
pours it into a flask my god yeah
begin begins to apply heat um and then
as he does this you can hear what sounds
like the stairway collapsing oh okay
and you can you hear just like the ton
of the wood splintering it's almost a
musical tone as some of the wood splits
and then you can see but like around the
edge where the staircase would be you
see two massive claws right on the lip
of the edge and then it pulls itself the
rest of the way up and it looks like it
looks like a professional wrestler
except it is a rat rattler a profession
rattling recyclin right in rattler okay
so I look at the alchemists granite all
right well if that turns out to be
something incendiary then you let me
know immediately
Wow I know gang giant rat I have a I
want to I want to use something right
now okay that I want a Buster potion I
have a little you have this [ __ ] that
you got from Chris Perkins anyway right
it's just one oh yeah where is it
I'm pushing a fire-breathing and now
seems like really really good fun yes
sir you can have burned down life it was
not the question to get rid of the rest
no the whole city's made of iron you
can't find it that's right you bring the
wood dandy someone's been thinking about
someone's been thinking about how you
are down an unburnable City now possible
Unferth fresh start
hi friend did he just tell you that you
had that and he didn't give you any
stats for it not at all
okay you can't have it you're gonna
sabotage me thanks Chris know exactly
what we need no no a time the job at the
time you want no I've read the fire in
the record all right we'll have drink
the potion let's go so I burn
all the mystery or what is the answer to
whatever that was so so you you
quaterback I feel like I'm in good
supervisory hands basically at the
hospital exactly exactly so you use a
professional someone already handling up
you pop the top now let's get some let's
get some initiative going yeah oh you
ten twenty twenty-one is 1/t yes
twenty-three as well yeah cuddle all
Aaron Nishant
alright so here initiation so this this
massive chunk of rodent beef this pulled
is doing its pull his way up through the
edge from a burnin my way he drops
himself to all fours you can see that
his back is just covered with rats that
has clung on to the hair and flesh I
made the right choice
mama rat he's gonna say and they and
they just they spring off in droves
he's going to say we should wait until
that one he told the other yeah it's
super and they're larger um more
aggressive okay this these are not your
grandma's rats so how big but how big
are the rest
giant unusual sense yeah are you yeah
yeah I mean I was there the giant the
giant rat like the giant sir he is like
a person right and then all of us all
the rest of his friends I would describe
as more rosy sighs okay cool that's the
time yeah yeah but it is your turn and
I'm not pretty large while I'm trying to
figure out if I could like ride them
have a conversation um no no a
conversation this is not time for
conversation I'm holding my breath
because I'm full of fire oh yeah you
have an AoE look at to a wheeze I got
308 a wheeze cuz it's a corner um okay
so these are all these things they're on
the ground they're on the ground they
jump oh yeah yeah I think they base we
all went off yet and I know finding
their way through the I would feel it
like to
ready set the floor center a a spike
growth growth on the I want to put it so
it gets the big guy you want to lay it
out at the far end of the room yeah but
not Thomas oh no no I know you finish me
well sometimes um the area becomes
difficult terrain okay you know what
that means we then create remove we
drive to or within the area it takes tg6
piercing damage for every five feet it
travels the transformation of the ground
is camouflage to look natural any
creatures that can't see the area at the
time the cell is cache must make a
wisdom so it looks it looks natural
so looks so as we Harmon exactly so as
you summon up independence is just this
is your action for this turn yes yeah so
as you summon it up the if you know had
you done it in the forest it would be
brambles and you know other types of
dangerous ground cover and this it looks
like the broken flasks and things that
you saw below right this is like ready
to pop yeah well listen no obviously
they want to pop Rosie let's talk about
it yeah what happened exactly
so getting hidden a big rat or just kind
of given up I'm aiming for him but I'm
gonna get whatever it is oh man that is
a lot of damage
whoo jumpin Jesus it nimrat yeah that's
a whole lot this is a gremlins to
scenario and they all get special powers
yeah exactly you very unique and wrap a
potion for every rat or the section of
the door where the gargling
by where you guys just cool like your
halfling friend just erupted in flames
is it's just like yes I didn't get you
chug a potion whose turn is it next yeah
exactly so you do it how I like to do
nice we're like really know knows you
know don't attack the enemy okay cool
yeah no all right I say that that's
almost as cool as acid thank you that's
a high compliment comes in it it's high
is what I get delivery then although it
agrees with me the giant rap is now
ablaze
yeah nice wondering that one of the
lighting rats you can tell Zeppelin Fort
Wayne um but it's clear which was the
lighting rats because they're completely
pooped like like they looked at their
like hairy spheres that sort of like
just put a pop and pop around right oh
yeah yeah absolutely exactly but there's
two other rats that had come in on the
back as well they were able to avoid it
completely they are like absolutely
unnatural speed but they're doing the
regular like the pause but it's like
sped up twice okay it's a bad scene
cutter strobe yak emerging from a mist
cloud that's what I say I did say yeah
why'd it have to be fat gross I'm gonna
throw a hex on my big boy
maybe if I may yeah and let some look at
you too let me quickly Vil there XE
[ __ ]
yeah hmm excellent I'm a hick flyboy
let's do strength uh spikes it go down
yeah strength no no have as much and um
cash I want to do it I got to do it
reading in that earth for too long yeah
and the death of legate my favorite
tentacle it fury ated me secretly and
only now do I realize the weight of it
so I'm going to do a tentacular
spectacular course Lord okay horse you
get all these wrapping flying all around
alright man well here dish up the Arkana
check let's see if it works any better
fetus oh yeah oh yeah yeah Wow
you ever be like salty about it maybe
works by the way even if you do it it's
gonna be a I think it's gonna be a
vegetable roll 14 yes no 14 is not in
that darn it it's okay good things are
still gonna happen when I say good
things I mean good things for you I
don't mean as good things for rats
no no that's off the air where am I
where do I get my tentacles where they
come out don't worry where they come out
because she has murdered a lightning rat
right I did oh I don't know they over
Corp space yeah yeah nice well yeah if
we're not giving the back okay
I'm at least one yeah exactly you
definitely come out of like oh yeah yeah
there's a bunch of scenarios where they
can interact with you so much Dan around
us guys
yeah yeah exactly they can you recommend
mercy exactly does this there's always a
ready supply of corpse me so you can see
this just upside down shuttering sort of
jittering rat and I'm soon as I come on
boy no way I mean oh yeah exactly and
then you reach out and then from it draw
the spectacular and it's almost like
it's in the same way like imagine like a
beautiful candelabra like I imagine like
in like a dance scene from Beauty and
the Beast okay
imagine the polar opposite of that so
imagine that this razor sharp lattice
geometrical shape bursts up and out a
second in some way by the electrical
charge of the rats and then as it goes
up and begins to slightly spin and sway
in the mid air pieces of it just start
to fling themselves toward targets oh
how handy
yep so I'll roll that stuff up on your
next turn okay uh dinar Blitzen yeah do
you get one I was on the big one still I
right oh yeah he's on fire but he
doesn't care I'm a I'm a simple man with
simple pleasures and I just go dude rush
yeah that's just a harm strike yeah cuz
I go right in don't have to roll
automatically handsome new cannon but
but but you're got the teeth on it again
you can't go to see no this this sharp
ground doesn't care you know okay I just
want to make sure you understand what's
going on oh so it's going to hurt any
enemy is he has not left okay so he
stole at the edge reclaim the sharpness
all right well if he hasn't acted yet
yeah right so you're welcome to go over
there it's going to take a little damage
to d6 is some six pack all the six to do
I would try to b4 to d4 yeah your every
five feet of travel yeah exactly
and so he has tonight can I ask to get
over to it can you go can I leap over
and take a right what's cool yeah what
are you guys all right no little Vikas
this is kind of cool you can cancel the
spell obviously whenever you want I
don't want I know but I love this it's
pretty cool all right
yeah uh I would like an athletics check
from my youth okay I haven't Linux 2 so
plus 3 X 10 so queer stretch up it's
okay so I'm gonna let you do that and
I'm going to shave a bunch of the damage
off but you take for now I want to see
the attack role of a lifetime on this
strong boy all right I have advantage
and I'm going to take advantage and I'm
also going to great weapon master I'm a
senior at amazing I'm a [ __ ] about Rocco
Mac I bought this rat all right Oh Oh
God all right Oh up from my tentacle
thing - yeah of course
or in corporate hell no okay yeah we
didn't we didn't know one fell that I do
that naked as in I don't get my bonus
but it's that's the swaps
2d 6 plus 3 plus 10 good lord it Louise
so 4 oh yeah 5 6 7 8 9 19 Canon [ __ ] oh
yeah yeah he's dead no [ __ ] you hack you
had his left heart his left arm is
completely off it's like if it falls
down the hole behind him did he did yeah
there's no on the right arm round my
house for me no you can't it um unless
you really want it for some reason but
I'm doing on the way out I'll get it all
right that's a big arm yeah exactly you
know carrying hoping I would kill them
with that - so get a bonus or you'll be
good it goes straight off basically you
just sheared off the lesson from the
shoulder down and then he'd whales uh
it's a ratty whale
and he swipes his claws straight online
sorry Craig no can you can you get us
back and get us at something right all
right all right that's a person exactly
it should sound like I'm just a man yeah
get going ah no I'll get you a key
electric 11 points you know go feels
like a man but yeah guys wow if it my
suspicion is that it's like oh my
gooooood quite have you seen everything
that videos of the cats with the
unfortunately low you know you got a
look at like they have some laryngitis
coming and it literally sounds like it's
not what I'm a person I'd never faked
like a bored person yeah absolutely so
at this at this point so the swipe has
just come straight across the face
emboldened thus his fellows began to
leap and cavort
he's wickedly fast rats you're catching
it right in the face you know and then
wickedly fast
rats are leaping up off of the ground
grabbing pieces falling down and then
leaping up again in the same amount of
time one attack right it's madness let's
see rat flurry mm-hmm that's for you
that is 12 points yeah Wow okay very I'm
not doing great
here and I got you moving around in this
zone has delivered some brutal strikes
we take to the rats go to the rest yeah
burn damage do something on fire oh yeah
just check I kind of make sure I'm not
crying
I'm sure you city is on fire I got it
alright that's lady only fire once in
her life
yeah it's special that's right yeah
exactly I did one shopping it's like I
could see the article um I'm spaghetti
that's it
walnut on grass that's unclear yeah um
so I look at the nine he's looking goofy
but he's in my spike area so I guess I
got to do that and we cancel that out
genesee um and I want to go up behind
him
and just wait no every age is 60 feet in
a driveway I don't have RAM and you can
do this from the couch yeah I'm great um
so I'm going to a 1d for my spell
casting ability okay I'm going to do
healing word and I creature of my choice
that I can see within range reading two
points equal to 1 D 4 plus my spell
casting ability modifier so that's one D
for press this which nice six you can
get 8 tasty will eight yum yum yummy
today what is your what is your healing
word I'm in Bouldin oh my healing word
is live you son of a [ __ ] no yeah um
she's like uh pepperoni okay I feel the
confident they'll give me the Falcon
will generate we got great healing word
yeah yeah I just I'm sure it'll be the
best thing you're going to think I'm
sure not to overhype this but this will
probably be the greatest thing we've
ever heard table after next time please
II be with you know she missed emerges
Rosie yeah um she has collapsed her foot
shredding field okay um there are two of
these ridiculously comically fast case
rats um one damaged lightning rat like a
lightning retina hey scram yeah needle
in hand there is this this this the
giant strength rat is savaged like okay
that's the that's the environment that
you see before you all right I don't
have a way to slow the hay straps so
that's going to be on somebody else but
I will take on that muscle boy and I
will do a find a key point and try to go
all all bonkers on yes funky don't sound
good yeah in rent space okay
so this is a quarter staff strike is
going to be a 19mm
and that is Julie when do you meet Plus
for a ten point
and then two unarmed strikes come in
active that's a 13 nope and that's a
14th yes okay
and that will be another seven points
down shoes yeah yeah yeah is it you you
give them a firm instructive whack
across the nose and then right just
right following the strike to the open
palm strike right to the solar plexus
straight down the hole there is yet to
manage these two haste rats and
enlightening rat as well cut wrists
route okay what are the what are the
Jews are on Twitter now what are the
positions of the true calm yeah oh the
great website so because I want to I
want to do some damage I guess let's
stop this this big boy first heat hoax
oh he's wrecked he's straight down my
leg action school I'm alright three
sicker over there tweeting then find me
and finally another one takes right
another large rat - hey tracking you do
anything histogram then no I can't say
boys I got no slow but I can eat but I
can I can shatter them that's what I'm
gonna do
yeah shot you're gonna like it shredder
uh alright so I select that that sphere
yeah that I see them all in
they all are doing that and let's real
yeah yeah you should you should you'll
be able to catch the hey strats together
okay they got to do a constitution
center and throw each of them sweet rats
can they be 214 somebody didn't that's a
show now neither of them did but can you
beat a 14 it's different kind of
physical challenges yeah okay watch me
do I have to make the COS position are
you in the our unit very image on them
autism get in zone almost certainly in
the zone ah were you there I should have
known the function of the way the pizon
okay I have a constituent envision so
we're taking a good wedding ruler
okay okay sorry to and I'll go ahead oh
no oh no murder you're fine yeah it's
Capulet
give me a half damage on a sale yeah
oh here we go for damage 3d8 oh one of
them - mm-hmm
ten toes and that's sixteen totally so
enjoy eight damage for you and then how
the other arrested I'm sorry
okay other rats hey how I take - you
take half yeah yeah it did survive eight
insist on yes they become like chunks
hmm no not not a story it's like if you
could exactly if you could go to the
store and it's like they've got like ol
rat and then it got like rats ready for
stew right it's the second challenge
that exactly exactly
there is Annabelle Poe exactly Dennard
listen there's a one there's one loading
red lightning rat and that's the only
thing left right you just took out both
the little ones yeah go speed you must
be Eddie Lena that sword down yeah it's
time to go connect on some get that rush
I need to talk to your dentist over here
time to get rid of them yeah you're not
gonna straight weapon master this I
don't think it needs it and I get plus
five if I don't use that so yeah
something's got me good plus yeah whoosh
my god
yeah twelve yes oh good got it hey hey
I'm the best to eat eleven oh well okay
I was always thinking well he gets
another round no he doesn't
but as he as you as you bring the tooth
the ruthless toothbrush straight through
him energy arcs five points Wow seven
energy arcs straight bags all the to
thing can I get it for second check yeah
you sure can
oh my healing word by the way is uh have
I got a treat for you yeah those are
many works
not anything seven he had some well
receive I got a little thirsty pressure
yeah we receive ah it's for me
alright it's for you I'm still no
profession he the alchemist says yeah I
think I've he turns around through the
pressure actually thank you yeah
thank you very much for with you I will
work I will send I will send a note to
Mayer France ignore immediately great
but about that portion oh yeah don't
drink these definitely don't not with
your mouth yeah yeah mouth your mouth uh
you could I think that it would be a
superlative weapon coating so topical
then I would we say suppository I would
not drink it with your mouth what about
a little discrim between lip and gonna
she can attend the poses perhaps
hmm don't do that so alright so I
collect it back for him I assume yeah
okay great
I cook it up see that in there I brush
with you often I say I'm not a brat
alright I know go see you then yeah
that's why I missed the way I kind of
give him a secret Dragonborn handshake
oh yeah yeah sure you can't see it it
was ass itself avocado and a fairy on
the car secret he goes over and looks
down the stairs that used to be there
and pumps to himself and digs around up
a ladder into a light attic um he says I
may need some help up here
finding the rope ladder great I'll go up
there be like okay I'm gonna help this
dragon do you I thought dragons could do
everything but Wow let's go oh wait
should we do some dragons are better
than other I want to not leave that
there's somebody go to a secret zone
yeah okay I get your way to Corinne so
yeah you're here you're there you see
much older equipment much older
technology stuff that's not really in
much use but there is a sort of fax
machine yeah exactly
there's a pinhole window okay from this
upper tier that looks out over the town
I need another perception roller cream
but this floor confers a different thing
all right do you roll the number and add
your stuff as usual but I have a a plus
that is applied from the that's great I
also have a VIN yeah yeah okay
picked it thank goodness because I'm
rolling like a garbage hit like two 20s
today hi Patrick Oh have one the bad one
when when when when my ring so if I see
everything if I hadn't in too hot
exactly he's like oh here it is
but you its muffled like even the sound
of it is muffled because you figure out
what has been bothering you come on man
what that's true don't do to me no not
looking down at the city yes okay here
from the clock tower at the northern tip
of the city you see plain as day yes
that belief shape of the entire city huh
the city is a leaf a leaf it is the
shape of a leaf now I expected the
curved outer wall mm-hmm
draws itself up into a leaf shape even
the roads everything about it is mapped
exactly to a the natural world what
about what about the base what's at that
room look at the stem the stem that's
the path into town no the one gate into
town as they done here I don't know but
I suppose right here I suspect we'll
have to find out next
Wow on the CT hey precious shadow
channel we are going to avail ourselves
of the facility's corporeal form indeed
indeed and we will return to hang out
with you shortly
don't go
anywhere will see a little bit
you