time at the enemies the past threatens
the fastest whether you were to make
attacks to second and then the question
play it flash and records to choose a
course in solution you thought was
prudent in any step of [ __ ] Krypton
will become the future it's that well
that I pursue in no mountain to Steve
but dungeon to deem them expendable
marks up to the top of the peak of
beneath maybe they come like sharks you
wait while I swim in that line again by
Carl Barks through is essential national
parks through it I'll send them all in a
natural box the postcard or most of the
parts included they regret for a cleric
confessor that did the lessons like a
contending professor but if you speak in
my official advice sign on the dotted
line English of the twice hello I'm
Tycho Brahe hey a painter painted packs
also a manifest Hereward run CEO of
acquisitions incorporated but today I'm
Jerry Holton and I'm here to play a game
Dungeons and Dragons with my friends to
my right Dragonborn narcissist look at
the NAR blip there we go first instinct
is that is very wonderful Ryan Hardy no
I know he calls himself something else
yeah in this gainer ribbon it's only
even one and and wells episode repping
the natural world back at it walnuts on
grass 100% right in the middle of it
ball all night a well not a heavy arc
hmm by the end of this arc you will be
exhausted by walnut on grass laying with
walnut you you will say this is enough
hmm not for long I turned down the nut
mmm developing an allergy exactly to my
left
not your grandma's Graham a rosy bee
stinger Wow sour and then to the left of
rosy bee stinger we have a newcomer
so we have a in our in our guys as Penny
Arcade
we also have a organization called
child's play whose purpose
oh yeah it's a bomb whose purpose is to
put games and toys in hospitals and
domestic violence shelters
where hopefully they can make those
scary places a little bit less scary to
that end we actually auctioned off a
seat at the table for what was then a
completely unnamed unannounced project
that became the seating so it is my
great pleasure to introduce Devine the
teasing sorcerer here with us today
do you reckon with its rifling that's
right yeah at a fling that there's no
foreshadowing there and we also have
Chris drought this time who was also
plays Dungeons and Dragons with us
basically I go actually my over here
yeah yeah yeah here four point seven
it's right it's all right that's why
won't Robin
I'll probably get all the way there so
let's see snow when last we saw our
heroes they had returned to the site of
the burrowing creature that they came to
know as the wandering crypt deeply tied
in with the CEO of acquisitions
incorporated in some way it's sort of
his white whale apparently he has sought
it and failed to capture it failed to
destroy it and it
we don't 100% understand all of that
maybe that's what this entire campaign
is about Lou knows is over the other
having happy not having returned to the
cavern prepared ready to you know
discover its deeper mysteries they
learned that the wandering crypt
had wondered and as I wanted indeed
indeed and as a result I mean yeah I get
it you got it
yes in the deep it strange trails and
glassing is though from heat and bizarre
creatures simply left behind in its wake
created a truly strange and alien
environment up to and including a series
of symbols that it is sort of edged in
the wall symbols that sort of sit
halfway in the depth of the glass on the
stone some symbols we recognize for
example the symbol of Carthoris Travis
patron the herb which we had seen inside
the creature itself but there was also
another symbol this piece of [ __ ] I've
been thinking about so there was another
symbol indeed the symbol of MELAS who
has a gruesome reputation in walnuts
order by the Enclave packs anima it is a
unrideable symbol children learn about
it
so that they can destroy whatever they
see it on and if its entire purpose it
is it is the literal icon and symbol of
the enemy a betrayer so in the ancient
history of the EPA Maliki and maelys
both held sway over a vast forest that
in the lore of the EPA once covered the
whole of the planet now that region is
to be like that it sounds 400 let's
bring it back to that one city at a time
so now the place where that power is
greatest is a region south of the sword
mountains called the crypt garden forest
still wooded but the power of the EPA
has waxed and it is waxed steadily ever
since this schism between Maliki and
bailiff bailiff ceased answering prayers
and became known as Mela the betrayers
so that is the situation we find
ourselves in you have laid your eyes
upon this
this icon of of hate and loathing here
in the here in the guts of this cavern
where these symbols are continuing to
Sparkle the ten tacular spectacular
unleashed by kethry strobe if it's it's
rays that he used to destroy the
creature of now withdrawn as though you
know like so many power cords on vacuums
maybe that's not the appropriate
metaphor no I like a did a weapon in the
face guys go to go they on variated
there it's several of them already went
through it that's true
no they go imagine right mission yeah
yeah yeah no no hit the button katrell
is cut at a three thousand pieces
wow you got some Devine just go ahead
and stretch I check in my space if you
take Michael it's a good one yeah enjoy
it thank you all sending three thousand
pieces because I take it back together
oh yeah anything right yeah I guess so
yeah yeah definitely don't you take the
bed that's the deepest irony um I'm
ready
yeah exactly so that's abuse this symbol
that should never be written a single
time is written by your guests at least
a hundred times a lot of time and
there's no way to get it out it's
literally suffused even in the glass I
mean it would take what what you are
required to do is not possible which is
to destroy it absolutely something to
challenge yeah I'm ready
yeah start talking about this air form
so I immediately freeze when trying to
like suppress what I'm feeling right now
because one I know that I'm supposed to
get rid of it and two
this is definitely the type of thing
that I would document but I'm not going
to why not why not Amy
I mean walnut is dammit um yeah I can't
I so I don't reach from
I think it's unreadable and I okay so
please okay that's what I don't say
anything to the party I also purposely
look away from as many of them as
possible and just fix my gaze down the
tunnel and just try and give everyone a
like okay let's let's move along um but
you know you guys might be able to see
that woman it's like stiffened a little
bit if you were everywhere you look
every every place every every place like
every like psychic lilly pad you try to
find in your visual field eventually you
discover it you don't know if they're
moving through the glass every place
your eyes rest you start to see it and
so you are you are basically trying to
find a place a darker place where this
is not visible and you come across you
come across a heap of shredded wheat
armour-wood if it looks like in that if
it matters pump well you imagine imagine
if a crow we're very very large think
about all the time yes imagine this
imagine the type she's kidding imagine
the type of net that it would create
okay so deceptively small nest is
actually very its Janice it is robust
and in fact there is there is there's a
couple eggs in this nest mmm jet-black
eggs and there are also eggs there's
also smaller versions of this nest sort
of scraped out of the walls the deeper
in you get so not obviously not regular
in terms of they're like a distance from
each other anyway I mean this is very
very natural you know an animal behavior
and so there's clutches and eggs all
around but in the nest that is here at
the base there is actually a person
inside this
asked who's whose robes have been
bloodied but you can see that there
their chest is still rising and falling
hmm so I look at it and I look back as
an orange is very quietly go medic uh I
start laying on hands
um yeah I just say can I think I can't
how much Bell dings okay
Hoss important to elastic a full nap
Internet
there we go I'm Christopher yeah we take
a nap no Dave and there you go uh so
yeah so then doesn't nest right here all
right yeah that's true I just cuddle up
in the nest you say reg is it regular
pillow next to the failure live body oh
thank you interesting that you see that
black eggs just wheeling a little bit
yeah in their nest
none of that all right don't fall down
do I go over they wobble I'll go over
and examine the person whose blood that
exactly
oh wait ha horns okay all right
now yell back I go I see more guys I
don't know what to make of it I don't
trust her because yeah she's not wearing
awesome opposition think Brandon
merchandise you can buy on Penny Arcade
homes in our Central Pacific well not a
very good door yeah only we don't know
what you said when one of them means no
it means everything like it that hits
you like an apart right beyond oh man
yeah listen it's done no it's okay
they're cutting it for some reason
dinars to best clearly I'm going to have
a specific you're closer double so uh I
see the horns and I'm like oh okay I
feel better about what we're little
wincing yeah it may be her nest
oh you I'm willing to to lay on hands
okay cool with this yeah she's bloody
she's sweating and this is what if we
don't I'm so going to sit here three
hundred grandmother's room to like tie
her hands
yeah you're right until I take out Chris
Emma tarring I just hold it up yeah and
I go okay now you can yeah
Megan Mueller all right I don't think
she did this
well not done grass everybody but yet he
could be disoriented when she becomes
healed or something and maybe she said
you know that's what size is she
what's our sequence it ranges but
there's there's a slightly taller than
chemo what size is this just like five
six I think we take her like if last
time we did this it was in the end and
that crazy guy who at night oh yeah
oh the underwear boy yeah is it all
right I mean haven't done all right yeah
I did to know how she got in here that's
all right we got a healer yeah cue it
lay on the pan oops
okay that works you're Roy yellow red
like mr. Miyagi it's Karate Kid how many
good points are you confer oh yeah yes
I'm a fool
yeah I know that's true oh wait my I've
got more now because we went up on the
board I read that you know 20 I think
I'm up to 20 I'll be 15 before so I'll
do we'll just do I also have he'll we'll
do 10 get it up and running
yeah what do ya got 10-foot yes mataf
right that's nice I don't know if we get
in a fight or something I have 4 X 1
plus so I didn't fit some of those for
me yeah I know I funny Mara
Davina Claire can you come to again
against against your back are chunks of
wagon torn cloaks your own your own
sorceress garb is torn blood is drying
on the front you can recall entering the
cavern and not much else so I have no
idea where the wagon bets came from no
no no no you entered the cavern of your
own free will and encountered something
and now you are in a nest
surrounded by weirdos yes surrounded by
scimitars and weirdos good morning I'm
gonna do this not it not it
I saved your life yes yeah yeah thank
you
ah don't mention it you can mention it a
little if it comes up yeah Oh your
friends if in the future you feel a hard
rush of wind from deeper in the cave
blow past the party mm-hmm well I think
of it it smells good to me I tend to buy
that like a well previously everything
everything else that you've experienced
has been some bizarre new construction
you know what I mean is it like freshly
freshly clawed stone the creature that
it deposits apparently weird symbols
this this smells like the type of deeps
that you're familiar with okay okay this
is this is coming from way down this all
there's a million scenarios you can
think of for this that's probably like
20 words there's like 20 drow words for
the weirdest damn underground bandwidth
Grove least yeah surely yeah super game
the moisture is this there's different
accents and moisture you can employ into
the defense and you want a lot of
exclamation points yeah like Danny I'll
say something right away I want to look
at that easily and be like miss you
might not know but we are actually from
acquisitions incorporated and then I
actually go for the level of badges and
and I say we're here on official
business you know don't be alarmed
during good hands but any information
you have is to how you got in here
have you seen equipped wandering
anywhere are you Christmas party that's
wandering through house the day does
that mean anything no not that
particular
um group that particular set of words
does not meaning the wandering crypt as
a as a piece of verge acquisitions Inc
mean anything to my irons incorporated
as you understand it specify service for
PCs well it's one of these places that
that you can pay to do things that you
should do yourself yeah it's a Radio
Shack of adventuring yeah it's the
Gobots so I just kind of go thank you
thank you very much you're welcome
oh I'll keep that wandering Crypt
business in mind if I happen to see a
crypt that is wandering mm-hmm but did
you see one earlier how did you end up
here I don't think I saw a crypt if I
see anything that is dead I'll let you
know okay oh thank you and then I pull
out like acquisitions and calling card
it was like our children car dealers
address oh yeah and one of things all
the classic documents yeah yeah and I
never know Eileen if something's Elise
you know I never - all night and I go I
we should just quick draft up a bill for
reviving her I think myself and I look
certain is me I like to do a perception
check on these pegs yes I'm a awesome
9-3 there at eggs well I like so I want
to oh yeah yeah you have a +3 egg come
lay an egg yeah not that I am survival a
hold on math it's over 20 yeah yeah it's
over 12 heads
so the twinkers exactly the these are
right chicken eggs yeah everyone like a
ham there right there is another dark
eggs
no one by my side or what so there is
another a more concussive blast of wind
that comes out of the back and then you
can see at first at first glance it's
probably ten eyes but it could be 12 so
it's nothing that I look over to our RT
playing I'm like halfway through drawing
up a bill and I go you know in lieu of
our extensive healing services bill what
if you lent us a hand
are you proficient in any kind of combat
or I'm proficient in fireballs that is
exactly what we need we're severely
lacking in fireballs as you would think
of our magic hurt anyway we would yeah
in exchange in exchange for your
services in what we I find I'm assuming
change these eyes that are in front of
us don't look don't look directly at
them but there's eyes would you help us
sure I can do that and then Eileen bag
tonight I go free labor this amendment
awesome look this is under this table
okay help us anyway but probably jump
into this we have to figure out what
this thing is a lot of stuff from the
Underdark is dangerous it gets a bad rap
it's just like primarily dangerous like
94% 6% good or okay until you fish it
off but I want to figure out what this
thing is have I seen it before so all
that good look I'm on board with this I
feel like we kill too many things we run
into I don't know I become the moral
calm I feel like the ratios [ __ ] yeah
forgive me there would this be a nature
I mean for my knowledge are you what I
am honored I would I would take it I
would take nature or history nor nor
tree and a major leadership in will
church I don't know word plan there that
will be asking to be a 13 yes
if you've seen it you think you've seen
something with this particular eye
configuration before but you don't have
to think about it long
I take cousin because just a word fired
so it's like this the way the eyes you
see them blinking in some regular
pattern so it's not a bunch of whoa like
um hunter like binocular vision it's the
same structure I think yeah yeah it's
not like six people no going home
nope and in fact as it comes out into
the dim light near you you can see that
it's actually clinging to the ceiling
spider of the of the cavern yeah like
this is clever bird-like talons beep
crow crawling in um you can see us a
horizontally split beak at the proud of
this thing I'm not familiar with this
it's yeah it's about four it's the size
of maybe four of your carts put together
a cart right just a bullock cart through
the air for some engineers are you home
apart baby got a cart gun you got a
crystal it says no noting the proximity
of the party pull and the rest of this
brood it emits a shattering whale which
is Shannon your psyche keeping good man
or all they're all amazing yeah good run
here yeah um oh yeah okay real quick
just trying to hit yeah yeah um let me
try and talk to it and go um so you
speak with animals okay so you says you
see you see walnut walnut sort of firm
up her posture and then go
yeah woman sounds yeah whatever that
noise is happening oh no they just don't
yes so that but like really scary Oh
measles and episodes so when I faded
that to the deep row is um I say uh
we're not here for your eggs we're just
passing through we're we're we're on our
way this is this is your place this is
your nest your time just suggest down
here down here dammit
it continues to approach this is do you
have a nest big nest black eggs can't
lose not do I have enough I say uh yeah
a full nest and I want to go back to it
yes and I and I say I say yes a fullness
um hiding with young yes actually if I
have full clutch of eggs I have no need
for any more eggs sorry I just want I'm
litrenta not here for you're not here
for your eggs eat crow and then let's go
hmm and then flips down that's amazing
and it says and we all go and what would
you do if there were five ravenous spiky
but soft creatures what would I do at
the edge of your nest I just feel this
movie for we hold the flamethrower to it
thank you threaten it um pick up an egg
I would touch myself real quick just on
the face like it well that no I would
really
really [ __ ] disrespect and I get
myself in Hance ability is foliate i
just want to give myself advantage on a
charisma check real quick and then i
would scrub involvement be script
yes de knife y'all saying i've exfoliate
I mean I really why my face Satan knives
and then I want to try and come in a
role to convince this deep crow that I'm
okay I guess that's just personally
which I don't really am shipping Jack
ask you a question yo go ahead you're
trapped in this movement what's your
persuasion good persuader you did it
0 guess what my charisma bonuses given
you can't talk to the crow yeah well are
you well know are you going to Cyrano de
Bergerac this whole thing yeah yeah this
to thinks there's two things don't come
to understand this is my guy probably I
seen this guy but hold on what um I want
to take a moment to first of all
emphasize that you know we are this is a
convocation of the shadow council if we
serve at their pleasure sir and from
time to time they see fit to grant
certain boons right to the members of
the C team for their own purpose perhaps
just to amuse themselves but I'm here
all I'm saying is I just want to draw
your attention that for now for whatever
reason you have attracted there they're
good lovin I did something when they're
liking you something to consider I'm
just I'm not the boss I'm just saying
that I've got don't defy persuasion I'm
just wondering how that happened oh yeah
you're dancing um yeah I know you're
trying to get a B Plato song yeah it's a
television I asked you the advantages
there's all kinds of stuff that you can
do here cool I'm saying you have Forest
Friends is myself advantage on a
charisma thing and then I can take my
advantage do I get with you
is it a random we haven't done that role
no I know Burnett circuits alright I'm
going to do what I'm doing designer she
doesn't work anymore whatever sure so
you get advantage on charisma
yes party that was a 14 I'm gonna roll
again that was a 5 so I guess a 14 which
didn't really do anything insane
everyone I guess I'm not that convincing
okay you for your throat in the music
plays okay so I go on I would let them
pass you shall not and then I go Enix in
exchange for something what could you
want and then I look at Rosie and I'm
like but that may be hocus-pocus a
second oh yeah I'm ready
don't that story yes it's continuing to
advance now it is sort of exerted itself
here near the nest and you have I assume
vacated that particular location
absolutely yeah yeah um it's rubbing its
beak in a kind of madness against the
size of the eggs in fact it in fact it
is closed its beak around an egg there's
a sort of wide serration internal to the
beak and you can you can see that it
just sort of adjusting them moving the
eggs around scooting them around inside
the Nascars think all over Hey yeah so
you would let them go because you
wouldn't want them to hurt any eggs
while they're scared trying to run from
you because you're so impressive if you
a shame if they you know in their fear
of thrashing around kill a bunch of x8 I
like start see from experience here is
an egg manisha jith it sets yeah yeah
the pro teary mlgsweden later you guys
dare over your chain right yeah it says
it says when my it says when they shoe
their way from their eggs they will be
so hungry I'm amazing
cool I love nothing about this um she's
bluffing because I know that that the
yolk is will high content good marriage
equipment but based on what protein but
they actually had probably like two to
three days ago you didn't understand so
we'll say that I related to all of you
we you know nothing about deep growth
that true I I feel like I've seen it
before but I think I've seen anything
lies and we dark I mean it is the kind
of thing you perhaps roll for and find
out how I try you know oh I wanted to
see if I could see them at the very best
I've seen boy what I wanted this how
about I try I am yeah now that he knows
what it is cannoli history uh rubber
crow can I do a survival check to see if
I know what the natural enemy of the
deep crow is an initial plan to the
night I'm doing it if you fail it and
doing a history on it okay yeah okay I'm
going to take advantage nice I'm knowing
what the natural enemy of rock okay so
that it was seventeen and then one more
time that is not good seventeen do I
know what is natural and Miss OH these
subterranean birds tend to they tend to
frequent the larger caverns they don't
leave the deep very often okay right so
they're not they're not proponents of
the light are we speaking yes okay um so
creatures that emit a lot of light okay
one of one of their most hated creatures
in sort of the middle places that they
like as a Remer as which is a kind of a
kind of evil plaited worm with
incredible heat and light the only kind
the attaches to the bottom of that shark
has as I remember hmm a short time okay
so I leaned over to Rosie and I go I
don't where they can use can you make
any light yeah so you can do a dancing
lights or ferry fire if if you want to
in life and fireball and clean again
forget fireball I can also do nitrogen
and we have fireballs I imagined a minor
relations well okay
yeah fireballs might be nice that's a
little bit of an offensive act let's try
this more we're gonna let's do an
illusion and then we're gonna light it
up nice and I know another thing to
notice Alicia's who's gonna pass it you
know do that data for ya okay daddy um
and so I said okay on the count of three
and you know a lot of light
and then I want to say simultaneously I
use druid craft to make the sound that I
know to be a rumor as here okay
good ideas I want to spoof it I hope
you're absolutely honest when that does
it do drink rats just like I can make
animal sounds or I can lose flowers so I
can be like any little Missy in the
trance
you're a flower yeah I am what crow
doesn't want to bouquet flowers
I can also all crow do an entertaining
it's harmless potentially effect that is
following these Oh beautiful I like
animal noises I'm unprecedented a ssin
for okay for nature [ __ ] got it okay
good alright so we're throwing out a
bunch of light yes
am i involved in this light you want me
to just hang on to it unless you have I
can put those dancing lights right in it
yeah many eyes yeah the cat want the
path I'm going to flash the lights and
then the dancing lights and the sound
and the normal maximum I even to go I'm
assuming running deeper in all right
running deeper in what I'm that kill it
is that what we're looking for
you guys should figure out which yeah
well on a scatter yeah I know if there's
any like let's leave I'm opposed okay so
I use in your eye and I tell all of you
like we need agree to get this thing off
our backs and go way deeper and find
this crypt oh and then I go um I go hey
hey tinkling we haven't been properly
introduced manners will not welcome to
the welcome to the welcome to the my
hair reminder call right now yeah we're
gonna ride you the rates are really
research there is a brain Madonn right
now it is on my first year um okay and
so yes I I say I mean oh man told us to
find the wandering crypt we're here to
find the wandering crypt
I like you're going out here yeah cuz my
laundry will find it again oh by the way
in all of this so we've come upon like
the scraped out zone right with the nest
in it however they can be here but
there's still a clear like it continues
on which
would have done and we not encountered
this tiefling in a nest right we didn't
come to a like I'd like at Google yet
we're just like it's it's it's
definitely starting to loosen when you
can see that the the caverns like the
glassing yeah you saw there is starting
to sort of break down oh it's a visit
apparently if maybe it's a period of
time I know I'm not sure you'll
investigate it but the stability of the
cavern the farther you get is is not it
wasn't it was not like dwarven made you
know like it wasn't it wasn't intended
I just thought your Dark Lord could like
you know make a good cavern or something
weird but no angle or stroke him could
use the necklace to choke him he's not
Terran guy he's doing it again this is
different stuff okay fine okay bassoon
what do we do that's the absolutely you
had a you hear we gotta go if we saw
that when we entered and now we're going
to test yeah oh my god even I want to
lead with there's nothing down there
looks like trash okay
alright as we go yeah yeah okay we're
gonna do this illusion in the peace out
okay tell me much tell me about my
illusions what's one illusion
I need pretty more data um describe for
me the mysterious lights that you
conjure I don't know okay good light
I'll make a giant as large of a glowing
orb as I can yeah yeah you specialize in
orbs sure today alright I do today yeah
no I can see the beans like se like it's
all just different orbs this is so this
a giant orb starts as a pinprick and
then inflates in the cavern has been
casting the glare and exactly this
casting takes for a minute to say so you
can see like all the all the striations
all the glassing and scrapes stone just
glimmer see those wretched symbols even
clear yeah exactly right I'm still
picking down like maybe I could just
tuck and roll marathon ahead you're
throwing out how bright is this thing is
the Sun is Sun bright first of all
you're not cool
hye-rin heard a lot now yeah if I'm
going to brag looking at the Sun for a
while
plus a cluster of like 12 reflected on
just right here exactly I'm not I'm not
convinced today if my dancing lights
would add anything to this to the star
how big is this I can light it baby but
it gets substantial and you're going to
make a worm noise yeah my yeah my lights
are not up to that like Dada Dada oh
yeah can you give me a little taste of
what that were noise might be just
coming off a piece of that how many are
like three animal noises on where I'm
noise where my spirit and I swear I had
one noise that's very good I'm
frightened that's a cool one is a little
dude you could look at your family tree
startled you're going to see some weird
[ __ ] up there yeah some beasts from the
deep all right so there's you did
basically a solar system is born in this
deep cavern incredible life just this
guttural rasping worm call you don't
know what it could possibly mean you
know you don't know what it's about
but the combination of these two effects
rumbling and bouncing around the cavern
caused it to enter into sort of a
defensive Crouch over the nest fling up
roll back some and get low and just
ridiculous ending it John obviously
hangs go from the window no not that
stake exactly so it's a ridge right now
it is is trying to the wingers have gone
back trying to bring wings in front of
its eyes it is an attractor it doesn't
know where to the whether to [ __ ] or go
blind this is how my father would have
done that yeah maybe both um brilliant
Monday's to peace out yeah we should
peace out and I want to grab leg on
where
I know we're putting the back of my hand
I want to grab the back of Commerce's
cloak and I want to March him out right
okay I'm gonna wait I'm gonna be the
last one to leave I'm gonna keep an eye
on this thing I'm quick so if it starts
to come after us I'm going to do some
hair illusion attic I'm gonna you need
to inuyasha cristo i well if he starts
to show some [ __ ] mouth and i'm
watching but i there are some like
alright no I give them racially like a
little tug just so you remember yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah you're evil serpent
just wriggling out behind you it goes
and sort of rolls up your leg and then
wraps up around your back and then ends
up around on your shoulder very cool
I thought you're gonna say just coiled
up his leg right in there no wonder he
goes for that that is the trusty
commercial assessment commercial where
is the same yeah ancient drow secret
perfect Oh tonight
oh well I never talking about your
Eureka
yeah that's all I ask it's my birthday
maybe I'm convinced of the Earth's and
dispel our is what I don't feel like I'm
sorry I haven't felt there is no good
ciliary you're in you're able to emerge
out and there's no conceivable way you
can see if that this deep probe would be
able to get out of the entrancing you
guys have left don't worry about that
yeah fill it fire now oh yeah sorry no
you're the one tell me Burnham wrong
with the ground I know
yes well now you're like whoa little bit
but not what I'm also you know the
pecking order to find great the rural
pecking order Okeanos also XP so okay so
they get me every time you say that I
get it says that we didn't can't cuz you
can't leave orphans you got a kill whole
family so we have a battery oh yeah yeah
yeah yeah
leave crow Batman's the last thing we
mean we could lure it to the mouth of
the cave you know when
the prune scenario is a role be like
what deep croissant to eat and then
start making that noise oh I kind of
grub the same as the worm yeah little
action I guess the car the car is out
here at the base of the hill sort of
halfway up and sort of a jaunty angle uh
double parking brake exactly it's rolled
all the way damn it
yes no it's like it's still there
coriander has found a caustic clump of
Hill grasses to chew on all right yes I
can't order you our new tiefling friend
let me introduce you to coriander and
and I bring them over I make sure that
you're properly introduced Oh Cory
honored on the freakout
yes mrs. coriander Gerry of course
long-suffering system what a miserable
work you're a fan yeah barely alive
horse is being too kind insane described
I think the original description was a
horse in quotes
Yeah right barely arse Natalie we are a
horse without you look I had the best
joke from that session it was a for
style whole animal chuck where style
product
yes for slavered probably well-known
brands for sure your favorite topic is
the generic this is a name brand no no
no this is the generic cialis you know
so but the cars and the cars ready
coriander is ready to ferry you back up
to the DNC driver's seat every time um I
wasn't in the engine can every time she
was thinking about taking off but I'm
sure she's not she doesn't have a right
guys town but I go I go
well we entered into egg hmm what would
I call it dead of gentlemen's agreement
fiefdom Oh
hmm contractor contractor employees work
in the in the actual document see yes
she it'd be something like
a tacit unilateral arrangement yes we
entered into a tapping unilateral
arrangement so you just you just oos
some kind of you know combat oriented
service so watch isn't you pull-ups or
base we'll see maybe we could what you
work if the dishes go in there i don't
know yeah yeah yeah you're going to be
able to pay you cover them up i could
fight the the grime in our headquarters
a pay for lays hands yes exactly exactly
exactly so you're able to you're able to
get your way back out you were
incredibly clever on the way I mean the
very first thing you did when you found
this place does make a special note on
the map I'm very confident that you can
find your way back out not going to ask
for a roll you roll back into bread
larch evening is started torches are out
the drunk courtier is bouncing well with
Helene how long it take us to get back
because on the trip there I want to ask
like how did you end up down there
what were you she's not morning anymore
you guys know each other Wow anytime we
need another dragon I'm a sweet ending
under dark demon I just thought that
maybe your problem all demons oh each
other is that what you're saying yeah
about the top of our agenda is what you
get for trying to string up a
conversation
yeah hmm I'm gonna try next to mess it
up well very polite but but at the same
time yes you get you get cut off that
conversation ends quickly fine um but
but you say no I have no idea yeah what
is would you remember before you end up
down there I was wandering into the cave
and then BOOM oh so when you were going
in their cave were you excusing
something in particular did you see
those symbols and did you tell me more
about that mainly remember the symbols
but I have no idea what they mean okay
you neither
Rorschach's that yes exactly
right hey what is your friends now
nothing I did make you feel good and
elated looking egg I love it
it doesn't fit hey hey I do there in
case anybody cares what it that looks
like think of a channel this is ready
what do you like when she like says
x-play yeah it is does it make honestly
you're supposed to look like HB like
look crap but you'd say it does look
like a yeah but turning problem yeah
exactly
on the sigils yeah happy relaxing so I
mean that guy is like you guys are you
just having a conversation
yeah it's just I mean it's the the drunk
courier is is definitely in a good spot
it's just loud or is there anything
going on I'm not just if this is you
know having seen a ghastly apparitional
version of it many times and having seen
you know populated entirely with
illusions is that weird
jim dark magic themed version of it and
then generally speaking you haven't been
homeless you've been out a lot this is
one of the first times you've had to see
what the drawing courrier means around
here like what it does what its purpose
is and there's actually so there's a new
a new challenger like if we were playing
the street fighter version of the c-team
do that you would see a bar that came
across and said here comes a new
challenger oh I want to look in at the
window just be like yeah
so you see you can hear the music even
outside on the what what kind of music
is it Jeremy countries because it what
instrument does it sound like oh no I'm
not thinking I'm thinking something else
yeah no oh it's a it's a lute it's a
pretty traditional huh that's a pretty
traditional scenario over on the small
stage that has heretofore been
completely empty
Tom stage yeah yeah you can see uh you
can see a woman dark skin
red red robe definitely in command of
this in um and you can see you can see
some very idle cup drying happening at
that I just gonna say my is profit
really yeah yeah yeah you can see you
can see that just you're not sure this
glass is being dried at all like you
think it is probably still wet and
occasionally someone will come up for a
drink and then she won't look at them
and she just kind of waved them away you
can tell that this is this is what this
Inn is about at the end of the day
imagine two points in this continuum
imagine just complete unfettered
creativity and then strength and
discipline over here and then there the
weird battery that makes this place work
hmm interesting
okay well I won just make note I'm like
I know that look on top of things
yeah but then um uh I guess it's me the
person I saw well it's just like okay
cool
yeah um like if you live here you belong
yeah I guess you can just go
yes our house I say everyone else
too loud I need to go to bed no it's
noise Oregon's you guys come in she does
she you guys actually get a glance of
and then she raises an eyebrow when she
sees that this person come in she think
us stay for that yeah she's with us
picking up strays
yeah mingle game okay she'd save all
that is my bad anyway whatever you're
exactly to go easy for you use four
hours of meditation right so as you so
you guys are able to make your way up
the stairs and then in the central room
of
that that sits between the four rooms
that you have you can see that omen is
still in there and he appears to be like
halfway through a sentence buffs in yeah
when you as soon as you cross the
threshold and he says oh and says
remember it's called the wandering crypt
it's not the stationary crypt you'll
need to find some way to hold this
subterranean creature in place something
I've never been able to do maybe you can
succeed where I failed and then it
shimmers and disappears okay that's a
friends are the same the same messages
before you know that's any message if
it's Kota at the end mmm and then I go
replay reappear come back computer oh
maybe please all right man I'm really
excited I just kick a chair um so do we
retire to our rooms what's your what's
your scenario this is how long this is
that long wrist situation yeah you've
been craving obviously that'll be good
for you too it'll get you back up to max
but but that that fight with the that
black puddle was pretty gruesome as I
recall yeah it's definitely exact of
that quite yet yeah yeah I mean we did
have a little powwow yeah yeah ocean I
think I almost saw this this bard is
playing maybe maybe get messed up a
little tight you know I only have four
head points left but that's enough for a
drink yes yes yes no do we trip heads
upstairs yes I've had a husband the
shadow council voted oh okay yeah let me
know this was a quick one okay good game
good game
yeah it was what a meteor eight minutes
Marty is right so so feels like I'm
stuck haha so feel free to make your
make your way downstairs get in hurry
board
woo I know team office I will see a menu
oh yeah yeah that sounds great
um I definitely want to order the
strongest [ __ ] that she and I've been
drinking together before oh yeah yeah
she is a she's a pro no doubt
cold nights on the front has calibrated
her for a specific strength of beverage
right I just cast her look and like yeah
you know you know the deal skew it yeah
yes sure look for smile she nods pours a
glass and then walks it over to you but
the head I mean imagine it's like the
armament of a warship like it is always
completely make no matter where she is
it's always oriented yeah toward the
entertainer mm-hmm and it's just that
single musician on stage if it is one
person but it doesn't sound like it Wow
okay can you describe her she has dark
skin she drew a red robe she's playing a
lute yeah is there anything else that we
can discern about her yeah she has dark
hair with a single red streak on the
front um she is a she's playing it
left-handed which is statistically
speaking novel but mildly interesting
yeah but it's it a lot more inning it
isn't a left-handed Luke's it is um
she's just playing it she's playing it
backwards facing mm oh just to show off
we're learning who knows yeah a keytar
yeah nice Sheena Farrell close this is
great and prophetess is a very big fan
bewitched how crowded is that is the end
it's good okay it's good I mean you've
had to take a steep and one of the one
of the tables at the very edge near the
near the bar I decided this place is
this place is jumping okay but if this
is the first time you've seen this
performer so yeah it may be that that is
the explanation or maybe they just
haven't been here nice okay where now
where are you that um I feel like my I'm
in our little common room with the door
open so I can hear everything but I'm
just like love that lost in my thoughts
thinking about via the symptoms I don't
want to speak up so I like I have
parchment out like I'm supposed to be
writing and I'm just not doing anything
so I have
sought you out and before you can do
anything on a corner of the parchment I
draw the symbol I say thank you and I
scribble it out immediately without
thinking of course not that's ridiculous
never seen that what is that let some
drow garbage men to my knowledge but I
mean if you take a closer look at it and
then well it scribbles it out so hard
she rips the like nice vellum that she
had out and then she's good at since
ridiculous trades that she's like I got
and then she's like trying to rip it and
she can't rip it and crumpled it up and
I was okay I'm like what are you getting
at what do you know about it all I know
is that I can identify it and every
other symbol in that in that space I
couldn't absorb I couldn't see it they
never resolved but that one did but I
don't know what it means um that why
you're bothered by it I'm not bugging me
I'm not gonna try to said I was bothered
by it
you said I was bothered by this is the
new thing for the father I'm not
bothered yeah I think others straight on
unmindful whipping yeah that's all you
ah I assume okay I thought that this was
yeah you were bothered sweet little
clarify maybe it's some sort of a
document something that I'm not aware of
where you rend something that an
intruder shot I just I'm it's just that
I'm the documentarian I'm supposed to be
the one that writes on everything if you
write on it's null and void and that's
not what you do this is what I do this
is my thing I'll never write again I see
a pen in your hand filthy guy and then
I'm and then uh so you know I'm well
that's like I'm sitting there and I'm
like feeling very trapped like I you
know like someone just walked in on me
doing something right and um but cut
through it's like being able to
recognize that I feel like there'd be a
moment now where walnuts like okay well
I can't trust him if he can recognize it
like maybe maybe he's like part of it or
something like that
oh actually an impetus just went down
yes
I didn't know you're selling me there if
now we'll remember that yeah - a - yeah
because now I'm thinking that he can
recognizes them he must have some
connection to Neela
get care the [ __ ] party apart thank
you something I love it hey so you were
down you were downstairs yeah
door opens in a bit a bit of a spring
breeze rolls through
you see Alby hmm the mail carrier mm-hmm
she rolls in looks around for a little
bit like expectantly is trying to find a
specific base sees your face and then
drops off a sheaf with the acquisitions
incorporated seal hmm okay I shake hands
at optimistic okay tipper I'll have much
I pick up gold if you want go for it
open okay
um I feel like this should be something
that walnut takes care of but I look
around half-heartedly
I'm a little bit tipsy just like I
haven't gotten mail in like 25 years
someone else in the sub feels real good
you know like Oh finally something sweet
yes break open the seal unfurl rate it's
actually it says it's a package
Oh more like a folio okay with that with
the aking seal on the front and I'm in
shock I inside you can see a a
reasonably heavy leather pouch in the
left compartment and in the right
compartment is a scroll that has a seal
on it okay um I want peek in that pouch
the pouch has a little jingle jangle all
right and there open it up take a look
it's [ __ ] stuck yes whisk alone okay
Jonathan Walberg
okay cool into that I'm going to open
break I'm going to see on the scroll
enough okay it turns out that there are
three Scrolls all sealed with a single
seal okay um new batch of crap I'm
excited and ready I don't know about it
you know Airlines there are give me the
humans ready you don't even know I'm
walking down one once cry with that
standing there while you ever do one
scroll right next because the raids must
cease again Lord visiting carton wheel
mission accomplished
okay all that money omen basically says
you know
tamam and drawn CEO signed on the bottom
menaces acquisitions incorporated share
sixty percent the second scroll says
with party security for the soiree yeah
like I feel about but I fell off the
documents like we did it but this signer
on it is actually it just says Trevor um
we change our werewolf life so payment
came through yeah hey me came through on
that question
don't wait collect wouldn't realize you
then no no but the great thing is is
that is that the reason you you got the
whole reason you got paid is because the
shadow council soft it so anyway so it's
like this it's like this Leslie shadow
um to to scrolls someone mission
accomplished
see team share two hundred GP nice girl
total okay no the third scroll there's a
third scroll the third scroll says a
surplus of wraps sounds like my kind of
surplus and alright and then below that
it says mayor Fran Elsa Gore four
hundred GP woohoo
Salas Berman spreading disease method of
disposal at contractor discretion
surplus rats I'm gonna slurp us
somewhere and it says it says hi ye to
NEMA's ear forthwith
mm Azir okay damn near killed him so I
mean who was the contact affair for
Nelson Gore thank you so I've been an ER
in like I feel like I think there's been
enough time that I witnessed this and I
she can come up and tell us all right
well he wants the gold
I want the gold yeah real bad no I like
should i mend that seal what is real
particular about that
oh I'm not gonna worry too much about it
okay okay she just kind of chewed my
head off man
oh did you try to write on her vellum
yeah I didn't know I didn't know okay
man it's not good idea okay um I will
pretend to ask her probably I'm gonna
straight-up hand you a bunch of gold
like you deal with this there's phones
in there hope you don't know um and then
um I will put my staff on my seat so no
it takes it I want to come back down and
listen to them tomorrow but I'm gonna
run you up there yeah exactly it's
called ya know so Devine yeah you are
here in this warm cozy common room um
nobody's giving a [ __ ] about the horns
seems like this is rally this seems like
it seems like this is this is a place
where anybody who comes in the door it's
like the Olive Garden equivalent when
your hair yeah your family exactly
um exact warrants are intended shouldn't
we the proprietor any rate that the
gigantic woman behind the bar um she's
noticed that you were you came in with
them and she for some reason is wearing
full armor to service this establishment
um it's not common she says you're with
these guys mm-hmm you made it through
made it sir what well sometimes they
leave with people and then when they
come back those people aren't there
anymore I didn't leave with them they
well I guess yeah I guess we found me
yeah we'll go with that
huh we're in a cave okay you hungry at
all yeah I could go for something to eat
yeah that was really nice-looking cuted
what are my options she she does a
mental assessment of the things that are
still left she says we have soup bread
rebirth and soup and bread okay
soup and bread sounds good it's a soups
of bread it's a common option a lot of
people get it that way she rolls back
behind the behind the bar ladles it up
puts a generous portion of bread on the
side brings it over leaves it on the
table past the table a couple times her
gaze turns back over toward the stage
and then she sort of resumes her circuit
of the up Dan was really expecting it to
be chicken chicken yeah there is chicken
food okay bread chicken chip cookies I
just like my mommy's make kale chip
cookie oh sorry I know it's real sad
yeah I thought your in the room I'm
still out there with Amy because I
should send a propeller baby walnut Amy
Eric who is Amy
the Falcons okay will you any can I get
a perception check no name I'm gonna
roll perception and it's a sad that I
have some of this time don't worry about
it
perceptional 1900 I see 19 hold on
do I notice you here someone does not
want you to hear it
you gave me your tie to hold it it from
any other game indeed what
and no I'm gonna at will how would you
know uh your society what I in the room
I'm like you do a you the window of your
oh no room has closed uh okay so I am
get up and I'm just kind of you know I
want to go check that out because I
don't want onyx getting out on the roof
again it's not a problem
it's been a problem yeah mess so I open
up the door my room yeah you see
something sticking out of the so the
window is closed you see a small piece
of paper sticking out from the window
oh I'm immediately over I'm already
there we've become one we rely God it's
recent maybe we don't get in here okay
okay okay
alright so wanna I'm looking at this and
as soon as I see the first line of
bright red as I'm probably going to turn
right now we realize and it says I want
to sees you the prey as prey is seized
two animals my teeth are on your neck
and then it just says under that Brahma
ha oh my god
so long has just gotten a poem from her
I can't
imaginary a magic imaginary girlfriend
also maybe enemy wants so confused so
now she's immediately like in a
completely different moods like I was
thinking about those dark symbols and
I'm just like who they're screamin I see
you run out like that and I go way whoa
what what you got there what happened
fire kids yeah oh nothing it was an
addendum to an official detriment no man
you don't need to worry about it and
then I go into my door and I shut it and
then I go over to a floorboard and I you
can Scimitar to like open right and then
I place it in and
there might be some like rock no there's
a hole down there it goes to the stage
and the bargain what part is yeah I have
like a very special piece in citrine and
I put it oh my god you actually under
that you brought your special citrine
with you that I just had that should
intercept and also only have special
rocks and stuff okay yeah
Christ is the time props I guess I guess
that's half of the stairs just in time
to see this whole thing play out
basically like you run in you run out
you run back in and slam the door I'm
like okay okay oh wait hmm okay and then
I hide everything and then I come back
out and I look all dignified mega I
filed it it's fine I got a code well as
long as it's filed dear listen I have
three documents they got two receipts
bills of quests complete we got the the
horts person now has both we also got
another task from HQ which I have
already read amazing and I read it and I
go wait what did you say yeah I read it
already but I'm not gonna spoil it for
you it's pretty good and then I look at
Rosie and I can see that she's drunk and
I'm just uh a little kissing and I I
look at the iron I look at Rosie and I
just go um in the future I just think
you know I don't mess with your Maps
maybe they just maybe we just you know
this is just like the second time
tonight
[Laughter]
look just do it I promise tonight cuz I
take the document a little Adam I think
whatever and then I get to the name of
the place and I go NEMA's ur name is urn
and his ear and the zr1 here okay yeah
and then I do a survival check do I know
anything about atmosphere oh so wait yes
I rolled it and it was a seven and then
I got six to it so it sure seemed like
your cartographer might either want to
ask about that geez yeah well
Wow I also the wanderer background and
all of sudden all right I don't know
anything about it then I go oh never
fear
at least I definitely know about it do
you know that
I totally know about it because I'm the
cartographer and I don't even have to
roll for that right no you get them open
it open you have no you don't I can't
convey no all right no I don't have jack
oh wait yeah yeah I don't know Vance
gonna add four seventeen yeah um it's
not on many maps okay
it is a walled city in the crypt garden
forest to crypt II yeah you are you are
from Nana's ear as we discussed in your
character background oh so you are more
than familiar with it are we have boyars
again I thought back at the bar that you
got you guys are all switching around
I'm just telling people a generation a
media oh maybe I'm maybe you're taking
me up on it because I'm I know you're
teasing and I'm like yeah we're like
eating a new identities I would drow
right and it's not what you're like
it's like they're like like they really
act like they're not looking but they're
like I like looking I know yeah I want
you I wanna go over there and be like
what yes you know but then what is that
going to accomplish yeah getting ready
getting into some [ __ ] I really notice
good
because I mean I'm in figure like this I
mean this place man see this post be
cool right now but I don't know these
are all drunk okay I mean they might
turn on in any second just trying to out
us up or somebody yeah the only one here
like that's fine fireball fire my man
there's our note agreement Park Hill our
way I would things go back there is a
button
absolutely so this is the I think
everybody has the information but I'm
here to impart
except I want to know for RP purposes so
when Rosie do you tell me where none of
users numbers here I tell you it's a
walled city but I don't know much about
it um do I know that that it's where key
things are from I think maybe Nazir is
not nervous there is not an old city it
doesn't have much of a reputation and
like I say a lot of the older maps don't
even included yet okay I'm still
figuring out what it is I think okay
okay well I got an idea but we could go
back downstairs and share it with Chris
and on Devine and see see if anymore um
just get everybody yeah yeah I'll come
we can do it in though I'm good say what
they did in the morning aren't doing
more to arrest Mike I mean we should
also send a letter back to omen that we
didn't find the Crypt I'm going to
carefully word back send another burden
it like didn't find it the end in
fancier terms
yeah yeah yeah the long version is do
the club mix to be continued yeah I mean
I'll look into that coming back to you I
go I go downstairs and actually you guys
then and then we can notify - Allah I'm
not you have something to say about
number well I will say that I'm from
them is ear oh cool you are using but
you couldn't take us there tomorrow yeah
totally
how long is it from here how long is it
from it's just past West bridge okay
yeah they're all driving grams what for
just three days I will right through
there two days ago today okay so I
should pass them here
that's right cool excellent well then
you were going to help us navigate
tomorrow and let's all take a nice long
rest
why not alone risk why not Alana hey
just language I feel like we need like I
expected right like yeah anybody I have
some crazy dream sequences this week
need an establishing outdoor shot that
shows the end right and then in the
morning yes I'm using the code says we
all wake up um okay you know sure to be
I had a dream that I was dinar just but
I was just crying I just could just
crying for hours like a lot like a lot
I had my lovely crying like fighting
chess pieces with a bo staff every weird
they're all because when I get it when I
get up in the morning and I'm doing my
normal thing which is like you know
whatever all the diagnosis of takes a
long time I go to leave and then I turn
around I look at the spot in the floor
where the note is and then I go to leave
again and I look at the spot then I go
back and I get the note and I fish it
into my stuff I do want to get out but
then I go downstairs and wait for
everyone to show up
yeah so you knew who Brahma was like he
knew that name you just like instantly
knew it was Jeff are we asked um prophet
we have out there name the name of a
certain bard
yeah yeah I just went right down yeah
yeah for docking reversal yeah okay okay
I does yes when I blow a little
flustered yeah exactly
breezy whisper Rosie wakes up and does a
hundred push-ups and then she's gonna
respect - awesome one hand one yeah yeah
but you let anybody see you know handed
as I fear there's a all core it's very
intense and then I come downstairs and I
I'm ready to have breakfast with with my
friend walnut yeah dinner gets up less
mopey than the day before but still kind
of opening and disheveled and comes down
slightly more put together than the day
before but still all sad it's just
escape trouble yeah agreement present
our having omelets you want any imma let
you finish
yeah I say yeah they're delicious I love
them I would love an omelet
thank you so much my dear friend I'm so
upset right now
omelet really hit this one one day I got
a very good mm-hmm
what we do in the shadows is rising yeah
exactly exactly so they just want to
rise up like yeah okay I guess I'm not a
prophet
notices everyone sort of filtering down
into the main room early morning yeah
the phone about that is James imitating
life I'm I am a sauce on them yeah haha
she's just inquired and yeah well what
goes on what um quite a thinking about
something else ago oh not Brahma what
secret note oh we're we're just that
about to head out on a on official
unofficial you know missus and we were
unsuccessful in our wondering crypt
search yesterday no no for now yeah she
says it's gonna be like that a lot yeah
we're gonna her house yesterday when I
said saying before about we kill a bunch
of stuff we run into like I we probably
won't kill anyone you know
I hope well say that now another table
right yeah maybe you're like top three
people yeah ahead of time yeah and we
will you are well there are batters yeah
why people in your family plans that's
it right
come limited data and Exodus Tom you
know so when she hears a year you're
leaving um she starts to she puts
together she lays out a cloth and then
stacks up a few cakes cinches it up
around the top ties it and then set to
the end of the bar I want to grab it and
pick it up and then once again able
leaned over the bar and liquor and I
want to say um it was the musical guest
last night
I'm prophets drawn hmm that was odd
record ear oh and I go of the drawn
accordion
I remind you is no relationship no long
because she's not here a lot
she's pretty good with the loot
yeah it's Haley put a mouthful oh I'm
like it's pretty good yeah yeah she oh
the work that she does is she she plays
the castle circuit ah well he knows a
lot next time she's in town we should
set up a bedtime sounds great I would
love to talk to her I would have loved
to talk to her last night but everybody
wanted to go to sleep so damn fine we're
dying for a to pain killing Saval you've
reminded me I can you almost dead all
bandaged and bloody like yeah like some
rats gonna come nibble on my toes thank
you want your dragon dead like it would
tell me guys what's the deal baby right
to the same place okay when I take the
case I give in to the horse person I go
[Laughter]
case hmm is that Alright maybe he's
injured in the big book of paper uh
absolutely yeah the big because the
DiBiase's gonna die no heart okay that
is so into the car you go rolling out
north you want to ride up front leaning
yeah come up a couple times today huh
you right up front with me and direct me
I knew okay all right yeah head out me
know your action GPS yeah
nice um you roll you roll up north first
day uneventful
okay uh camping fishing by the boat yes
yeah so anything on classic laughing
line in foliated dodgeball exactly
rocket ball leaving in the background
Bryce cream actually exactly
you basically roll straight through
Westbridge this time there's no there's
no reason to stay in this town right now
you honestly don't know what would
happen
um yeah I think I'm gonna veer around it
I'm gonna give it a wide berth
like I'm gonna riding straight to the
middle of town just like slipping off
the guards as necessarily hey Todd hey
Rob bitchin corner I know I like no to
your great surprise the town is remain
standing
yeah at any rate the two people who
lived there yeah exactly at cause I'm or
then you continue north through West
bridge and you can see you can see that
vast apron of the Crypt Garden forest
sort of reaching out in the great
distance closer to the road and then
there are there are signs that lead away
from the main road that you don't
remember going in in the crypt garden
forest is a place where druids and
ancient elven sorcery holds sway it's
not a strip mall there's no you know
what I mean like there's there's I don't
know what you mean yeah there should be
nothing in there yeah um there's no
paradise yeah exactly
sorry it's not again LM only there
aren't great savings on cups believe it
oh yeah I'm on top of the Carmen you
have like mixed feelings about going
near the Crypt guarding force yeah now
also the exaggeration as we're going
towards it yes so there is so there is a
sign planted in the road of substantial
measure wrought iron and wood that says
NEMA's ear and then points off into a
road that you don't remember and should
not be there so I definitely have like a
sinking feeling where you think that
something is wrong but you are in denial
and kind of hoping that your be wrong
about that
yeah that everything is actually ok so
the card is is continuing to roll deeper
and darker through this forest and I
mean you know just from looking around
this is this is your place this is this
place this is the home you couldn't
return to after the destruction of the
order which you were not able to stop
because you were young and unable to
help and thought you had a better plan
the wages are that are coming back now
yes as you are as you're continuing to
press further and further in and the
light from the canopy is getting darker
and darker you see in the middle of an
enclave an axe anima Grove you see a
walled city rise out in the gutted
center of this wood so I like don't
believe what I'm seeing
like but on the other hand I can't
believe that this is happen but on the
other hand I can because of like being
Cydia sness of society and I'm just
following my fists and I'm on the roof
of the cart so nobody could see me which
is like tears streaming down her face
and like her nails are like cutting into
her hands it's like like cannot control
ourselves just rigid with rage but stays
quiet as much as we get closer there is
a great gate even at the even at the
entrance at the bottom of Suisse these
great walls are smooth stone they rise
up and they bulge out around the sides
you can see them sort of disappearing
into the distance the city widens from
this point and this great gate is very
similar in fact to the sign that was out
posted at the road where it's a mixture
of wood and then a vine with leaves that
look like steel meshed through it and it
says men Azir on the sign but it has
druidic writing in it which I can read
what does it say would you like to read
the description
or do you have the druidic description
here uh yeah it's there two sheets for
the for the fans at home um
yeah hang on wait where is it Shh oh no
don't I have it on this one another
birthday she yeah sorry this is a new
sheet guys yeah yeah we leveled up this
is your level four [ __ ] no I don't know
where I have oh here it is
I know drew attic hidden messages with
it can only be understood by who no
druidic maybe
yeah it's with anybody crazier than that
because even if you know all languages
you actually still need a magical means
to perceive it so I can't reason because
if they caught it isn't like a written
language right it's a language of it's
like steganography the data is hidden in
structures in natural structures right
so the it says man is here but plainly
in druidic it's a graveyard I don't know
I feel like we'll play please really are
you happy w home huh the place yeah
something real yeah men at the top of
this wall at one of these two guard
posts on either side of this gate say
what is your purpose in them Azir
calendar yeah your house yeah you're
you're a ticket in I think you got a lot
of rats here right oh we're here to kill
the rest
um I just say oh uh we're I'm just
returning home brought some friends what
district and what districts and I've
been digging up everything the hammock
did yes ma district that's a different
it's a different spelling obviously it
has a different derivation yeah the
apology is usually that means but it's
still gonna show me a hammock I need a
tree let's be clear yes
young laundry personal draping sleeping
weight having the horns right they
laughs apparently the hammock district
means something to them they you can see
one of them moving up to crank this
giant wheel and the gate opens up enough
for the car to roll through announces a
sapling in the gate that's trying to
grow and I'm going to get cheered on
yeah good big girls it goes dark with me
you know one of the guards like that's a
good thing like yeah I believe but I'll
go you at home Rosie elbows dizzy and
she's like even though like we probably
could have just pulled my head across
I'm like I'm still very into the fact
that you helped us in and I'm like chill
yeah yeah yeah I've been like an inside
guy really there's like a like the tax
or some better pay to do more work in
this town well yeah it's like Rick
Steves it was like I don't like name is
Iran a dollar a day yeah you know bad
that she's an indentured servant we
track ransoms are a legal thing you're
like all it she's forever contract now
right yeah yeah exactly yeah free will
Deborah so you enter in to the town of
NEMA's air it seems like there is a
great main road that sort of winds
straight from this path and wines as
deep into the city as you can see and
then a very small almost like tributary
style streets and paths that lead out
from that Center sure why not more more
how about eight how about more City
what's the best city and you can see
that this main road actually travels
straight through the bottom so in the
very center there's a corner there's a
sort of high ridge that exact sort of
sits in the middle of the city and you
can see
housing of a very different sort okay at
the top of it that's the realm known as
the hammock but you can see that that
that's rarefied places up on this sort
of
round spire but you can see that this
the main road actually travels straight
through the bottom okay not in control
of my faculties so so wiener like upon
entry we just are forced we're made to
go beneath yes yeah got toilet it's that
that's a little bit in the distance okay
but on the on the sheath much like the
other place much like the other jobs
there is a small version of the map that
shows where you would need to go inside
the town and you know well well I guess
a yeah turn is saying where's city home
here in the main Mary yeah yeah lead us
to City Hall sure yeah you good it's
basically straight up the main road but
the mayor's residence is not on the
upper tier the mayor's residence is sort
of like a pimple or something it's sort
of like exists at the base of it and
people lovely wear it wear it wear it
wear it would wear the pass rolls
through that spire in the bottom right
at that edge is a little place that they
have carved out for him Sharon Lee okay
genomic everything want the cart yeah
stop it pitch it up we walk up to the
front door you have our paper I believe
yes so just not a yeah
oh and no there but I mean there are the
two things walking around just like
regular old it's the hot then mix the
mix has a higher percentage of teeth
wings than you okay
Jana site about underside I mean people
it's a drama huh well see you drove it
up
no no not appeal at all cool yes just
sugar alluring and exactly like yeah
time you walk by they just like you're
like this place is great but there's no
there's a little sense sort of around
the mayoral man's there has been some
attempts at Gardens
interactions oh I don't seem to have
gone super well yeah yeah it's like
absolutely at all black in the face he's
not here he's not MLG that gardening
yeah your local gardener you know it's
just a paved city yeah it is it is it is
very very very very sterile like an
unkillable scarring curve and yeah it is
just very very urban it's like a city
girl from a kid everything's built from
tombstones
ya know it's made me from dead yes I go
up to his door and I go to knock I it's
my mom's skull weird I'm not sure oh
sorry I'm trying to make it like as an
action since yeah what's happening right
now um so meanwhile now that I know that
Davina's from memory I have have not and
will not make eye contact with her for
the rest of time I'll walk up to aspire
store because I have absolutely no
respect for anything that's going on
right now
it don't even knock you know yeah sweet
open up and then I just say like as it
just like automatic I'm like my name is
walnut on grass I'm here to kill it all
of your rats were here with acquisition
incorporated points out the rest just
are punching a mother bear I'm going to
the wrath wrath and then yeah a man sort
of toggles out from a kitchen with a cup
of tea hello I pull her back okay guy
say excuse me
right I mean really you're right right
here I think another way say we're with
acquisitions Inc I'm the leader yeah and
the Baconator I'll kill all your rats
for you cuz I'm the best
oh that's marvelous
you know how they can be oh you see one
rat then you see Jen I all right now
then 20 then you see I are going to stop
and then huge rat oh yeah there's a
there's a mix there's less lag there's a
whole spread
really bread eggs yeah thank you any
time anyone says eggs you just burst I
just keep talking cream paintings but
like no you're just reading I'm like
yeah I believe last time here yeah
business is all business
yeah so he openeth he takes a humorous
passivity he's glad that the document
that he filed a couple weeks ago is
resulted in people in town willing to
engage with this sort of with you know
to do with the vermin issue obviously
it's been a problem I get a lot a
compliment like this is a great place
this is my town
well good job I'm glad I'm glad you like
it I do
it's young this town is this town is a
like a young man Hill trying to find his
way in the world yeah it's it's only up
it's on him down for sure if I may on
the up and up
and the up yes yeah well yeah what
what's this guy look like as you're
dealing no no no I'm just super curious
human human now for anybody who sort of
should like to have that kind of
acceptance on up here you're like oh no
I'm not going to get a good reception
here
I passed minor illusion just for you
just a tiny little tree just to maybe
give you something to meditate on the
coupon you guys are going from the creek
running forest no I don't that you're
clearly agitated I know anyways yeah and
I just like you're either angry or horny
all the time we're trying to calm you
down right yeah yeah our P a different
character again you have a thing you
know what it means you have a branch
just roll with it you're hot and you're
cold you're yes in your mouth yes
angry expression in out right sure yeah
you know I don't know if it'll word it
but I just like you're you're facing
away from all this and you're just like
you're your fists are balled up and
you're you're like making sounds like
I've died and goose it was like say make
a tree I make a little tree that no one
can see what you like I put it right in
your gaze where you're [ __ ] like
crazy focused and I come I just like
actually gently on the hands and I go
back to paying attention you know I look
at the the tree and it looks
like I'm really angry and upset but then
I kind of look like I kind of look at
that on my you know there's something
nice about that I look back at Rosie and
I give her a nod like I think everything
is going to be okay
direct yeah through gritted teeth mirror
so he she says please please he reaches
for your the scroll I shadow to him yeah
he makes some quick marks on the map
where the rats okay well you don't like
anybody touching the document do you
know I let him but I just it's like as
if I'm just like Kelly one more [ __ ]
thing yeah exactly I need you Rosie and
I'm like just guard issue yes I know I
called you at it don't get nervous
that's it yeah there's nobody at grab a
pen Baker too quick two quick shots on
here the places that have had the
biggest complaints about rats in town
his feeling is that if you're able to
resolve these nests then you'll be then
than his issue then you will satisfied
the requirements of the contract in his
eyes and will be in receipt of fainted
right and a quick question for him yeah
we allow you feel about drought are we
like a musical rats that we find but he
says well I think that if you I think
that if you would look at the document
that method of disposal is at the
contractor discretion if these rats are
not in them is here then they are not in
my domain I can't count on them for both
definitely yeah nobody likes me
okay all right wear it so the reps are
have you given up some exact location
for yeah there's two there's two marks
on the map it should be very very easy
even just the map but you also have
someone who knows their way around town
as well okay so do you want to lead us
to one of these points on the map yeah
can I get a perception check from you
Rosie and from you Devine yes sir here
in our magical youth attack uh there you
go nice hole thank you hi Rosie be
singer in the dice hole - 113
okay so where'd you get that you know I
got 18 yeah another teen you think you
think it's probably nothing okay I'm in
great I don't know about this city I'm
very interested in time Percy no well uh
Corey a toy all right I got 18 and it's
probably nothing but this is a this is a
weird town like I said it seems like it
was made like there's some kind of a kid
okay
you know what I mean like it's art very
very regimented sure milquetoast yeah
highly coughing it's just like a fractal
almost okay like everything that's in it
is all just different sizes of the same
thing it's like no modular yeah we yeah
yeah with mayor's cottages a certain
size on a stand but he attend but the
other ones are they're very similar in
construction just turn to face a
different way right you know what I mean
yeah the different size of cookiecutter
um yeah McMansion exactly okay but it's
probably fine
that's what you're telling me well yeah
I mean it's you thought you'd notice
something but this place is just really
weird like a liquid like the roads that
go off on the sides are very very small
not really cart worthy you know what I
mean kind of like really four foot
traffic awesome Oh Eddie's yeah yes
problem the lorries and other center
Isle is really the only one that's
appropriate for would it be something
that might cartel
prefer a background would allow me to do
an extra check on like is there
something you need to check a distant
restaurant it's odd alright you leave it
I mean you're not you're not wrong way
around
yeah familiar how hot is it you're not
going to be here with it with a layout
like this oh you would not do this like
okay it's bad city planning yes exactly
well is there to the top okay so
actually even math and we both go yeah
it's fine um and then you're going to
take us to the first of these locations
okay so the nearest one is the ironbark
in a few short blocks it is at the end
of one of those is at the end of one of
these small paths that branches off
branches off to the left again and you
can see sort of what with a branches
yeah branches yet we go to the murdered
forest hotel yeah I don't like it
you know why leave me alone Jerry
hahahaha and you can see it seems like
they are making I like it if they're
making they're making the best of it
back here like it's sort of ducted in
the back of this cul-de-sac looks warm
inviting a little bit smaller than some
of the surrounding buildings here but
you know not not inappropriate okay
right not the worst record this is off
the top like an invoice or I mean this
is this is a hassling bar let's just
let's just come right out
oh yeah all right I'm using that's
what's going on I don't appreciate the
expression on your face right now this
is a halfling bar a little bit rates is
what we need but I'm into it I see this
and I'm like yeah this is my kind of
place
I like I don't know if I'm supposed to
be here not everybody's what I don't
know her I don't work over everyone this
is like me like walking feel like my
daughter's room like your toys
possessions and I'm like what's that
we're not children
I like 30 people
Susanoo and every oven everything
exactly okay
but the door is short I mean let's let's
be real about it it's under average size
but this Ibiza perfect exactly I mean I
don't I don't notice at all that you
guys don't get to build or I know no I
just placed good rhyme yeah you you go
right in and as the as the party goes in
it's like you know it's like duck and
weave yeah you know I mean you were able
to avoid door damage by Marte and all
through
that's like when you go to any time you
heard not like in Philly or Boston or
any like old colonial like tourist like
all everything were still yeah the door
with Tiffany you that's not even that
tall even to timber like this today a
giant in those places yeah like I said
only like six four thousand gulp did I
never leak and all I know I don't like I
can finish my cry oh I don't know it
whatever not you I wish they would not
listen okay and like a deltoid pull so
that I could pass through I'll be fine I
accept it so um so as everyone is
ducking their way through the doorway
getting in you are just sort of passing
you're passing your vision around the
interior structure of this place when I
say low of course I mean the correct
ceiling height thank you right I say the
bar is low I mean it's the right size
for people right uh I say low I mean
high I mean it is basically you're in a
dollhouse yeah um and but it's it's just
right and then someone comes someone
comes out from a swinging door in a
kitchen that's operating in the back and
when they come out and see you they drop
the plate uh do our hey mrs. Preston no
okay um
he immediately gifts he immediately just
gets down on his hands and knees and
it's just cupping the glass and the food
and keeping it up in a pile of refuse to
be taken out later okay but other people
are starting to notice you too and this
is not weird for you this happens you go
don't you go to a new place and you can
hear the whispers in a halfling tongue
you hear them whispering grandmother
mm-hmm you guys know you speak at
Estrella notice the sign
yeah but it is nothing really I guess it
could be greeting her again yeah
halflings really good
I so like do we know we don't have other
words I don't know
so bother kids so immediately people so
a table near the kitchen the four of
them vacate the table and then one of
them brings a fifth chair over to the
table and then three of them go back
into the kitchen and two of them leave
and plates start to fill the table and
you are directed very gently to the
chairs thank you my dears thank you so
much you guys have a seat if you're
hungry thirsty just let me know and I'll
get it taken care of I get this exact
same same except it's people throwing
garbage at me yes
you I guess I get an egg apart II yeah
we recomm be so the the proprietor
emerges from a large door on the
opposite side more of the venue large in
station right Eddie says to what do we
owe the pleasure
oh not this it's nothing like that I'm
here on business
these are my work associates please pay
us no minds we're we're just we're just
here to take care of what sounds like a
little bit of an infestation problem
that you guys have we've done everything
that we can to try to tamp it down if I
had known that they would send you I
would never have made the request now we
acquisitions Inc we don't mess around
sweetheart okay well I'm certain that
your companions can manage this why
don't you stay up here with us oh I
wouldn't dream of it I don't want to put
you out any more than I obviously
enjoying this by the way like clearly I
am I'm like oh no no honey please and
I'm just like seriously bring us more
food or it's gonna be bad news yeah Kiki
classical times children emerge with
symbols little Tooting horns dinars so
jealous yes I mean because I'm so
massive my favorite day yeah I like
other gonna bring you guys I'm like
talking to the waiter while you're
hugging the manager I'm like you guys
are new to me I tell the kids like
immediately the weaponry is trained on
dinar it's mega toodles and then that
the Friday says we sing the old songs I
appreciate that so much
and I think your establishment is just
lovely and I cast a very meaningful
glance at walnut that said like I'm
really sorry for like being nice to
these people could I know you're not
crazy about the whole place but this is
these are these are my folks so I'm
going to be polite but this is very
complicated glance I'm giving it a lot
going on here but you get it you see
what I'm doing
it's it's not we don't we don't need any
any special treatment this is a lie I
will need any special treatment at all
yeah but we're we're just here we want
to take care of the business and make
sure that your lives get rid of rats as
soon as possible
you could stay here in the end we will
go down I will bring the men and women
of the in down to deal with this problem
while we just eat and and go to a
location it's uh it's not I mean it's
not the worst guys want to just have
them do it for us yes
or have them just write down and we did
it by the way or we did it all right if
that hunger is we can be right here yeah
yeah my girlfriend's here would love it
if we could actually Corral the rats and
bring them with us is that possible
the debtor lives it doesn't matter - now
could he come down with us sure
would you I'd like to see more yeah
absolutely I love to do that yeah
anybody who wants to go down is welcome
to but I would love it has been a long
day and I could use just a moment of
respite Matt would you accompany us down
sure yeah okay you got your rat we can
make them do it we can split the party
and then I can go to location number two
how naughty these Reverend but yeah okay
okay so right now we have Devine Carissa
and maybe walnut yeah
well I'll go through these red okay so
it is you and Rosie having this bizarre
TGI Fridays a party experience they
bring out a real birthday happy me on
your giant harp it's way too small
this round like it is as high up as they
can get it - we have to like push it up
and they're like they're all clapping
and I'm like every time you breathe long
it really kind of Sunday's like really
just like one bite it's like it's
probably cold and dirty down there guys
used to get a coach got moisture a
version of the ice cream
yeah you just shove it you just throw it
behind you they lead you they leave this
is very convenient right here they leave
the three of you out behind and these
these alleys are there you know not
fossil yeah you're able to squeeze your
way around behind the building and there
is with the old-style cellar door okay
so pulls that open and then it is dark
down there but this dark vision of Go Go
yeah
right Ronan yeah yeah I'm I seen them in
this area dark cellar keukenhof yeah I
mean this is this classic in cellar is
going to have you know kegs case with
lines that go up into the into the place
proper where they're hand pulled and you
can see as you as you find your way down
you can see that these are have become
not and porous right and you note your
ear spread does not include hails ah um
so drunk ass right yeah yeah I am going
to complain to management because good
be great
so but the farther the farther you get
down you can see that the the walls
themselves mean it's a classic seller
and so this is really just hard packed
earth yeah that is cool and surrounding
there and I feel good their stores oye
finally finally a place where you can be
I like this place yeah exactly
okay to leave anything we all I love
this video is very good the keg barrels
one of them bursts open on the front
yeah
and it splits out the binding the wood
splits inside the two iron bindings and
rats just pour out whoa hey sweet boys
so I need some initiative so we all wash
our on your rack belt definition that's
okay that I use system now very initial
we'll see how it's done actually I am a
[ __ ] yeah same thing it's not it's
not the best so what do you got - me too
- mm-hmm so two five seven boy okay well
nut to frisk and Devine ELCA Fritz
you're saying that your serpent has its
own initiative that's right thank you
for reminding yeah yeah let's do that
good snake well
all persons of migratory music for now I
will use the dinar because there's
basically two taken scenario they make
basically game
they're like seelye hailed yeah lizardy
hey every turn but so the situation is
just this burst huts at your end so
basically and what a way to tell you
when you come down yeah it begins to
hiss and rise instantaneously oh yeah
and then it dude mega tickles yeah and
then it turned out it sort of coils on
your shoulder and then leaps out and
it's buried by rats
oh no tell me what he's doing he's
didn't he got a lot of yeah got a lot of
the attack fund in fact if I had had my
way I would have said do that that's no
good my lord my friend why did he do
that yeah damn you told me he did yes I
did not think he would do that it has
its turn to act he can do it everyone
don't he go at ur start stay on all the
things I don't like form on me by like
Oh what this is a good time for this
question yeah
I've become aware of that what some say
is a gamebreaking device among familiars
which is the help action can you
describe this action to me yeah we all
learn together the check the help action
yeah I think nothing would bring me more
pleasure while you well read is that
basically upon its turn see it can add
this action come for us help to the
first met a fetching for not here and
then that is advantage on whatever the
roles gonna be that's amazing so it's
like hey I live advantage just give it
to me so it just gives advantage just
jumping from personal person if it yeah
I mean on its yeah I would it would have
to yeah
I don't you like a bit of a cable I
think it might be but I mean obviously
you can you can rule it a different way
it's just a critical you know it's fine
well you just have you're asking for
permission when you should have been
asking for forgiveness yeah exactly
well I'm mad I'm gonna broke up like it
okay so if it can help you you can lend
your aid to another creature and
completion of a task when you take the
help action the crease you eight games
advantage on the next ability check
ability check it makes to perform the
task you are helping with okay so that's
fine alternatively we can all be open a
bottle alternatively you can eat a
friendly creature and attacking a
creature within 5 feet of you okay you
faint distract the target or in some
other way team up to make your allies
attack more effective if you're how I
attacks the target before your next turn
the first attack role is made to the
advantage so it there are some
limitations in there okay it has to
attack right it has to attack your
target right or just or like draw it
away maybe it's not great with a snake
and tell you what there are familiars
that do better on that not great with
the snare unit ready to eat that's the
next one yeah so he's already in the mix
hey everyone come back yeah but bring
some rats in there Matt rifle and I'm
saying this oddly so that the the
proprietor who I assume is still here
yeah yeah and it's like you know at the
moment before this keg is first he is
like well you have understand if we had
known yeah if we had known that
grandmother we're going to be here corn
and then jail this rat mageddon yeah I
can't wait to feast on these rat yeah so
so so you hear a squeal somewhere near
the bottom of this pile and you see it
just wriggle out from the back and it's
and it's just like you wanted yeah it's
like jumping up in midair yeah and just
like like um like this picture is all
scaled down but like the four Casteel
combo it's like he's just boiling up
leaping and just be yeah yeah yeah I may
be the dress but these are can also
these are these are regular rests that
you'll see this far okay that's far okay
we're on our us situation yeah that'll
run when you go five soon yeah right so
here at so dinar right then a which is
the name of the serpent of your weird
snake I think this nut is real name is
Locati
really would you like to hear some drow
language BS yeah oh yeah give me like
any dish it up what do you got I don't
know if I have it
my sweet button table time yeah that's
true let's table this table it you
retconning son of them no sorry no it's
good yes oh he is he is within 5 feet of
me he is he is he is brought back
delicious pray mm-hmm
feast right in your mouth please my boy
I need a bike you know operate up why
don't do it okay well nimona done grass
you're tearing to see you're starting to
see Zee the hard-packed walls of this
cellar starting to shake loose a little
bit you're starting to see cracks
forming near the base cool
I don't notice I'm still looking up it
yes I say thank you for going like it's
gonna be good and we got ya really alive
you're gonna love it
yeah I mean fireballs it's up I got
something better than fireball oh we're
good to go
yeah yes I retinas all yes just auto
ahead yeah well what do you got with
there walnuts on gas well it's a little
something Wow
I launched my cat cannon no no she's
like I let the rest consume the city I
know that's what I'm saying like she's
like oh look how he's living creatures
yeah I I feel that it's like I wanted me
to be able to attack but I also want her
to do so alright so I want to look at
the person I go don't worry you know I
got this um and I want to be stuff do
student animals and I want to call out
to these rats again surprised its
offense I want how much fun yeah maybe
so you know I said name might not work
it might not be cool enough and I am I
save the rats and I say I say you're all
that's left of this natural world this
place belongs to you by birthright you
shouldn't be living down here you should
be up on the streets and I should take
what's yours and then and then and then
and then I'm gonna wait and see if it
does anything like I said I don't look
good while I'm talking about no it's
okay
no I didn't do it won't give me that
persuade go oh cool um
is advantage yes yes yes are you mm-hmm
okay there's the 4chan big money now the
15 yes 30 rats sort of slow like hot
furry water around your feet the other
time yeah and up the stairs and then out
into the out into those folks and turns
of the street it's runtastic skipper
yeah we're like badges I'll take care of
it
30 of how many was that how many ways on
a CEREC million is about half a row okay
nice well done
are they all in like a big clump yeah
they're basically just like frothing
like imagine like like that like so
maybe like the head on a on a mug of
beer like it's just this awesome
foam of racked angled cool and a
halfling basement so it's already like
good cousin Julia so the roof yeah wait
we got let me talk about how tall you
only yeah I mean more about this
Moonbeam um silvery pale light shines
down and a five-foot radius that's real
good
yeah don't tell me about the damage I
miss moon be 2d 10 on say for half as
much damage on a successful one ah yeah
alright save is desk Constitution that
comes along I'll good no rappy yeah I
can't have to find out
look alright uh let's go see some damage
to does it failed oh no no no this is
good time
three all right if I listen get your to
stand either back yeah for only like
could you hit right yeah yeah yeah
so no no I'm going to use a single
damage clock just like I'm not gonna
roll 30 Sam stalling
it begins as a tiny circle like a coin
sized circle of silver light that
rapidly expands to a 5 foot diameter and
again if you're like a demo video that
may be too big Assessors are often
flashes flashes out and then when it
comes back together into a single point
and that emerges there's nothing there
there's nothing there at the base now
that they know that their turn to go 3
much much larger rats burrow through
what would be the equivalent of a
baseboard in this soil dig their way so
you can see their noses pink noses
peeking out of the soil so badly
yes approbation they emerge don't like
disease teddy bears at the end of the
day yes thank you days so fix them so
three of them three of them emerge and
they immediately leap on walnut but they
don't find purchase just bounces
straight off of the plate
yeah exactly I can Garden to leather arm
exactly no it didn't work they try to go
after you cut risk and sale they come
after Devine what's your AC Denis 1414
they do not find purchase so it's like
we're all rather stubborn like there
they're increasing in speed as they as
they tried unsuccessfully to drive you
out and I'm trying to fight they're just
like rubbing in the office yeah like
batting right honey in their head yeah
like sugar thank you Miss prom you got
you know a lot of rats but good news you
get shitty rats
not great rats we're going to take care
yeah the you know the owner the owner
was clapping wildly after the moon beam
and now is it clapping ass load
oh okay and he has begun to back away
toward the stairs oh good oh good
I don't wear no no we are at flokati
okay so he is gonna get spine we all
know I don't know how would you find it
that exact that's probably the day in
the plural sense yeah exactly we hide in
their region
yeah we're known consciousness but maybe
only have none of that
uh so I'm going to ask it to hold it
needs to be your unless are you fighting
for me where are you position would you
like some of this it's close it's a
really tight basement it's a closed
panic yeah you want some tasty this cool
snake yeah this morning
here's make yourself is I mean I need a
situation where we can meter engage
snake use each time I don't wear them
out yes murder it is so I want to UM I'm
seeing these big rats come how many big
rats come in three just three three okay
I want you you can't speak with animals
actually that's not true I could pass it
as a ritual if I wanted to because thank
you YouTube yeah yeah sure I waiting on
your Ref come on giving the candles out
I you know what I have a thing to do
much I guess tar we're gonna do walnut
upon seeing at Vivian just completely
neutralize them oh yeah her face just
like completely drops angers you've
you've got it and then walks upstairs
walks past Rosie and dinar in just
stands outside old are these are girls
active by the way it's still active by
the way oh yeah and it's only about
accused crisis if we go away
oh it's concentrating ever forget yeah
good God it is yes she's emplacement
forever yeah exactly challenge every
features yeah you mean they'll be well
and I can move it around that's what I
recommend yeah yeah definitely I take a
magnifying glass
hey you I usually have to disengage but
I wasn't close so there's no one out
there like the the halflings no the
halfling of there they are out doing
your will in this town wonderful the
that has a proprietor and his you know
cadre that we're going to do this they
have melody have melded themselves back
in to the back into the inn um oh really
yeah yeah they came back in they did but
they left my friends in the basement
yeah yeah that's interesting I really
like to call attention to that excuse me
hello in the permanent record really
thought that um you had volunteered to
take care of that rat problem but it
seems my friends are sue feels very very
powerful friends she is any league with
the moon she is in league with the moon
I'm just like oh alright sure and you
have come past us your activists as
idols I haven't yet we debated already
because hangar people's filtered back in
okay alright well I'm not going to move
but I'm gonna look meaningfully over
dinar and be like I'm just really
disappointed right now felony here this
is like that's the worst sunburn and I'm
gonna be surprised one of nice
everybody's is a worse Sunday I've ever
had higher self you can you tell me your
name just for curiosity what's your name
dear friend makes really bring me let's
try that one more time make friends
Marvin Marvin Marvin Marvin you must
offer big so I can take my Margo
Tobi off so you've seen this
annihilation but you know we'll continue
you you step your way back up in to the
very thin
alleyway that is back and I need that
perception
you know I got it I don't know you know
I know you got your are disgusting and
also not what yeah why on a clean roles
I got as much as you can I can see out
of my office
yes I'm confident that we're the town I
can see you're not one you you get so
you you you back up a couple steps you
see this happening you you're walking up
the stairs backwards you turn to go out
and then as you're walking around the
front before you've actually emerged out
into the thoroughfare you are struck
from behind okay I real play that like
that take six damage was okay here I'm
gonna keep you in Turners well that give
you an initiative so the weekend we got
a radical that's kind of those rightful
place sorry I'm tired of egregore I gots
exactly okay out there a tree rats but
you think that you've seen a new level
of rat disposal here all I see I see uh
PPP kick them into the Moonbeam trying
to figure out about a tail yeah that's
like hockey just like Wicca man yeah you
use one egg there's not big incineration
am Nicholas quit sacred calm great
account which makes today I do it one
thing that I don't have a card for us
we've forgotten oh thank you and you're
welcome but I call it tentacle lash dad
French Guinea to make way for it I would
love to what is it versus pinochle wish
rats this is my heart you're fighting
Brian I'm sorry
how hard is that they was never here
Oh Melissa joining standard yes of
merely spell attack okay romantic
okay I think I like my my just in case
there's more now dude there's a lot to
do huh hello okay whipping it's on so
I'm going to go ahead and typical it
through there one on the opposite side
of the of the Moonbeam we are they have
all sure crept in from the right side of
this I envision the Moonbeam it being
sort of central right now so this so
they're over there but you can only fit
easily hold you if you're trying to
bring somebody around that's no I I can
do you I know what you're putting down
guys step over
yeah ever I need grab one of them big
rats yeah you're at what in plump ones
yeah throw it in goodies do your whole
face into the beam juice that's almost
done my friends helping me although it
says this is 13 yeah 39 these are okay
yeah it's a red so so so so you so you
snatch it how much damage does that do
so this gentle boy is going to take one
be six Pearson comes going to take four
magic sorry and I'm gonna yank him into
the beam Devine would you be so kind as
to give us two t10 so [ __ ] by the time
the by the time the tentacle lash comes
back to you there's nothing in it kind
of use like that's all in it if you
really want you for a second there's a
skull and then if you reach out to grab
it it's just fine not quick enough like
the next time I got support net disease
in effect there's two of these rat boys
down here are they within I think each
other absolutely oh they're they're up
there remember they're all trying to
engage you in a lake all those would be
over to those are at a really cop the
orbit I like it one horns I don't want
to hook that don't mind it's the real
deal
he knew that I read to turn around
whether like what the move out was well
yeah I checked what another Ostrander no
no hold on Chris that's why make sure
you know that if she does pull out one
of your eyeballs are both good I get
mommy pit attack rolls against you will
have advantage in real life
yeah yes okay it's okay with me listen
you you obviously there was a donation
to child's play
we support that when I represent we know
exactly what it is is the year why you
keep it on if you want to blind Chris
drive on this astray mr. kerrity as you
know my children what side is cooler
with the eye patch is this one of this
one
I will pivot no it's that sound could
you guys keep your cute little yeah yeah
yeah all about a century comedian to me
please so you're just scoot your your
Moonbeam yeah go over there apps account
o bean sounds yes yeah yeah bn.trek cool
it wasn't Hey oh no it's better any
later and Wow
sorry yeah it's alright one extra that's
never been fired it's never is good your
evil Searchlight yeah cash it isn't an
ulcer fantastic so this cold light moves
over and then when it moves past there
is nothing in its shadow whoa
now we got to guess some of that yeah
it's Tasha good good stuff exactly in
time so you yeah yeah that's okay oh
yeah you look on the video you have been
sir compact and this is the timing is
actually right because you know because
you have always known from the moment
you got into town that you have a
specific task and it's time to set about
it so what what what so the you are
struck from behind yeah we're going to
rock forward you've been struck again
for two points no let me turn around
oh yes it's out yes yes where is this
[ __ ] yeah
are we seeing anything no no you're
still down do ya okay so that's it I
just say good boy I just as his action
yes Yves my compliments he smiles yelman
it's your turn I turn around where I see
you see a woman clad in black with a
reflective a knife that is reflected in
the moonlight alright Billy Lucas made
of glass or something like that and as
it as it tilts you can see the hated
symbol stand on its surface and then
disappear as the night turns amazing I
use without even being able to control
it and this on instinct whoo I trained
as a wolf
oh well Maya what's that yes and we have
official names for all the all the
transformation we do and I also we had a
really hard time coming up with brown
bear and I really want to put forward
Honey Nut
oh it's extremely nice really good table
top you up okay sorry um we'll get there
thank you Oh Miami weapon anybody is
this no luffy but there there is a soft
leather there is a mask up to the nose
okay cool
so I want to jump on this person leap or
leap normally when I leap okay so I want
to do this as if I was going to do if I
if I were to do a bite on the third yes
they would have been knocked prone but I
just want to do the knocking prone
portion of this okay which they have to
succeed on a DC 13 strength saving throw
okay thanks strength is good yes yes
what flying colors a little girl they
pass oh yeah okay great well then I just
bump up against them yeah yeah so
basically this is honestly not a bad
thing so you basically now it's like
this classic
image of the bear just upper wolf be a
welfare guess up paws just on the
shoulder just snapping and biting at the
face because risk as you are conferring
you're delighted attention toward legato
you notice that there is another rat
sort of observing the proceedings not
not engaging in aggression of any kind
just simply observing and you can see
that there is actually a glow a glow of
light from the surface much like my own
head under the stage lights um there is
actually a dim glow Harris no no a black
T through the top of the head this is
self insert the brain over Jerry stop it
I feel like it's important for you guys
I got it's important for you guys to
play the classic step I want to teach
you the real stuff you can see that the
skull is open and the brain is actually
exposed and casting light in the room
and like I say there's no aggression
ready smart it's always brain right it's
just giving it is just observed the
proceedings well I mean can I make an
attempt to uh something I can see it can
I try to communicate with it top teeth I
try let me try
um friend
sweetheart systems are 30-year low eat
sweet rat of my dreams
these your breath were these your rats
very matter-of-fact it's just a dead
no not very
[Laughter]
there probably it's rats who were it's
like sorceress supreme that's like I
draw my friends in yeah I know
figured it out you and I haven't seen
before but yeah very much a rat yeah
this old man whether he's trying to
pretend it was honest goodbye got away
without know is it foot I drew it weird
snake fire melody this is so nice
interesting fancy possible cuz I am
yelling it's the truth about the whole
show he invited you to I apologize and
then recast that moon beam over him and
his snake
oh don't when mm-hmm blah blah blah she
apologized I ever had Sally should be
mad at her a you know attacking
teammates is not honorable
no no no in our game now I don't know
Moonbeam okay but yeah Missy step which
is it a reaction I got immunity I have
immunity so there are different movies
at the same time I can't take it I'm
twice ya know it a lot like let me check
it out now I don't think misty step is a
thing that you can use to do whatever
you get out of this beam I wish you
decide I'm more like the light that
blinks when the chat is just like really
angry and you're eating misty escape I
have a sign oh is that what I know I
don't have this is a video action yes
it's not a reaction okay I doing wrong
so I absorbed the moon all right look
Harvest Moon that's nothing I don't know
Jonah lemon yes for well 99.04 allen
points to me so you you've seen its
effects before yeah and now you think
that there may be something that you
know about the moon you think that maybe
the moon has some kind of secret because
this moon light doesn't feel there's
it's cold but it feels like it is made
of a thousand points I feel shy rubbery
thank you sue
I like that you raise little your
familiar - OH familiars deadlier than
annihilated no forever it's just sweet
boy sorry ya desired like much like the
rats he's just a vapor I got II sorry
I'm alert his name is bigoted okay so
I'm sizzled yes candle eyes as well I'm
sorry I was rushing for Elsa's been
there I would have been new to them
first
oh yes um back out to the alley sure
your assailant is me now
doing everything that she can underneath
the weight of his massive dog to hold
her ground
I'm swipes for your exposed belly and
fails yeah can we hear any of this she's
not that far away from your there around
you're inside of intense yeah that is an
active and bustling place and I'll be
Neal and Lolly decide she's making this
sounds right like she she did know I
wouldn't know how that was for you yeah
that was for house that was for how you
alright
walnut um I guess I do buy you a bike
I guess I do a bite Gila by he's not
gonna kill her
whoa fight hoping my mood is not good
okay um laughs so that would be a 15 no
oh man no he's no success but but you're
really cool business you still have to
do the DC saving throw even though I
didn't successfully bite failure it does
claws no it just says target must
succeed on the DC 13 there sure I'm here
that's on kit okay she'll give you
missed the attack like oh I did at a
point it's not super cool I apologize
right that was it we pray
all right cut wrist route alright you
have been attacked by someone who you
found mysteriously and without
explanation in the cavern right it's all
starting to look very situation she
hatched out of one of those eggs like
this you what I think she's one of these
goddamn birds and create stuff together
I communicate to everybody else
yeah [ __ ] turn crow down here she
said when your own turn cracked because
I was moon beams then click the live
down here I'm so excited I get uqq so
how do you how do you respond to these
treacheries uh here angrily well why I
tell you what Patrick Rothfuss said in
response to a tree what what does this
or betrayal is what you get for having
guests on other than me you didn't write
me back I hope that you were not mad
about the comic I oh that's true oh he
didn't ask about the you know just I
always a surprise
oh no I meant him a meal before it came
in right I always do I never use my
special sweet boy I would never tried it
right right okay nobody puts it right
back
you didn't run me back and too angry
when I haven't done anyway well it's
probably yeah probably sorry oh sorry
you guys I guess I'm just talking dead I
thought the horns were cool hex norris
action night so next if you'd a hex
number one and you got x-ray and then a
shatter there which only yeah this is
the worst one I can do
at so Constitution saving throw for you
voices my my fourteen would be attempt
now attack ball this is like a million
jfl yeah girl yeah Sharia letters like
that so yeah constitutions versus
fortunately your constitution is
negative one okay yeah hmm that's really
not gonna do it so you're gonna enjoy
mm-hmm
the taste you know feel of cotton Rath
you need to direct the iron yeah I need
three days good idiot whatever then you
might have to buy a new set yeah I don't
have enough I'll get two of them right
yeah oh thanks yeah you bend it into a
dark contract so we got a we got
fourteen plus what is this lower so 18
for you plus 18 damage and that's my hex
so that's 20 for you oh nice how many
points do you have to be 23 okay know
what yeah okay no but I hit you for time
you hit me for 20 yes but I guess you
have to so I have three all right yes
no I did not have you're writing that
like no we have to succeed it is no
disease turn reduce guys lead roba which
one is yours
okay mind over the white ones yeah that
didn't pose oh yeah Amy preyed on you
bust my people I'm gonna Moonbeam you
again yeah triple Mundi I might even
still be in it
fried it is we're gonna divide do I look
okay as my aunt I just got out of its
range and then for the for yours and
you're just gonna hear a little bit over
frying him help me kill me scared my
gosh I wish you had left this is if
that's all it's done no help one more
alright well that was fun at 8 now cuz
it says it took man's exactly eight I'm
at zero Frank oh oh
is recognition Makani moon I love it
that's one are dating you should marry
mom did you take her joke and then do it
America jerking me okay actually okay
we're good friends she continues her
assault attempt sure you were gonna kill
me trying to go for trying to glide
trying to get ready to license okay um
and valiance it's just the weight of
this massive hound yes oh wait as a and
on my dying breath I say I was saving
myself for a different death not like
this
I'm supposed to be special so she does
nothing no she's not it was working
equally matched I'm going to one more
time try uh to save in it no I wanna
okay I look right in her eyes and
they're the eyes of like a oh yeah wolf
unhinged alright and then I do a cry
into the night and then I want to summon
wolves with my forest friend oh I do the
count horse crying any big they live in
the forest was pops they should be
moving coyote it's pretty sweet it's
really it's pretty early we will so you
so you how show you how deafeningly
capybara you you have nothing li yeah at
like right at this foe and that just the
volume and piercing clarity of it and
just pushes her down and then on you can
hear claws on roofs and you can hear
dogs braying of dogs of every stripe
every every loose dog has ever got a bad
deal in this town oh yes no it's like a
part of them that like we another
ancestor natural they're an American
their inherent wolf attune little snails
are just like
look at this range of proof just they
just pour into the alley until the alley
is basically just this brick of dog yeah
dog City right there and reign supreme
exactly - oh that's what I do I know I
hear that I'm a jogger so I am TV and
all those in a second yeah Elvis - your
coffee here that's true we order another
round we have to check before yeah like
hurry up no no I took care of it Oh what
happens is terrorized then one more wait
what happened what did I do
they imagine that there was a kind of
hunger that just lives in the heart of
every wolf I mean they're hungry like
the wolf right they're hungry like the
wolf thank you um no problem same page
just that there's just that secret
hunger that's never slaked and never
satisfied by the scraps of the master
and it all comes it all gets poured onto
this this entity that no matter what
they've done probably doesn't deserve
this moment just like arguments like
snouts pulling off pieces of armor it's
awful I'm slated you know having been
starved they begin to disperse and run
out into the streets howling and then
Devine it's your turn so you can you
have emerged from the basement um I have
alter self can I alter myself to look
like him I love you so much
you cheated a night
you absolutely can cool I need a roll
for that no other self to the river cool
awesome I alter myself to look like him
I just think low stairs yeah and then
come upstairs for
so you see Cece kisser astrov emerge
from the basement polishing and we're
just like I heard your thing everything
okay yeah yeah let's go
is it yeah no rats all gone yeah okay
cool alright are you being perfect is
incredible exactly I was like why are
you talking about the ultimate the
ultimate awesome save next week I'll try
to do justice to Devine oh we're not
anything there we are ending our own
shadow council so good thanks so much
for hanging out
thanks so much to Devine roller intro
super badass finale we're going to go
endeavor to use the facilities when we
return we'll shoot the [ __ ] for a while
please hang out with us we'll see the
second
you