turn at the enemy the past and threatens
the fastest weapon you wouldn't make it
past a second and that the question play
a flash and let us to choose a Carson
solution you saw was prudent in any
sepulcher poker tune will become the
putrid it's that well said I pursue in
no mountain too steep for dental duties
because them expendable marks up to the
top of the peak of beneath the AUD they
come like sharks to witness while I swim
in that learning game by Carl Barks
through it so send your national parks
through it I'll send him home in a
natural box the closed top of most of
the parks included save your breath for
a cleric confessor that is a lesson and
life is attending professor but if you
speak in my official advice sign on the
dotted line and list of the twice I love
chill out you don't you I'm in control
here sorry I'm in control
hello I am Tycho Brahe attacking impacts
I am also almond run of acquisitions
incorporated today Jerry Hawkins and
playing a game of dungeons dragons with
my friends to my right dragon board
narcissist in our work there we go I
want to be like a strictly in Taekwondo
click like a bunch of these in a sock oh
my I'm not gonna they are in suit oh you
can tell me that the idea of a sock
filled with those they like it takes so
much to like for me to get look at it
here's Ryan for getting my name's Paul
George also to my right Amy
I mean walnut dawn grass
repping the natural world Enclave panax
anima in the house obviously to my left
not your grandma's grandma rosy bee
stinger brand new grandma man see ready
for deployment today very exciting also
to my left
emerging from a mist shroud its cthe
wrist brow like is it sir yes like I
lose this now I want to know you want
every week no no I'll work on it
yeah I'm not doing anything else
certainly now let us like let's roll
back when last we saw our heroes
they had busied themselves trying to
ferret out a an interlocutor you know of
some kind in their midst
it turns out that some tea flings are
bad
occasionally evil horned people you know
it's a stereotype right but at the same
time like this is definitely a dangerous
assassin on top of that they party
busied itself managing the surplus of
rats quest that they had received from
Mayor Fran Elsa gorf here in the city
the cursed City of NEMA's ear you'd
manage some activities at the ironbark
in we're able to manage their rat
infestation heading north to the next
place that had been identified
you caught made the acquaintance of a
Dragonborn alchemist Talia chief
the bat murder large men's room they do
large Benjamin he reps it and their rats
had gotten into a delicious supply of
mystical potion rhe now exactly right
lightning wraps you know obviously well
represented in the fan art from last
week three guys they were just another
good just a friendly tuft a very strong
large rat also and then very fast rats
to Conway exactly but it added muscle it
had destroyed the stairway up and in an
effort to secure a rope ladder from the
Attic while not dog grass has looked out
of a portal window and was able to see
the entirety of the city of Mnemosyne
and determined something novel perhaps
something that she had not expected
which is that the town itself appears to
reflect a natural shape the town appears
to be
constructed you know summoned created in
some mechanism to you know reflect
exactly the shape of a leaf and not the
hated icon of maelys as some might have
thought erroneously twist yeah but
anyway we'll find out no but that that
is don't write it that is the very
moment that we find ourselves walnut Don
grass absorbing this fascinating new
data um so I'm not here with a yak Cal
yak I keep thinking is impale yurt and
I'm like tell you but um some of the
hell yeah uh can I take this I want his
arms are just full of sure a rope ladder
then I go on I go can I ask you one
question
you can ask me many questions perfect
because it's probably where this is
going um I go what do you know about how
did members here come to be do you know
anything about this Hein city that were
in well the tower that we find ourselves
in now is not a part of the original
construction I have a means by which I
can move the tower from place to place
wherever business is best for someone of
my talents wherever the Benjamins are
not large enough that's right there you
go my judgment yet don't go changin
pendulum case it's all about lesser yes
yes lesser Benjamin there's a hole
obviously as a range of Benjamin he says
it is a strange town but not without
coin and it has a statistically average
level of strange herbs
stranger spices eleven herb since my
hello what what kind of strange herbs
secret the numbers are not the numbers
are not correct there are plants here
that generally speaking must be secured
at great expense from the Underdark
oh no I thought I smelled something
interesting and familiar well homey yeah
nice um where where when I if I were to
look at these strange plants where would
I go whose well like it is peddling
these I I secure them myself you do okay
and you get them from the Underdark and
sell them here and there's a market no I
need not a decent it just wrote as I
suggested you know ordinarily one would
have to secure them a great price I see
some of them are not legal in the
traditional sense
sure nor are they legal in the legal
sense okay yeah they're not legal plants
I don't think you could put legality on
plants anyway but let me try - sure
you'd be surprised
yeah they're probably legal in the
Underdark so I'm going to come up with a
list of ones I might request and see if
you ready Howard them go ahead and spit
them out oh I like fancy pants it's a
it's a private discussion okay
these are from my youth that I've I
missed them yes when I was about 14 is
the first time it's called under cronic
have you heard of it under dank that's
it Johnny
okay okay in there and I'm I want to say
uh Olivia do you have any idea why they
would be flourishing here when this just
yet meh Monsieur doesn't show up on many
maps because it's a relatively dis
attend is of a relatively recent vintage
sure I do have questions as to how it
was able to be created
so soon and so far off the main roads
that's the question on everybody's mind
I think that I think that myself and my
little tower are not long for this town
and then so I'm like around the other
party but I look at him just like I
think that that probably a smart idea
this makes to be made hmm
he turns around lowers himself down the
down the ladder that goes up to the
attic
throws it down down to the second floor
nails it into the top and you should be
able to get down from this area oh we
get down so do you ah all short you have
to roll to get to all those rubies just
Rosie um okay so we've essentially
finished the rep yeah you haven't you
have said you have satisfied the letter
of the law on the surplus of rats quest
I have some thoughts about the fact that
it was glowing under the one red place
that ate our nemesis is fitting body
hood yeah I mean there's a couple of
spins there's that there's a dead body
we left in an alley right well she I
didn't kill everybody in budge I was
attacked by her so it was okay she's
still I feel listen I feel guilty
leaving a rotting body I did murder her
a heavy door restaurant I heard that
they have people probably healthy no
take care of that oh yeah they said I
did murder her but she was me
right yeah yeah yeah she said new things
well yeah she just kind of took a swipe
at me but I mean yeah city slickers you
know parents it was her dialectic right
I mean so if you were attacked - and
this was like a concerted effort by some
dark agents of this weird town to do me
in and you that's what I'm wondering is
I who would have known and if Sunday's
were like sea quality at best I did
to point you that's like the atom attack
see our does I mean technically fast and
great yeah who's really under assault
yeah what did you expect my taste buds
I'm nothing along the lines of what you
guys experienced you know that I did
there wasn't very disappointing halfling
named mark I knew it was gonna come back
so that's that just pretty effective for
me so you guys just had a good time
well right so at the time I told you to
see at bad bets sorry at best a thief do
you still have the birthday hat on right
now on the horse hire time I never took
it off yeah I think partially my vision
moving it do you quickly have to like
look over it in different ways I'm the
victim here
um yeah like that's this this is the
city that we're in right now I it I know
this place and this has not been here
forever
I don't know how do you know the place
because I'm familiar with the area Rosie
because I'm familiar with the area
just care I've been this way once or
twice well how old is it can't be more
than like 50 60 years old right now
overnight camping more than 20 25 years
maybe last all this takes together all
right
oh that's what I'm saying is that so
they built a city to murder us and then
give you a bad restaurant experience
this is a lot of trouble I know every
bar sitting in the trap maybe it's just
a shitty thing I don't think that yeah
maybe really treat everyone like this
who knows what that banana here did way
try to kill YF of every party that comes
in yeah I am concerned that I was
specifically attached to us outside in
the alley alone and also the first was
maybe specifically attacked when his
body was taken over by or I guess didn't
was an imposter to him okay and we found
her all the way out in the smallest
retinas pieces to go we found her all
the way out in that deep Kronus
Yeah right how did she know that we were
going to go - she wouldn't fire from
here - Lee right right but then we just
happen to that day also get emissive and
then pull out we'll go to the wandering
and I mean this is an official document
to the best of my knowledge can I do a
roll actually to see if it's definitely
definitely an official like a true yeah
job there's a real job now I'm wondering
right yeah um yeah altered form if it's
not in the movie
uh oh
not it's getting good an 11-4 like a
perception check on it uh yeah I mean it
seems to be it's in order to in line
with the other jobs that you have
received okay to the best of your
knowledge I'm just in this world I'm
just wondering as in the smell test if
there are coincidences so great as
finding a traitor from a place that we
have a job to go to on the same day that
Hoover people are that's right it
wouldn't be hard for that person to set
up this rat business and then request on
behalf of the city and the mayor so I
don't think it's I don't know that he's
at the top but there is no one wage and
we didn't beat him until until we got to
get that money anyway I have to do I
work out yeah we went back to the cave
that has a deep groan essent because we
believed it was the wandering crypt yes
yes that's a lot of us we thought I were
told to go so we went back to
investigate the wandering crypt and we
found Devine who just happened to be in
there and we went back to the crypts at
omens bad yep any moment job an omen
gave us right but how would Devine have
known that omen gave us that job unless
then she must have been spying on Oak so
if there a way that they can be
observing those communications that
we're getting from Roman the hologram
who's they whoever who are they yeah
whoever this this Devine character and
this person who attacked you in the
alley if they are were a dirt out dirt
okay so we're just Cultus gonna be
darkening we know anything about that
symbol and that's how we know this is
regular occult
once a lot of people are involved we do
Hartl security and they luckily within
an hour someone attacked like we're
we're sociopaths to an extent right
commit a lot of murder
Oh everyone would become its let him
right here yeah but murder I do it's
okay it's not murder
covered under company policy yes it's
all under the policy on to the polls
okay I'm just saying this isn't anything
to act on but it's isn't a keep in mind
I guess strange that Disney would have
known where we were going to be I also
think that's strange
I think everything about it is strange
at this point let's go and let's go talk
to the mayor let's get paid because it
was a Hester why he won't pass oh hey
whose pain is gonna happen there's pain
I guess maybe you know say yes nothing
is remodeling that yeah and he's there
and he also like said as much when you
talk historically a payment if you think
back to the last jobs it's true
historically payment comes from the head
office because they take their cut first
right here okay but we want to switch it
so he was making some little promises
and yeah how do they any of all it'd be
a sweet nice boy when you're talking
tram go in there show me I'm a machine
yes okay that's what you want to do when
I just look into his eyes and see what
it's all about
yes so you make your way you make your
way down the rope ladder it's fairly
it's a fairly Cirque de Soleil type of
experience we look awesome yeah it's
it's very exciting at about in the
middle of the ladder when you're able to
get the rest of the way down and it's
quite a it's quite a hike back through
that Central Corridor back to the
mayor's home the camera moves away from
the party well what revenue I've got me
well I listening you're doing exactly I
get it um cameraman gets bored exactly
it's like see I need excitement he has a
time exactly so not be a role it's good
so a man stands in the doorway
of the mayor's house and enters in you
can sense behind him that there are
others but he enters the house alone and
as he does you can tell that for no
cigar expected to see someone else at
thee at the entrance but friend Elsa
Gore quickly adjusts his raiment to
deliver a facsimile of professionalism
the closest he is able to manage at any
rate and he seems surprised at this
guest and he says world right I didn't
expect you I've managed everything that
you've asked just dough world rival I
fancy myself as in ER and tonight we do
have something to celebrate I've got a
new bottle of Razer wine let me get let
me get disappears into the kitchen brie
emerges with a bottle of a silvery wine
inside hands the bottle to his guests
and it says Oh glasses goes back into
the kitchen it is at this point that the
man in the for a uncorks the bottle and
whispers into it seals it back up as it
comes back out with two glasses you see
the man uncork it again pour into each
Cup offer for Nelson or a glass he says
I understand that we had visitors from
an adventuring company and for no cigar
says oh yes we managed the you told me
to deal with the rats and I did so I
went to all the pillars of the community
asked if they had rat trouble created a
job I did this all myself would be God I
I secured the services of
acquisitions incorporated a well-known a
respected franchise I'd heard that they
had done some work in Westbridge and to
to great effect here continues exactly
see he says hmm sis did you make any
special note of the druid they had with
them and Fornell says I drew a daughter
of these forests I know that they held
sway in these parts for a time takes a
sip of his wine and the man the visitor
begins to sort of pace like a panther in
a cage he says she is a favored daughter
of Maliki of a now-defunct order called
The Enclave panax anima now defunct but
they weren't without their trick they
weren't without their tricks did you
know it's a piece of trivia do you know
that they had a spell that would turn
the wine in a guests belly into thorns
so they have a reputation as being sworn
protectors of the natural world this is
how they did it with blood there is
another way the way you were to help me
manage he says what is your primary role
as a mayor of Mnemosyne and he says well
to
not to allow that I'm not - and
Blackthorn's
and blood erupt from his mouth and the
guest says I'll help you you were not to
allow the preconditions of prophecy you
have done so and you have failed me all
right so you continue through the tunnel
exactly about any of that knowledge yeah
yeah yeah Wow you continue through the
tunnel cool and as you'll recall the
mayor's little house sort of sits almost
like a pebble in the shoe of this giant
hill that exists in the center of town
as you approach the as you approach the
home you see it much as you did before
lights are on inside warm and cheery
compared to most of this place it has a
it's like like the iron bark in like it
it doesn't feel the same as the rest of
the town there's something different
happening inside got a good energy about
yeah yeah I'm excited just get that
money yeah I'll get paid folks walk
right in open the door
can we open the doors it's not good all
those things that I was talking about
knock on the door appreciative yes we're
manage yeah yeah we're trying to finish
them now yeah it's like exactly I got
something to say we're not much for like
hospitality or manner that's right
right we're here for money and answers
so heavy reom have you ever seen a pea
vine yeah yeah yeah all the time like
they're like they're clever in a strange
way right if you actually see one grow
they always trying to find something you
know but they always have a they always
had a little curl so they're always
ready to get a hold of a fence post
right climb up a lattice there they're
ready to go to work and that's you see
something like that here you see
shreds of robes and breeches sort of
suspended in this wriggling mass of
black thorns that are growing mouths
from a mass in the middle reaching up
tapping on window sills trying to find
their ways out way do I recognize
especially this situation but you have
heard stories right maybe see the man do
see it's coming at him
no just Rome's when do you recognize the
road with us we recommend oh yeah this
this is definitely his deal yeah get out
of the mayor did it for the vine oh my
god you guys suicide hey I'm so slow -
um but no I mean you truly for ever you
have heard you have heard old stories of
punishments okay they haven't into your
lifetime no punishment like this was
ever was ever deployed yeah but you've
heard about it okay um is it something
that only you are Enclave does uh what I
know is it you've certainly never heard
of this outside of that from another
group and like I say even now this would
not have been the norm this is just that
the mystery the lore of your of your
sect okay so we merely doing I want to
do this the thing when someone's in the
passenger seat of your car
I'll go like this ya know got stopped
short yeah soccer iOS app I know I do do
not approach that that is uh um I
wouldn't yeah how would you pay I wish I
want to go right up there yeah we get a
pulse like I want to take his death
yeah just see how did I want to say we
do not want to get closer to that
because those branches that you see for
those variables that you see that are
searching when they find you they'll do
to you what they've done to our friends
merit my cheese here
ah was going this this grimace and then
once I looked at these guys just well
we're not getting paid by camera ah but
I'm going to cancel my stuff in his
house do you really like the floor what
is that we're just going to step over
the decorating I like removing a body
but it includes yeah yeah I got a lady
body look weights not what night with
Skyrim this would be our new house yeah
exactly baby because you can so you'd
kill whatever was in there yeah I mean
you know what's in the room is you're
like is it it seems like a desk
everything is just elevator know if this
is this is just his living area okay you
don't give me a sense that he has a lot
of guests in here it's not spacious this
would not be a place for meetings to
take place it's for a mayor this is a
pretty humble dwelling can we
investigate yes if eclis can I roll them
but you can do whatever you like
I wanted I'm seen with all that I want
to see like you either we think of you
the Mayor was turned into vines or
something how did this befall him let's
look for some clues looks like a clearly
I want to look outside now we're all the
Sherlock it's going to be a 17 Alyssa
well
blam-blam-blam-blam yum-yum-yum-yum
alright thank you so much I have my I
get my magnifying glass out and you need
to take out a much larger better just
put my oh no no no no she takes yours
and then puts it out like that
a bifocal I give up yeah it's a sunray
you get yours out and I'm like me don't
be such sweet heart you're you know
you're no one who is your private writer
we're going to also role I want to look
outside no I'm not looking into any oh
sure I want to see you like let's go if
anyone saw this whatever the tri-carrier
looks like yeah that's pretty good
what happened 1920 wait wat and I want
to know if I can discern
maybe if I know what's going to happen
if we like what the brambles trying to
do I know about anything what it does
like
once it's demerit it's like maybe if I
leave it it'll just take over the whole
city could you'd be way into that I'm
sure maybe like a 16 if I'm doing like
an arrival right that's crazy
Gribble and cobbling together your your
lore knowledge and your regular
knowledge just of the natural world
um it's seeking if it doesn't find much
soon that it will probably just shrivel
if this is not it's not grown in soil
you know what I mean like it really is
just this knot of thirsting roots you
better not go near it
yeah I met his friend Nell destination
see I love it I don't to be why yeah
yeah
all right nothing recent no yeah um
plant so yeah but not I'm not having not
having access to her well I mean it's
not there's not gonna be a whole lot I
can do here coming off of this what do
you think of mine at 20 well I love your
nationally don't remember everybody's in
it everybody's going to get their love
okay just a really good role yeah
everybody can get their lives so you get
set up on yeah camera right here that's
really all right here but that's the
real key that's the one thanks little
rough there to you there near you you
can you can see that someone came in but
never really got past halfway they came
in sir walked back and forth and then
left very recently you also see a bottle
of a silvery liquid on a table with one
empty glass and one full glass okay so
this looks like a case of poisoning that
looks all legitimate to me I would I
would agree okay it definitely seems
like that's a pretty novel configuration
yeah yeah yeah and well not just a good
one all that check this out
the the wine
I know that you love to drink than I
love my deposit you're a drunkard I is
it it I pause for something I like yes
fair fair but this this seems like maybe
this is related to the scene that we see
in front of us
someone else was here I feel like at
this point why I feel like uh there are
stories of certain types of druids who
had this power in the past
I mean heroes of legend great protectors
the best through its really of all the
driz best huh okay
oh great sings violent for a druid well
tell me about this best druids only
happens
Dragonborn of druids yeah sure I guess
uh I want to point to NGOs um this is
something that no one has done to my
knowledge in a very long time
certainly on my lifetime and maybe not
in my mother's lifetime and this would
only happen if it a person was truly
deserving of punishment a black tender
let's start to sniff around your boot
okay I'm gonna cook the bottle and take
it with us I'm not gonna drink it okay
generous I think it's poison I don't
understand what you're saying really but
I think like really something if
somebody poisoned something this is good
good stuff I'm gonna kill it on the
house plan house plan went crazy I
yelled it yeah um yeah okay you can take
it with so there's one around my boot I
kind of like budget yes yeah pull it
away
it's nice around you yes I'm time
process oh yeah so so you see this
you're framed in the light of the
doorway and you exit the the home and
out into the small garden that he's
attempted not to absolutely murder here
out in front of the house I'm rotting
fen yeah yeah he tended dun dun dun oh
yeah wait Lamas Morrison yeah he just
needed advice be
I was thinking that last horse that died
because she was consumed from the inside
by thorn I did
Oh Roger you know what's coming the fine
um there are yeah the girl okay - very
boyfriend there are full house
okay all right sorry
notice I know as long as you want to
know so you're saving me time so if I
don't have to entertain you
this is great news for me there are no
less than four black-clad assailants
what in the garden just like he was
growing them yeah good just stand-in
there at the time of every sale goes
like a variety me yeah oh who do you say
oh all right I said she's a Colo I've
called them up from the house I go hey
Rosie found a bottle of wine
I give us a bottle of I'm in here I
found four dudes out here I think I
found who killed him
they're looking at me and I'm looking at
them yeah I don't think they see me if
they think I'm a fountain I don't try to
be like a fountain I'm like yeah I don't
nearly have said I think we need go out
there okay I need help okay
yeah let's go try to communicate this to
everybody there are murders or the body
okay I say hey did you know what
happened in there
murderess noob really matters in the
garden but I yell out not today I yell
out yeah verbally I say let's go further
into the house get the drop on now yes I
did their murders oh I know they are the
in those can see if you could surprising
ah I think initiative is a good thing to
rule and that's the best initiative role
I have ever gotten
for real nice one for me oh that maybe
they didn't get it in time that's uh
nineteen for me I'm not your sister 1919
one negative once I got it I I've got a
14 okay no you wanna okay we uh how is a
nineteen for you it's very good
what's your down the stool but what's
your decks will not write my decks
personal question it is I got a plus
three modifier to succeed okay how about
you Chris all my decks didn't get a plus
two okay
the way for Satan to answer no no just
your decks in general yes exactly see
Rosa Rosa I didn't know how you're
curious I don't really patch up at all
after the rest oh my god I'm not sure we
didn't like fling take our real long rap
no no get a potion from the elk and I
think you guys we're all in a rush to
get back get babes oh yeah I can I said
it alright her little what I wait I did
the world as much I did not do a bear I
need to keep when I did the wolf needed
all I have an advantage on Constitution
say my reason I just lost right oh my
god why do you have so many dis yeah I
have Sony disadvantage if you promise I
can take you another thing so you guys
did a bone zone you can do it yourself
I paid into my own yeah exactly
every worth it or no I can't yeah I'm
going to put that I want to put that
[ __ ] to work alright alright so like I
say my initiative was completely
completely out of control it was very
very good and they fly over the over the
short wall that sits in front no foliage
is safe from these these dangers whoa
massacre works so hard he
he did he has worked for months well I'm
his gardener has worked for what four
months all right now here we go this is
what I need so right now the feast that
they have available to them is a tasty
treat that we call dinar Blitzen I'm
like did you look at me wrong yeah well
how much oh hey did you move don't move
yeah so what's your AC meeting at a roll
bunch so it'll help me just timewise
Yeah right yeah tea break people I guess
I get asked every week a new character
dies yeah who can it be this weakness
and then all four of their tiny bodies
turn pilotis like a yeah well I'll
distract them yeah yeah would you walk
with your blood
yeah remember me there's eight points
well and see baby butterball now two
more points how did I just punch it oh
no they're they're coming up and you can
see I mean this is obviously he is sort
of like tanking he is in the door he is
basically the wall that separates you
guys and these assailants but you see
you see just in the in the light you see
flashes against black knives okay all
right walnut on grass yeah what do you
have for me
you had to you had to ask
oh geez
oh um well I have a distinct feeling
that I'm going to turn into something I
get that feeling around you a lot yeah
one never knows yeah master know it's
okay to play well I'm an only piece form
you have left at this point you're like
wow
nice wheeze away I live in an attic no
no I'm going to turn into Honey Nut the
brown bear hunting eyes the brown bear
delicious
alls I'm just like milega to turn inside
out and then turn into a bear yes like
swipes that's my transition sequence so
you made you basically basically just
strong-armed Denar out of the way
yeah I want to body block for him yes I
want to take to damage yes and I yes
hello McCoy he's oh no I want to get
past them and I want to attack the
nearest nurse one yeah all right okay
yes no this is it this is a super
awesome image yeah for me at least
because you slight you you scoot out of
the way as well nut and then are
immediately just pound the giant paws
into the ground
so yeah usually saying I got it it's
final models a crushing each other my
job walking with Joey I'm not into when
I turn into walnut or into the bear
honey not accidentally clipped into
denars notice but now you can sit wild
in the corner lift in our sips and he's
entirely inside yeah yeah especially
that somehow there is a bear like
equipped in the Hat slot yeah yeah I
know where we've become one are
seriously there's a park again give you
fair skin yeah eat like they seeds in
ours name plate so it's over honey not
how's it happening I am into too light
exactly so even even just the
transformation just sort of push the
group of them yeah back so they have new
strategies that they have to employ they
only have two yeah I got to contend with
a big etiquette end with this beanie um
roll for this
not in a 20 minute of 20 that is
excellent
oh and this is a this is an eight I
never know what my dissection um hold on
sorry
whoops plus four so it's a seven
piercing move on but the thing about
brown bears is see folks the thing about
brown bears that's like it's like it's
like we got to focus like all the
cameras
just a me can you decide it's the walnut
nature moment this is true it I am bring
what I want its mutual
so now I get why liking is that a claw
swipe all gross
not good seven so I have swat at them
but I can't see my kingly yes back up
yeah nice back away from our Guardian
tonight it's just anger it's just rage
Chris tryst route whoo all right I'm
going to try and counteract some of this
here there's [ __ ] BS sorry I don't
cuss on this and my child's watch we uh
I'm going to throw let's see here juice
do I got all that good stuff
right yeah the only as far as I know all
I've done is all I've burned is shatter
so I think that's what I got when they
say if you're rotating out right I mean
right yeah it's hard that's the one so I
would you say that these foes are in a
20-foot cube because it can this cube
that you're describing include your
allies yeah absolutely
so you know my targets enemies no it
doesn't matter I look hard as you know
as everyone oh no I'm doing I'm waiting
a very fire I'm trying to get a return
advantage to the group its way while you
feed it when you try to steal ice but
yeah I mean I could hey you all care if
I see you guys lives matter
those are damage well sure sure but I
mean it would also make you easier to
hit he's doing saying a lot of 880 I'm a
big there in what configuration time
minimize send them first to party in
there okay card yeah I could hey you if
you're in the if you're in the crowd I'm
good no it hits everybody if it's all
creatures that are visible or SAR all
creatures weird that you have on your SS
I'm going to do that right really on the
other edge that you can screw it you can
you can very easily catch three of them
safely okay let's just do that okay so
yeah fail those dexterity throws please
I don't think that's going to happen
you try life such a bite for seven seven
all right so you so you you you wave
your hand and then they've it's sad for
them because they'll say I can they've
taken such care to dress in a spooky Hot
Topic adjacent fashion don't work and
now they're glowing for real
yeah it's voiced - now the election of
November damaged oh I see you I know I
go a naughty naughty when they feel a
little bit that - yeah yeah at the same
time so wait that's action yeah and then
I'm gonna do what naughty naughty is
like yada yadi no that's not good daddy
franky hey where's the other one that I
cannot see because I'm going to do I'm
going to throw a hex on that fella my
understanding is that you're not a
missive you cast a spell as your major
the main part of your action you can't
cast a bonus spell did you boys actually
no I don't think so
what that's what I thought that was a
bread and butter of this thing you hear
the bonus and then you get the action we
rule in but that's my understand your
secret dips actually the bonus snag
negative power yeah yes
in another huh it's a 58 laws of power
my ex is your boss action that's it is a
bar section but I think it's a spell
I'll figure it out by the way it's very
far - I'm using it as a can trip - I
mean I can't use it it's once forever
but yeah it's my action because
ordinarily I do hex and then oh I know
one of these bad goes I'm trying to
figure out if that's just more rad
trying to decide if you get to do that
and all right well then I do bonus
action first on the one I don't plan on
hitting with the other yeah and then I
do the action that I always do is that
bad
yeah no just somebody came up they were
talking about on Twitter and you know
this one has some guy on Twitter yeah
yeah yeah but I thought I also saw a
comment that said that it says in the
official rules that these are just
guidelines and if it's really really
yeah you know what I kept all my actions
no no no we're not gonna get that okay
you're not going to get that but I think
it's I think that's a hex combo I just
like how it feels I think I think that
I'm just going to let that happen
what that's my understanding for that
what that guy was saying yeah sorry but
this is everybody no no no my
understanding was that
where is the way I have in which I had
used hex was I I messed up an ability
check and then I attacked on that check
but that just has a way that works yeah
yeah I got I can do bonus in action but
my hex doesn't actually will be they
came more well in any case in a case
that's welcome to the land of rule 0
folks yeah yeah I just like that I like
that you spit some nasty curse at them
in addition to doing other stuff so
there's this very fire doesn't very far
so you basically you want to ask the
person who stayed out who is the person
and Bera spell and it doesn't damage
them because I didn't do damage to know
what do you say when you hack some will
you say to people this one's the full
meal deal I got the voice and I got the
the gestures so what do you do I make
those dr. strange hands like that yes
spider-man and I think yeah I go flip
but it's a hex that comes out and said
Oh weird hex
come to me I'm nothing no I've said it
so often that I say you are hexed but
I've said it so often that it just comes
out next yeah one word X goes out I'm
bringing sexy back
well I would say female me never that's
pretty cool too yeah yeah I think it's
cool alright so I say yes I'm bringing
next event guys shoes next time the
breedings mixture time so what what are
you gonna hex uh Oh as far as his uh
checks I'm gonna do I'm gonna do his
deck her checks hex edge her checks in
this decks yes yeah check max deck
because they're just going to take an
extra protect uh yeah cool
ah rosy thing stinger you uh how could
how can you modify this scenario tell me
the we have four target you do give me
their situations physically their
parents have gone away for a week stake
every thank you no problem every stream
no no problem
they their their raiment seems yeah
sanctified like they seem like they seem
like a priest
everybody went through midnight yeah
okay we're trying to find the person
looking the most damaged the most
damaged is definitely the one who has
been interacted with he spied this Honey
Nut yes okay all right
and they're they're dressed in dark
clothes dark dark robes and they have
daggers thank you
all right Rosie scoffs says you are no
true agents of shadow and she casts
sacred flame because Rosie took cleric
levels when she leveled up and she took
three pretty tight spells one of them
being sacred flames bigger flame is a
piece yeah was that we confused when she
loved with her was it like a
no it's purple no she took them she was
not confused was he's rarely confused
but she took long surgery because Titus
house Oh alibi yeah and command guys
know yeah only users somewhat rigid like
24/7 yeah she was taught about you can
convert ready now but I think I'm going
to standard sacred flame is such an easy
choice yeah so um save on a deck throw
that worked out what are you doing um
Wendy a tree and damaged almost landed I
didn't oh yeah that's right in the
[ __ ] okay ah remember though you get
four four points of damage nice flame
like radiance descent upon honey nutz
target yes what are we had the fairy
fire yeah and now it's
immolated right with real fire as well
if there are the arms are sweeping in
desperation cracks dinar Blitzen looking
plump yeah looking plump buddy I'm to
health die yeah I'm sort of limping away
that is it yeah and they started I get
out of it like behind a bush and start
touching myself
still got rat bites on me from before
yeah whatever
no but it's like melting or look at me
zodiac is young donor why don't we all
look at me but I need to make myself
feel better
Susan woman says the bush is not large
oh no like it's not a Nara special oh
it's not providing the type of
protection that he thinks I am I kind of
I think we're lost in translation but
anyway I might I unload all of my points
onto myself so now I'm 22 I'm so happy
better yeah I feel a little better take
you out relief oh yeah
pick up some different yeah yeah yeah
yeah I'm ready to deliver
I'm ready deliver results I pop back out
I know haha all better guys no no first
but for him it's oh wait another yes so
let me put a sock on one of the branches
so we open yes
what is the system alright yeah this is
this is what occurs next now you are
being fought by a glowing flaming dark
priestess how I like them of some kind
their attack misses you completely but
others have now joined the fray sure
they have descended on you sure
and they goddamnit no suggested in
Savannah they basically just fell loud
to see they just collapsed on you and
none of them it's just it's just a mess
of dark knives like none of them are
able to deliver it
walnut unrest oh honey no um I would
like to grab on I want to finish off
this actually know what look nibble on
everybody I'm playing here yeah a lot of
stuff like an alien
oh come on I want to grab I want to bite
a fresh boy Oh juicy um by the way you
deserve I'm going to Oh wah wah wah wah
William yum-yum-yummy shadow council
means I get to roll Barrowman I invoke
your blessings upon this game a lot of
times well the 20 in my entire life oh
so good gotta give me something that I
don't account for senators like laying
on hands oh wow you got it what I got oh
what a nightmare okay so hang on
so uh eight of force twelve oh wow any
damage
oh my god energy then I also get to do a
claw attack it there does it have to be
on the same target no maybe the text
says one bite and one claw attack as an
attack action to defuse your target a
menacing fall attack the two claw
through them and throw that meat add
another yeah what am i doing yeah what
if I just roll to see if I just like hit
somebody a bat somebody away what if I
don't do damage and I find out that
information for next I did kind of sweet
so if I kill somebody on the first
attack it wasn't the first attack was
the bite right yes yes I know but
they're so they're all so close I mean I
feel like this is this is a pretty safe
one you tell me so I'll hear about it in
my tension they so you your head goes
out you turn your head and just clamp
down on a neck oh and just one quick
motion is over it's like a hair yeah you
know what I mean and then they just get
flung over to the side if you like right
over it in our sex bush what is that US
bush it was you feeling myself so let me
see everything exactly but but there's
still there's still three others that
let me they're trying to fix our your
little red wagon let me see oh it was an
eleven so not good another intimidating
swim yeah yeah exactly
I said yeah except I go okay if you like
the lips going like Berenson Omaha
and lots of fiber yeah oh love it
Patricia oh um see we got here I didn't
pay attention I'm so wrapped up in that
that bite well I was thinking about that
was invited a year I was great I did do
a bite
that was a dope-ass bike all right well
it seems like they're not super built so
maybe I'm not going to throw away one of
these let's just do a classic Eldridge
blast the nineties uh they all hit yeah
do we have them somebody who still
outlines in the mix oh yeah this the
rest of this crew or the Sahara Chloe
China all right come on pop it charity
the one you just kill but that the one
you hurt before or is this different now
that was a fresh Island oh boy I was not
very far away okay Oh what is it good
I'll get it so that's going to be a year
20 mm-hmm
Karia all right you're gonna love all
this damage already 1100 you know if I'm
an idiot I should have aimed this attack
at the guy I did hex on that's okay I'll
remember for next door
that's a 5 it's a tasty 5 mm-hmm and
that's the end it's just a little a
little like I'll up that swipe and then
I do a slightly more active chase here
elder slashguard yeah have our new
mistake okay all right yeah so it arcs
out to you and you and strip it away
from you no yes you instruct one of your
attackers with your source cereal might
Rosie be seen part of a complete
breakfast okay so we have one down three
to go
is that correct indeed okay I'm going to
use my halfling nimbleness it's tough to
dart nimble yep Oh order just to slide
and displace out we have eaten I think
many creatures that have other size
larger than me and so I believe that
these probably are I'm very small in
there oh yes average yes so I flip out
past honey-nut and past these attackers
and I'm gonna take them from behind
boom like she knew like she do
so you see you're sliding under the bear
yeah over the bear Eliana de faire yeah
and I can feel a little tickle on the
way under very good yes quite over the
hood it's a hazard that's a danger zone
I don't get near in the hot shot as you
said you get under there fired I do give
you a like a little scratch on the belly
for being such a good honey thank you
okay so yeah coming in and since I have
slid through them and behind them I was
hoping I might get advantage on my
tackle well okay no in fact you get
disadvantage I really hold you know good
impression he's ready he's very fired so
the student cancel each other out
oh I think okay so I don't rolled as a -
no no just grewal one day find out of
the two dice that Chris wants you to
have and the two bad dice I want you to
roll it
all right you wacom yeah girl can tell
you that are you the key point to and
you okay to kick it out to kick out the
jams yeah um so you sure give me the
first damage hey first damage is a 7mm
cheese and then I'm gonna do two on our
strikes and just whack them with the d
AP yep that's a hit
that's an on attend haha and that one's
going to be a 15-minute yeah okay and
another ten Lord
that was a blazing round with the
Challenger economy's called this know
where I gotta be
I know that I know the Chandra so so it
underneath you slide under the furry
Boulder that is
honey-nut slide out slide between two
foes right in the back of the head with
the stick and then two shots in exactly
the right places and the so just
crumples like doesn't fall over just
crumples like implodes and falls forward
that's it for that is it for target
number two now Chris
I want to talk to you real quick about
hex you sure because I think that I
understand something about hex that you
should know yeah right okay okay okay so
if a target drops to zero hit points
before this spell ends in R over the
durations an hour right you can use a
bonus action on a subsequent turn of
yours to curse a new creature so you can
take that curse and you jump it from
photo fill I can't give it to you this
time right but keep that in mind for
your own use you should write a note on
this because you can you can maintain
that that DPS bump on any target for
your friend it's like the discord orb
yeah I don't get this over but yeah oh I
get it
exactly this is over which that's how I
feel there now there are now two more
two more foes dinar Blissett yeah to
church
yep I'm gonna go after one of them so
one text ones very fine they're both
very fired not okay we got there XE guy
okay alright so I'll go after one of
them so I go through the closest one
bring a little toothbrush Papa make like
a like button and smash and turn yeah I
go what is it what up it's your homie
you wants baby I got smash that like
button we could get one thousand
subscribers that oh my gosh you guys and
then swing I want you to only murder
that like why the [ __ ] like whatever
things I don't like button just go take
it our big prophecy I get advantage on
right yeah from you get advantage on him
from fair fire e-e-e I'm not gonna do my
special big voice one actually I should
if I got advantage lending my big boy
swing which means in a word because he
will take it away it's too late now
oh yeah cuz it's a great combo you're
doing up in power tax right I'm talking
about my great weapon master yeah
exactly
Boop so if you get two dice great weapon
mr. makes money
I like it oh gosh we need a lot of wind
up on this oh yeah that's it one Italy
sort of so classic your turning got you
gotta use I'm playing a world would that
means what is it for you
sorry this is still new to me this level
for yeah this is the great game yeah
it's last time too yeah I'll just get
+10 to d6 + 3 + 10 it was a juicy hit
roof that's a [ __ ] of the one I find
the quickest damage that's a 3 so 4 by 6
7 17 that's what I said a lot of damage
buddy Jed rolls if he's dead I check
another action no he's yeah if I said oh
no he is not dead he is not dead
and in fact you you bring you bring the
sword down good
just clamp right down into the shoulder
and somehow somehow they still have the
presence of mind cool are you married
the sword comes down and they're dagger
comes up underneath the plates 410 and
like looking at your SEC Bush yeah that
yeah you exactly get back over there
it's been some more quality time this
soon I need a rest for how droughts do
it this
oh yeah we're I think it was something
like yeah you just manipulate the energy
field oh yeah
like Symmetra yeah yeah never the budget
traitor protectors law so your your
assailant dinar is going to try to
capitalize a second time just mated no
no did not able to do it this time this
time it's good skitters away off of the
plate going after this massive bear oh
for 8 points and I say no but it comes
out Rick yeah you can tell me in it is
no it seems it personal but the dagger
the dagger just goes in to that set fat
layer on the belly which is like face to
face just working it in look exactly uh
walnut on grass I also known as Honey
Nut don't worry it let the knife do the
work so nice to know her she's like but
uh I'm going to do a bite on that one on
the one it is stabbing me on yes I'm
gone
seventeen mmm-hmm eighteen I can add 18
ah Xiu where's my date
I lost it already the junker again yeah
okay that was an 11 oh now you're saying
and then I get to do my claw attack
please mm-hm
yeah and another 18 um now this is 2d
search she did really care like really
yeah I get to do a lot of hiccups of 6
or 10 damage oh yeah that was a pretty
premium set of turns from dinar and
walnut tree that you can be a magical
creature and like know all these spells
or whatever but nothing is more powerful
than just being a regular old Barry bear
but I would win the ultimate scam right
is that if they reduce you use your hip
points then you just wallet again yes
bill Rab well yourself unless you can be
a bear a message of you there and the
beauty that's right good advice
okay um Chris job there are two targets
here that has been winnowed
substantially carved
hollowed indeed hmm harrowed oh by your
olive by your fellow wow what is that
I'm inject I don't think it also cubed
entertaining or is it elder people ask
what do you do
I want to find out why that's such a
good salary buddy loves that one Mike
don't export anything I'm going to do a
one of those stars must plucks on my
clothes man forgot about that one no no
okay good deal I'm glad I'm glad I'm
going to hurl it at which one's the
which one is the worst-looking ones you
hex boy or but today 2x in there go
ahead on that what erekle
then I would say they're both in a
really awful okay state and then
automatically hit so it's not really a
danger to use it and mail your name
right
so let me acquire I do is three times
there's man yeah three before
oh right there sure it's not that you
sure it's not the 44:24 sweetie even
after the level yeah okay does it change
you to get Mormon this week on the Selma
cloak oh I see so that's come be three
and big money all right
seven seven why can't you [ __ ] can't you
trash damage look at you you think I
would jog with bad roll and then you had
those like seventeen bench I got I'm
just a gentle stab for Michaels like a
frond yes I mean just rushing the face
it's my fault work like actual magic
missiles like a sea levels up he'd get
four missiles or is it always only by
myself in earth it has it the only thing
that I would say okay Barry believe
there's two things one hiya chief
specifically called out the make of his
cloak oh I forgot predators a knock off
right now and and to its super top
secret so it's a good new chief yeah
they get you killed upon Brad seems only
fitting right here to me so that's it
it's like this these these as the three
as the three friend orbs you exactly
cast out bursts reaches out strikes the
target they are they are stunned by it
and they they draw their dagger across
their own throat well come on man I want
that XP on man yeah that's how many boys
are down what is in there so wait can i
intervene when i see them doing this
yeah i wanted to interrogate yeah can I
scream like command and then real quick
don't do it when a Shia I want to say
stop gnarly on how much damage does
their own throat-slitting do what is the
damage on a dagger and it's like then
kill them
I'm going on and go for it again Wow
three yeah all right the mowers doesn't
oh yeah absolutely
so am i there not a chance to be like as
we see them do that I don't have your
own turn well they did this was Chris's
turn so they're killing themselves on
Christmas Day sure Holly Internet
yeah whether he supports it 100% yeah I
love it
so there is another target for you Rosie
there is actually there's only one
target lat I thought you said they were
both yeah I thought it really a ritual
suicide yeah I misunderstood as well
well then Rosie would like to tackle
with her small body and hold her staff
to its neck and start to interrogate
Barrett's life for now and try to get
some information I know I know the ropes
for the Charles you know I understand I
understand but we got the rod and the
child so all right we'll combine them if
we need to all right so you want to
tackle okay and I guess an unarmed
attack but I don't want to do any damage
I just want to mobilize well yeah yeah
you just want it you want to trip them
up I can that's true but it's my turn
grab grab make them knock I know but I
don't blow out okay let's see in a
temporal okay good one
okay yes what both sure exactly fine
though
so you so using the staff of the master
is begin to whip it around it takes on
that clear confusing whip like shape
you're able to distract them for a
moment with that bizarre arc and I get
behind them and hold the staff against
the against the neck basically it's like
a takedown right blamed a living so
there with using so they're with you on
the ground
you're mobilized by this okay this hold
all right so I'm going to ask them
straight up first
who they work for and if that doesn't
work then I will try an intimidation
they don't say anything and in fact
they're struggling mightily to escape I
tried an Elvish Andrew Connick
well in case they don't speak comments
nothing no okay I'm going to try an
intimidation role that is a sixteen tell
me how you try okay I've got I'm pretty
intimidating as it is I am very small
but I have pinned them yeah yeah I'm
bullying them with with a coarse ass
right around other necks and I lean in
and I say I suspect you know exactly
what that wine does to a person
and I want you to know that I have the
rest of the ball you see you see that
their use their eyebrows crease at the
mention of a wine okay there cuz they
don't understand what's going on okay
yeah I mean you you can mean it's clear
like do to the extent that it's not even
doesn't require like a intuition or
something like that like that's that's
not connected to I think if I see that
and I go yeah it's why not killed you
yeah it's a bad it's a bad vintage yeah
it was an off year yeah really it was
not too cold it's not terroir cause yeah
well yes you've got very dry yeah you
know more - no - Pinot Grigio more
didn't war is still good yeah yeah good
okay you feel it'll work but like not to
me yeah nope murder love one exact okay
you're trending they're not but they're
not buying it no no no by tan in fact
they are able to twist their body in
such a way that they are now on top of
you with the staff okay no well it's my
turn my turn is it not it is now dinner
stripping well I must snatch him up from
behind then I'm gonna get I mean let go
there how full-nelson actually yeah I
know what I'm trying to
is going for himself I know what this
guy's mess up yeah you know true w to
leave yeah so I haven't grappled I was
gonna say it say I wanna die - can we
heal them that I could fly into
Christmas focus hey how about a even
funnier yeah like we're all in agreement
or any want to keep trying get info out
of these yeah I like to I mean all right
hit points left
so what's how does grout sorry I even
grappled anyone before I didn't know
that was something I could do til
someone told me other day grappling yeah
so what's what the was it fatty gravel
em boy do I get like a joy target I
never drank to it
target is grappled and restrained escape
would be what a DC something yeah I have
okay DC tool maybe there's like a
strength condoms for you oh yeah yeah
yeah just give me the robot will know a
lot more 1308 Ohm's advantage I think I
still owe you said it on attack rolls
okay
crap was running the test yeah you
probably I can beat yourself oh all
right well yeah I think this plus degree
so ii k yeah yeah yeah you're able to
pee yank them bosses Rosie I'm so strong
I Powerball that's what you're good at
him yeah exposed ribs are you work the
by you command am are you just I'm just
I'm gonna hold him I know he's gonna try
to keep wiggling yeah okay I'm gonna
hold on real tight big strong man I
don't it man yeah you you got you ever
you have a tremendous amount of size and
weight yeah
I call on it on this pre yet all right
what's this it's their turn now
oh yeah they get to move yeah okay now
so do they get out oh okay just be sort
of left initiative and networks and book
a power that's all good hidden
dinner and it was all right here that's
not over until they're dead
exactly yeah you know in our world a
crossbow bolt what strikes the person
that you are holding
what knows only dead no okay
not it's so sad for them is look so I
use them on the shield yeah with the are
we back in initiative order yeah exactly
for me or him okay so woman okay
so uh asket fast as I thought yeah I'm
going to come out of my shaver bear my
super bear shape and I wanna just go up
to it and and I want to say um so I want
to say her name all si are you like are
you working for me Lilith are you
working with me let me say may live a
lie down so okay at this one oh my god
okay just don't say her name
oh wow I'm gonna really lean in really
quietly and I'm gonna go are you working
with nailless she's just shrinks and
struggles mightily against an arc but
that's not going to get her out of this
dragon prison that's what I could do on
my Kristiana differencing worth it
yeah I'm gonna say it to there where did
it cross me
well UOP turn away from that whoever
he's doing that shot uh I got only
literal in Hanceville some of guys
research I think you okay it's been in a
circle Karam forever to prosper oh yeah
good idea
but this time I do a I speak to the mind
to mind we don't have to say may without
loud just look at that she continues to
shriek and scream but you can you can
sense that catharsis is speaking
directly like it and there is his body
language has become conversational in
its way so boy is that you who sent you
I see the symbol you carry thank you
first oh this one yes you know it's like
if you bear our symbol as well also
that's it who is this cuz I don't know
it becomes come on I'm also confused
but I am terrified that you would have
that obelisk and not know let me help
you become less afraid why should you be
scared of this because it may list
shares nothing with anyone why would her
symbol be on that maybe she didn't share
it maybe
my God took it from maybe you have
adulterated the old ways maybe you
adulterated your ways maybe you're not
the cultivation you're like really sad
yeah yeah yeah exactly but the bottling
is just like you're just napping here uh
Rosie beasting yeah I like that I do
this the ER but in like 24 points I want
to get that that vaguely occurred on
television on a rigid etheric feels like
Christmas hats as well in hand and is
now scanning for the source of the
crossbow bolt perception clamps na oh
yeah works 21 nice good lord
there are so many that at first you
think you must not be seeing it
correctly good run oh I mean Kate
alright like you think you think that it
might be some feature of the
architecture at first like a
crenellations or you know what I mean
right but there but I eventually
resolved okay it resolves in your mind
that this is doesn't you see at least 12
our cool see
right so yeah yeah this this is usually
you've been alive for a long time hey
you know you made the best you made the
best of it is the first thing that
occurs to you all these fools are young
grass exactly in dinar what's in okay
warn them
yeah verbally yeah yeah really all right
um you guys keep your heads down
is it shitload are trees around here
like are they circle there all day from
like go under all roofs in it the
breakfast yeah else with the creaking -
gasps enjoyment shield basically yeah
yeah alright yeah let's all get back
inside and close the door uh yeah so I
got a new plan for our buddy here you
know a meat shield so I start walking
back with us or the house and I
everybody want everyone back in the
house and I use this guy as a shield
they start walking backwards okay take
them in right I'll take a banana sheet
yeah yeah take her yeah
how they all do women by the way that's
your guess just silhouette
generally speaking you have to make a
more robust got sort of fragments
exactly exactly
you take three points three crossbow
bolts sail from these roofs and find
their way into this servant of MELAS
if you hear just an exhalation in your
mind just some artifact of the living
the red and most of you you pull them
you pull them back in and then you're
back and the whole crew is immediately
now in the midst of this writhing mass
near the end of what it can accomplish
without
feed give it the body what would its
owner die
yeah I don't think we should feed it
yeah well walnut think we should be no
feed me there's a whole movie about this
little meeting about what all wrong well
it's actually like projecting her voice
to penis size
like itself pretty hunky Pony single
read or not um no I was like oh god how
I caught myself in the Battle of ribbon
on the but no jerk that's a me wanting
to do one that was good
which issue it okay so now we have a
corpse so we should check out I want to
look for symbols on it yeah I definitely
immediately as soon as I see that are we
able to get around some are safe of this
creeping Meza thorns within the room and
the building it lives here okay so we
should act to move this is it's this
Atlas your now there's no rooms clear of
it well this I mean this this way is
just a new venue for it can we try that
anyway
it's having it having a great time
bathroom video so as so if it as how did
you have firm as you have pulled it in
as the as the bolt strike your charge
here but as soon as they go limp you see
the dagger in the hand start to swing
sort of like a windsock I point to it
and I go ah this is about a good thing
it's not really I told you to trust me
look look like a hook oh yeah hold up
yeah it goes it goes directly in and
sort of sticks in and shivers and shakes
and then goes in and then the symbol of
male earth gets even stronger on the
surface and then I look at that and I go
curious why not I can't explain it
but I don't like anymore now that I've
seen it this this gross thing is
encroaching on my God's territory
oh my focus is it taking over your focus
is that where you're afraid I thought
they were just going to hang out
together I thought that the other ones
would just would get absorbed by the
strength of who I've chosen as my patron
really is not what's happening I see
that happen and I'm like and I take the
dead bodies hands and make it go don't
what
so it was great I go to our new met
party member gross really that's rad
yeah
I want to see if there's anything all
right search the body and I clues
actually there is a light silver chain
okay um they were great
yeah right uh never break it inside the
raiment like hood this is a different
this is a different configuration you
see this is not the same since a cast or
a roll this is this Ram it is not like
what you saw in the alley okay okay
different does it look like
as or nior looks like a totally separate
thing look like like are they up the
same group and this is maybe less than
perfect I'd be your guest they
definitely bore the black bag okay okay
yeah I true but but the the other way is
leather armor place definitely that's
not really what's going on here okay
this is more of a ceremonial ooh
category okay clergy coal type Raymond
okay um so now you guys are locked up in
a house that's completely surrounded by
assailants I mean to my mind and full of
Daddy is only I would say that that is
almost the optimal time for a commercial
break slash
restroom enthusiasts breath room
enthusiast group let's try to form that
online let's create a hashtag that's
about potty something like that yeah
take advantage shadow council of the
shadow council facilities make you know
make yourself make yourself at home
we'll be back shortly hello I'm Jennifer
cave our camps and these are other
people to your ear before thank you for
enduring the commercial break lets us do
more of this stuff that you like if you
subscribe of course you see awesome
animations by Z bash you inset something
to consider
alright now the great animation they're
the [ __ ] best
now when last we saw her here
they were they had hold themselves up
inside the manners humble man's and were
absolutely 100% surrounded by assassins
the daughters of maelys surrounding the
hovel what do you do in the face of this
terror so we are trapped between a thorn
and a gang of mail services that yeah I
think it was gonna say this is a classic
euphemism right that's one of Rosie's
tried-and-true use mrs. um so veg there
is there there's a spell that I have
called path without trace now this won't
obscure us completely which is I believe
how I know exactly using it all
knowledge I feel like the description
the description sort of implies that you
can just do whatever the [ __ ] you want
but it's not true I was radius from you
masking you and your companions from
detection and if that ball you read
you're like ah we're invisible yeah it's
exactly but the best spell ever yeah but
actually everyone within 30 feet of
creature I choose has a plus 10 months
to Dec 30 subject and can be tracked
except by magical means so if we want to
try sneaking out
I can buff all of our self checks okay
look it's me go so it should be like
passed with some trace just with minors
popular pass without trace unless you
fail spell check but that doesn't fit on
the card yeah yeah we kind of go around
the edge and maybe like on the
background oh yeah exactly
do that if that's not good you guys so
that's that's that's one possibility and
um here's another one they pretty spooky
yeah if we get I assume that we're in
this house out of line of sight of
Vienna there I mean there are there are
windows but you know this is a like I
say it's not a it's a pretty humble
abode because I could attempt to speak
with any visible mind to mind you have
this problem at least yeah I could see I
don't want to talk to all of them I just
want side yeah you could we try and
parlay real quick all right
it's an odd odd stance for walnut to
what a parlay with the sisters maybe I
want to know where to find ya
I have a reason okay it's all agree
consistent Billy let me give them find
out where they're gonna look for an
illicit alcohol
yeah what are they what are they what
are they what are they doing here what
do they want
Wow like a hain't briefing I put my
fingers to my temple and then I take the
dead bodies fingers and put it through
your hair so she can check that yeah
yeah and we're both like should shop I
just I say no we have you surrounded
what do you want it both immediately
start flying through the windows they
don't talk guys in it like what I say
it's good in a few seconds there's no
more glass anywhere on this house fires
next gave their answer
can I ask neatly like uh with like an
elbow just like nudge a part of the
bramble out the window don't think
without anybody noticing yeah part of
the branch go out oh sweet branch was
like good look like a yeah sure sure
sure yeah I take a hot fine yeah so
you're basically just like trying to
reach farther back on it you know away
from the way from the seeking you sucker
yeah tip I mean you know how kind of
lure morning-glories to like really kind
of get a while you know it garden you
got to give them a place to go just
giving this little guy somewhere to go
right exactly yeah yeah so you can you
can tuck you can absolutely grab him
adjust him as a as a sure plant expert
oh that one I would allow expert yeah
exactly go that way does anyone have any
better ideas no okay hello agent IO is
our back door yeah I think it's like
surrounded by thorns at this point or
till we get to rest well you have to get
over this plant okay but there's
definitely a back door okay
from the kitchen yeah all right dan are
you lay down we'll walk over you this
sounds tough but fair
oh yes sir
yeah point to the body and I'm gonna
know how and draper over the brain I
don't know because wow this seems like
real I don't everyone in favor raise
your hand
we're friends Janet like what do you
Oh YUM oh you goddamn egg up stop you
don't want this present and the more and
bolder coming in the head she is done
sweetheart you okay you got a foothold
in her and she goes crazy
no let's step over the body that was a
very good joke it's late it's just drop
off yeah I don't know how quick this
thing's gonna envelop it so it's like
yeah I am the least dexterous so I maybe
should go first
check it out in like in event you gotta
jump over this is probably the best
weekend substantially but this this
infusion of oh no a fresh food well I'm
going to do this quick no definitely
right no no right down onto the right
under the central throbbing core of this
mess
even the FEMEN the the friend that you
tucked out the window sort of whips back
in so all that torpor that had sort of
gripped it temporarily is completely
gone it looks like a chainsaw the the
different arms I think it's like I look
at a sea star like it's like one of
those really deep it just kind of closes
in around the top and anemone know it's
our birthday I'm Emma here an enemy
anemone from no moszer wow that's a
Blanc Blanc type ELC exactly hello we're
myself an inspiration exactly
okay so he said it is basically closed
itself over and has just begun to sort
of tighten and then shift itself around
this man how they're trying to go but
yet stood around it yeah absolutely I
think it does all along up now it's busy
oh yeah went to passing out trays - yeah
yeah oh here - the door going to be
upset or and then yeah covers Brisby
sitting on my back yeah go let's go
let's go let's go all right well while
we've got a moment to breathe until I
only have nine health I will use a cure
wounds - how do you feel like not now
now's not the time to what not
getting quick what x+ yes I know I
wasted it all the great bush you're
gonna lay some onion yeah give yourself
some here's one ga+ spell-casting
billion modifier hmm
three rule nine great thanks good
everything yep okay just in case mm-hmm
that's good for probably two hits yeah
yeah can we do some perception is to see
if there's any indication that crossbows
have been fired outside the back door
make sure that no beans there's no glass
anywhere on this we're surrounded on
this house
okay sorry I need to pop down we could
live it right yeah like a bed okay I'm
sorry
please letting that so leave late apply
live yeah die leave like a straight a
little fire here anybody a lot of people
could be that I would do uh use a
prestidigitation to just make a little
Kindle little Kindle yeah
right now it's wet wood I mean it yeah
it takes him good know Patrick Rothfuss
wants us to check for a basement or
cellar or secret passages or something I
was actually really good I was thinking
cellar but I also like huh that's like
last time we went in a basement I don't
want to we're surrounded I don't want to
entrench morale I'm gonna tell you guys
this because if I do it then Jerry will
punish me yeah somebody else good I did
think of attic what well you don't wanna
go any attic there's nowhere to go but
it's spooky hey [ __ ] it it is yeah but
it might be sort of Austin here well
well if there's testing as I mean what's
your problem yeah can I people it up
yeah kind of see like a cursory kind of
like look and see if there's like a
business I'm like I see if this is going
to have any kind of like 18 but there's
there's definitely foes the difference
between the front and the back is that
in the back he has cut his garden into
tall hedges oh okay
male 8 okay okay cool why don't we sneak
out that way so just to be clear if I
you pass that trace on us and we are
behind cover we would get +10 dexterity
bonus and advantage on I'm being sneaky
covers exact for anyone come
it would be difficult for them to track
straight also I have masks of the wild
so all we find no matter what yeah I'm
doing great I will not difficult a wild
is I can attempt to hide even when I am
only lightly obscured by foliage heavy
rainfall ice no mr. other natural
phenomena so like you know we need to
like an anime character I put one leaf
on their head yeah whoa
gone hey Vienna ball like this it's like
some stick falls on you like where'd she
go Bonnie subs thank you sorry sorry
turned a log
alright pass about trades y'all yeah so
where are you trying to get to oh wait
okay well first around it I think we
should try and let's try to get in you
know how there's that big tunnel that's
cutting to you this much giant line yeah
how far can we see you like and it's not
hashed that's not at all tunnel is it it
was covered it's actually just opinion
no but no no stubbornness have a cup
yeah yeah it's like a train tunnel
I see getting therefore with stores and
things carved into the side what do we
see like so if we're looking at and we
can see that this tunneling since
consumers at the end of it that way it
goes all the way through it's a slight
turn in the middle yeah just in case
here to go to a larger instruments we
don't have a male engineer shop maila
sorry bailiffs maelys it's not the
hammock district we're not no not sure I
need a rest anywhere okay we do work we
all done rest would you go to the head
we would take the long run quick it's a
quick detour to the hanok district Yeah
right all right everybody
I'm a casting pass without trace on
myself but all right so stay within 30
feet of me if you want text bonuses yes
okay let's go let's do this not first
you're on me oh yeah go to what yeah oh
yeah they're on me now you can carry
really no I know bad yeah yeah okay okay
are you just guide me everybody climb on
roses all will be safe Yoda typing I
guys a 21 plus is what it's 26 for me
okay plus I've already so you're
sneaking yeah go ahead and give me some
Oh give me some of that stuff I'm a role
in anger you get +10 to these checks so
that is a oh an advantage
oh no one no one has ever seen
yes what you got a 435 Jesus
I don't every day I could get here and
there is my goods yeah it's a fifteen
okay we're looking for first lady my
flowers five or three I don't know
we go to dinner in 1513 38:15 and we are
not very large yeah that makes sense
I'm just excited you're wearing one I'll
go off my bonus I get minus one stealth
yeah even with a posting time I tell ya
good well stir everyone's ultra-quiet
except for you yes
you're like rustle in the hedge okay
it's like I'm fine but my tail keeps
hitting them it's like why are you more
time I wouldn't have to decide without
hair it to you you you sort of sneak out
and then walnuts it doesn't have art and
then Chris Chris takes out and the narc
comes out and says quiet quiet quiet
quiet [ __ ] back in the corner yes if
you think you stink typically like the
common goal like this is it but where we
trying to get to the tunnel yeah they're
away is there a route to the main road
we want to blend we want to get out go
into the crowd it's near I mean this is
the mayor's house is actually near that
right that route and that's that's
specifically where it's placed so you
have so you have gone out into the maze
like garden that he has manufactured for
himself in the back um he won't be able
to see it in the spring
anything strainer
um and immediately as soon as you leave
the back door uh first three of you
looking pretty good and then it's just
poor porcupine DiNardo and RQ kind
yeah next can so but honestly here
that's a 2 and a 4 hmm nice it could be
way way WAY worse glad I up so these so
it's so both strike around the frame of
the
of the house as the door opens and you
emerge I'm an affordable hit no no no no
no I something I hear good damage I took
no no no these are the D 20s ah these
means that you do know get hit hmm
sorry so you hear you're trying to sidle
around the back and then sort of lose
yourself in the moment you can't let it
go don't ever
there's plenty one time you can play
forever dad's linguini we just want to
get out of the perimeter of this of this
uh right it's circle mentoring so we can
get up concrete abstractions
you can definitely attempt to create a
distraction I want you for a friend say
yes or yes yes what kind of forest
friends I would like to summon a small
woodland Bert no actually earth here's
an interesting thing right now it's
actually a crow nesting season if you
get close to their nest they physically
dive by me this happened me I felt its
claws on my skin for real quite a grip
region yes they yes there's a one it has
a hard one where's my cat surely it
isn't interesting so how about some
crows and I want them to do or you know
what William birds on one was at
territorial like try and get them to
dive on the people that are trying to
take aim at us like even if they just
come in our full songbirds we're their
babies or nice you know full Hitchcock
on it oh yeah yeah I want them to just
even if they're just bouncing their
little bodies off of really nice get out
yeah well I think it's pretty cool so so
I do like a whistle or something sure
wait how do you how do you want it just
that you use your pro whistle um so I
can't do it but a cool person that can
do the bird yeah yeah air horn of
whistles no that was and then Fox is a
lot of air one face the face of the of
the hill that sort of Bluff looks smooth
but as you call you can you can detect
that it's basically popped
Oh much like much like the the deep crow
nest it's popped with tiny tiny nests
and immediately just these sheets of
black bullets leap out and start to
swoop over the roofs oh can I ask my
flavor yeah absolutely and I say as I
what about that you've made an enemy of
the birds yeah a real pro deploys my
friends my friends all right no very
nice so this is this is going to buy you
a chance to get into that mess to get
mixed up in that that social group in
there so your boys whether your
destination is there's this it's this
crowd here where we ultimately trying to
get to we're getting out of town yeah
when we go this we're not going to get
paid we don't need to be in NZ or any
longer than go to making you upset let's
look at it we got to get out we got a
regroup yeah don't read anything run
your head renown yeah okay okay so so
basically trying to try to get back to
the cart trying to get exactly try to
head back to the carts you see how you
can navigate that gate they have up
front if they can intercept our you know
messages they definitely don't know
where we're saying we'll figure it out
later today tomorrow anything no no it's
true there's various day it's bizarre
but there's actually more see team
tomorrow trio tomorrow let's talk about
later yeah yeah yeah well hit on the
young game wait wait hit on the thing
get so you so you try to mill yourself
you dinar gifts tells me as you can try
to become something like the travel-size
dinar yeah you know what I mean get
boxed up a little bit I do it yeah just
combat roles yeah yeah keep tumbling
they just never but never stop it's a
sonic thing also serpentine yeah
serpentine tumblers indeed you got a kid
okay up that I've ever liked to Melanie
Galaxy Quest yes was like dad rolling
from everything yeah
different - no no Wilson it's about so
god what's it Alysa
the clock is counting up down that was
engraver me we do see teens for exactly
like this is operation ultimate
permanent game you got 40 minutes left a
seems like a good value okay so the
services this is this is the scenario
you get back to I accept go away alright
um you get this sometimes this device
wants to tell me important things about
Windows but I don't gotta want to know
so you're able to meld yourself in an
assassin's creed Ian scenario all the
way back to the inn where you had left
the cart and as you approach the cart
from behind coriander excuse me
you see you you see a daughter of maelys
now the horse emerge carry another horse
emerge and draw the knife not stop it
right across coriander well my best
friend in the world
time out Jerry you're sick holy [ __ ]
no he's infuriated the anti-shah
barbarian rage that's messed that one no
I'm out of himself I would go over there
and heal it but I'm literally out of
healing so I've been keeping myself
fairly a lot even a top even a top the
cart yeah
there are assassins mmm not behind the
cart more assassins emerged now I want
to play this anymore
no you [ __ ] out of my game up all right
no no it is it alright it is it is at
that point that you see Dawid but the
beans motions are not as you recall them
uh there doesn't appear to be what you
would describe as a spine you slicker
here I guess just good winners from
Silent Hill you guys shuttering out from
the crowd that you extricated yourself
from you can see people just by virtue
of her emotions separating and spreading
away they is intensely unnatural mode of
locomotion and you can see directly from
the middle of her forehead her eyes are
closed but you can see directly from the
middle of her forehead a lashing whip
reaches out and grabs a daughter of
maelys and then flings it behind her
whoa
thank god you're here to help okay I
knew she was part of our party more of
these whips emerge from the center of
the forehead from the eyes palms strange
blue whips emerge and start to seize I
elbow you I'm like you doing this yes
yes I'm lucky yeah just talk to her just
like grab smashing them together fling
them into arcs and then up from the
Great's of the city slow what must be at
least a hundred rats I love this these
are not the rats that you managed so
these are rats this is myself insert
camera the cranium rs.10 the Jerry
Hawkins rat self-insert oh no trademark
the Trin no not your lemon Dorinda no no
no no no but for me it's just like I
want to make sure that you guys get the
full I want to make sure that you see
all the great old creatures Yeah right
you have that you have to go to an inn
you have to fight goblins right also
have to manage swarms of cranium rats
and as the a disease rats they just
sweep through almost like a flocking
behavior like a single creature and as
they sweep through a round devine up on
davines shoulder it is like a single
organism that's moving through and
wiping out these daughters okay and in
your mind you hear the word follow
follow just reminds in all of your mouth
okay worry we radio follow that was
going on I want this power that's nice
I'm gonna get my I'm gonna get my
bracelets just a little time yeah okay
you don't we don't have to they don't
have to go anywhere the voice tells us
and could leave we had a cart without a
horse can we do a perception check on
this voice okay I do I can't do insight
on the voice sure if it Davina like I
want to well I just want to know like
sound like Jerry is this like a rattler
know what I now 17 it doesn't sound what
I always it doesn't sound like one voice
okay so this is a HEIs mine situatio to
my work resistance is futile in this why
are we leaving tonight no we shouldn't
um no I think we should I think we
should follow her he tried to kill him
but I don't think it sounds alright it's
coming from the rat oh yeah I give away
I can I can I reach out again with
awakened mind towards I'm just sort of
going to cast around
yeah can I reach the beam or what seems
to be to be shy reach the rat am I able
to share your yeah yeah this is under
the Dragons here this is exactly the
sort of thing you can do
yeah I want to I want to tell me tell me
what you say I those English deserve
common they're speaking I'm trying to
figure out how to say it in English in
the word that I know yeah I want to ask
like what like what what
pseudopods like what sent you out you
know what central organism do belong to
you and a big question mark and their
money what's your huh yeah yeah what's
this about talk tell me about the to
this thing was this what you get this
follow and no she drives a hard bargain
following yes yeah as we as we're
witnessing them lay waste to the
daughters yeah they are they approaching
us oh yes so they're creating a
perimeter around the party okay but not
crossing it I mean they're not going to
like Barris oh well you know they're
giving dear
they're giving you a agency they're not
seeing you right surely die I know many
of that throat life ask you stem the
bleeding maybe yeah you're look at the
Devine resin I go from one second
I'm on your batteries and we're
definitely we're running over the horse
can't buy a horse
this is coriander why have a banks and
yeah I'll fill your belly looks good the
typical thing you do is you dump a jar
of eyeballs oh you do the it cauterized
that's another that's I do have a
healing potion I'm actually the girl why
don't you get a better one
I don't know Marilyn throat I don't have
anything I think we actually have to
kill the horse Pinot Menendez horse yeah
and it how much blood the dude I didn't
let me do medicine I'll do a message
check yes I've got my hands over corn
because craters is the only creature
that would stands me my my conversation
is going 909 all right I'll last like
that the card is sort of tipped forward
with the wait okay
I'm telling coriander a story about
stars to try to take her mind off this I
tried amend I won't assume that I can at
least physically close it if not restore
that blood but would you like to believe
oh okay he wants to first deny yes
good it's fine we can't we can
collaborate if this game it depends on
how much extra blood but absolutely I'm
yeah that's it that's yeah if it if it's
enough if it's an artery absolutely
there's a lot going on yeah you're like
a really worried about exactly so baking
is all right she's actually not she's
our drivers are negative no I am beat is
it just the one like through the SSI
last yeah all right no I Ament it
percent now where is where does that
leave us a lot of blood on this ground
person you are you into it the word
follow comes with even greater intensity
we gotta go you did what you could
people are starting to shrink and yell
in the streets
I bet nature take its course at this
point wait we have to go very well
that's a good nice you old you feel
anything
shake the Devine puppet how could you
betray it's quite understood wised dad
look sorry coriander is is in pretty bad
shape
we got nothing we did what we could I
have to go we gotta go really want to
save it dump out the healing potion down
his throat
it worked on dude we got his head
crushed by the skull special don't you I
don't have any more healing questions
only one that have I had nothing my my
one that he said this would be great if
you through it add someone huh hello
it's the same one we use before returned
its healed and now turned of metal and
minute healed him but I do think turning
the metal would be different River
coriander what's worse than death that
it's a cold metal hook statue patient
hot process of metal horse a circle okay
the damage I'm so so so the the the
perimeter that these rats are making is
sort of like a little wave it's
constantly rolling and crowding on
itself alright so I just on court that
healing potion and I go my host power
out of her misery yeah and then I just
dump it down our throat and give you a
rub yes
that neck holder yeah hold on belches
growing our nose yes it's just that the
girls okay and then I go we got it we
gotta go okay
she becomes encased tips a tail
so did too yeah in a super metal horse
yeah in bronze I'm going to kiss my
pants and put it on coriander's and I
should say I'm going to come back for
you
we're taking that statute of bass while
you guys are doing it I've already begun
to that's all I knew I'm going so that
it doesn't get angered yeah exactly
I'm sick okay so this thing basically
like a single creature with with greater
intensity and enthusiasm you see Devine
sort of pushing through always sort of
in the epicenter of this wake of rodents
I'm listen I just I had this I'm just
describing with a Bini so it sort of
rises up almost like a prowl in front of
the party constantly rats are constantly
rising and spilling up over it it's
almost like a cowcatcher
right type situation in front of train
and it's just guiding you through
streets that you haven't seen yet into
new parts of this town skirting the
hammock district sorry says yeah the
rest you find a you ultimately end up in
a sort of statuary garden there's a what
should be a fountain in the center
currently dry and you can see a figure a
cloaked figure with a forced smile
reaching out toward whoever would
approach this statue and at the base of
it it says Mendez veil and they lead
they sort of boil up over the edge in
like a froth of rat and you can see that
as they approach a grate in the base of
the fountain is raised up and the party
is directed down below this statute
sewers
so I love Mendez mail never follow a
right to a second location like this is
what a1 101 because they say yeah yeah
alright it's like the most common idiom
never know you're a quick perception
check on this statue yeah sure um yes
face nothing nothing decide after you
yeah barely got there remember six carry
who's my I take my focus how is it baby
what's going on with the Mahler symbol
what's going on with my symbol yeah
I give me that perceptual that's it hey
it's going to be tasty
mmm mmm okay so what is that
yeah he is it appears to be it's not
doing anything odd or strange but you
notice that this figure is wearing
something similar can I do perception to
know if I know it's do I recognize this
at all try the name or the history I see
that's good
woo-hoo-hoo-hoo 24 paper so totally tell
me exactly what you're trying to learn a
very good want to know the guys
recognize the person that is like
personified in this statue get a 24 I
had eight share 20 I have an 18 plus 6
24 you wouldn't want you don't like what
you see ok that's it
yeah you what you see it would be easier
for someone else ok someone who didn't
have the level of investment that you
have in your own identity it would be
easier for them to see it all right but
these these features are not alien to
you ok well I want to roll the time
anyone else is rolling by check
something you suck you know
all right the statue guys
that guy I was confirming yeah guy we're
right on the nose wrap everybody else oh
did you see Emily's reps I said I grab
the clothes for wanting things have you
killed your friends like a lot of rats
we clearly haven't taken care of the rat
problem yeah exactly
if you hear the wrong or greater our job
like guys all right I want to go in the
sewer I get aa plan to study exactly so
that so they've continued to make this
place for you it just like a circle that
sort of exists around you wherever you
go as you find yourself as you find your
way down this is definitely the sewers
yeah this is this is definitely in a
sewer Ian context but so they are clear
basically running through this with you
know absolute you know cartographical
knowledge of this area obviously for you
it's brand-new but they're leading you
very quickly through a chamber after
chamber and on at least two occasions
you they walk through walls
I don't like anything about it we're
very trusting disease right so so
basically there are two places in this
in this traversal that you go through
illusory log walls yeah okay I'm making
a map of this as we go at least mentally
yeah yeah okay can i because when we've
been using history's history for your
June 16 yep that's great that's great if
you had to okay I got a back out you can
get us back out of here I leave bread
crumbs but then the rats keep eating so
it's really notice it you never know
really well I know like like they get it
in their mouth before it hits the ground
that's why you bought the sack of grain
that was that like nice and really smart
that's so clever you guys
oh wow you guys you're like I see you
doing it like I really use even
breadcrumbs it's smart and you're like
eating a bread well what oh yeah I guess
yeah exactly
um so but behind you is this is this you
know again like
invigorated corpse mm-hmm just sort of
shuttering and the head doesn't appear
to really know what it should be doing
it's like not it's like the not it's
like it's like um playing it like like a
play school of my first body right
thanks anyway shad with it buy something
yes and have that is a co-op since yes
yes exactly it's wonderful scent co-op
its clock worthy so you after you've
passed through the second of these two
illusory walls in addition to all the
twists and turns that got you down into
this zone you enter a chamber that has a
glow much like the glow from the rats
except on a massive scale you can see
you know this instinctively it's risk
the architecture that's here is not
surface architecture are these places
that I would these are deep either leave
places and it's in fact it's a low sim
place even to him even I would say I
would say that let me describe the image
and then I will go into why it's
important yeah even beyond the revulsion
that you would have it's even worse for
koutris there is something like a
wishing pool or a scrying pool cracked
in places in the central chamber you can
see it's sort of in a the entire room is
sort of in a triangular shape and this
is set in a circle that's shattered it
could no longer hold what it should
whatever was designed to hold and then
you can see shot through by three long
spars of root or what passes for a Rudy
you recognize it in the sink it leaves a
root but it appears to be made out of a
kind of stone right it's shot through
what appears to be a massive
okay that is giving off the same light
that the cranium rats give off but you
you think that this can't possibly be
the optimal scenario for this so this is
this is stone roots reaching down from
the city and then it looks like a like a
skin on a drying rack like it's held up
in it's sort of held up on this vertical
shape splayed out across the roots this
is an elder brain like this this is the
hated foe like the end point in a
lifecycle of the elephant race the mind
flayer I see just like be the enemy the
enemy Oh killer no filler yeah and a
body yeah yeah it did it yeah no and
this brain is how big massive okay
massive but like I say like a like a
giant look at like a buffalo skin or
something on a drying rack like its
massive and strained and splayed out and
edema glow it is it is identical
identical to the rest I bet he's really
smart good
is there like a tiny little rat under
there no no you know the other types
there's a tiny little curtain you open
up that need to love no there's no
there's message there's nothing like
that
and in the press in the presence of this
in the presence of this light Devine
just falls forward in classes sure she's
just meat puppet yeah okay
here's just a slam jam the question is a
wine you or me or both of us I don't I
look at you and I go do you know this
place I know that I wouldn't have come
if I knew this was where we were headed
if he was if I knew he was going to be
here
yeah why didn't anybody tell me that I
go I too think that this is sleeping
under this places I had no idea you know
what it is sleeping I know I don't know
what it is or I know what it is
no this is this is not this this it
would be very strange yeah this is deep
stuff I'll share it with you I explained
yes okay yeah what with what I know of
it you have these types of things does
it
oh I mean how hostile is it yeah what
does it get inquired Otis sees these are
not I mean I know being suspended and
pierced like this is not the it's not
that this isn't like a trend with elder
brains or something like this isn't like
yung elder brains are getting into
dating oh yeah maybe somebody using him
for a dark purpose dolphins but talk I
thought porpoise doesn't take words and
I agree could there's scheme you yeah I
suspected I won't have to reach far to
get to it you want to talk to it I do
absolutely I did I say I asked it um how
did you come to be here
when the city was born it turned up
great heaps of the Underdark
and my pool was seized
those are the pools I got cool they're
like cool guy just yeah cool that's why
they do it yeah no no I'll be there
I understand that asking you of all
people for help
presents certain complexities but I know
without asking that both of us despise
this city the Spy's is a strong word but
if I had to choose how long have you
been here oh not as long as you I
imagine
give it time I'm you guys are in on this
call it's that safe to do yeah you can
see my mind turns inside out yes exactly
I need no no no sniffing oh it's like
that it's like when I live in a balloon
is flying around the room she's thinking
first you think it really hard for
second did you just I mean you take your
place up on the safe up on the top what
what do you what are you looking for us
to do the roots of this town are grown
through me and they have made it
impossible for me to return why would I
help you because I can give one of your
number something they did not know still
existed again sweat sweat very stoic but
sweaty what is required of us the roots
that bind me here must be destroyed
closer to their source the source with
visible from the surface no they must be
destroyed from below the buildings
themselves here have roots to the street
yeah you get your spicy meat-a-ball
should we decide to do that what becomes
of you I leave and I grant you my boom
does the city benefit from you being
trapped here does someone benefit from
you being trapped
I think the birth of this city had many
unintended consequences I'm trying not
to take it personally then I often yeah
yeah I'm like real boy 749 they bring no
for real though yeah it's a fine real
quick hey you circling I got Louie oh
you don't know you're not that man
what's 60% of 200 gold why I'm just I
just want to see if you're for real
I really want to happen something that's
how we maybe a commitment maybe just
pops in there you know I'm just thinking
it like wow I was just thinking it I
wonder if he knows what that is you
would like to I can have a deep deep
knowledge deep thoughts by who we reach
it further back hmm
it says one moment when you think a
thing is that different from saying yes
yes fortunately yes I apologize do you
know anything about a thing called a
wandering crypt Oh Oh tell me more the
Crypt and it kind of wanders it's a
living dungeon yes
it moves any moving so the enemy of 1
ohm and ran
I've never heard the name I'm innocent
have you ever heard have you ever heard
of a phenomenon like that moving
wandering done we do not call them that
well you call something else what's it
called was that this is a beast that
burrows like a mole but is a domicile a
construction this is a question oh yes
yeah seems like they're not unheard of
all right so this isn't just one because
it's either a kind of thing where you
can you say the word that you call them
that is it something that we could
absolutely we should even understand or
parse or is it an elephant thing you
hear a sound that is like a mixture of
like breaking mason jars and uh parcel
mouths okay hold on just a second oh
yeah that makes sense cool we were gonna
try and remember that
hi got it don't in the bulk her the
night on my back today was that date I
said why would why would that thing
leave behind the symbol of the one who
controls pounds I know realism it's a
good call random I think I was here from
the birth of this town and whoever
planted its seed did not truly
understand what they were doing okay you
have a name friend
do you meet many elder brains well no
but it seems so impersonal elder brain
will suffice we have a habit of being
betrayed by people we we help so I just
want to know who to curse after you
inevitably betray the elder burn yeah I
wanna assign a name to me I'll call you
elder brain one just in case we need
enough I I suspect that a mind like this
would have we have already been betrayed
if that's what's going on here so other
than that possibility I don't think that
we have a quarrel we will perform this
task for you
next one we should write up a contract
can you sign paper I have I have an
agent who can sign Sunday it's a rat
this is no give a pin already colored in
this one name she's going uh-huh uh-huh
yeah what's that got it
her and then a girl leaf leaf ha ha ha
well and then she just kind of like
holds it out with like slightly down
like it's all the rats gonna sign that
would be sorry I did not a rat
scurrilous a rat scurries up onto the
document and then reads it lightly the
whole body the whole head have to move
back and forth it's a light a light of
this to let just yank that from your
mind yank writing this versus an oven
just this is it is important to you that
I sign this and I'm actually aware we
had kind of embarrassed it said I'm
sorry we're still corporeal this things
like necessary important does it surely
must have for me I apologize I'm just
like really like that here's your enemy
isn't me why don't have a call with me
he has information it seems pretty
powerful I can you not the rat reaches
up to you I'll give them give my I give
you the quo yeah okay he grabs it
or shoulders it and then rose a bunch of
ill essentials
right okay they hated symbols all right
no okay great no no no you're not you're
not getting the read in here is alien
even to the town which is itself bizarre
Francia what's like you in control
Devine pretty well and you've got a mob
of rats like look I don't like ill
acid's
but this thing has number one
transcended I don't understand its needs
all I know is that it's given us this
task in exchange for something say it
took out a group that was gonna murder
us pretty easily
yeah ass everywhere say uh just maybe
he'll answer maybe won't it will enter
um I go uh I go why why did the sisters
want us dead what would after do you
have any idea you serve their goddesses
lover okay alright we don't know what
he's talking about i whitey wait say it
again
what goddesses lover I don't know you
must have us confused
so signals pretty weak down here that
doesn't feel like me they all right no
guards no one like us uh uh how do they
how do they know how do they know I
don't know who you are how do you how do
you feel when you cast your eye upon
their sigil do you think that they allow
the symbolism aleihi candy written and
said well this just makes you think well
it's just uh I find this out on a
conference call yeah I just I had to
hear this from a brand yeah well I was
like I yeah a cat's out of the bag
who no huh nothing right okay just take
that as an answer like sorry fine sure
do you do you know if there's any there
are three routes okay this is where
we're we're how do we get them where
they at
Challenge I will spend mr. murder quest
I will send my servants to lead you to
each of them okay okay back in a jiff
any more questions you want to ask from
yeah this is big money brainer who has
all the answers I dunno where's my egg
right now is I miss my eggs don't have
eggy doing good you know anything about
stars leaving the sky there are things
that are not our purview my domain is
the deep place that is what you will be
helping me get back to I thought was
written shot do you you useless brain
man yes do you actually want to ask it
about they yeah I'm just curious like we
hung a guy oh you like it just yeah yeah
it seems to know everything and now it
knows the rules
Yeah right so yeah now it knows it's
what you want to know how's it doing how
you doing
come closer good with his mama oh all
right dddd oilmen yeah close right all
right I look been able to do it until
you're gonna really yeah no no no don't
be sorry
right but you can see good higher close
you can see the princess hmm holding a
holding a baby
hey that will not stop crying it's just
like that eggy well she's doing good
that's good
I can't help think it's like trash
mother garbage hey don't mind a judge
set by Judge mom filth mama I'll feel
better
exactly so I we've talked about I'm
were collaborated yamma but I am red no
you have no special adherence to the
symbol of malice or that oh the goddess
I attest everything about this city I
can imagine what do you know of this I
found it in a deep place show the focus
and maybe show it to myself so I can see
oh sure my eyes I found it in a deep
place perhaps not as deep as yours
it says but if its resonant like a like
a cello note it can't possibly it can't
possibly fill the room because it's
completely in your mind but you feel
your skull vibrating with it and it says
the air hasn't been worshipped for a
thousand years
do you serve it I tried my best
his power ceased when he no longer
answered prayer ah it sounds it sounds
like a joke but I first thing that I
thought was like agree to disagree
all right there are some things that we
don't even get true you may not know
it's true it's true though hey we got a
cruel jobs we got three routes to manage
yeah and we are going to manage them
next week all right feast feast up we've
got a commercial break coming up we're
going to go use the facilities and then
we'll come back for Table Talk
don't go away
you