turn it the enemy the pastor threatens
the fastest weapon you wouldn't make it
past a second land the question play a
flash and records to choose a course
solution you saw was proven in any
Sepulchre poll curtain will become a
putrid it's that well said I pursue in
no mountain too steep but don't
attendees to send expendable marks up to
the top of the peak of beneath this EUV
become like sharks to it while I swim in
that line again like Carl Barks through
it ascension national parks do it I'll
stand of home in a natural box the post
time for most of the parts included save
your breath for a cleric confessor this
is a lesson and like to cite any
professor but if you speak in my
efficient the by sign on the dotted line
and list of the twice Shadow counsel I
invoke the mayor Labor's please you
I am Tycho Brahe heya panicking pack
slam also am innocent Hereward run CEO
of acquisitions incorporated but today
I'm Jerry Hawkins and playing a game
with dungeon dragon with my friends to
my right Dragonborn arses dinar
boyfriend doesn't have a lot of energy
levels are low sick after he 3 you take
after a three you you went to sleep at
two o'clock in the morning and you did
you have a big lunch it was too big
stupid yes ok is too big is there
anything in there meaningful yes there
anything else that you would like to
complain about no I can go to pillow for
the game laughing hey guys hello big
game no cows I almost called you Amy
that's not appropriate
Oh antics in Valley Bailey who is that
she did
we're prepping the natural rope walnut
dung crap daughter of the enclave panic
anima man again my gimmick the fart
sound that's Caroline what other way for
this I don't know it's not that I we
finally go to this part of this let's
duel like was it as like a victory yeah
thank you doing that
I don't know what is the victory of not
your crab Aram dignity indeed Rosie be
singer everybody celebrate it
celebrating our way mix that with your
hand
yes Lou no Chris wrist Rob thank you so
much thank you for making the time to
come and play dungeon dragons with us
today it's just an honor and a privilege
I like to be sat next to so it's just
something I do know he's he is and you
tell me if I'm off on this an aromatic
gentleman there's that experienced never
not that if you look he left last he
emits a presence no like Christmas oh it
is cloud listen it's like this when last
we saw our heroes they had taken a task
they had agreed to be at least
temporarily the servants of an elder
Brian deep below the haunted ass city of
nemesis now the process of Nemesis
creation it churned up massive chunks of
the Underdark we're creatures like this
hold sway and it was deeply deeply
inconvenienced by a matrix of evil roots
that has actually projected and pierced
through the meat of the elder brain
making it somewhat unlike the creature
that is described on the on the
character sheet in the monster man if
you look it up these are really really
bad generally speaking you don't get to
see a creature like this when you're
fourthly I looked up elder Brian and I
didn't find any no no no initiates a
moment spotted yeah but having managed
the first of three routes managing a an
iron golem with the use of clever
prestidigitation glowing
genitals is that a variety of approaches
that were able to deliver success you
backed that up with some revelatory
meetings with a Minotaur servant of
walnut Don grasses order the enclave
panax anima or EPA do an effort deviate
bother to ask him his name
I can tell it to you later I screamed it
as it died it's a woman is dead yeah I
can hook it up but no no aspirin no I
guess I have somebody on Twitter like
does ever find out his name and of
course that person I told them but is
that is that again dig through your
montage okay yeah okay right now yeah
see in 20 Maris yeah you can feel
confident that I have named important
characters in this scenario no having
gone back down to the elder brains
chamber and then gone back up another
magical Mouse staircase into the third
of three chambers you entered what
appeared to be a my candid commune of
some kind you can see them just standing
up to their knees and raw sewage
apparently for them that's the you know
equivalent of a buffet my kanuda various
sizes indeed friendly young Mike ended
offering up gifts to dinar blitz in my
head for the people at home is a fancy
word for mushroom person right yeah yeah
I think you know there are these jelly
candies hey it's a movie food a red
green and yellow
indie truman they're the greatest I hate
the idiot Heath listen we're you know
again later we're never going to settle
this we could use the rest of the time
of the show and we would never get to
the bottom of this one there because
every an opportunity during tables back
but it is it so indeed they offer you up
a wide-brimmed mushroom friend slash hat
so imagine a imagine a abroad
round hat and the traditional you know
traditionally made of wood descendants
made out of a mushroom person and there
are in fact eyes on top of it that when
not asleep have opinions about things
that they express with the eyes
something to consider when lashes are
heroes they had entered a final chamber
composite you know I would say the good
70% of this chamber is something you
would call an eye of various kind
surrounded by them all focusing on the
party as they enter and indeed the
massive bulk of the fungus in here
constitutes a single organism that has
in fact grown up and around the entire
chamber and then around what you assume
may be root of some time historically
there have been roots in the chambers
that the elder brain has sent you to no
reason to believe this is not also a
root great um so does anyone have any
ideas I look back and I look at the
group and I noticed denars hat maybe
just like don't say anything about if I
said does anyone have any ideas about
how to get to what's probably the root
maybe without murdering the whole
mushroom family I have the question why
do we care we've been sat on this task I
mean I like them I like mushrooms as
much as the next guy but it's there our
way and we can just mold down and end
this used to say we're doing a bad thing
they don't like me a people this is
something that I think you will not
would agree risk potentially which is
that destroying the style roots
freeing this elder Brian and destroying
mensier is kind of a big deal these
mushroom people we can maybe they can
help us destroy the roots from how if
they're who knows if any of us can
figure out a way to communicate with
them maybe there's a way that they can
help us but I think that destroying the
root is
more important than saving their life I
agree and maybe they want that juice
inside maybe they can't get in there
because there it's just those soft you
know little Muslim slippers these
people's fault that the Underdark got
you know that the underdog was brought
to this town
yeah is that what our job is that what
we signed up for did you sign up for
let's just kill the mushroom families
password by Melissa yeah we should kill
a mushroom family Zidan with a brain
it's like coke siding with Pepsi that
makes sense why are those sounds
delicious
why don't ya yeah yeah yeah
it takes it well I mean the way I that
wrist looks at it is that we would have
to we would have to do this anyway to
get rid of them as you're right I'm
assuming you don't like never zero
walnut and AD we not had we discovered
these roots on our own and sussed out
that they are what's holding the city up
then we would have cut up whether or not
we knew it was a brain it's true uh I am
slightly haunted by what the minotaur
have any vaunted um that my people's
ancestral task was to fight elicits the
hiset yeah yes and now we are about to
let I'm not mistaken over a big one
right at loose well place the final
stage of one he does seem cool
you're there cuz I'm something right I
remember out are we jumping to the glue
we don't know we're going to murder a
bunch of measures yes talk to anyone or
walk around we're like like if we're
gonna kill everyone sorry are you sin
are to communicate with the mushroom I'm
liking it the good hat it's a nice hat
and yeah they're all complimenting me
and you stink something at them and sir
I try
think think think so what Denard is cute
honestly is what I was going to be mad
like as their friendly neighborhood
Dungeon Master
like you need to [ __ ] commit you know
what that's what dinars do I am playing
right so you you you hold the brim and
really focus your intellect through this
you know fungal dish you can you can
feel the Hat trying to adjust itself and
get a little more comfortable on your
head nubbins but you're not receiving
any particular signal something novel
for your purpose mmm
Chris wrist wrap is that this room and
this is very convenient obviously this
room appears to be there's the the
ceiling of it is the sky I can see some
of these these constellations yeah it is
quite all but by any sense that you can
leverage you are in a place a round
place surrounded by these new friends
well you've come to well you've come to
believe our friends and right from the
top of that root structure that central
column just a dome of the sky and it's
an incredible comfort to you also to be
so close to the forest even in this
haunted subterranean place the canopy
the inviting safety of the tree canopy
over the top of this room is definitely
putting you at ease and likewise okay
you can see the stone towers of the
monastery reaching off in the distance
you can see them rising up and you know
that with only 10 minutes walk you would
be back in a place of safety where you
knew
every person by name she times you want
to go hmm [ __ ] what is this I see you
see a gigantic dinar Blitzen ah looking
down the way that the way that a person
might look at a box of chocolates just
like reaching out toward distress and
then nonono reaching out toward this
fantasies of eating yeah yeah yeah
beautiful work mrs. Hyman listen I know
what you want at a document you want to
tot access the insects there's one
aboard I'm delivering on a race don't
ever usually exclusive oh okay you can
put it all into one adventure how much
to ask that's not the end consent you
continue this I'm listening because um
it's a comfort to you even now if
initially you think that you might be
rising because there's ever an
ever-greater dome with more richness
than you can imagine just a boy a velvet
sheet strewn with diamonds expanding
around the top and I say you think that
you're rising because it's taking up
more of your field of vision the fact of
the matter is is that there was never a
room could the best of your ability to
assess it there was no room of any kind
and what's more is that all of that all
of the the terror and anxiety and fear
of your isolation and it is isolating to
be a single creature always at some
level divided from other creatures you
realize now that that was a nightmare
that that was a kind of Perpetual
nightmare a falsehood and and it just
falls away all of these things all of
this all of this tension and anger is
just melting away and in fact and you
are hurdle
now Oh through uncool space a little
little bass oblivion exactly your your
body is a friendship to the creatures
that live within and on the surface of
your body oh yeah
and behind you you have an awareness
that a bright trail a Rainbow Road of
spores is just bursting out across space
and because it's bursting out across
space its bursting out across time I
want your body for lack of a better term
is a wonderland
it sounds spectacular it sounds
psychedelic I shout out the name of one
of my teachers nyan cat young Cod God my
Potteries but even the name even the
name is is useful as a piece of trivia
but the thing that separates you from me
on cause is alive
oh no that's a fiction it's a fiction
role and it's a it's a fiction and there
and you into you always there's always a
sympathy there's always a sympathy for
those who just from an accident just
from a tragedy of death by deeply into
their origin that they are separate and
that they aren't unified they are enjoy
for lack of a better turn on I found my
way back exactly and it's and it's it's
precious it's precious now in this place
you are always delighted to see others
who swim in this dark ocean oh as well
and it could be left
it could be right your orientation is
cylindrical it's irrelevant
it brings you a little joy just to know
that this is another thing you don't
have to worry about but near you near
your shape in space you can see one of
the tiny vessels that much similar
individuals use to navigate and swim in
the way that they can Oh through the
black ocean that is so tremendously full
of stars these are some good [ __ ]
mushrooms you can say well technically
these are lawful neutral mushrooms
you're like poetically describing this
like so can't wait some fanart
no hating it but you're you're aware of
it as you're aware of anything that
comes near you in absolute terms right
you can see it's like a imagine imagine
of a cap
imagine a my candid cap but turned
upside down and not full of joy right
and then imagine another smaller thin
cap attached to it in some way that
enables it to move through the ocean
there are you know if you know for a
fact it takes you a second but you know
that the creatures that are in this cap
are called halflings and you can see a
family the small family now you know
that you know that they can feel a
section there's always going to be some
division between them but you know that
you know that they have a family like
the family that you have - not eternal
right it's not perfect it is enjoy but
it's something close it's good enough
for that we do you have to respect it
right man you can see a a mother and a
father these are their terms not
relevant to my candid I respect them
right
you can see them in there and you can
see a small one what is called a girl
just full of wonder something
approximating Mike and enjoy her tiny
hands at the edge of the boat just
absorbing it's you it has to be you it
has to be the sight of youth that is
creating this pleasure
yes it's me I'm the condom how we can't
know she can't know there must be a way
that she's perceiving me even through
this that I don't understand that's
right I'm not behind I meant understand
that's right now she can't it would take
time for her to melt and they seem to be
going somewhere else but you'd like to
think that you might be able to
understand that joy at some point if
there were another opportunity it may be
a thousand years hence
but this consciousness will endure right
as they do yeah
now it could be an hour it could be a
week it's not relevant it could be a
year
before this joy fades and you are forced
to contend with this endless nature of
this ocean and you receive comfort from
the other creatures within and without
your body and they give you the energy
that you need to progress and to
continue for example your eyes here
your eyes are aware and they show you
the mad dishes and majestic wonders out
in this place and they say here are you
here are we happy here are we happy but
maybe there is someone like us there
maybe maybe they are worried right now
we could comfort them right there there
are there are creatures inside the eye
and their domain is that of sadness but
they have taken this on voluntarily they
are the weepers
they are over here and if they may be
you don't have to wake them up and you
hope that you won't have to know but you
are afraid that you might and then that
pang of fear is again blanketed by love
and joy from all the way out into your
extremities added to your massive form
that is the home of all these creatures
right I'm the best no it's true it is
absolutely true indeed it's always been
true you can remember the small creature
that you were but it's Justin now and
irrelevant and potentially untrue
something to consider
okay there are entities you need to get
ready because I'm not even done there
are entities in this place then you can
you can conceptualize it you can
conceptualize the arcs of their movement
there interdictor II like they it is
their intention to become close to you
and you are not a hundred percent
familiar with this shape this is a shape
you are not aware of you've seen
something like it a spider but spiders
don't swim the black ocean and they're
not massive they're not gigantic and
they're not made of metal and so this
distinguishes these spiders from another
type of spider is there any awareness or
any joy that you would like to
contribute
oh my god what a loaded question have
[ __ ] any sorry any awareness or any joy
that we would later interview okay so
all in the mushroom board right now we
are seeing different very very different
things from what he is seeing yeah are
we all seeing everything or is this
through Catherine you are the highest
okay we are all the eyes absolutely only
you
right eyes right yeah this is the body
oh I am the eyes you are the eyes I see
you literally see I see
okay so I see these black spiders you do
and what what purpose or function do I
sense that there are other parts of my
body The Weavers the weepers yes both of
them Reapers their very existence is
such that much of the suffering that
would be sustained by the rest of you
it's concentrated in the weepers they
take it on I see okay so I am joy you
are Joey okay we are joining typecasting
over here and I see the black spiders
and I I take joy in their in their giant
nature in the bath their the
technological advancement of them their
their pure black blackness and black
ocean I find them
terrifying but beautiful and that that
brings me joy I find joy and not
understanding them and knowing that
there is there is something there's
something that I had I get to strive for
there's more to know correct yeah in
this in this being of knowing and
feeling like we are all things and and
individualism doesn't matter to not know
something is so rare
I'll have that mystery exciting is it it
brings me joy we are joined now these
creatures and you you know that this is
true merely being isolated from one
another
creates so much pain that there are
those that act in a way that does not
create joy they can't help it there's no
reason there's no reason to dwell on it
but being separate is such a
to some creatures that they hurt each
other they hurt themselves and you think
that that might be their intention
they're getting incredibly close to your
flanks right now they're long the long
steel spindles of the four legs sort of
not not swarming there's only four of
them but you can see them approaching
with these sharp tips the sides now pain
is not a concern but there is a sadness
associated with that breakage of the
body but not pain not I never pain they
are they are getting incredibly nearest
can can any of this joy be imparted to
them
have they been separate for too long
consider it consider it how am ia bring
that joy what my vessel is all
encompassing what what case do I have
I'm not like them I am connected to
everything and yet I am not connected to
them there is a sparkling path something
to consider
they trails behind me and eight it is
something I leave it is ours something
we leave is there a way that the weepers
might there you go
be able to contain the their desire to
hurt yes and if they can consume the
desire to hurt can we impart the joy yes
it must be you may have to explain it to
them okay where they dwell inside the
eye is a dark place you may have to
confer upon them some comfort to ready
them for this task
okay can we promise them that we will
take away the suffering and replace it
take away the dark
that they've lived their lives in and as
replace it with joy and make sure that
they know that they're not going to be a
part anymore I think so I hope so okay I
don't even know that we need to promise
it to promise means that it could
possibly be in our nature not to do so
sure it is our nature it's just a
declaration to fulfill this right not
wrong where's the knowledge it's just we
know that we will yeah because it's what
we will do
there's no other way okay now how would
you like to increase Harmon we are doing
we are joy we are we are trying to Paulo
to the Ivar's Mayflower Compact
let's see
okay no doesn't work if suffering has
come from them being a part than
encouraging them to join us which seemed
and their suffering also kantha we first
take on they're sort of like suck it out
of them I would I would hope so yeah and
I don't we are the weepers willing to do
so yeah I guess you have to find out
yeah apparently I write a very dorsal
ish yeah okay yeah we we are we entreat
them yeah they could confer some of that
unity to these beings in pain yeah I
extend full of Corti ssin well the eyes
and there are many each with their own
enclave of weepers you have but to
identify and then send the weeper and
that is actually just a dice roll I
forgot we're [ __ ] sure it's not so
different after all
Oh egged two boats roll no oh yeah on
the die okay any bonus to this ice roll
uh a sheet where's your if we get worthy
a weekly knock yeah you had this
possibly anything that's Canada benign
okay so you you commend the weepers
comfort them in this moment before they
leave okay Weaver's you are you sent
forth from the I it is your purpose to
bring unity to those who do not have and
as you are launched out from the home
you can see that there are even more of
these creatures even more of these steel
spiders and not for no not for there are
more they have some way of hiding in the
Black Sea but the I it's entirely
possible that the I was overwhelmed by
the isolation
since you have you are not being sent
directly to one of the spiders you are a
little bit off you're going to need to
use your own ability to attach my bag in
this context there isn't anything all UI
um is that yeah what what would I answer
them you use your dexterity bonus if you
would I do I forgot it
no no no don't forget the shadow council
even I don't lace hold sway oh then I
definitely want to take advantage on
that also I want to say that I'm named
weepers
dan thank you so much John Palmer take
this advantage cool I'm glad that I use
it maybe I'll get a better one hey it's
a so that is a with my decks about 14 a
billy you're able to twist your body in
this seat and then swim directly toward
one of these massive spiders great
Weaver I get a negative one Dex you do
no no but Janardan are also has yeah
yeah I'm going to do oh yeah well bless
you shot okay lassie shall account what
you know that what's that my role the
same number twice that's super 20 right
know how this game works 21 first one
will have another opportunity it is with
the six actually because I get minus one
as you as you you're able to twist your
body and sail down there is an open deck
like that of a seagoing vessel on the
top that is sort of set down in the guts
of this steel arachnid and you can see
that this deck is rising risk the
torment of isolation you've never seen a
creature like this but it is easy to
sell that they are there is a sickness
there is a sick
in
there down with um well I have to know I
guess it's like I don't know yeah it's
like I want to take I want to take that
sickness and that suffering and I like I
want it right it's easy it's easy it's a
simple process is it
yeah well this process yeah yeah as long
as you know it involves that involves
that green seed there um
Rinku wonderful what do I add to it is
it decks just for everyone that's okay
yikes no we're killing it with the rolls
yeah so thank you
give me that sorry okay so you you reach
out as a as a weeper your body is
designed to bring harmony every facet of
it is designed the same spores that
exist in the trail is it in your own
body and you can convey confer harmony
on others as a direct result but as you
as you attempt to embrace one of these
creatures imagine imagine a high abdomen
the spider ship itself and the creatures
that dwell on it they have made this
ship in their own image you can see that
they themselves have four legs it's
almost like a like a hairy massive brown
spider with a head that comes up almost
like a serpent and then looked down it
has a mouth full of sharp teeth as I
said you used to endeavor to embrace
them sure and I want to and it does not
and you are not able to incorporate it
again I'm if they accept they descend on
you wonderful on the deck
this is it's horrifying sure I guess you
can hear is that they are commanding
each other they are
precisely what to do at every moment
they're telling each other they are
telling each other what to do and you
you suspect them that horror that that's
separation the need to gesticulate the
flap and to do all these things simply
to be understood right and then there
are those who are telling others to do
things and they are not doing it
themselves and they have no awareness of
it they never do they never do
it's in conceded universe that you've
been exposed to on the deck of this
craft is inconceivable the they have a a
blade a weapon that looks like a
crescent and a half circle attached to a
steel rod and as they sleep as if they
sweep them down on you it's not pain
sure it's sadness just the breakage of
the body has a sadness because you can
no longer be of use right and something
to do to get points seven days you take
a point to seven yeah you are struck
repeatedly one of them in their fury and
isolation and rage clamps down bite on
the firm on the armored cap that the
home has provided you to protect it and
in that moment it draws its head away
and you know what it knows and it knows
what you know and it's stunning it is a
stunning process of they purchase each
other they attack ships and feel
individuals and buy and sell them and
that is their purpose here that is if
that is their purpose for the home ok Oh
how will you bring joy what happened
mean I die okay back to you know roll
very oh darling episode 16 I'm painting
all right I roll better head yeah so 24
going uh I I want to I want to use that
that that trail behind me of scores to
kind circle as many as I can
you have to try by shell we have to try
let me take a look here what would you
like use your dice plus two for Dexter
oh okay nope simple that's all I need
that's all I need you are you are your
body is designed for this place this is
this is this is just this is as simple
as standing up or walking across the
room so so you begin to turn the massive
bulk of the home and flood this space
with the spores and almost instantly you
are flooded with the realizations that I
communicated to the weeper they they are
denizens of a of an ill of a sick
society and its torment its torment it
explains everything about their behavior
and then as you are aware of this you
feel intense sadness not from this side
but from the top and you can you're
aware that at at least two places long
steel legs have begun to penetrate the
outer skin and they have begin to scroll
along the surface toward each other
they're crawling around the outer edge
of the body one of my one of my denizens
they are but they are not weepers they
are not as a rule
oriented toward this purpose you are
welcome to communicate with them and try
to make sure that they understand what's
happening how you phrase it is important
I turn inward it turns inward we turn
way turn inward yes and express that we
how fortunate we are to not have to
contend with the idea of being separate
if we do not understand the construct of
separateness then disregard and continue
but if you do if we do know that there
were there was so much value in this
cohesion
however finite
USC's of the century yes and they
understand ice what can what can we do
we eyes but anything that you see
weepers can be applied to okay so there
are there are these spiders these ships
have begun to crawl and chew they're
operating around the mid-session okay
vapors can be tasks do I have an
infinite supply of weavers beyond
counting wonderful so I will send can I
send one weeper out of two of our eyes
wanted each of these these spiders ever
walk again with the purpose that we are
attempting to attempting to is the wrong
word with the with the purpose that we
will become one with these organisms and
take away their deep sadness and their
sickness yes okay that's a 20 for the
first shooting and 18th absolutely there
is a creature you are aware of it dimly
but now you've been given full awareness
of it because you have been tasked by
the eye and you are sent from an eye
almost in an elliptical orbit fired out
and then drawn back to the surface you
are you land on the deck of a ship
shaped like this spider creature is
crawling along the surface and you have
an awareness that there is another one
just like on the other side and they are
slowly working to carve the ship in half
I'll go to the closest one and sin eat
it bring them on board yeah absolutely
just roll for it mm-hmm tennis something
absolutely uh from correctly from your
hands waves of spores shimmering golden
shimmering spores explode out onto the
deck miss cloud yeah a mist cloud if you
will
oh this is the mists cloud that's what
we're talking about yes exactly
the spider continues to crawl but those
who are here on the deck in instant
cease their travails they invade they
come close to you because they long to
be close physically as well but this is
not where the spider receives its
commands this their ships have have
creatures at them and they manually
direct them like them like they're
crafting something do you know where
that is I get a size instantly you know
precisely where it is that would you
like to go there yes please do say
modifier mhm 12 you enter a room this
room is full of physically much larger
specimens of the same the same creature
you flood this room with golden spores
and immediately immediately they pull
back on these levers the slider just
detaches floats away you join them in
another different kind of life as that
ship sails away home what is your next
what is your next effort how will you
bring joy we are being pierced there is
a there is a sadness a grinding sadness
around this link
can can joy be returned there do you
mind my denizens Abel it's time it's
time joy can be returned there it's just
time what is what is the aspect of this
day enjoying this linguistic challenged
yeah yeah
much I'm gonna listen back to it and
then calm myself crawl in a bloody bed
okay Joe I'm gonna buy directional
microphone and go here here what is the
aspect of this this entity who is making
us experience sadness no in relation to
me in relation to us where is it there
is one is you would say it's on the
another creature we call this their
belly good creature that isn't this is
you know rotary as you are it is a
uniform see but the cuts the sadness is
deep this is a this is a ship that is
purpose-built for this type of war and
you have a you have a you have a sense
that some of you are being taken into
these ships then of course it didn't
occur to us earlier because of how
foreign it is its but it is absolutely
it is it is beyond comprehension to
exist in that way we must we want
this makes any sense we must move away
relative separate from or we have no
concept of that if we have some concept
it's a philosophical quandary so you say
you until you would like to move your
body in such a way that our creates
distance of yes I want a Jamiroquai it
must want to travel without moving
they must have - that would be at 12 if
we're using the same either way this
course object yes the file with this
enumeration this is the only number
unnecessary all this Jarvis know what
ice cream - yarn thanks only joy do it
this one grows art you you turn the body
card you can see against the against the
sea there is a bright shape a green and
blue shape as you are turning it some
portion of your awareness is given over
to a curiosity about it but the act of
turning has flexed this cut this savage
cut in the side and the front splits
from the back and the back falls away
and it is yourself and you are aware of
it and it is aware of it and there is a
moment where you are still connected and
joyous and then it is gone falls back
this is the capacity that you have to
guide your body through space and it is
gone
and you are drawn as though by a a wimp
cold toward this orb and the heat is
incredible as you near it and as you
push through its sky that a long time
since you've seen the sky but you know
you know what it is and you can see that
there is a crack in this place a deep
crack and you know that that can be a
home too that can be another type of
home too near the sky is no good that is
not a joyous place but a deep place a
cool place this can be a home you wake
up and there is a moment of Terror as
you are in sold in your body's rosy
beasting orchestra Strauss walnut dawn
grass and dinar blitz and pulled away
from a full unity a full understanding
of each other
and deposited in this fragmentary
nightmare but you you become accustomed
to it you can remember that you used to
do this all the time this was considered
normal just look at everybody else yeah
so this is a cavern there's no sky above
there's no canopy there's no dinar
Blitzen snacking or planning to snack
thank goodness there's no cool
there is no cool stone tower of safety
and refuge as a as a once upon a time
experiment or would such compounds yeah
psilocybin yeah we're aware of exactly
what has happened my my suspicion is
that the alchemy skill that you do have
the Arcana skill is probably like 30%
eating things you should
that's just my guess well that's how you
build it yeah it's like I came but like
for your consciousness yeah
everybody else is conscious yeah yeah
you're looking around and it's like if
if at any moment you hesitate you can
see a friendly my candid provider a
support structure to help you stand nice
look down I'm gonna go I told you guys I
didn't want to kill how much of this do
we remember to the fader up all of it
you remember you remember it as though
it was real and it was real it's all
real I'm crying and Rosie's probably
extremely moved too because I think that
there were things that she saw that she
recognized in that yeah absolutely
absolutely I think things that you know
intimately right
okay so let's kill the mushroom people
yeah yeah exactly you can see that on
the center of this in the center of this
column obviously you're surrounded by
eyes and the rest of these are the sorts
of mushrooms as I said last game that
exists on a tree like when a mushroom
has to find a home on a [ __ ] those
platforms cylinder if I did exactly
right strong firm mushrooms that are
sort of around in a sort of stair step
circular stair type pattern around the
middle until now you did not know that
some of them were mouths as well
twelve mouths fifteen mouths around this
central column speak and they say this
place is too near the sky for us this is
not what we are meant to be it is no
harm to us to destroy this route but we
have sent an envoy with you
if you are ever in the deep places of
this world we will be again what they
mean no should rattle one of them
climbing your bag because we know what
you know and you know what we know and
knowing that we cannot allow this city
to remain finally someone is talking
sense
um yeah I feel like flaws like like you
know puts it like past the midline
knowing that they're all you know we're
all it's all one yeah no you know that
resistance acetyl and this rikknen
society yeah put the hand on one and
says uh I do know that this is this is
too near near this guy um and so I said
like we will we will destroy other route
that's that's what we do and so we're
about that's what we're about and I and
then I'll just say like and you go
continue spreading the with the
questions joy that you do in the way
that you do so well so what you do you
could they say that they can destroy the
truth it's already destroyed oh good I
was very nervous this happens I miss it
gosh well they'll take credit for
destroying - yeah as is our destiny and
we we will try to find a deeper place
perhaps as soon as you can find some day
yeah when we find a deep this place we
will bring you to that place I have a
sudden distaste for destruction feel
like I've been going about this the
wrong way
yeah maybe now we won't have to murder
her maybe they always turn our corner
this will give you this is going to be
the change
yeah so thought about Jefferson
Minotauro yeah chattering I'll for I
can't help it al for my name is you ever
ended do you mean al for isn't even been
fine but what was it all for you
put alpha on the tombstone okay exactly
Valley well what was it all for them the
mouths around the central column you can
see that sort of cinched in is leveraged
its body do whatever needs to be done
and so we are joy walnut dong grass you
are join just nice to meet you buddy
carrion my yeah free with you
truly don't you the dragons everybody
who uh we are doing yeah good thank you
blow up that is all I wanted all I
wanted it but my victory condition for
this game was to have one of you say we
are joy without being prompted and I got
that like 20 minutes ago so like I said
does a dragon how do you see a lot of
gold a lot of treasure
why XP yeah it's just a lot of we serve
as a table talk you know just a classic
GD created a see if they're all the
dressers goblins displays rubies some
kind of drug trip yeah I'm sort of
interactive he is co-op drug trip
exactly but I look at that next pretty
well be like oh it was totally great so
they had been voicing at this point and
it's also some throwback I'll go into it
in the table talk but there's some
throwback stuff for the old-school nerds
in there and DM so I figured yeah which
is your mind around it exactly what
we're doing but but like this is the
reason I was when I emphasize that this
is D and D as opposed to whatever I was
doing before was that you have the wheel
again oh I do like you have to wait for
me to lean into wheel or does enemy
nerds like I like the audiobook so your
penis you're playing know you need that
know great I do I'm not going that was
like a telltale game yeah I go I'll hit
X up no I mean keep doing your
semi-fitted sovereign will remember that
and they will oh my god I'm especially
so I look around and I'm doing my best I
feel like I have a question like is
there like a lingering understanding of
my like was that like like a team
bonding thing do I have like a reluctant
knowledge of them on any level yeah
how granular there's not even your
leptin like I said business what you
wanted to know yeah
no it's the thing that's fading is the
connection between each other the memory
of the of the harmonious whole that has
remained with you all right but you'd
but it's just it's like it's like when
you wake up from a dream like the things
that you knew about each other so
there's looking in that place those are
fading out fast just individual images
in icons symbols and they're just
they're slipping out if you guys take a
look at me I'm I am feverishly writing
where I can yeah and really I give up
because it's I know it's garbage like
you know you write something the middle
of the night I'd like to sleep and it's
just two words just trash it doesn't
mean anything
I'm so disappointed once diligently
documenting this doctor
that's that's your task it's just a
really good picture of a mushroom and
the thing I suppose you should go see
how our elder friend is doing no even
point of it all right now are you in
here yes you can see if you can see the
I'm still connected the cranium ragbag
it's 101 hip-hop yeah yeah Monsieur pop
pop oh how fun so mr. HIPAA so up that
that sort of cylindrical spiral around
that central core you just exploring it
drink going up a half way going back
down a little bit nervous mm-hmm goes up
a little bit longer comes back down ah
then what do we do you just having a
good time he goes back up halfway we sit
down and watch him you know what's
happened
oh yeah well whatever it is what these
spores doesn't appear to stick to the
mouse question yeah two questions one
has everything still made out of stone
here as I hear stone and metal and
everything yeah for yeah I mean if
construction hasn't been altered many in
America well I'm just wondering like
where the route was because it's right
yeah the givings is the guess you can
make it an educated guess that that is
to substrate upon which the sovereign
actually grown in this room okay okay
okay is elder Bryan wherever al freed
everyone else we're gonna yeah yeah up
hop-hop-hop leaves you back and you can
see your majestic princess staircase
sparkle back up into form and as you
come down this the chamber is a hive of
activity there were always sort of like
in a fairy pods from this you know group
going out and engaging exactly engaging
engaging in unique tasks as they were
assigned and you can see that the entire
group of them appears to be working
actively on the brain right now so the
it has been sort of held up almost like
I said it's going to drawing rack almost
stretched out distended like you assume
that's not its normal thing that's not
it's kink you know what I mean at this
at this time the the roots that have
come down of withered so small that it
is actually sort of resting sort of
hanging a little bit off of it imagine
imagine like a wet shirt on a branch
it's just sort of hanging over these
roots that no longer have any sway or
power and you can see that even inside
these the holes that are dug through the
brain they're full of rats you can see
rats sort of like crawling around in the
interior structures cleaning and
preparing the flesh or you tell them
exactly what to do a lot of guys love
this brain problem it has a lot of
medicinal yeah exactly if the deer mouse
are clearer than our mouse yeah where I
read this yeah like it and then you can
see as it they're their work
is just as dutiful instant that is
crawling around the surface and then one
by one you see each of these rats
reduced into a liquid that collapses and
runs out of these channels in the brain
and then slowly fills this pool beneath
the brain and it sort of slides off like
imagine them on imagine Portobello like
off of a like a like a grill spatula
yeah just you hit on it eases down in a
giant brain yes off of a giant piece of
wood yeah yeah basically into a brain
pool a pool of liquefied rat that's
right you're you're not a medium because
except for pop hop-hop-hop does not join
the chorus they said no I'm gonna tell
you that yeah be the voice that you have
heard before that you recognize from
this creature is projected you know this
as though there is an echo but it's no
physical voice shore it it says you have
done as I have asked yeah and now I will
do as I have promised hmm there is a
chamber beneath this city that is warded
with tremendous sophistication against
scrying but my network is dutiful and
each of them has a tiny piece of my will
which is greater than average let's say
black writer trolley yeah you're great
you know we pay like minutes like it's
just uh I can easily
make my way back to my domain and I
shall return to me this dutiful servant
of mine after he has shown you your
reward and I pray we never meet each
other again that the incentives to work
together may not hold in the realm I
command all the contact do is trust me
I'm sweet can we roll anything to see if
we can keep flying
yes flying about what because well yeah
yeah we have to give it a go you see
Fistful of dice yeah yeah well yeah you
think this is under the Dragons you can
do whatever you want my my thought is
he's telling us to go to some deep
deeper chamber that's protected by magic
against crying and there we will find
our reward
okay sounds real [ __ ] show yeah yeah
yeah that's rats gonna betrayal sounds
good too on that what's a good little
office what well the secret chamber does
this city is somehow just is organisms
protecting that's like almost like
that's the heart looks like that's the
beating heart of the city yeah walnut
thing she's like she can't get any worse
than this when deed indeed and she
opened those things so she hasn't told
anyone
yeah no answer that crazy trip that's
different yeah hold on even after we had
that trip together yeah hello music
clatter it's like we were like one you
know and I'm more inside all of you
personally immediately you know this
lingo - well I would say yeah - we'll uh
my character name um know the taste
Island alright well known you just like
ready to go so I'll look at the rest of
the party and I'll say um I think we
came here to do what we're contractually
obligated to do I catch a rat problem is
solved with the exception of one so
we'll call this a problem as a I
understand if no one wants to come with
me today I am I'm definitely going to go
I'll go I'll go if you I'm trying to
hide that I'm kind of smitten with this
with this humor elect yeah what can I
get out of it and I'll come that's
important might as well see it through
Korea can we ask one question do
whatever you like
other Brian you can do it everything do
you know what happened to the Homewood
star there is a pause but that's not
that doesn't characterize its
communication and he says
- cthe RIS he says drow I'm going to
give you a piece of advice it's a rarity
file it away I would be very careful
about using the stars from your clip
I'm worried about that this week they
regenerate yeah something refreshing but
I'll remember yeah I think at it
okay see I scraped so low okay we'll
remember that as always
okay I've been told I could do this plan
a whole [ __ ] game just like a total
adventure from now on we always have to
have that like sort of meaningful every
man look here cuz everybody has that
like melting like when they're going to
remember that remember that yeah it
should work hope he doesn't but he does
mm-hmm yeah hello
I asked the brain if he likes my new hat
it's a brain can shrug yeah it does that
it just for other guys guys he loves it
he said a little how did you not yeah I
mean that one not you know but yes eggy
Hattie
yeah yeah exactly it is all cute stuff
Kevin yes
no no good weather that the Hat does in
fact have two eyes there's a pretty bad
illustration happening on the air of
that yes it has opinions on things I got
really cute one yeah that's always like
how we're doing it which way is facing
up I assume you're sad oh that's my
lower one here's Marin there's oh no
horrifying one well mine gross one is a
mushrooms for look like at you can
decide if you dislike Susan is no
exactly like it's like listen you do
your vote text k80 a tip and both of us
staying today Wow know what you decide
alright I want to just for F people that
are gonna be listening to this later on
the podcast I want you to know kids
looks like an adorable cookie and
Chris's looks like a piece of human
anatomy can I help
he's a tall person I'm thinking like I
am a
yeah yeah yeah exactly when if they've
had there's a little teardrop raindrop
when it gets computer to the table talk
yeah sorry sorry gotta go hit the
self-destruct button the reward is I
don't have to oh my god mr. in just a
magical um yes well it's like inching
towards or like looking at pop-up like
can you you take out yeah he's a hopping
a couple times
obstacle times in place and then leads
you out in the opposite part of this in
the office of part of his chamber which
is a cracked and shattered version of
you assume where it would dwell in its
normal place it's just it has equity
looks like a ruin of some kind but you
can guess what it must look like in the
seat of his power and he walks directly
through the back wall he works through
the wall sure that's not the weirdest
thing ever since there honestly yeah
that's like this literally the least
weird thing yeah disappointment [ __ ] you
really Wow I want to wake up to the wall
all confident like I'm definitely going
to go through it but then also just kind
of be like yeah and then I try and go
through it yeah it's warm it's warm
imagine walking through a curtain of
warm water
I don't just and disturb your raiment
you know but it definitely you can just
get a cascade of warmth as you pass
through this you all see her pass
immediately through the wall the other
it's not good I mean as a sconce it has
like a torch yeah like I panic when I
see you disappear Judith wall and I'm
after you like a shot I've cooked in too
long yes it's a phone that way through
the peril of the map yeah yeah I got a
contact a mod to get down did you see
shadows deep shadows and you pass you
pass through this wall there are three
more just like it
each of them each of them completely
indiscernible from
a normal structure and you could but you
can recall that when you came down
initially even to find the elder brains
chamber at first yeah
there were walls that you passed through
but these are but that was very fast I
was also like non-consensual like they
just took us no you were going out of
the way right you were going to a place
so you're passing through this is
remembering something or it doesn't see
it doesn't see illusions you know what I
mean I receive real walls okay so we go
through three of these and that like
each time would like more speed and more
gusto yeah yeah just more enthusiasm
you're getting to the end of the book
Yeah right married it does last twenty
six fast act three you guys so you so
once you once you leave to the last one
it makes you wonder how much of that
subterranean structure was real and how
much of it was some kind of a projection
because this doesn't look like a this
doesn't look anything like that
architecture it is is how to put it this
is very organic the rest of it and I
mean like the organic I have least I
mean this looks as though it was created
by natural forces right as opposed to
everything else which is you know it's
likely you would build at a dwarven
Forge or something right
I mean it's like the ceramics it's got
all the little stuff is they go here at
the fountain is an image or a dream of
something that the brain knew perhaps
this feels like it was created by you
know dripping water over a substantial
period of time okay and then it is
basically a tunnel and at the tear at
the very end of this tunnel is a bright
green light okay
it's a fair distance and we were all
together
I assume I've walked through yeah yeah
yes go into it as you as you are pushing
through it the closer you get to it the
more intense the first of all the
suspect the warm forest like a forest
and a high summer smell is coming out of
this chamber and you can see roots vital
roots and leaves yeah absolutely
they shouldn't be able to survive down
here this is not where they do their
thing and as you exit the tunnel and
emerge into the chamber there is a
single tree and it is lit by a shaft of
light coming from the ceiling up and to
the right almost like a it looks like it
might be a great like a street grate or
something like that and as that light
comes down and strikes the tree beams of
it project from leaf to leaf until the
entire tree is illuminated like a
crystal yeah yeah cuz it's very it's
very thin waxy leaf but you can see that
the light is just shining from leaf to
leaf they're just generous with each
other around the entire thing so this is
this is not a type of tree that you're
familiar I don't know anything about
that
it comes down as the the trunk comes
down but sends a roots reach around in
front and close around a pool of water
okay great okay and two strange fruits
of this tree are they a beggar belief
there is there is the best way to put it
is that there are swords on this tree
that are not yet right
in some cases in some cases it might be
a short sort okay but the proportions
are wrong okay okay okay
you know you know what I mean like
they're hanging down in various states
of of development okay
weapons but there is one that is
complete regret and it hangs down from a
branch and like an apple there's a tiny
piece of stem that goes into the pommel
and the bow is just pregnant with it
like it's the sword is like drawing the
bow down it's so strong it's not in
danger but the weight of this thing on
the branch is considerable oh it's just
like so while not walking through all
this and it's like that so don't tell me
about the order so you have you've come
in you're the ultimate you are allowing
way yeah you have you have projected
your way in so there's a new right
friend denying and those two then we
were like we lost yeah like we have like
yams I think I think I'm still gonna go
in the back though you know so you come
in last
yeah come in laughing he took 17 points
of damage
this boy however oh good thing I I think
I don't know my orders I mean I was
first as soon as as soon as he crosses
the threshold of this chamber the leaves
that had sort of gently been swing all
turned instantly to face him that's him
it just him and the light is incredible
minding light is incredible it's like a
radiant damage yeah okay he is not
bodily out of the chamber see he's he's
out okay I kept um cast darkness around
him yes he's still in danger I know I'm
out of the apparently I got knocked yeah
out of the room so outside of the room
is he in danger or I perceive he's in
danger nothing seems to be happening
when he's not I mean I feel real they
are you okay yeah well hi I know what
you do man real bright sorry but I can't
start this on you which means you can't
see [ __ ] dark visions
worked in it but it'll probably keep you
from taking more comfort yeah
Oh does it uh I guess well we'll see I'm
not in a mood to start back in yeah yeah
thank you it does all are you like this
darkness I cast it on you okay but you
are blind like you you're all you are in
special dark yeah yeah
you can't no no no dark vision and non
magical light that's probably a comfort
to you right now I feel will do dancing
lights inside of it to get light because
not that it says non magical light can't
eliminate it but you might be able to if
you really wanted to see for whatever
reason I say what's there what's the
radius in this bad boy eat okay I was
going to say no I guess it'll still work
I can have I can have lagari poked its
head out just ahead and then strayed
visions with it and then it leads me
should I want I'll prep to do that but
right now I'm going to stay out so can
your comfortable darkness but but yeah
this is the entire so imagine that their
roots so the stone is at the floor of
the stone is fit together it's not slit
this this tree is growing out of stone
okay and the roots that it has in
addition to the ones that have formed
that pool in front they go up the walls
all around and the roots themselves are
interleaved with symbols of rough
protection and comfort okay um so I want
to like I want to go up to the tree and
I wanted to try touching just any part
of its root and see if I'm allowed to
get close to it absolutely okay great I
hang back with you yeah
well I'm like I the tree attack
including under our feet laughs he's
going to figure it out it's like should
I go heal it returns it I don't cross
that threshold oh and you want to be
like by Hemingway yeah I want to
introduce him again I don't know Matt
either
well I go with them I wanted to pick
some friends yeah
selling off first yes I guess no is it
is it is welcoming and so I will
probably the idea of this is the natural
environment it's actually you know
giving moment like looks to her like
it's presenting her weapon goggling it's
um it's a scimitar who knows so she's
going to walk up I think in see if it
the sortal give easy they just right I
mean just like the perfect right off the
trip oh just just one not even though
emotion is conceded you as soon as you
reach out for it's just yours geez do I
feel any time yeah you're you're flooded
with soreness you're flooded with wisdom
I'm flooded with with them you are
flooded with wisdom is a just real quick
in case you need the stats right now
it's a plus-one attack plus one damage
b12 like the rat group one d12 cell
would be my rap group what did you know
l1 d12 but in the blade is another kind
of knowledge okay it is an awareness and
a consciousness so so you know when you
were trained to become animals
mmm-hmm there's a process and you have
to often involves a dream where you have
to follow them and earn trust and things
like that you know how to become a tree
like this ah I do you know how to become
a tree like this just from holding ass
yeah so you can grow weapons for us now
I'm have any friends I'm not just like
ah oh my god he's engines like an Iran
game to be in if it isn't read its
president Aeneas okay like you can just
see it you can turn your hand over
and it can be sat if you want you can
just see SAP
you can see your veins change color is
an instinctual problem wellness yearns
tree form this is has this is this is
your birthright as a daughter of the EPA
this is your birthright
it's like a little Megaman screen it's
like the new de mierda to do change of
color
well hazards that's amazing okay um but
there's this other thing so there's this
hanging with it's hanging with these
plants and various and various states of
maturity is the weapons of very safe not
all civet ours it's just this is a tree
whose purpose is war and there if there
is something else that is right mm-hmm
it is a seed pod a seed pod thick
I mean readied ready to pull and
emblazoned around it in different
ancient druidic languages is the word
names ear listen I know that this is not
the best time and while I'm not dumb
grass but we have to go to a commercial
break
I'm sorry I'm not that's not what is not
my choice and the PP palace that's right
the Hani gala was phone yeah come hang
out come shadow council I hope that our
Labor's have pleased you take a moment
to refresh yourself and don't go
anywhere come right back hello I'm
Jennifer key Larkin what it's going to
continue on just real quick in case you
missed it
walnut dong grass daughter of the
enclave panic anima has just entered
into a chamber emblazoned with symbols
of protection and comfort she has this
tree is a war tree of some kind that
it's fruits are themselves weapons and
she has just seen a ripe seed pod on it
emblazoned with the word Nana's ear and
if you're like a C team nerd than you
know what that means
sure do and you're not and you're new
get out of here yeah too bad ya know a
lot to catch up on you're worried it's
all digital you can get watched online
it's like please please do that
it means graveyard yeah well it means a
couple things
well you're right Alf for said that it
was a war route right senator who knows
why the gate said what it said that's a
good point I can trust can't trust
anyone you can't trust a Tuesday no you
don't ever write over trust am i right
how would I pick up this sword as if
it's ever going to leave my hand again
and I want to cut off the seed pod now I
have it nothing happens
Oh something happens I'm gonna tuck in
this yeah yeah the cat museum decided
social as you as you as you reach up and
pull it off you can see that reflected
in each of these leaves so the entire
chamber is lit and nourished by a single
shaft of light from the surface and
playing across these leaves you see
scraps of language okay like I would
imagine druidic language okay so imagine
that each leaf as you saw as you go down
from the trunk each leaf is like a page
and then it just this revelation just
progresses throughout a relief this this
this plant this tree is a trove is
itself a-- a record a historical record
but that's not the only thing that you
notice
so wait there's more but wait there's
more as you as you pluck this ripe pod
you can see that the roots that have
come down from the tree and projected up
around materially change in structure
okay
meaningfully they become made of
something like you have noticed in this
town this odd commingling of stone and
metal harvested by the process whatever
is inherent in this corrupted version of
this seed that founded this city you are
seeing the true version of it you
remember the minotaurs tale that the
Enclave Ward with the elephant and they
did so with the use of a siege engine
that they planted in the surface and
then it committed war below this tree
has some other purpose in the heart of
the nemah seer the corrupted NEMA's ear
there is still a true account of the
Enclave
at its heart and the roots and indeed
the central core and the branches
themselves cease to become cease to be
organic shapes and they instead become
gruesome animated Lance's of steel and
stone and you can see that that ring of
roots around it harvests leeches from
the walls the materials it needs to
launch itself straight up growing
through the ceiling the central core of
it becomes a kind of grinding burr that
reaches up through the ceiling along
with its sister roots and it annihilates
the ceiling of this chamber this is no
longer a safe place for living things
well is everyone okay here's my fantasy
would you do I want to pick the library
and then the tree got mad I try to kill
it immediately
so I still have this thing right you
have it okay you have a seat of the
Nimitz here this week on what it's not
gone but it is something else it is
taken on its purpose and it is currently
in the process of boring out first this
room and then presumably in a widening
terrifying arc do you want me to drop
darkness on you you want you this Oh
move it yeah I'm gonna risk it
I'm not going to come back in the room
at this point no I'm one of the trio
take anymore damage and the trees not
really there I have more d20 s back here
okay well I can roll during that there
must I'm full um real quick before we go
is the pool of water still there yeah
can I make an attack attempt to smash
some of that water before we go
yeah you can't okay I'm gonna you look
to collect these fluids everywhere you
go well my daughter a seedpod and
there's a pool water and how to feed a
parent yeah yeah I'll SAP the bag of
these listen I'm gonna walnut Sinister's
do it gasps they're coming up oil - um I
think walnuts going to like build a
little friend I got a microphone how
would you feel about a 17-2 get water
yeah XE cool you said that it's like
clean sane and living it's like a
whomping willow exactly you can still
reach down in here it's just not a good
idea being here oh okay well I did like
I say the central imagine of the central
core and of the trunk of this thing ran
a blender yes you are basically at the
bottom of a blender and it is blending
NEMA's ear mm-hmm come on come on come
on while I climb this guy oh my god
basically this is a breakfast making a
protein shake
um yeah I want to run and I want to like
as when I get to turn are just like be
pushing everybody over nope
I'm sorry don't know my being said once
we're out of the chamber
do we feel does it feel like maybe also
next to the chamber is not a good place
to go like maybe this is not expected in
it or it is a progressive revelation
that involves the annihilation of this
corrupted City and you are at that
epicenter of it in fact as you're
running down this this natural tunnel it
is splitting overhead like a pea pod and
you can see daylight whoa
we're as far down as I thought I want to
you can't be [ __ ] I think you know I did
not oh you're running the walls we must
be way down there
why no no in fact rubble rubble is
falling I mean it would not be
impossible even from here to get out I'm
gonna playing Marco Polo I'm gonna
question our real quick and I'm going to
the snow upon him the power of jump your
jump distance is tripled until the spell
ends and then as stoic Lee as possible
but also like I'm very friendly to Rosie
and I go grandeur perimeter I tried
assure you over to dinars sure I'll be
like you're sure what's going on oh my
grab you jump out of here yeah oh hi
Santa when we leaving friends a - to his
beautiful dark deficit momentum delays
oh he's happy
yeah what's happening darkness I've
chopped darkness okay you can come hang
on us oh and there really is shaking
okay I didn't know the fear right so
it's a Carol get rid loves like dimness
but it's petrified of stars yes yes far
to go be not afraid of the dim you mean
we doing jumps right I love you right
going off green man uh-huh you're on all
right yeah yeah you get strength four
days I'm not sure all right sounds good
you could just hang onto the hem of the
robe all aboard the strong boy grab grab
the Hat
yeah you don't need that much height a
lot any any height that would have been
tuned by the additional weight is not
what's needed for this purpose you you
are running through this thing I have to
say it's split like this seem you're
granted the spell you gather everyone
towards you and bleep out and now you
are on a street that is being shredded
and if you look back there's a couple
things that you see first in the
distance you can see
kaalia Chiefs
clock tower and you can see that the
broken clock face has begun to spin and
whine too fast
Oh to that this excites me yes I heard
you got that oh yeah you see a light
around the bait of it and it just Falls
oh and then the light ceases but you can
see that this grinding burr but just
ever-widening as it takes on minerals
and steel and glass it is just
continuing to widen like a flower as it
grinds up through the central mound of
this city well that got to be excited so
excited just having brief flashes of
what tells it to stop no no people are
people are terrified screaming they are
there screaming 100% of the thread is
strong right now this is not this is not
a good place to be
I keep everyone when there's no there's
none
yeah there's no way to conceive of it
Hulk jumplist like I don't everybody put
in to tell you hook like a full city
block you show up and then this is
another another strange thing so imagine
that as this mound is pulverized imagine
that like pistils and stamens imagine
that it blooms even at the top and out
from it come these
arcing steel wires that burst out of the
top and then fall down in arcs around
itself and then an additional ring
around the city itself oh we should grab
the cart and maybe go yeah this thing's
on the moon it's one option whatever
you'd like to do I'm going to jump us
ken right oh where we are do I know
where the card is they already started
relative yeah you know Holly ah chief
you can see that this is being okay over
eyes yeah you you have a sense of where
you would need to go and hopefully it
will still be there yeah all right well
so do you have any interests in staying
with Nazir and finding out who's done
this I'm not going to find anything out
while we're I'm screaming this while
we're on tonight we're jumping I want to
find any information out right now
unless I stop this and then just trail
off like I would like I like there would
be any world in which I would stop this
it's just funny ahem like a like a calm
conversation like well by humping 60
feet in the air
terror destruction all around listen
yeah but this is a long problem
yeah sure when you get outside the edge
of the city if we can get outside the
edge I guess you guys can see I was like
no no no hold on oh go ahead you vary
this every every up so let's just get
outside of the border of the city real
quick ok um without our dead horse you
pull a cart I'll grab no we're gonna
come to this yeah I cash why waters
warming enhances its enhance ability and
I give you the big strength yet a
Queen's vigor full strength now your
your caring capacity doubles when I sure
hope that's enough now you're a special
horse now you're special never seen one
is hearing more and more stuff we don't
by the way hell we're in the cart you
just have to embrace that cart right
you're saying uh you're going to win the
cart
at this point at this point you are
actually jumping the streets are no
longer streets that you would walk on or
trust we can't get the car there's
living straight down the middle just
like the tunnel so at this point you've
been reduced to leaping from roof to
roof very cool it's the best thing
that's ever happened our stuff best
campaign of all time no I'm sorry cause
I say so you're leaping and then you can
you can you can see the district not the
hammock district you can see it BAM
Uli's leaps into bed yes and then you're
you're good all spell reset that base of
these these cracks project yay even unto
the edges of this town now and you can
see the cart pathway down in a crack and
you can see coriander's steel form it's
probably the only weight that is keeping
the cart from disappearing down this
crevice - ooh so heavy
sorry I dare say huh uh-huh
all right so does it look like there's
any chance we can save our cart
I think so this is Dungeons &amp; Dragons
yes possible it doesn't mean I question
if I could do it I might have to drop
you kiddos off at the pool that's fine
one minute taking a poop no it doesn't
is what a good parent does and they
can't go swimming yeah we come in the
people rise yeah yeah there's a lifetime
that cardiovascular yeah it's a whole
body exercise so even now but even now
in this district now that there's the
central core of these wires and this
external core this other circle around
that central ring now they seem to be
hitting random places okay so we need to
real quick is just sending them out how
far are we from getting out of Elvis
from where the cart is and where safety
I'm sorry maternity you'd be you would
be able to get out of here fairly
quickly if you had a strong means of
Dragonborn yeah exactly
a one of these one of these roma metal
hoarseness one of these tents one of
these tensile projections from the
Nana's ear core lands in front of the
cart and strikes coriander and coriander
dies again yeah really yeah oh I get it
idols yeah my god she goes back to life
just long enough to dying and then I
feel betrayed by yes I quit but but but
you know you see one close now that you
see now you see one of these wires close
by you can see that it's almost like a
it's almost like the end of the pea vine
oh okay there is a reaching clever
nature to it oh so when it lands socket
and strikes you can see some of the
vital sap that you would collected
before you assume trying to harmonize
this area you assume that it is
preparing like almost like terraforming
the city of men is here oh yeah
but the metal frame of coriander is
filling with this vital SAP ice it's
like the end of Star Trek - okay yeah
everybody go - I never saw no and you
can see the seams you can see inside the
seams between the limbs on the neck you
can see you in here the vines and growth
tightening inside the metal form okay
I'm all in favor just seeing how this
plays it I am I'll follow you
cap it down to the yeah into the dark
well I don't know what's going on with
coriander but I think that we should
just try and grab our cards we will hope
it getting home getting there sure sure
task we stopped
Bernard to the frolic heart like an ox I
could throw it listen how about I throw
it I'm gonna say like you better get in
I feel like I could just grab it and run
for it no lash him to it where do you go
run faster if you don't win I don't
think it's wire strikes at home look
straight through the window and then you
can see just a few seconds later vines
and plants spreading out along the
outside of the house oh okay real ones
real ones
oh yeah we gotta go this is amazing and
I want to let it happen so I want to run
down there and I said are you gonna pull
this thing or Eilis everyone get in the
car you're gonna throw it everyone I'll
pull it everyone get the card the
coriander on top
coriander is trying desperately to get
out Cornwall to her feet oriental
horsing ah all right turn in come bear
all right let her ride on you yeah but
it's it one of one of this one of this
feet is is in a crack it's just like ah
all right Rosie Oh hold on this give us
a matter what else oh yes right check
what's right okay I'll do anything I'll
there anything for Kroy oh yeah you have
a 17 yeah yeah yeah so gentle just here
you know what I'm gonna give this moment
to you tell me how it goes
okay I'm panicking and I'm not a strong
person and I but I run super fast to
crack I know that there's vines
happening but coriander is my best
friend and I see that she's trapped and
I got my little money got my little
hands around her scraggly stupid little
foot I'm yanking on it I'm like girl you
gotta help me out and she goes heaven
bless now and I'm like come on come on
come on you can do it and I look back
and as vines they're taking over the
street I can see them starts coming with
the cart and I know dinar needs help and
I'm like how we gotta go we gotta go
coriander and she goes and she pulls
with me and I free her exactly right so
she pulls her foot up out and you are
just holding on to the leg yeah and so
you see
coriander full-height majestic sun
shining off of the bronze plates you can
see in the scene ririn see you can see
tiny leaves beginning to sprout and she
pulls the cart out of the hole and then
waits dutifully yeah I was like like
don't almost too slowly get on the hop
of the cart like oh I feel my own body
into the crate this fascination okay
holding there weeping I pull myself
together immediately yeah get on the
front it's ready to go take up your
classic crack your classic realm
marvelous
it is the nap already happening dinars I
don't know I can jump super far now
super strong sighs maybe like I was like
okay remote link yeah like you never
stop
you know I don't have this be true
because it's [ __ ] amazing
imagine a scenario imaginable again and
it's just it's power horsepower yeah
pulling the front of this cart like you
you've never had command of this type of
pull power and it is uh she is pulling
this thing through these tight tight
twists I'm going to need some dexterity
for you to get out of here that's not a
problem
yeah it's like I found this a nine oh
yeah - I think there's a mouse I can be
a tough one you can alright alright
let's do that seventeen yep absolutely
so you you are coming around this tight
good as I described before that some of
these roads and streets are really based
on the capillary sort of structure
inside of a leaf or screw and so some of
them are very very tight you scrape part
of the side off the spoiler is peeled
straight off the top I was so cool they
get caught on the edge you can just jump
back and get it how do you want to play
this era within by dinosaur like a diver
spoil it pull it
with the skull just pulled up twist it
off usually it's on for a little bit
you're like you know what we'll fix them
to get back now if it catches another
side of the edge of the building that
spoiler is gone it is gone it falls on
the ground the ground over the floor so
I was wrong go closes up thank you I
love the floor can change down there is
a cleft all the way down to the owner
ducts as deep as you can get no no
anything like you can ever know and then
it lands on the Eldar brain I kept alder
brain with a cool spoiler oh I think
it's the best he's like oh hey you know
what I can do this so so you view that
the cart bursts from this back road out
into the main vein down the middle of
the leaf you can see various forces of
the city for some inconceivable reason
trying to keep people in but you are at
that you are basically at the gate now
they are trying to close the front gates
of this city who's that one people
trying out visit these are the the city
guard that you've seen you think you
might even occasionally see a daughter
of maelys in the day how much all right
yeah are there are there and are there
people trying to get out like this they
all the they're tried they're trying to
get out and they're trying to close the
gate do we see like know how to have to
put some kids yeah I'm going to save
people no al yeah you could probably
over the gate right I just carry ransom
yeah yeah yeah as well as valuable yes
because their dead parents will pay a
lot yes I see so you're so you're you're
snatching up you're snatching at people
going back and forth you are barreling
toward a closing gate right are we
blasted gate
what can I do ask this game magic with
Otto must do this quite give me a are
not dexterity check let's and then after
you can security check tell me how you
are going to try to pierce this gate
okay well I'm gonna get brought a little
help from my friends mostly my decks
check is 15 I like it and I'm also going
to roll intimidation
oh and just
Green were lucky lucky y'all be lucky
lucky hassling a lot of things happily
on Bertha yeah that's much better
so my decks is the 15 intimidations of
21 as we are barreling toward these
gates the sound comes out of me likes of
which you would not have thought could
happen it was in there it is wordless it
is a combination of terror and joy the
combination of coriander being revived
in the city destroying itself and from
Rosings tiny frail body you hear MA
as we approach the Cape it's also got a
horrid but basically I mean imagine like
a just like the prow of a ship cutting
through the water
guards are trying to create a scenario
where Rosie basting ER and her best
friend do not escape and they are not
there's nothing they can do against this
steel horse bronze horse right
corriander right as the right of it just
a slit where they're trying to shut this
thing down
the hose just BAM straight down it
swings wide people are pouring out on
either side of the cart behind you and
the destron valley branch of
acquisitions incorporated the inheritors
of initiative see have escaped nimeth
here we've got farms full of children
yeah you're dropping them like you run
along that you sponsored by again and
every day exactly sound like exactly but
yeah like a collections bucket like
donations versus a couple more jumps and
you should be able to catch up with the
cart I put the kids down yeah I hope you
bring us got out oops
jump I put the kids out at the crest
yeah and a browser that there's a point
at which the cart sort of lists a little
bit to the right
like quickly and you can see the dinar
is attached to the side
costura Straub is stable to open the
door for him he gets in the side of the
cart and it closes everybody in their
traditional immediately go sleep their
traditional time strong yeah but I I'm
looking back at never like folding in
yeah and that you can see now there's
even more of these extensions coming out
from the NEMA's ear itself and it is
surrounded in a perimeter like exactly
along the outer edge of the city I'm
going to drive I Drive the cart to a
vantage point that it's high enough that
walnut can get like the dopest view of
everything that's happening with yeah
this is like my Death Star blowing up
like yeah exactly I rain front row seat
oh yeah I guess I guess we're we're safe
and then I get to a point where you go
to you can like eat all of this up yeah
yeah um yeah coriander has been through
a lot and at least she's she's hauling
and like you know instantly you know
that this is uh she's worked hard for
you right and she is hungry and thirsty
okay which I'm going to offer her
conventional I'll unhitch her from the
cart and take her over to a spot where
she can get some nice grass she's not
into that so much anywhere I'm she wants
blood now made out of metal no no no no
I don't believe he is walking around she
hasn't mind the grass okay like that she
doesn't it's not going to work okay uh I
look around I offer her my arms she's
not you're not cool okay not a car just
me just licks okay the very businesses
if there's a tongue it cool this oh can
I talk oh she's a she's a plant horse
now oh she has to be good plans to be a
difference rate um she might be hungry
for water or shine so she um she is
walking back and she says missed the air
okay and she walks back toward the cars
okay she just going in the cart when she
wants yes she she's like tapping the
door okay I open the door uh she puts
her
you just horse head comes in snoot
yeah that's need to eat yeah and it's
nothing around your coin purse it's
about now I got a lot I got coin on me
for one of these one of these here
adventure just like snuffling and then
it puts a couple of couples smooth cool
licks against the side of the coin pouch
open it up here I got my gold piece
that's it oh that's what she that's what
she eats gold to eat going on he's gonna
be good I like it one to it yeah is it
just two more melted but she's not rude
about it
oh yeah like yeah it isn't like like a
bag of oats I mean it isn't like oh well
right but let's hear coriander 'if we
put him in a slit in her back going it
was like a big event I want to know what
she should yeah like it it's time you
get like open yeah I just latinum nope
okay I'm just gonna really cut in our
progress of opening at 60% less and
coriander's taking a 66 live gold coins
later yeah she appears to be satisfied
okay we might be able to accept it it is
a travel expense yeah you're right
that's the ultimate she's right metal as
well she's a vet Elliott this is a
business vehicle yeah exactly this is a
video what you tracking your mouth fair
enough subtract those five points for
their horse person don't worry Oh
express it um
I look at you I like a coriander I'm
like she's worth it okay so people
people are so it's like this right now
this is your secret that's right yeah
well five is not bad if it's a good
horse but you're you're you're looking
down I know you're looking down at the
city you can see people are still
pouring out the front they've any
attempt to stop nurses it's gone but the
city itself is not visible okay great
it isn't it is completely cocooned and
this is like the wire is it loca with a
bundt cake yes pan-pan like it's just
your specialist so I'm just waiting for
the hook to drop because I'm interested
like I don't know if you're nice enough
to like let woman actually have this
Viktor here I don't know come back in a
couple weeks
so you pretty complete come back we can
see what have a nice yeah gotta let it
incubate meanwhile I just want to say I
still have the seed pot of the Nemus ear
good they're going to need it plant
another one
okay you also have the other seed which
Jerry said that we could ask him about
this mat that's round yeah real quick I
have this the seeds do it I feel like
this is a place this is a place for them
my bag of seeds from the stream of
annihilation yeah do you want to join a
treaded lesson yeah yeah yeah yes I want
plant all of them yeah perfect um okay
so this is an area that used to as a
Holy Grail this holy ground used to be
not only you know this is like walnuts
place is the enclaves place so where she
grew up
or do we know that yeah yeah we could
okay you all know that okay um so I
think at this point she would like to UM
take the bag of seeds I'm gonna regret
this take the bag of the vital glowy use
put them together shake it and then just
start from the Johnny Appleseed min
around
yes definitely yeah just like yeah we
yeah because she's not going to plant
them it's like you know nature's gonna
grow the ones that are meant to grow um
and she makes it rain on the place below
with you what can can really help like
covering them all with dirt or are you
feeling like they don't want to they
don't out with it okay okay like a maple
seeds
so the vital SAP I love having as many
opportunities as I've had the last few
weeks to save vital SAP homes good over
and over and read it as bag of ooze know
that insufficient
so please respectful thanks so Rose
Rosie is mounding verse yeah sure over
these seeds and
they grow quickly like more quickly even
than you expect quickly than you would
expect for magic seeds even even more
than a bar with high even more quickly
come and what is grown out of them
not every one of them germinates like
you know what I mean like there's only
so much that the environment can support
in this zone but three pods do grow and
imagine them almost like like bassinets
imagine that a frond a healthy strong
support comes and then growing out in a
kind of bassinet is a dryad
oh snap for real for real it's a really
good seeds them all yeah why dryers so
there there are three of them there
every Drive there are three of them here
and they are growing quickly mmm maybe
we should leave them to what they do
well that's like I don't know if I'd I
mean there may be a mother
yeah I was like I'm not right I'm not
going to be responsible for them this is
there for us now okay they're going to
be wardens of this place in the Enclave
shed and that's how results efforts when
but there's the vastness or just sort of
gently swaying in the breeze of this
hill
can I examine one of these triad babies
yeah sure what I see I think I wanna
grow up and pure of edges last night
yeah it looks like a it looks like a
baby a halfling baby I mean very small
right just fold it in almost like
imagine a combination of a baby and a
Brussels sprouts it's like you know it
there's a lot of like to end Geddes
there's a lot there's a lot to like with
the vegetable
there love that nice bee costume there's
really and while we're watching them
yeah how quickly I want dairy yeah
however mother taught me back teenage
just about five minutes you're gonna
deal with all this [ __ ] I don't want to
fight them leave now then leave now
let's go we should go they're the new
wardens of this place
exactly maybe they kill any straggling
townspeople all right I'm going to like
to whisper a little fact secret
something over each of these three oh I
like they will they will need they will
need this these secrets it is a sort of
a blessing of shadow that they can use
to their protection in case you're of a
return I like everything about it so
your horse well fed well compensated
yeah for enslavers days indeed indeed
you are able to pull the car there are
other carts of varying sizes pulling out
still skidding out of the place and then
finding the main road going north going
south you can see a trading cart sort of
up at the fork looks over the city
decides that's not a good place to go
puts the cart back on the North Road to
head north maybe to janar or Scala some
one of the northern case you want to
take the road sign is like a souvenir I
was actually just thinking like what do
I want to write on the road sign yeah I
know I want to take the road sign nice
for your room yes I like to take it I
love it yeah you you hear you're willing
to take it it attacked you you're in
Eileen Tommy Beck no but I do want to
thank I do want to flavor our departure
is just real quick no I'm come in and I
want to look out over the you know what
was name Azir and long before that was
you know the EPS ancestral home but more
importantly like where walnut grew up
and she just whispers a few just little
words to herself but a like a almost
suicide like a fine
farewell to her fall and my sisters and
mother and grandmother great room there
and many many many many more than this
as the card is pulling away yeah but
just like what she's up on deck on the
roof by yourself with yeah thank you
take the sign you hear a voice I says
well that's very touching but elder
price you don't think so I hear a voice
a real loyal top of the cards is it pop
up with a hip hop from Masseria mr. pol
vomitorium it isn't it isn't the mouse
who died face it looks exactly like the
statue that you saw in the statuary
garden the guy over here yeah
the villain Mendes Mendes fail yes oh
where is he
he's with Izzy what he's with me he's
with you on top of the cart do I
perceive it can I see it is he real or
is it a can well I like whoa here I was
getting some like closing the death of
everyone I care about
teleports behind you nothing personal -
oh yo yo E um what is my perception oh
so that's a I'm 13
you don't really don't you don't detect
anything out of the ordinary this seems
like there's a person on that and I say
I recognize this in the statue and I say
you
and then I I'm trying to attack him I
guess go for it
okay huh what's his was his posture of
the opposition and I hope that I say it
loud enough that the rest of my team
hears that I've said you okay um me know
say blah you know I'm gonna attack him
with my um my system I pulled with my
cult resource ah so that would be a plus
what is normally at this stuff what is
my normal life 2's plus 5
whoops 9 anyway I just gotta swipe at
him yeah like you ha it just goes
immediately through his entire torso and
then finds purchase in the roof whoops
I'm ready he's waste police watching the
he looks back in a wash at the town I
know you caused this did I didn't didn't
didn't I didn't invent an EM Azir who
did you're complicit in this
the NEMA's ear is a tool used by the
witches of the enclave to assault the
Underdark I took a weapon turned into a
city a city that you destroyed but it
does grow from a seed so there may be
franchise opportunities come on cuz what
do you why did you make this city what
do you want what did you stand to gain
from this this time it was an
interesting experiment but I serve an
entity far greater than this world and I
need to discern ways to serve her better
if that means I fail on occasion her
power is sufficient to absorb it and
wellness says you served it betrayer
that's a point of view and I say I serve
nailless just even hearing the word
she's like she is that the overwhelming
urge to punch an incorporeal person um
I say so what what are you here to do
now gloat I won this round honestly I'm
impressed and given your lineage
maybe success as a family business and
he winks out what what what a dreary boy
up there okay with that ultimate was
that to me I heard like parts of it us
okay he said my daddy's successful yeah
that's why I have no I I say that I grew
up I think we should probably talk when
we get back to base later did Rosie here
to exchange since she's out fun by the
way IBM up to you you heard her talking
to herself okay I didn't hear the other
side oh no I'm crazy yeah let's whack
yell walnut she's gonna do her up there
she's just nothing yeah yeah yeah it was
a big day yes nothing around um now
don't trip i explosive here we did so if
there's a welcome breeze from the south
on top of the card a little snake winds
its way out of your out of your satchel
and take
the tip of your nose comfort snake hmm
oh look at him and I go oh really got a
name you what I'm gonna kill you
no I'm turning over a new leaf um shape
city you know I'm just gonna real quick
I've got nothing else to do today while
we're driving I'm going to speak with
animals real quick to the snake I mean
did I go friend
friends did you see the other man that
he's here I heard him you know anything
about him
where was he he was right here here and
snakes over there yeah right here sir
coiled up tastes the air a few times
curls around taste the air over here
there was a man here yeah oh that's true
there was a man here the image of a man
are you certain well I'm tasting and
tasting no maybe there was prey here
well yes yes there was
where's the prey gone we will find more
prey that's true that's very true
any comfort yeah yeah stick is me okay
that's a product yeah thanks hey that's
real good um anyway and then I as I want
for me an ache acquiesce never never
chocolate value see ya when I pull out a
the carcass of a cranium rat that dinar
just pulverizers walking on did you
secure to suspect Oh piss crack open a
cold one good whipping boys there's
something about it that is not right
No and I dangled around a little bit
that make it dance I hear this is a
problem of thing falls back into the
baggage but not a bit okay that's all I
got yeah
you should go back to town yeah let's go
back to read large you can't we got
can't you get one more I don't have it I
don't know it's okay you won okay good
one we did that oh so you but you've
obviously had to go through Westbridge
first sure all right
USA oh yeah Vince you're running 300 you
through you it's been that type of thing
you consider just going hmm just go all
night mm-hmm just probably Mexican I got
any room it was good right now anyone
yeah it's pretty packed up yeah anybody
else you go there you got out of there
first I mean if you're going to get
lodgings to try to be for the people
that's oh yeah you know what honestly
yeah I think that you area manager you
really you pull in you pull in through
the on the long road through the north
entrance into red larch you can see the
just the comforts of this place you can
see the old quarry off to the left you
know you could continue all the way down
the main road take a left at well verse
and you know pull around that corner and
get to the drawing coordinator but
there's another Road to the left almost
immediately once you get into town then
you roll through you see there's a few
children who like try to stay in front
of the cart like too long and then then
they make their day make their room they
make their jump and congratulate each
other off to the edge you kids yeah
exactly
you feel back you see the comforting
drawn and Koryo sign with its small sub
sign of acquisitions incorporated
attached below midday here at the DNC
not a whole lot of activity dancing
Audra is not playing today it's entirely
possible that she was described as
operating sort of the castle circuit
playing for courts and Kings that's
where you know that's where she's at
she's cool like that that's where she's
at you see a tired
prophetess drawn behind the behind the
bar extra tired more tired than normal
no oh just perfect of course you see you
think that she has been at work all day
and there's not really much any there
was there's really anybody else helps
with it what up Rob can I offer to like
take a shift for her she can get some
rest
she she looks at you like she doesn't
understand the language you're talking
about I see well I thought maybe it's
not rude right she is just she's just
trying to process the language she did
she lived by night this is like this is
better she might have a yellow back yeah
I know I just thought I'd offer she
could maybe take out as I said she says
you can start front of the house you got
it ana Mari Mari giving you a room
upstairs so there's there's no pay at
least at least not at first
right what can you cook uh I have a
whole suite of halfling recipes that
have been quit hittin my family like I
can do a mutton stew that'll fire your
socks right off hmm
okay I got I got sandwiches PB and J's
I've ever had little ones in here I know
how to make all kinds of stuff like
Maggie she has acted Spanish Minh my god
he's not even of like cheese nuggets
yeah ice cream sundaes I know how to
make a good one
this guy knows we're talking about can
you do a cinnamon cake oh yes
this is not for that this is nothing to
guess oh absolutely
you should have sooner your birthday I'm
delighted to yeah I put brown sugar and
butter in there in such a way that you
won't you won't think it's it's a
non-magical but it is mmm all right
um she she says okay brings you back I
mean right around the corner so I don't
know if I've described it as well as I
should have
so let me help you the door to the
drawing courier opens and immediately
once you come in the bar is right there
to the left
the the open areas to the right there is
a stove a stage and a painting over the
stove of three children but behind that
bar to the left you get behind the bar
by going past it and in okay behind
there is a fairly simple larder but
anything that you use to cook and bake
is going to be behind that and then
around there's an area that's not
visible from the open in front of the
house am i impressed with the accretor
mom this is this is definitely a country
kitchen tear it's it's well it's well
maintained okay and it's well stocked
but it's not kingly unity that's fine
sanity soon a second question is like
this is a grandma's accoutrement
second question is there a footstool so
I can reach the human-sized implements
in the kitchen you may have to get a
chair for mouth okay I'll do that and
then I'm going to start cooking me a
cinnamon cake big enough for me and all
my best friends to share nice um you see
that she pulls a glass of beer for
herself and then sets another one back
there with you and then she leaves the
back of the bar and then she goes out
and sits down in the front room of her
own hand and raises a glass to the
picture of the three children over the
over the fireplace mm-hmm Rosie singing
what it would sound like probably a very
bawdy song with the words or just like
the hums or is it like a meal deal so
hums and them one like really male in
bed or come out yeah I got like it when
guys are like put a sexy but you realize
no special emphasis no just like no it's
not the only word for to remember is
there any business you would like to
file away I submit the report about our
adventure leaving out any details that
have to do with the male-female symbol
yes even our altercations I just say
unnamed cultist the other thing is I
file an expense report Wow so the five
goals and I also file a a official
report on the payment discrepancy date
you yes why because it turns out head
office the tone ache helped you with
math yeah that's right the snake helping
with now yeah just like on all right you
help me and with my curses um nicely so
so you're up and you're you're up in
your room
yeah our your II where your special is
your yeah the work on your desk sir
absolutely so in your room there is a
documentary of satchel that has scrolls
in it and you know these scrolls quite
well these are scrolls that represent
gainful employment paid work throughout
the realms oh we're delivering indeed
uh-huh do what if you want to tell me
what can I open one out to see what it
says absolutely one of them says in one
month's time at the very top of it in
exquisite script
it says dinar Blitzen is to report to
Scala in one month time and you can see
that the value of this job is one gold
piece so there is a note at the bottom
of it that says one go
peace was the minimum value I could
place on this job and I will expect it
returns to Mesa God there are two more
Scrolls okay inside pass more scroll
cost five gold pieces just get a goddamn
horse over there
okay fair minimum yeah there are two
more Scrolls one scroll yes says I'm
ready crack the vault of the Horde
you've heard of the Horde the Horde is
it a somewhat tawdry novelty Casino
operated by lizards folk in the shape of
a giant dragon's head person 11 oh I
think yeah second the second job says
protect the vote of the Horde ha
so what's the what's the value on both
either both of those are 500 gold apiece
oh we are supporting the party for that
we are definitely a yes oh I pray that
our labor is today has pleased you hang
around for a little bit I'm going to
take full advantage of the potty
facilities when I come back we'll break
some stuff down don't go anywhere
you