permit the enemy the past addresses the
fastest whether you were to make it past
a second and land the question play a
brash and reckless to choose a course in
pollution you saw it was prudent in any
Sepulcher pulchritude will become a
putrid if they're well fed up with the
win no mountain too steep or don't in
too deep systemic bedlam marks up to the
top of the peak of relief maybe they
come like Sharpton to win while I swim
in that learning goal by Carl Barks
through it so center national parks
through it I'll spend a moment a natural
box the post time most of the parks
included save your breath for a cleric
confessor
that there's a lesson to be tiny
professor but if you speak in my
official advice sign on the dotted line
ambition the twice hello I am Tycho
Brahe hey hey okay impacts
I am also omen if it Hereward run of
acquisitions incorporated but today a
chair afford cave or camp and I'm gonna
play a game of Dungeons and Dragons my
friends no one gets them like done our
blitz and splits them oh yeah yeah fun
rhymes with that no no I run that
ruthless toothbrush hit some hmm right
now I'm gonna throw this out here you
tell me if this is acceptable
okay Amy are you ready yeah walnut dong
grass on the prowl for bard ass no a
hard last given men that hard pass that
can we get there okay so I'm brand I
tried is it is that every angle that
there was our passes huh okay yeah I
wanted to really get it all together in
one place for writing my thoughts no
like at the time yes yes
those are really halia that the tangles
um we asked we also have rosy bee
stingers a hundred and twenty
it ain't a laughing thing when that
staff swing honey okay
I'm going to see if I can remember yours
I might not be able to make it up baby I
know if some it's um is it something
books is something about Chris wrist
drought that's it uh uh what's your name
hello Donna equality I don't know I got
it I got it clouds it is um we call this
drow Chris Brown emerging from a mister
out like who's this now well I kept it
going just yet all right hey so we have
been playing Dungeons and Dragons for a
while now let's bring the channel which
is to say the shadow council to whom we
all report let's catch everybody back up
on your way back from the doone-gate in
obviously you made friends with young
Trevor mm-hmm currently not you don't
know exactly what's going on with him
right now but your suggestion was that
he take over operations at the
doone-gate in he went to his filthy cave
to his best rags ostensively to bring
them back up I'm not gonna get framed
for murder when he shows up dead bodies
a cop today not the way that I like to
think of it is that he is that he
operates a place where furries feel most
comfortable you know what I mean like as
a proprietor can you imagine that like I
also I never imagined it I bear the fur
fright 2012 so yes I could actually
imagine that first night there sure was
there I was like Trevor asked
that's right Revere you um on your way
back
obviously you set up a truly bizarre
murder mystery dinner scenario the
governor that this side of the table I
would say enjoyed a very high level on
your way back you left quickly
but on your way back Rosie B singer
suggested that you take their route
somewhat off the beaten path perhaps to
avoid the fuzz as you emerged into this
you got lost - he'll recall and we're
exposed to a truly bizarre phenomenon a
subterranean crypt unlike that which you
had seen indeed one that one that's
unique properties seems to raise
interest at the home office
you saw the or documentaries sheath
performing bizarre tricks of Otto
origami folding itself into birds flying
out you thought you saw some very
strange things it was also during this
time in the base of this chamber that
your friend Chris trout became obsessed
with a round dark gate that bore many
symbols of a round thing in life and in
deep wrong yeah yeah he was sprung but
he was he was like he was like a
mystical Express I got it and I loved it
yeah he was mythically sprung by this
eternal gate and the weird echo it
seemed to have of his focus a chunk of
black material stolen from the Underdark
upon escaping this zone you returned
home to find a skaaland Dragonborn
princess platinum tip-to-tail exquisite
armor brutal retinue they rolled into
the drawn and quarter and took eggy no
but as I believe that the euphemistic
term that we have leveraged the bar an
egg that you had invested quite a lot of
hit points in
um Bobby wait for it yeah and she was
meet I mean let's be honest she she
stole myself five she was me which was
probably the worst thing she did yeah
exactly
but they have still think about it but
they have and then on on the way out
after having succeeded rhetorically she
gives herself her own I five yeah what
does it mean what does it mean who would
do that
you guys look I owned a lot less episode
yeah yeah also didn't call out um teens
became aware yeah oh I really forgot
about that yeah how could happy with
what I was gonna say this is just be
there the left different as soon as you
want me to describe you're barred of
your affection well and I just want
everyone to remember how much of an
[ __ ] oak was oh okay [ __ ] worst
it's actually officially on I updated my
character sheet and it actually says I
saw it under enemies it says oak the
Ranger so I shown it was looking through
everybody wearing their chief I saw the
UN event notes like hell yeah I [ __ ]
got in there
yeah it's that oh yeah he put her okay
so it so to lift up Granger let's roll
back very quickly you also did encounter
team Bellerophon a crew of three
ostensibly aligned with acquisitions
incorporated in some way that has forced
sworn the use of a document sir they
feel like the paperwork just gets in the
way of their initiative and they also
claim to have some kind of a license
twelve our cars license that allows them
to step on local franchises and that's
basically what they did um but obviously
the he is the worst me I'm supposed to
be neutral I guess like I'm supposed to
simulate the universe and then you guys
react to it but I don't like him even
and I make him up to yourself in d-did
he via the clerical stuff that was in
their retinue currently unnamed some who
worships a God of currency what does
that say about them and then we also
have
the bard of that party whose war loot
found four targets with one pull of the
string you'll recall that the bolts were
hiding in plain sight and as hair pins I
don't know if you saw the fan art I did
yeah that was cool
I did it was legendary it was yeah I
think I was very very well pleased but
yes so that should be just about
everything it was a big episode there's
a lot a lot of stuff happened that time
and it got [ __ ] nuts
but yeah yeah so the the Stalin retinue
is now wheeling out you can see the last
of their four carts they rolled in here
deep who knows what they were expecting
but do you say that Prince :
is gone yeah and this is something that
dinar would know Scala is an even more
northerly Dragonborn Enclave who
apparently thinks about other Dragonborn
the way that dinar bliss and thinks
about all other seasons so there's a
apparently an interior hierarchy yeah as
well he's close here on meta mean yeah
you don't get does it um you know no he
doesn't like it no he didn't know who I
was that's now about I thought I was
human probably look that was so okay uh
you're just letting her walk out with
egg what I it's not my kid I'm not a
kidnapper
I came by god no this is my child now
you thought oh that's how I second born
were not about this I'm telling you
that's not yeah look I don't just get to
say like I found this your child it's
mine now I don't wander on the
playgrounds and say my kid my kids that
one no this one yet no I'm gonna say
like you're not a kidnapper business she
much of a mother like how did she get
separated from this precious egg I sent
and I threw it in her face I know this
is do I want the egg yes am I upset it's
gone immensely obviously look at me but
why kids save lady give me your kid I'm
in character now okay you're just gonna
let her walk with eggy I'm just going to
let her leave this is not I'm in
character a parent yeah probably the
mothers not gonna I'm not sure it
alright it's gonna get any kind okay
hey hon I got a dozen others first
that's important I was also present
that's a separate thing game HUD 11
let's kill her
let's go out there right now kill her
and take the egg who's with me
ah she learnt a lot of armor here reins
whipping they're strong northern steeds
into action now hear me out let's kill
her and take her horses till the horses
know that car and adopt her I will be my
great grandson yeah I love this it's a
lot of fun it seems like you're enjoying
yourself yeah great plan yeah if you're
just gonna let him go I think I've been
thinking about it for a week as someone
with a child in real life but I'm like
if someone just claimed my kid and again
that's just playing friend what would
you talk come on ya never let me die
then are would let a child II have no
claim over go I can't I mean I'm in no
condition I'm still like I've got seven
points right like I'm not doing hot from
my adventure yeah an acid cave I'm not
exactly thrilled if you either and after
the cave and a lot of people here uh and
I can't think of a good away all right I
know love can go fine we just you know
who carried it in baby didn't I nerve I
said these things to her I told her
these things yet it drew kisses I did I
kept it alive
I kept it but my healthier than the
Goblin did I could demand a paternity
test they're like way off in the
distance there could barely hear horses
what I could do is what if I got all
right well cigarettes them we need to
recuperate
on our way up before we do that oh yeah
I was going to say you can too rather
what did sits up to you absolutely and
that's a great play especially with your
warlock in tatters all right let's do
okay as you're heading upstairs hmm
you can see as the last cart leaves you
can see proper lookout it may be like a
sigh of relief just as soon as they're
gone she reaches back and gets a glass
and a bottle uncorks the bottle sets the
glass back and then just proceeds to go
to work hmm yeah I got another glass in
there stowed so down there might a want
a partner drinkin tonight so she set the
bottle down and then just pushes it over
to you
nice tip it back no flinching nice
forget konschak that's right oh yeah I
guess my golf I dare you are like that's
not so much more that's much more like
junior high D&amp;D yeah it's like you've
heard about alcohol you have an idea of
what it might be like to drink it you go
yeah exactly and then same one two same
way one might attack the darkness Yeah
right it's in that context um so so you
see where you want to head up dorsey L&amp;X
anywhere uh you could look around yeah
all right look around down in the main
room yes sure well that's that big boy
day oh man what is for combat was just
for comments just for combat skills are
great we could show it off I also showed
off do you enjoy uh oh so twelve we
could say it was perception that I'd be
a seventeen exactly unless I did it
gives a dice can you see their real dice
on the you will die yeah Tyrol no
they're not up but it's here okay I love
it happen so was it twenty that's like
so huzzah
you'd kneel down and look under all the
table graphics let's undo all the tables
was on top of the chairs in the table
hmm staged quick peek behind the bar
onyx is not around here okay
fine enough then I'm going to go
upstairs and do some paperwork because I
realize that
we got 200 goals from the kart quest
assuming there's something at 300 gold
for party security so I was just going
to send back paperwork that said the
premesis is secure and just kind of like
see what happened sure let me go
technically it's very secure
y'all done before we go to bed I'm going
to use minor illusion and I'm going to
make an illusion of eggy on your pillow
huh why we're going to go sulk and sob
yeah and go I'm not happy with you
and I'm very sad so I'm going to bed
yeah but there's a little edgy there
waiting for you and it's and then it's a
heart-wrenching in a way where when you
swing use like this why God why does
every day where you can deal with sleep
without us at all but I need a memory
process he's slightly larger than the
bed difference if you sit down you get
the boots off and it's like you didn't
really just let it happen
you like what you said push it down yeah
actually so please
oh um am i able to I don't want to
address any of these guys they all go to
the room and I'm just lingering and
looking up over my focus am I able to
remember and jot down what those other
figures were around that around that
ring on that gate but there's one that
you remember oh I assumed I'd be nearly
done son done yeah bot we set up on
still store what is that looks like
Chanel Chanel yeah yeah that's beautiful
all right to the diner door should we
put it in one of the dice boxes though
that it'd be a close up of it yeah yeah
seriously you want yeah you want to
throw it in here so I can get a look at
this oh they have oh so the audience can
follow - no I've got there you go
it also looks like one of those like
those turtle tattoos you can get we all
know what it looks like yeah or an abaya
has a little bit so sure two moons
perhaps yes ok whispering hi
ok candy in it enough but yeah I mean
there were eight total right but many of
them you know shifted and swayed okay
you think this is one you could
reproduce but you don't have any
of what it is they didn't like the other
one where you had to focus and then in
the presence of the gate you knew as
though you'd always known it but this is
this is not like that you can it's a
glyph it's without a condom but if you
know it does you don't know what it
signifies yeah okay
all you know is where it's you know
there is near something that's important
to you right okay I will then also
retire good idea
I'm going the game good okay I sweep I'm
going to sleep cuddled up with my new
staff nice staff and master because you
told me that I had to take a long rest
with it I'm going to understand that I'm
looking at three short really a short
rep I would be one graph is be even
better yeah yeah yeah it's like I mean
that's that's yeah that's the longest
arrest if you have this kill yourself in
it yeah there you go to Union Building
now that you've had a long rest and you
load them into a crossbow which I have
now I have a hand Cross árboles yeah
yeah yeah oh yeah I grabbed a bunch of
crossbows but I planted them all around
there yeah absolutely so you are you are
spending time with neither that level of
what's better master sure sure so it's
your intention to to is really yes it's
six star I'm meditating on six start
thinking about her what her ascension to
master maybe then maybe you as you drift
off to sleep you find yourself in a
clearing in a bamboo forest there's a
cool breeze seems to be mid-afternoon
the harshest of the of the Sun is sort
of kept at bay by the waving stalks
around you you stand there with the
staff of the master and you see before
you three stools and there is someone
seated on each of the three stools and
they each have the staff of the master
but each of them has a slightly
different version
so that the person on the far right has
three stripes as you know it the one in
the middle has two stripes and the one
on the left has a single stripe red
stripe and you can see you can see
children and adults sort of coming in
through forest paths to observe
something they see if they seem to know
why they're here okay today are they
aware of me or am I just absolutely do
you are you are standing where a student
would okay in this configuration and
does my training allow me to understand
this configuration
oh yeah ritual that I know you have you
have almost certainly been in stools
like this teaching younger inherence of
the way of shadow okay so it seems like
I'm reliving someone else's experience
of taking the staff so I'm going to go
to emotions I'm just going to play along
I'm going to do do everything that I did
in my rituals and that I've seen however
many dozens of students do in theirs go
through go through the motions and just
kind of like see where this takes me
okay the person on the far right is a
halfling woman not quite at your August
age but not young and you can tell that
she is sort of vibrating in her seat and
she doesn't have the calm patience of
her fellows on the stage that sits
before you and she throws herself to her
feet and stamps the staff of the master
against the wood planks of their
platform and the man in the center says
I would like to apologize for master
Albert she's only 300 years old
apology accepted
faster yeah seed at that accepting an
apology on behalf of someone else does
not Robert doesn't does not endear this
master mm-hmm to you and there's a jump
off of the platform down immediately in
front of you and she says and you can
tell so on your onion you can even look
at your staff very quickly six star over
and rook and so you can guess out of
that how it goes okay and you're being
assessed like a fish at a market okay
and then just full examination idly
twirling the staff that you've just now
come in contact with and master rook
says do you think that your shadow path
can compare with the way of the open
fist I absolutely know it can but that's
not the point of the monk paths master
monk path exists for us all to better
the world to seek to better ourselves to
understand things not to compete with
each other master six are less like but
keeps it cool like a pain like this is
pure entertainment this is like their
television equivalent I think they're
having a super good time
some I what makes you think rosy bee
stinger that you can master this staff
to be perfectly honest I don't know
anything about this staff but what I do
know is that my dedication to the way of
the shadow is unquestionable I have been
studying this for
20 years of my life I've taught fellow
students I've researched I've been in
some of the finest libraries in the
world this is what I was born for
there's no one better suited to take up
a staff like this than me roll
initiative
Oh nein nein the staff staff of the
master comes down huh and interests in a
split second you bring it up with one
hand just in an effort to glance the
blow-off right it comes in you get both
of your hands on the staff of the master
okay
you can you can tell already that you
know more about it than you did before
you know it's it's it's a it's supreme
craftsmanship but there's definitely
something else to it and as you moved it
up to block it it seemed to leave a
trail almost through space and it's your
turn okay if you die in a dream you're
done in real life I know so that's true
so still in the first dream level though
okay Roger
I'm going to I'm going to if they're
doubting my devotion to the way the
shadow let's throw some [ __ ] shadow
at them I'm going to leave a singer I'm
going to whisper something crazy spooky
sounding and I'm going to cat hey Lee
yeah I'm gonna cast darkness on myself
if you want to see some shadow here's
some [ __ ] shadow for you dr.
dark yeah yeah
darkness so darkness is a 15 foot radius
mm-hmm
it is a
it can't be seen through even with dark
vision non-magical light cannot be
illuminate it mm-hmm not right so you
basically are just in the middle of this
horrible darkness but you're not able to
see opponents either crack cracks yeah
okay gonna half-ass yeah yes yeah no
perfect yeah yeah no I get it it's a
dream I really do you going to work out
yeah just that's how it's going to apply
away yeah Sora Belgian nice
so there is a murmur from the crowd at
this response mhm and you can you can
sense and hear of the staff of the
master cutting through the marble orb
and it just comes off of you like an egg
it splits clean pass and fall apart now
it's your turn okay welcome to dream
combat yeah this is pretty tight wait
okay so tell me there's a marble orb
around me I know basically the staff the
master comes down and sliced through the
darkness oh this is peeled away okay you
test the darkness yes literally attack
we are literally activate off on that C
team we literally attack the darkness
and it stays attacks yeah yeah okay okay
it's not the same um I'm going to use uh
hold on hold on hold on hold on I can
I'm going to do step of the wind mmm
which costs me a key points it does and
allows me to either disengage or - as
bonus action okay so in addition to
moving although I can't move because
we're in comments so I'm going to
disengage as a bonus action as I try to
pivot around in order to give myself
advantage on my next attack Oh to peel
around yeah yeah I like that yeah let me
see it
I'm down this didn't kind of rule you
want I want to see some acrobatics okay
oh yeah let's make let's make this look
right oh wait [ __ ]
you yeah that's real good so it splits
off the staff the master sweeping down
for you again but you perfectly pivot
and pirouette out of the side this the
staff is only one of master rooks
capabilities here in this context I am
wondering how you feel about if 14 AC
doesn't hit all right that is it Swift
sweeps right by you you can hear it sort
of whisper you can infect as you see it
come by you can see that at that speed I
mean it's almost like it's just
spreading through the air like it seems
two or three times as long as it should
a question do I have access to my
regular inventory or am i an inception
stream of guns yeah yeah so I have one
of the things that I have my inventory
is a check piece that is a rook and I
don't know if that is relevant it seems
like the kind of things that might be
yes yeah just like I've spin it and they
don't learn join oh yeah um is it do I
have access to the stuff in my in my
inventory right now reach for it I'm
gonna [ __ ] reach in there whip it out
and it's probably girl looks like an
idiot but whatever I'm 120 years old and
give a [ __ ] I'm like master rook does
this mean anything to you no I'm just
come on forget it you don't you can look
I just thought into it you have
advantage yeah and you're like that
that's why I have advantage I'm taking
mercy I'm asking yeah you can get behind
and Kalka crosses the ropes
in the most tradition is about avoiding
combat where possible yeah this is
awesome so I have the advantage I could
stick my core stuff right up his butt
but I'm I'm gonna ask you a question a
little bit
story-wise it's awesome thank you thanks
very much he's it's like a imagine like
a tea ball type situation just
sweeps the staff straight across the
brook and goes my rook that's rude yeah
yeah alright fine so I try it
goodbye rook on the cross that off yeah
just very good dream yes dream on yeah
right dream work and then cos she's like
sorry I've got three good berries
oh well you've got a jar idols crab dad
open see what happened dream bigger yeah
you like a beluga whale and he's got
work for this so he's gonna he's gonna
swing on you I guess though he is uh-uh
no it's on a single foot he leans back
and then pokes out with the rod but he
is not able to do anything with an ACO 7
ok great so again I do feel like this is
some kind of my brain is feeling that
this is a trial so I'm just using all of
my [ __ ] way of shadow moves I'm using
next is going to be patient defense
which means that all tax against we have
disadvantage I mean and I will and
that's another key point right it is and
I'm going to continue to I'm going to
try to strike to disarm him I don't have
disarming strike but I do kind of want
to strike at his hand more than to cause
harm to his oh yes I do that that'll
India 16 good and you'll get there tip
that is the that is the hand a cease
yeah yeah little thingies break them off
to snap them yeah give me some things
can just roll the damage so that I know
move that's a lot of damage that's of
damage I'm 17 I was like yeah I roll out
that still has damage 12 no that's mine
don't touch it all 12 fingers are broken
so you see strike the hand I'll blow and
V the stab you see the staff like he
loses grip on it and it flies you know
up a couple feet and then while it is in
the
he takes this opportunity to unload
Martley strikes how I say bow I have
commit to flex missile and grab the
stuff I think that that is described I
think that the flick missiles is used
nice visit Pat no is me I never know
your forever the you know yes the the
staff is was not a directed at you as
right away I attended but now I think I
finally have something going here
so an AC of 17 battled hit okay now
three points of damage and I need you to
succeed on a DC 13 dexterity saving
through AIA 17 absolutely but you can
you can tell that a person without your
training on that craggy Peaks would be
flat on the ground as a result of this
strike and indeed master Brook seems a
little surprised that that was not the
result there may be something to this
shadow passing you know what I mean it's
tight as hell yeah I say I told you it's
tight
all right here so while the staff is
still in the air let's see what you got
okay I want to leap up and grab it yeah
your double stuff [ __ ] yes I am alright
have you met me yeah actually here let's
try some doesn't be a good acrobatic
snatch and then he called me in college
that's 11 I got it okay looking for 10
okay um so you now you have both staves
yeah do with her neck you hold one in
your mouth high like one piece of player
as you grab the other staff and set it
down you feel a spray on your face and
in a moment you are on a swaying bridge
in front of a rushing waterfall with a
full moon hung in the sky this ripe
okay Wow to the Moray all right I didn't
learn hits äj--
right right around here I got to save uh
can I do a perception see if I can
intuit anyone nearby anything in wisdom
regularly yeah it's not super hard okay
you can see master rook okay walking out
along the bridge toward you okay I'm not
going to take any kind of aggressive
stance against him no you get on that
one yes or cut off the bread here on the
strike you have to pull out this vine
yeah that's the only way that's not
gonna and that's how long before only
witnesses in Russia yes yes the Russian
waterfall I want to I'm going to shout
at him across the the din of the
waterfall this it doesn't have to be
this way
this is chosen was I um I I don't want
to fight you our two paths can coexist
peacefully and in fact enhance one
other's abilities don't come at me I
will [ __ ] you up Rome at me serious he
is continue to come at you he says you
understand why the trial by combat is
necessary of course but remind me
refresh me on it obviously but do you
know for sure for the sake of X to the
gene-specific you love it you have an
artifact you have evidence of our paths
ancient wisdom it belongs inside our
traditions no one else can have it I had
to be tested and how did I do
we'll see oh it's not over okay
he holds his hand out for his staff I
toss it
right off the birds the moon [ __ ]
duck in the moon like I'll never get an
idea it's like Waco
yeah there's no passing for that he he
says like this and adopts of stance that
you know practice stance with the staff
and sort of beckons you to respond okay
so you see him enter a practice kata and
then the deeper he gets into it it the
staff is like a rotor like it ceases to
be it ceases to be visible as much as
coherent stick right um and no more
prequel references y'all so exactly now
it's nasty um and he says he says trust
me so he brings that he brings it into
contact with you you don't feel pain
it's almost like a it's almost like
you're observing it as a third party hmm
you can see what it represents and when
it is in this state when the staff is in
this state it's almost hypnotic and when
it comes into contact with you he enters
into a sequence of punches a sequence of
martial blows that have an intensity
that you want okay this you want it like
you see it if you saw it on the shelf
give me the punches if you sit on the
shelf and so and so he connects two
times and then goes back and then you
can tell that this is the this is the
this is the student stance and he has
allowed you to enter the master stance
so come after yes I'm gonna do it
everything he just did right Meerut Jack
hmm wait I have lucky I'm lucky your
love is a lie rural a natural one who
that's 15 seconds okay in this because
we're he's not really trying to get you
so as you as you lash out it's almost
like a whip like how flexible this this
rod is Ennis after you connect here
after any punch attack that you do is a
d8 instead of a d6 that's the best
education I think that's in addition to
the +1 attack +1 damage oh my god so
just I'm not going to I'm going to say
d8 it sounds great but it was one d4
before so now now it's really it's
really going well now it's worth now
it's really doing at all Oh guys yes
yeah yeah it's just it's cute and as
these two as these two punches connect
with him you're back in the first place
cool breeze and you see a fourth seat on
the platform and that is when you wake
up oh you guys like the I'm three years
old Alec Colson sorry yeah yeah human is
supposed to be your hug you spend a
short round we all wake up and wander
out into the main area if you like hi
the weirdest dream dan which is trying
to eat me oh my gosh okay
in fact what draws you what draws you
out of slumber cuz I sound almost like a
like a handbell like em okay good con
nice if it hasn't been a long rest
oh yeah yeah you guys you guys are good
and you're you're you're good Chris okay
health-wise three days later not not any
other way but help help only yes
specifically as relates to HP yeah
and that ring that ring is coming from
that central room that adjoins all core
of the right okay
I look at my staff and I pick it up and
it's lighter that was before my myrrh
hmm I bet well loved smell good
yeah so this is this actually going to
you all you all here in the morning me
grabbing my stuff yeah oh my god
everybody knows about the rest even uh
we do not make eye contact duck in mind
away they don't animate that they get
out how do we get over all new
characters as soon as I ever Mel like it
gets like it something like well I'm not
just a little tingling line but I guess
soon as I hear like hey well it's just
like immediately in the room like yes
what yes I'm ready like it was like a
quill so behind her hair and like I was
like all over her hand like this is like
this is morning walnut yeah well hasn't
had a chance to get stoic it is it's
like from six to seven it's just party
time yeah and if you and if you look in
the back behind her is a book and it
says documentary for dummies yes I'm
doing it's like Garfield nightshirt yeah
exactly yeah she just went working all
night probably yeah well I mean she only
sleeps for some of the hour all right
it's just it was meditate realm we're
going to do like play her all no damage
switch safety need there's nothing to my
character I don't think she'd sleep I
don't know I just
you can I need it just really a lie and
a real life yeah yeah Rosie sleeps right
now to risk so our role to see he
survives yeah
hey that's aegis Mario look so is any
not long a long night yeah yeah well
that's cool is it well that's deeply
respectively of my advanced age sure so
you you pushed open the yes what I see
you push open the door
you see a you see a man of
about six feet hmm balled up head a
blue-and-white tavern draped over the
front shining chainmail underneath mace
at the side hmm
uh he doesn't seem that he doesn't
notice your approach um so then I
immediately very quietly close the door
slink back into my room and start like
rinsing everything off and like getting
my arm like my armor on and then uh last
look before I go in the mirror I just
make sure everything's okay and I look
at my little a kink seal and I just
shine it up real good like when when
Gordon Ramsay visits the dorms and
health care so you come out and Rosie is
like she's just your biggest fan she is
such she loved you so much she's so into
that well here she comes now
we're just talking about you all 'not
you hear the sound of like what a cat
sounds like before they're about to do
our hair ball form
that's a breast and then so we know who
this is right it's entirely possible
yeah oh I think I know you know you
wouldn't move it indirectly I guess oh
yeah I wander out like fun just
disheveled
it miserable mobiles are [ __ ] up
sweatshirt on and like those sad sad in
mopey okay this is as soon as the fourth
person enters the room he says I'm home
and run CEO of acquisitions incorporated
I don't know how long it would address
him um however you would like yeah okay
you get a jump on you guys you're as
your dinner yeah I say gentlemen or
ketosis omen I remember you I don't know
though if you are seeing this illusion
it is because you have
filed the initial dungeon assessment
templates in such a way as to trigger
initiative seat yes I did do that right
in front of it he knows he knows an exam
fee and assistance like yes the paper
you have identified it's only part of a
massive subterranean creature I call the
wandering crypt this beast and I have
history
it ranges the destron valley devouring
lives the defense's within to their
tunes to the power of its prey if I were
to enter this haunted place it would not
endure me and I would be destroyed
instantly your inexperience is
ironically your only chance of success
you are to prepare to the best of your
ability and return to the Crypt
posthaste
in the meantime new supplies will be
sent to the drowning courier within the
week time war a guide you I like that
like when you thought it with omen like
while I got all flustered and then once
it was revealed it wasn't him then it
was like oh then I can talk to us yeah
oh you got a break now so now I can and
now I found my boy telephone okay yeah
after I guess after like it flickers out
or whatever in a puff of green flame
okay and then I want us to says does
like one of these and she's like okay of
course in turn goes well y'all heard the
man every time she's get yeah you know
she was just totally focused now like
omen told me yeah I don't know if you
heard but omen told me specifically
direct orders like that we have to
prepare for something called the
wandering crypt yeah so of course it is
sweetheart
we still need to maybe talk about what
happened left her in there um you know
that's actually really good yeah we do
quietly yeah I was I was uh you see my
demeanor has gone from when we all
entered the room I wouldn't make eye
contact with anybody even to my shame
shame and my negative feelings about
what went down and that really well is
this something even thinking about oh
yeah all night of how to yet because
it's like you know I'm going to come
stuff out a little bit like how do I
justify like they've seen some some Dark
Gods business
go on around cos risk at what point of
my liabilities like you know what we
could do fine without you game one get
hunched and we're good
you're two for two on betraying us is
thank you thanks right true it now that
I've heard this I am involving oh
because this is this is why I am the way
that I am if he's doing I was much
closer on my research on life studies on
my in my face to my chosen patron and it
all it took was one round of assisting
Ullman drawn to recover the soul of one
of his sisters and I've lost contact
with that which I have professed myself
to so are you turning into a villain to
him maybe there's a heel turn yeah so
you're not an omen drones fan you got at
this point yes okay
everything that's gone wrong in my life
happened since my employment with the
home office and I'm here because I had
no other option have I told you that I
don't even know how I can be in this
town well I mean that's a huge question
so like what do they like in person and
like aren't I great just like let's go
down the list started owning because she
was great too not as good so you think a
lot about what the Goblin told us oh
forgotten oh yeah pennies ago which
aligns with your current attitude even a
stopped goblin is correct twice a day
later today yeah wow that is here's our
that is not so pretty stop Goblin I ate
the day after go so yeah I'm I'm really
distrustful and I will I will share with
the party what
was given to me what I found on my
person that first day in the alley and
outside of the drona and courtier is a
note apparently in my own hand that I
wrote myself that reads I cannot
I must not I will not what
and this coin
someone threw at me behind your ear what
could that mean
right now I'm interpreting it to me
trust this man again
and we are going to be fed to this to
this creature it's you're my only my
only interest here is that it seems to
be bound up with with my chosen faith
you know but other than that no could
have been a lot more useful if you just
wrote my almonds flat I'd ever seen yeah
so yet it has been filmed right I should
have done it I never know when they can
fire yeah a little more specificity I
didn't do it yeah you're very and drop
my family holiday or their soul is too
often it up I think it was important
Yeah right there so my allergies there's
been a lot of strange happening since
the four of us found each other it was
your whole thing just everything yeah
your whole thing hmm Rosie you seemed
particularly concerned about the Stars
the other night don't get me started
yeah don't get me started I get it I
don't enjoy that the words I get the
point
I'm a straight shooter it's true you
lost the love of your life awesome I
ducked at a kid and then lost it I marry
a door but about that came close that's
so clear I meant yeah everything I love
to take away from me he also found that
I mean we also found an entire cart that
was a potentially personal dark magic
we'll fill the personal dark magic wand
that's right we haven't really talked
about what first of all who what not
your Percival no no a different first of
all don't I probably I remind I who are
your the viewing audience
oh I don't either what and so it's a
woman of course knows everything about
acquisitions incorporated right um God
day or sex market right yeah the FX
moment because jesus essa' them well she
says personal dark magic
did your dark branch they see who is a
brother to jim dark magic who is a
member of durant enterprises who is run
by omens sister a very shady group
although now i calls everything into
question because who is the shadiest
iran we don't know yeah not our on
obviously I don't our drawn being Roman
you know I'd be a real slight bring it
yeah yeah yeah I don't know Christian
said not my drawn I got I got my dress
and then at one was like kind of like
look she's like well I'm so are when the
documents I was writing could see us and
where we were when we were in the room
actually I didn't explain that to anyone
and then I go well here's the thing when
I was filling out one of my forms and
it's very technical and even really
understand it but it started writing
back to me instructions that we should
leave the room that we were in and so
I'm just kind of concerned about all
this negative um and talk like maybe
they can hear us
they're watching us sleep wait well
there's no believe someone from head
office yes the head office sorry
yeah told you to leave an omen cool
enough to go back
what does it seem weird to you um um now
it seems weird that you say it out loud
didn't seem weird last night and I've so
much paperwork nice laughing we're
losing weird last night no now this does
seem strange but who sign it which of
those which of those of those creeks oh
and I of course I have a copy of it and
the name of the person from the offices
secretary Justin Secretariat secretary
and Secretariat yes
sorry Harriet the horse yeah yes it just
said the RFS secretary in' the secretary
in' but I have no knowledge as to who
that would be
where'd you know so much it's true I do
everything someone could know and then I
go maybe I haven't gotten to that part
of the book I mean maybe I just haven't
found it in my document yeah I love you
yeah but what what are we doing now
we can see if there's been a delivery of
more quests but it seems like we've been
casted there's figuring out I feel as if
find a chicken mmm
yeah let's do some shed drilling looks
good I don't need a family I don't want
to get you in that room again yeah yeah
I think maybe prophetess might know more
precise to problem detect process um let
school have talked to prophet as and ask
how many other franchises there were
here in the red large maybe I can adopt
something else I got to find another old
voice I mean get a chicken egg carrying
around this meg can we uh can we go
downstairs to see the cat when I got out
there roll the rope to you this I don't
see the cat no honestly didn't go into
it later but onyx collection in your
room how many things watch you sleep
yeah a lot yeah it's like they're more
different letter s a cat can't sleep
unless 22 little things which are honest
was in my room that's right
okay so fight so I open the door he's
still in there finish sleeping um okay
well well I guess everybody's getting
ready I want to go up top onyx and I use
them
Kiki animals yes you can sleep with
animals and I go onyx
oh great merciful onyx wake up I've
surprise for you just rolls from but
this just I stood at this half open with
a side that right that little to slip
and then needing the paws and making
biscuits it and then right over on
to the back and the pause go up and it
says this place is for rubs yeah all I
could yes of course I want to give some
good scratches oh that's a trap and then
and then she says a she look she looks
down on us and she goes I onyx I know
that I owe you a favor because you you
did me a great many solids as they say
yeah and so then I say the chicken I say
yes an entire chicken and I say you can
only choose one and then walnut throws
of your hands and she goes but have your
pan and then is or friend always like if
you'd like Oh have to say bye to you
like my voice free oh yeah exactly
oh my god this is so mad look this is
what it shows a little bit a priority
but I'm a beggar is like delighted yeah
I look like a person I go yeah it's like
it's like like do we all get together
they're overflowing into the Ziller ear
and I know tea chicken I say I gravity
the kids it's their most of the size of
me very happy that it is chin dude get
away from me like monkeys yeah yeah have
a big brown feel upset yeah 99 yeah this
is this is yeah this is club dance a
real cluckfest you've seen the you've
seen the posters there's a lot of
chicken iconography don't worry for an
obvious reason
poultry themed event you know it's not
weird yeah in seconds the room is
transformed into like what you must
imagine a pillow factory must look like
what was it I mean it's it's like it's
just like jumping from chicken - chicken
like minute those red midair twists
again again it's it's on it's on ice
basically and then walleye just says as
she's summing them she goes uh welcome
to all of you and sorry - one of you
yes chickens chickens are running their
asses out chickens are running out into
the hall running down into the common
room Indira yeah no alien egg though yes
imagine like a know like a liquid like a
flow like a river of chicken oh I don't
have to imagine it I know it's real
I create I don't know whether yeah
exactly you see engineers of the chicken
train hoo-ha oh just bouncing from
chicken - chicken I mean this is
something you're gonna have to manage
okay great um so then murder it well I
mean it's just like giving them test
bites that's not gonna do much if I
married a chicken no I was not
cats are can you don't know what Jerry
has planned baby's gonna be living it's
our custom address our cats woman yet
you have to stop um okay then uh and I
said on expensive ate because I see that
uh she's got a little bit of blood left
going on unique and I say um I say all
right your honor bound take only one but
you may take it in full pick the one you
want now before I send them away all
right just the jaw just clamp on a plump
red hand mm-hmm and then it's like nna I
mean oh the flip and then the neck is no
longer an assault object and well like
us this is the strangest wedding I've
ever seen and I've seen a lot of em less
violent weddings so everything's so
beautiful veil yeah yeah yeah Birds a
couple birds have jumped up on the
windowsill and or out on the roof mmm
okay so then I immediately now like
trying to keep up the whole thing we're
certainly seeing all the chickens on
excessive chicken and I go I'm thinking
like now there's a lot of how does a lot
of chickens in here you know I had a
whole plan for this you have to cast for
Danny yes Ellen boxes yeah
get really foxes summons bears I don't
want to what he talks is becoming more
animal keep escalating what it bears
gorilla headline you have five rounds
like what do you do perhaps way too many
chickens um okay so now tentacles huh
now you go to sending us into the
various laws that clipped to infinitive
yeah the only thing I could leave them
if this is the decision-making on yeah
whoops well um so anyway now I was gonna
look very officially in so Julie like as
she does like uh sure all the chickens
out like okay you've had your fun
oh go on yeah go on get yeah they're
down there they're hopping they're
hopping all around they're trying to
jump up on tables hmm I mean the places
people are lifting their place chickens
are going beneath like it said it's a
risen authentically ridiculous scene
we've concocted here well I sure did not
pick anything that would help me get rid
of them I kind of done it outside
that could've died out okay could I
could have done a lot of things yeah
it's kind of a [ __ ] it it's kind
of a collective I'm winning so actually
no I want to walk up to proffer
like nothing is going on yeah yeah this
brow is frood like you feel like you're
like on the precipice of hearing mom
voice and I eminent and I why I just
head it off at the past by going we saw
your son really we did he would up he
was in our room question though if he a
chicken because so it's like that Lena
parts of their being movie when that
when they've got us and just turned into
a pile of crabs yeah all my was there
and then he just was chicken only did he
say spread out on the floor omen turned
into the chicken that's actually
possible
we saw omen he was in our room upstairs
an illusion of him and then suddenly
they were check yes something happened
and then they were chickens yes and she
says
he has a wizard friend hmm
the less the less spoken of about him
the better he's responsible for this
trick they played on my door
yes well familiar with that trick yeah I
I told them very specifically that that
was not an acceptable usage of the
drowning courtier
well it certainly gave us the wrong
impression of the establishment at first
yeah it's been a problem in the past and
now look what he's done to your actual
establishment um she she she shakes her
head because it holds open the door so
what's up makes a sound in her throat
mm-hmm can we get that something yeah
sure hmm and chickens um like a moth to
flame on her mouth all right now no make
it my favorite is a highway to the
danger zone goodbye Kenny Loggins and
like it just right in the mouth yeah but
if any one of them just jumps and flaps
once yeah into the mouth it just happens
for 15 minutes no no that arising none
of that happens this is the bore episode
oh they're they're running out there's
like just one there's one extra one oh
that has found a place beneath the table
that it seems to like but onyx appears
at the head of the stairs and begins to
step down the stairs and while I go back
I said one what are you growing chickens
now yeah they go I know it's a principle
of the deal the art of three chickens
yes look I don't care about chicken I
want score rhetorical point yes
absolutely so that's that's the sir
that's the scene is it is willing to
abide by the terms of this agreement if
only because it thinks that being around
you will almost certainly result in
additional birds well now it knows what
I can do yes you can active on the bird
this big it at any
yeah I just whispered think about what I
could do with my yes gross yeah
kiddie pool are those a thousand mice in
your pocket here's everything I think
that I think onyx would be happy to see
you um so so in the situation so she
says is there anything else upstairs
that I need to know about the wandering
crypt yeah so we were done uh she she
shakes her head like that makes you can
see her jaw set in her mouth
as soon as as soon as you mentioned this
crypt what do you know about it this is
a story all about how my life lovely I
got I'm just living that I have been
made to endure at great pain virtually
all of omens life and I want to
apologize as his mother that he has
gotten you wrapped up in this now too
every now and then he centers a
franchise here
he makes me host it and for what the
last group were the rudest most
inconsiderate young people I have ever
had the displeasure of hosting do you
happen to remember the names of any of
how could I forget
hmm one of them doesn't even have a last
name I'm sure he has one hmm but he goes
exclusively by oak one like cringes yes
uh uh yes yeah he has a him he has a
friend a cleric no credit to his order
hmm named Phoenix and
and I love it this is kind of where you
increase of Joaquin - yeah well it's the
full meal deal I gave it and somehow
through no fault of her own I'm ready
a student of my wife got bungled up in
their operation Bramall ooh yay
and when they and when they and Benes
are all one word Brahma bull you keep -
you ski oh yeah and when they came that
usually they have usually they have for
when they're posted here but I never met
the fourth hmm and they were here for
years
pudding never finding what almond said
them to find until eventually they were
moved on to other tasks near manage that
they never found it and he could not
accept it he could not accept that this
script was not real
last night we practically tripped into
one of its premiere mouths do you
another list do you know how many crits
there are on Toro yes 10 have a good you
entered a crypt you did not find did he
tell you why he wants you to find the
wandering crypt no only that we were to
prepare immediately to do so when omen
was very young his sister auspicious
entered a crypt like this and never
returned he could never make peace with
it and he has spent his life trying to
find something that doesn't exist
because he can't accept what I've
accepted which is that auspicious is
dead a real fox mulder vibe to it hmm
I want to believe first you have some
somewhere and I'm seeking is what we
happen upon in where we were last night
I don't know why that would trigger omen
to send a message to us now but I'm
assuming that we got closer than
Bellerophon did you need to be very
careful the place he is asking you to
find is not real but that doesn't mean
that you aren't an incredible danger
trying to make this happen
there's going to come a point where your
lives are on the line for this thing
he's chosen to believe and that will be
a very important point of decision for
you
now wait the thing you are looking for
the thing that you have been searching
for just happened to appear in a crypt
we like stumbled into doesn't that
strike you as odd well the crypt emerge
from the ground when I was running along
next to you right it erupted from the
earth right but what was it odd that
this secret crypt
right next to town where omen probably
has lived for some time hmm just like
exploded out and had the exact thing
that Catrice was looking for well didn't
they drop you off here for a reason I'm
assuming yeah write letters to yourself
maybe this thing has a taste for
drawings no maybe I'm just saying it's
possible that this creature is able to
manifest our deepest desires the things
that we're looking for the most in order
to lure us deeper into it go it is if
it's real it's real really not it seemed
very real lesson it is in as much as our
as our as our work here coincides with
the same time seeking hmm I have no
reason not to follow but that's what I'm
doing before we do anything resembling
going back in that crypt I need to put
some [ __ ] protection up on your crazy
ass because we could you almost got us
all killed
we're not going back in there until I
know that your God is not going to make
you insane again or we could just all
get in writing that if this happens
again that we just really didn't leave
em in there and I think that we're all
Baconator yeah yeah I Jenni was gonna do
it yeah when we were in the crypt itself
sure like do you want to be on a team
with us I can use a lot I need to be
because I don't want that's why I had
last night to happen yes I would rather
that we had established some sort of a
kill switch urn and I usually whatever
the in world equivalent of kill switches
no is of the a team when they had used
to give me a block as a blessing milk
for you on a plane because he was scared
to fly yeah we needed that device for me
yeah so that has a bit of trouble
because you can cannot give a hook to
Miss Lee so we can - yeah carry you
around as a liability that may betray us
has any of you related in
tail of Baracus yes do you know a
hypnotist or someone who might be able
to cast a spell on my friend here
I'll make him take use of chicken to
make him think he's a chicken or similar
just something something that we will be
able to shut him down at any moment if
things get off the hook yeah you're
talking to prophet I talked about
process yeah none of us have that
ability lists anything way to tax him or
something somebody made me forget before
he weighs 90 pounds dripping wet yeah
you'd be surprised
mm-hmm how much damage this dude can do
yeah he's very he's hiding a lot of
tentacles willful yeah a lot of
tentacles over there yeah I wouldn't
think so
you're like a puffer fish here's him
this and I hope you might focus up this
don't point anything it is st. basil
chicken it takes years but I guess it's
like every second and then but I've been
dirt nope nope no this has has given me
agency before this is protected me
before I was in an alley here in red
large if I can if I can seek it and find
it again if I believe it has the power
to protect all of us sure but in the
meantime protect us from what itself
yeah it from where I'm gonna tell we're
talking about two different things
okay okay yeah okay so pops up
understand we got my god was nice guy
good guy
okay okay I'll place a good and then
this tooth one that's not good I'm not
fitting me it doesn't like this mean I
don't understand why yet okay but if I
can recover what I used to have I'm I've
been clear I have not been troubled by
this mouth God until now that the lower
level okay no okay I will not allow that
I have very hard I am just clear so you
took prep promises what is it you what
is it you want to happen and I can try
to make it hum I feel like it's my
responsibility now to protect you from
my son okay
I sensed it somewhere in the world
grievous is shouting
squirrel it's what I just heard from Pat
so I thought about that for a second
and then I think the thing that we want
is to be able to say some kind of
command word cacao cacao because that
won't come up and I think Black Widow
and Hulk or she's like some again real
oh yeah yeah yeah
what are you hear out there nothing but
the rain I want it I want some some code
that will just put you to sleep yeah
it's good idea you're a hundred percent
comfortable with us having that kind of
power would be great Kevin before yeah
that's that's your you're good you're
like Commodus want me to fry might have
installed one before while you're
talking to properly like the papers are
Express and I'm I can just hear you yes
indeed I've won with this chemical
attack layout yes yes
each tentacle has a pen so here's again
you hand me the forms and it's being
signed as you remove the finger not is
normal to Scots I love you know how we
have gross friend did yes
she says watch the bar I go okay what we
gonna do
she she had the fires heavy opens the
door goes inside you hear something
creak and then she emerges and comes
downstairs with a slightly worried look
on her face she says we had a wizard in
our company who was very useful
90% of the time must be nice what's this
[ __ ] just to say it's the same thing he
should add some flavor she gives you two
necklaces nice uh and she says hold this
hold this necklace okay right
she takes the other one and
she cinches it and the other necklace
cinches oh do it again
she unseen chah's it and it loosens up
ah men she cinches it again yes and she
says it's up to him if he wants to wear
it strangle him come on boy yeah any
idea I have a peach lord similar Frank
West for the unknowable but in times of
Solitude at times so we could just
garage him at any point about what this
will do for us giving done do it for a
long time okay
just long enough it's just long enough
where that right around the carotid
artery follows up on Titan does it does
auto-erotic asphyxiation existence you
know yes I'm really glad Colorado
erotica cigar is one of the base classes
like yeah I was going to dip into it
it's rogue yeah I wanted a I like about
our level up anyway you want to bowling
it up you want to multi class second yes
that is the deficit okay so guys can i
yeah you you I don't think I have it
yeah I currently have the extra necklace
all right friendship bracelet hahaha
so do I should I wear it or do I just
need to hold it I would not wear it
Gaia's goes away tonight and I tie tight
it a little bit yeah one tighten yeah it
seems like we're going to go before the
slave Comicon is fun right hey mr.
president oh yeah yeah yeah yeah I
really so I feel this is in character
obviously not really Kate but I'm kind
of into it like I'm like oh there's like
a BDSM elements do it cool like I'm just
like yeah I got that warlock yeah yeah
yeah it's the pet play episode sorry
Scotty for Athena don't listen I got my
own because you wanted it cuz this this
thing is just like this this vessel is
just meet any Alex yeah which is like
plays right in the river yet it's the
whole universe not even a legit setting
to enjoy what existed
get ready for those laminated gifts I'm
making them as part of our leveling up I
did take command you know things could
get pay your viola is you were ready to
take it when I actually loved it I think
did you think that yeah I got tongue
wall I just know what the bonus actions
yeah as a bonus extra kiss is my sleeve
now yeah okay
red room of drought yeah yeah no you put
on your character sheet if it's under
the problems section power transfer so
we're trending yeah got it
yeah all right what's next masochist
eros I got there whoa what I took a
little while marry the bar like nothing
ever happened by the way masticated
thank you by the way of Providence do I
owe you anything for this gadget I'll
get it back to you bring it up probably
okay what do you want to do walnut like
I feel very torn
I trust prophetess completely more than
this hologram of this dude well the
longer were alive the more we can
collect on our equity however profit did
we have any mail me do miss Cole the
mail admit yeah because it seems to me
that we you know file all the paperwork
we've done everything that we needed to
do just wondering your friend with the
mail bags come by Alby she hasn't been
but you know when we'd be expecting her
maybe are you sticking payment from well
that also maybe you know more quest be
good watering right right right now
maybe to grind a little yeah we're son
yeah right right now there are not less
cool guys one just like let's kick it go
right so hover on the map or yeah yeah
yeah should I'm kidnapped and quick did
I do the wrong thing yesterday
I gots turn into the fight oh my
meditating on the bar your thanks for
the first hole in that lady's kid
you haven't even listened yeah no smell
like chickens in here hey it's very barn
oriented hmm right now I go alright so
how what unrelated sorry here's your Wow
I'll take out a second five minutes in
the mural yeah good our pain yeah sorry
we all get sick over flu had the bird
flu um so does anyone need anything from
any of the stores good for healing
potion yeah some real one yeah yeah I
mean it worked fine okay I'm shred you
tried last time and there was not going
it's not that always right it is there
anything that I could possibly is there
a store where I could get something to
whip up in my herbalism kit yes I'm
proficient at that Oh - what are you
trying to do we're trying to go make a
healing salves
a healing occult ax yo alterus one part
chicken five parts chickens chickens
chickens yeah and then delicious with
chicken yes it's a chicken are we good
yeah you need a chicken inside of a
chicken sighs check actually that's
ridiculous well I would never pay money
for palance's she gather herself a
little stupid probably in a meadow yeah
and come back with full full ouches um
yeah you can when you're out there
doesn't keep it undo that even I kick
out your herbalism do we want to go back
to the place where the tomb was and see
what it looks like and then I think week
we could now we can also asked around
the town to see if what the word is on
the bird omen oh and let's not forget
there's like there's this juicy dragon
board princess we could try to find out
more information and go to go hurt hurt
her a little bit mmm oh you get a reward
for returning your table no it doesn't
sound like she's going to do that but
thanks
what if you want to go kidnap the egg
like I don't support that
I know yeah I play palette a little fast
and loose but like kidnapping it is like
a little too far outside their else just
an egg yeah yeah it's okay anyway this I
was in I was gonna tell you this
conversation is ongoing
yeah I feel as a fundamentally it's a
film yeah listen cream first James
listen judges dragon is a game where you
can make [ __ ] up and maybe Dragonborn
like it's if you get mad at the at the
parent of an egg and you don't say that
their parenting well enough you get to
be the ward of that egg until they can
prove to you in a trial of three parts
that they are a worthy parent to the egg
they look I just [ __ ] made that [ __ ]
right I don't
Ross this school yeah the right let's go
just a [ __ ] kidnap yeah that's the
whole [ __ ] world Billy Laurie no yeah
no I was long wigglin well builders ah
donate today does CPS steal children
kidnapped them from their home yeah no
well yes yes for the children maybe the
goblin have it again this could be
immortality I doing her it's all yeah
volleyball she didn't good with it I
don't know I mean so me speaking is
limits almost like compass here is just
like whoa omen told us to go check out
the thing yeah she's looking antsy I'm
safe to do it now apparently I hope so I
don't weigh a lot
you just wrong on me hmm live you're my
[ __ ] now yes right sure uh I want him
to let me know if you you lift me you
tickle me that's what I do is I get it
yes I have watch I'm outside so you dare
break icon we could go we could go seek
it out because I don't understand how he
intends for us to prepare for I think we
don't understand in any way you know for
all we know we go back there and it's
gone if it is indeed a wandering crypt
what red room is there a history check
that I can do honest uh yeah you look
even today if I you're welcome to do it
but
message specifically says that he calls
it that you know okay that may not be
EXO so lame but based based on my
knowledge of stuff and my background I
should be able to know at least where to
find information on something if it's a
real thing and you love the library
yeah yeah yeah but you have a card for
the red large angry oh yeah I'm well
known in many libraries gosh okay I'm
going to roll history and just to see if
anything we saw sure in that correct
anything we experienced anything we've
heard from Roman and prophets rings Bell
yes and I know it's not gonna do
anything all out I sold the game the
campaign is over yet there's a knock
outside and the coupon that is a big is
for me yeah it's not kind that so the
cake made me feel better yeah
my name is Sylvester Stallone what whoa
all right it's cool okay Franklin was
very accomplished musician look I'm
number one okay what do I know
that's a 23 yeah I totally get it I'm
straight up your knowledge transcends
space and time yeah I wrote several
books about the laundry of Chris yeah
exactly that's my crib no not your
[ __ ] you know in high school your
nickname is rose Eastern yellow on
during a crypt B singer oh my god just
joking
together digital yeah yeah Chad smash it
I wrote when T [ __ ] you on the back oh
no there are all kinds of I mean it's
like if it's like a crypto archeology
thing right you can go back and you know
of all kinds of of calamities that could
oh the calamities that don't have any
real answer that you could apply stories
to like you you feel like what you have
been told now obviously there's a
difference of opinion between
prophetess and omen about what it
represents and what actually happened
but there is and there is a good
argument to be made that there is
something that connects disappearances
of towns individuals you know the
tectonic activity like you can see that
there's the the history of this valley
has things that could that could be a
part of a single story like you can you
can sort of see these these tales these
sort of like half understood tales
coalescing around a possible plausible
line of causality okay it doesn't you're
not you're not willing with your 23
you're not willing to say that this
isn't a thing okay
cool all right well uh any more b-team
information we can get how long were
they here I'm asking process like how
long were they keep their number oh yeah
I like I loved dinar was the only one
who we like didn't leave it in leave a
bad taste in mouth I was like they're
critical like you think as I look at
proper and I go um just because I'd like
to know because I wouldn't want to sleep
in the same room but what room did
Brahma sleep in how bad do you want to
do okay weirdo but what how bad do you
want it I can make it happen for you
we're just curious I was just curious
yeah you see like walnut upstairs like
sniffing the sheets later being like
yeah it was like a fume yeah this one no
I've no whatever smells like New Age
smelly I find like a long blonde hair
and I'm like oh my god it must be it oh
I'll trade you
you plant some straw you're like look
beautiful blonde another uh she says
that Brahma slept in denars room but
that onyx was sad for a while after she
oh how I don't think here I don't have
my cell anymore but I'm gonna ask onyx
about her after our next short return
about five yes he hang on on it okay I'm
gonna be back classic at Pacific okay
Emmitt four years give or take four
years hmm long time these failures yeah
yeah oh my god
nice yeah first first at-bat tough yeah
okay it's been what in real time it's
been what like you like this a dick
seven nights we've known each other
right yeah that's true
known each other a week but what a week
ago what a week huh
the real treasure with friendship follow
yeah okay so it's daytime are you cool
with going out I'm fine with it yeah
alright look at the big fun hat yeah
yeah sooo again sunglasses leave the
sloppiest sign yeah okay and the other
with the the okay the cloth or the huge
ribbon yeah what should we pile in the
cart and go check out the Crypt in the
sunlight let's not go inside
I have Baconator I say yes bring bacon
yeah very satisfying yeah yeah alright
let's go full all right
you pull it out by what you mean a card
mmm YUM come on down hit the long road
take the left up the lane you can see
well wrist spot but halfway up across
the street sort of kitty corner there
you can see Bruce Fein poultry they're
having a hell of it yeah so big say yeah
way too much in the glades you gone and
seen if there was a poultry shop huge
savings there's like the sign in the
window this is like like like meats
sourced you know they've removed it
campus stuff yeah there's two good one
let's look at the other direction I like
a particularly nice Mountain Valentine
yeah nice so you pull the cart left head
south down a long road it's between here
and the doone-gate
and yes I have the map back to the mound
kind of it was it's going to say well no
no because you you actually no I
call this and I was overjoyed when you
made a specific note yeah you made a
specific note on how to find it again
which will give you a delicious savory
bonus excellent time on your history
rule okay and you know what's that bonus
I won't tell you okay
negative 2 you also advantage I have
advantage oh well I had got there
everyone with me and apparently bonus on
combat there you go that's pretty good
you're clean ok clean so you basically I
mean this is like full-on gramma tier
execution reigns one hand map open on
this on the bench to the side flipping
it over looking at all the signs and
portents you've made a note of there's a
few small sketches some particular trees
but it is tricky if you hadn't made a
special note that wouldn't have been
sufficient you find your way off you
even show off a little bit you enter
that network of old roads from a place
that you didn't even go in and are still
able to find the side of this the side
of this mound which in the middle of the
day doesn't seem as heroin I know that
none of them noticed how cool my
navigation skills were so I say loose
premium I'm like whoa I can't believe we
found our way back here I was pretty
crazy was at night and everything but
here we are we found it again I always
knew looks like I was in like I sent my
ways tournament also it was right Oh
employee it's like so because of my
background uh where I'm like the
Outlander but I have the wanderer perk
so I was like I always have my bearings
and you'll know your surroundings so
it's like bombs like yeah good job you
legit impressed Thanks whoa I've got a
worse than the duration are we not even
still in town how do we get here
every gene all these trees look the same
and I've learned from you aimed dirt
I've learned from you that this this
means great job so I do this at you I
get so mad that's the only thing I have
a thing yeah so you so you can see up
this Ridge you can see the sort of rough
footsteps going up like some Tufts of
grass have been pouring out from the
wool from walking up and down this path
but you can see that sort of you can see
that whole sort of punctured in the side
of the mound up there
okay so when we ripped out of ya so
because we popped out of a different one
than we went in just verifying what a
hole this is feeling so this was yeah
yeah yeah yes emergence that merges yeah
egress hole do we want to think the legs
it'll guide the hole yeah I was going to
say do you maybe have any kind of shapes
that might be interesting for
reconnaissance and the newest
reconnaissance shape sink I think I've
got something in my bag of tricks
yeah I got something I got just the one
I think you're gonna like it I think
yeah I don't really like this one um and
then uh well it just like a little like
whatever is really Roy Mustang thing
alright anyway and then does wild shape
and turns into a weasel the wildest what
with a sweet breezy um okay but yes I'll
talk like that when I clip Baroness I
talked to ferret ferrets are kind of
baller honestly yeah you can't see it
but I have a tattoo of one now I'm only
want to turn into shapes that I have
tattoos um so I turn into this tiny
little wheel which still has what you
should be seeing a image maybe Kiko
Waveland I said I started sneezing I
start I swivel my way up and then I get
a guy that's in mom knows Jeannie but
here are you're going in the home yeah
in like I feel like we should lesson
learned
when we go in these things they close
behind like we should prop it open even
if just Amy is going in we should like
try to rape Molly we should try to
diameter of her weasel form Jansen no
you wasn't
yeah like if we could do anything if
there's anything around we plus to
reinforce that opening it's good I can
still help entanglement
we don't wanna eat in it yeah get a tree
and like trap it in what about that
toothpick my sword
yeah no you crazy I'd rather let her get
killed but does anybody have a well I'm
a weasel so I can say I make a little
noise is that fair to make where they go
oh yeah you want a rope you said
wavelength wrote here yeah okay yeah you
had the rope should take this regret
remember we're all in a hide I have last
night yeah but this don't you hugging um
any kind of only what's around this
world around you lovely quick around the
country glandular me this is my dream
block I heard yeah I had some great
dreams too
they're really fun and cool also
although I had some good dreams too
yes yes oh cool but yeah one of these
abilities that I'm taking compromise we
got disgusted sigh look so excited
because I think come up again so giggly
no you listen we love God knows me to
say let's listen to Sirius in so you are
new at role-playing yeah and so there
are some things that you don't know so
you're like I don't hurt your friends
yeah I do people really want to that
work but do people do people want to
hear about my character generally know
when you're not role-playing yeah like
but when you're role-playing this is a
great time to tell people about your
character that's all I also know this is
the optimal time so luck so Chris Cobb
are you saying that you've made some
cool selections for your love for I did
and this is a question have you already
paired it down there excuse me fair is
not the right word yeah that insensitive
is it yes but people in the YouTube
comments are telling me that if we do
the mind thing I can actually you can
come back and say oh yeah this is yeah
because I shouldn't be making like oh
yeah you're making like it's way cuter
language is are great but but listen but
we have to say that it's a little bit
higher pitched maybe I get a sense of
what yeah exactly
okay I mean being upside the wall
nothing I hear you
oh I'm into the hole enough speaking
link with the fish
what's reason yes I really like yes
yeah I have two things that I could
needle number one I took I took like a
wheel ocular I took news it was open
source weasel name yeah I have a cat at
six level every time I do it I have a
plus 5 Michael Biehn no I took thorn
with but I'm flavoring it as one of mine
Wow tensile I'll pull your weird snakes
yeah yeah weird snare especially with
tab but I bet you it's not any good I
don't think it's not valuable turn the
inside out I've also taken as a an
invocation I've dropped alarm which
served us so well and I've taken fine
familiar whoo I think dr. guidance no no
that was what I could do for the for
this whip oh I think I'm just I hate
effect that is okay take it easy
mouthing wit and I've selected a have
the attributes of a poisonous snake but
tell y'all what it looks like is one of
my tenth Acula spent a spectaculars but
did it leave when the rest of the spell
abated horrifying its effect gross looks
like a rail on leech studded with movie
crystals you got a thing I can send my
new friend down that hole and I can also
exchange vision with it oh wow so you
would you like a friend down there it
was so much more than our little evil
for I'm just like I'm going to do a
reconnaissance ah yes reconnaissance
yes so kind of always you are Satan the
devil you know weasel nut is the best
character weasel net you weasel nut is
top tier Oh local nut okay so um so if
you want backup
watch it I don't think it can hurt you
can't don't let's not be cavalier we now
utterly close the tape good TPK play can
you just role play yourself finding that
technical real quick yeah Oh like like
when it happened music like have them
Matt how you like what do I have what
are hello what what can help
looks I need to find it
Miller no yes yeah well yeah I go like
let me see that accompanied I've ever at
a rope and it just like Peaks up I'm
like huh okay chicas yet not now
oh wait a minute maybe you know or not
alright I toss it on the ground
that's I [ __ ] [ __ ] we like the really
serpent yeah oh yeah they'll find love
and that beautiful so I guess they'll
find love in that hole I communicate
don't be surprised when this thing comes
that it's not I tell it what to do oh
good it's a good thing it's not a bad
one because your worst appendage yet I'm
sorry can you show that again this is
your worst appendage listen sound like
weasel yes GA repent it sucks
somebody at appendages and yet so much
[ __ ] down yeah we're going yeah in their
rights with one exactly I got a lot
going on I'm sorry guys my is go right I
am and I'm now looking through this
right I can't I can't see here I can't
see the outside a little bit I can see
down there right now
and now though and now the serpent can
see through your eyes and Gannett a
worthless it's like your body switch
with it yeah just like flopping around
II right again all chanting tada
all right well the soap doesn't wobble
weasel in the snake okay if you see any
any wack [ __ ] going on with his snake by
the way let me know and I'm gonna what
didn't one of you yes yeah so you so you
pad up through the upper mound of soil
the Vettes Whittle but yeah you guys
pushed out before in please
straight through the MA of this whole
zone hmm
and then down and just sort of the cool
darkness beyond that this horrible thing
slithers and hisses
about too much yeah cool it you know
yeah straight through the whole mode
exactly is familiar and then his young
and it's just go go to as your eyes
adjust to the darkness of this passage
you can see that where you had sort of
the regular stone the slick stairs the
strange apparatus that sort of hid
itself as you were going down the stairs
before mm-hmm just nothing like that
this is actually a natural cavern
burrowed out of rock and you can see
strange scratches down the down the
stone the left and right and then above
you you can see that it's actually sort
of scraped through this can I do a
little smell check yeah absolutely I
have keen smell which I get as in John
what does it do I'm just it's like a
perception check but it's just based on
you based on a little wheel commute I'm
definitely needs a hand under five
that's the summer smell again so there
is a there's all kinds oh yeah those
nails deliciousness down here you smell
smells worms bugs mmm eggs mm-hmm like
good dragon morning no oh no never no
it's gone forever
I might not affirm you to hurt you I've
never had a master Oh dark in my way but
but no I mean so there's all this
basically as your what is the tentacle
smell like well good question fresh-cut
garden hose it's like plastic yeah
garden I like a grass you a little bit
vamps because I want a real answer
it smells like from your from your
Wiesel Ian's consciousness yes it smells
like a sword smells
dancing and so okay baby you tonight
we're just cataloging all these things
in your mind you're sort of you're sort
of running down the list like what order
you're going to eat him in it's like
okay I'm going to go for the I'm going
to go for the millipede then I'm going
to have the worms than you would of
course and then there's this other
there's this other smell oh it's a
brackish old water smell that is deeply
offensive to the nose oh so I look at
the snake so that could this can see
that I'm like I'm not little fur I get
brush tail yellow yeah there's no defile
is something and I ranch
I guess I do my best impression of a
weasel trying to point at something I'm
like yeah so you can you can see it as
well so just talk to me because I'm here
sometimes I just get some time going to
get a little overwhelmed by my animal
senses and I want to confess I just want
to continue down the path which to you
so you are moving farther and farther
down and you can sort of get a sense
that this is where the chamber was
before and where that chamber was is now
large sort of chewed out stone more or
less the same volume but you can see
that where you went down that initial
stair now this rough hewn stone that's
happening again except it's a much wider
area mm-hmm so it's almost as though
that part of the chamber hmm just ground
itself down through the earth and what's
more you're starting to see those
scratches have become something more
like a pattern so inside the inside
these scrapes you notice it
instantaneously and in fact you're
you're familiar
uh you can just feel it sort of coiling
and turning with delight I need an hour
can I check from you like sugar love to
do that for you
rollin that boy whipping boy not exact
that's a real well yeah go to one you
with a super one that so as I say so it
sort of Turtles it turns itself into
almost like a corkscrew and it's just
flopping like flopping itself against
the stone and you can see it sort of
drawn over toward symbols that are
increasing in definition so I think it
looks more natural and more raw than the
farther down you get into this you can
see that it's it's um almost like the
surface has been melted into glass mm-hm
you can see that these these scrapes are
becoming more and more coherent symbols
and you can tell through the connection
that these symbols are the symbols of
the gate you can see the symbol of the
earth and what's more you can see it
rising against another symbol and it
tries to eat it oh it's actually trying
to nasha it goes over gnaws at the
symbol pull it all on a second don't
look at it we're fit some needed I'm
sorry yeah you can get here you don't
know if it's because you're not there
physically or if it's something to do
with the link you have it's familiar
it's very hard to make it it's very hard
to make it out you recognize occur like
through its yeah you recognize the ER
instantaneously like the rest of it is
difficult yes yes so as I said like
stand alone complex yes like it's got
its faces like the circle on it and so
what it pulls this weave as I say it
pulls down it's sort of creating this
giant glass stair that descends down
into it but there's there's no there's
no whatever that was is not here
this is something else roads indeed and
you can see that those symbols continue
to increase in definition they get
sharper and sharper the farther in you
go hmm all right I am feel like this is
as far away as I want to as I want to
get so hope thing but what's the weird
sneaking it I have a glass yeah really
uh so it's getting a little crazy down
here do we want to all go down here do
we want to like relay this to the group
what do you think oh yeah let's let's
tell the good can you see these symbols
I can't like my it's not they're not
resolving for me yeah one looks like a
one dumb squiggle and then another even
dumber squiggle and they look like
nothing oh my god squiggles great this
is my special quick those are special
squiggle for me you yelled at like do we
hear it oh my god squiggles yeah and I'm
like I'm like I've got eagle eyes on you
I know I'm just like hovering behind
your neck like that variable Phi yeah
yeah
we will decapitate you yeah that crazy
please angry yeah yeah I know none of
these spaces look like they could think
that a person could go down them so
something scraped these out and then
descended down yeah exactly sort of
pulled it looks get sort of like pulled
its way down and in its descent it's
left this bizarre language right what
you're super heated the edge of the
rocker something is if something has
happened to the stone is it big enough
that the group could get there
absolutely no but I say this is a
grandparent Italica the grand old alike
this is orc [ __ ] like it ah you're going
down your territory alright yeah so I
want to get so can I get the listen up
can we get the familiar back up yeah
can you come in there hey guys with a
little more hesitancy than I want well
yeah yeah ultimately it gives up
ultimately it gives up I didn't know how
to do and then starts to flop around you
might bite him and bring it
all yeah I want to do that ah I wait
telling exchange sighs too late about
you know I bet I thought I'd do a small
bike I do a really tiny bite yeah yeah
and then I grow and then I do take one
oh yeah if you can look this up on
YouTube it's really great when like
ferrets grabbed something that's like
way too long anyway and it's just like
running all the way the thing with the
snake like trailing behind just go on I
can get you everywhere and if you get to
the hole just to pull it through yeah
exactly exactly I think your eyes turn
back to normal yeah what happens is she
you'd bite me and you'd like the
tentacle yeah I go and then my eyes go
back to normal I go units heard me I
don't make that sound what's that mean
all right I'm commanding you I'm making
sure there's no sign of man coming to do
a perception check on you okay failure
yeah it was really good though it was
really good yeah
funny did a 20 I did a 20 it was funny
not only for my section here which
everyone out of the bottom okay yeah
it's your agent right yeah I presume
that you're fine I've put the necklace
back in my pouch no necklace come right
back you sure we're to have bracelets oh
it's like always
yeah a little bit I'll leave it like oh
yeah yeah huge like your name uh you
know so I'm back you come out of the
hole my swimming week and this this
thing hmm cuz we're turn to expenses
hopefully you know that it's out of that
yeah yeah well for some reason I can't
stop and I like to do a couple little
victory squeezes around with it I'm
cheering you on look it'll relieve it
your anything a little war dance yeah
please just answer indulging me that I
just like really get into the animals oh
never sent no I never better I'll go
into it to that table quitter why are
you that fair you can do a voice you do
that voice every time oh yeah I won't
weasel not always exactly and I pitched
Italian dialect so you're the Italians
coming in and out
get the at the end right imagine trying
to try this Amy do you see if this see
if this and wises you yes
hi I'm Trevor the werewolf yeah snap
kale I run the doone-gate in who are you
why I wanted you and Trevor where did
you ever go
Trevor's fresh name is NaN regional
dialect you support him
hello increment welcome good night and
go partying you got me yes okay okay I
run down the stairs I fight the monster
please Wow well we're talking about
terraces and I'm just like I don't know
victim uh stick okay so you guys still
listen and we're like we all just decide
we're going to back down there is that
the thing yeah I think I'm back in the
wall now because I'm my weasel times
done yeah alright so but you you take an
effort to make passage easier for bipeds
on the way down but as soon as your as
soon as you're through that that area
there of the loose soil it really is I
mean very walkable good walking scaler
exactly this is very huge hole no it's I
mean yeah it's good
I made it what else I did that question
do I feel do you know do I feel any
different now that I'm down here and do
I feel different now that I'm down here
and seen with my own sites am i affected
by these let's say I was going to say
you've always want to walk behind you
yeah use all the way we're just going to
I guess it's not clamp your eyes if you
start looking at things weird you've
always wondered even in a temple too
little you never felt odd Oh God right
yeah you know you know you don't you
don't have a good sense of what it is
like to be in a place of communion and
your you know your divinity this entity
that you are fundamentally you know in
the thrall of yeah there's no
churches for that on the corner you have
a search in the model yeah you have it
you have a sense yeah you have a sense
that you understand what that person
feels like what an inherent feels like
this seems like a Cathedral this Dalek
do I so do I the dark light crystal can
those camera looks do I feel like I am I
getting any sense of like Monell is it
because while I want to lose can you
just to lose myself no in the music man
yeah mama forget anything no no no you
don't talk about games awful no yeah you
don't feel it Queenie because I regret I
want to keep looking with my own eyes
mine is I don't know leave like I could
pop my familiar up and then I can just
look through its site well it's I don't
know I I can I won't a lot like we'd
leave you back in the same I'm already
I'm taking away still like I'm lying to
you yes I just haven't here and I'm
looking through its [ __ ] your vision how
worried about him
no I got my leash I know but at the same
time like I remember a mirror okay I'm
also the only one you swung on you have
last night yes so this you can see that
this is sort of like I'm boldest room
when you map it immediately to where it
was before just your natural enthusiasm
for cartography you begun to apply the
experience you have of the previous
space you can tell just from a
volumetric perspective like this must
have been that chamber but you can see
that it's just sort of like the reverse
of it it's now pulled down in the front
of you to down into darkness but there's
all these there's sparkles from where
this stone has been converted into glass
and then as I said before the etchings
and symbols are growing more defined the
farther in you get I want to do in our
kind of check I want the 400 one I want
to check I want to looking for is
whether or not I get a sense it would be
a wise or bad idea to
you know some rubbings like to get some
copies of these things just just to
consider them even management you can
track you can use your identity right so
we'll get the second one in there
let's not solely this die here on the
advantages don't need it this time but
took it okay okay so you know yeah
that's high
obviously I'm totally hungry yeah so you
have you obviously give it sheet of
paper in your paddock character sheet I
do yeah yet the you try to do a rubbing
of it and the symbol is actually a
couple of millimeters underneath this
glass so you can so you can get you can
try to get the markings you can write
over the top and trace okay but a true
rubbing is not possible because somehow
the symbols are in the glass as you're
moving down so as I said there's a grand
stair the sort of goes down into hell
okay then really that's what kind of
looks like before things like this one
that is now more of an inverse yes or it
was a dome dome exactly so that was
there yeah and then it's imagine that
shape yeah just having pulled itself
down hmm
through the rock okay stared in mind as
if the Crypt had wandered not going to
put any words in anyone's mouth since
then in oh well we got there Lester
okay it's like the thing where they and
zombie movie they never say zombie yeah
it's like a dinner where walking about
so long as Shamblin yeah we're The
Walking Dead scope okay
and you're not feeling weird apparently
not okay no feel all right so let's keep
going going assuming right so you get
you make your way down you don't you
don't lose your footing but this is very
smooth lose my footing
I lose my friend it was a couple down
step I know on to thrush yeah yeah I
know so farther and farther and
a little bit then it goes back in time
so yes as you're moving down the the
symbols are growing brighter as you move
and to the extent that not only have
they begun - not only do they have true
definition and clarity but they seemed
to Sparkle even in the dark of the
cavern and the farther down you've
gotten there's a lot more natural
moisture that coolness that you felt
earlier in the cavern has only gotten
more this is just heavier um there's a
cool moistness not a warm with the best
weird slit this is cool yeah yeah very
cool there's an awesome moisture level
and you can see but you can see a debt
bounce down this far you can see that
there are actually pools in different
just in a sort of like a random
configuration from the scraping of the
water water or was it look at Oh zip it
yeah we want to take a little patience
if Jen do a drink thank you
Rangers gulp yeah now let it I left both
let's go straighten stuff ready your
ears to bleed
alright that's better
bye bye your powers combined yeah yeah
yeah so let's take a drinks and now we
know where hey so tell me tell me we do
I push you on the way and I'm going to
sip it and then cut my hand in it and
probably not drink it until I'm pretty
convinced it's not corroding me as soon
as you put your hand into it
the pain is incredible so okay roll
initiative yep right oh my
we're gonna asleep nice excuse got a
feisty on you I said good it's cute ah I
miss phantom vision is everyone is mom
breathing now you got an 18 oh [ __ ]
that's great thing all right I'm gonna
rely on a 10 watch you guys I got a 14
whip how do you get the frist a for Oh
as always I'll go lie on there for you
here
so you're you can however you risk
bond to a searing anger water bone tear
agony okay you know but look I'd love to
know the pH levels are like ya know
midpoints damage it also just the noise
it also have a basic could be ugly
yeah how many hit points good damage
point no you're good for that won't ask
forget I'm just saying it's bone searing
pain okay well do one for that because I
asked Amanda yeah
all rights what I like X for your ass
like that's for Pat them
yeah exactly I got one so Pat retinol
stuff so Rosie so you are first in
initiative and I would love to know how
you can tend so as you pull your hand
back out of it
it's not wet right okay you pull it out
and now your hand is completely clean
okay
and from that do it but as you're
pulling it out gross it is coming out it
is following you out of the pool okay
all right essentially like a gelatinous
cube like this you know you're [ __ ]
with powers you can't possibly convey so
I know I don't know what that is anymore
I know that's a thing but I don't know
what it is okay I I'm going to I don't
know that I don't trust this my bath
gonna do anything to goo how do you
think bludgeoning doesn't probably so
actually blushing probably does
I think slicing generally doesn't go
doesn't work on you all right I'm going
to try of logics more I'm going to do AB
legend instantaneously my my without
even thinking
there's this there's a split second of
where I draw my breath and go for it go
nuts with the rods
go nuts with the rod and it's a 17-day
it that's marvelous
thank you that's very very good okay and
by the way I'm just going to do a
martial arts and a flurry of blows I was
going to say you should because it
because you wear whenever you hit with
the staff of the master it converts your
very flurry of blows into d8 that's
right that's right it does permanently
yes that's any many of my own arm stress
okay okay how do you go to sleep so if
you if you've missed with the initial
attack you don't get the bonus okay well
I did hit and that is already 12
two unarmed strikes are going to be an
eleven and seven cheese there's no key
well Wow yep
so total 1211 831 [ __ ] a beautiful
mind that math was so friendly alright
you're AB so it isn't all so right it's
a liquid but it's not water
okay and you feed it up you dilated um
you have found a way I mean there's no
discernible limbs organs anything it you
found a way to hurt it it actively
recoils this it looks like the like the
reverse of a surfing wave hmm so I I see
it as soon as you struck it it recoils
back or and curls around like this and
sharps bad I say something mean to it -
yeah hey [ __ ]
yeah just like that you're a piece of
[ __ ] your shitty juice bad liquid yeah
okay pick a state solid or fewer water
all right yes I'm it is [ __ ] colloid
zoom all right [ __ ] colloid you see
you see rows of spines emerge and sort
of fold themselves back into the liquid
and it extends a gruesome whip of
ghastly fluid toward Walnut dong grass
huh I mean just like fluid I rolled it
before and you were number two um so
Carmela yeah right
he takes you take five points and how do
oh no but so it's like so it's obviously
the solid the solid tendril the Wow
obviously you feel that and it's it's a
real thing but you can handle it but
wherever where it touched the skin I it
begins to devour Oh No what's up how
many hit likes do you have I feel bad
I'm number [ __ ] with you no now I
have 26 you say 26 points
okay cool the walnut walnut just got
[ __ ] right oh wait hands off I'm sorry
sorry sorry sir give me a second
well I'm plon plon yeah so we at one and
I'm like I feel myself against it and
you know I try and shake it off and then
just like feeling it just like eat away
at my skin that's actually exposed like
looking at it in horror and then looking
at the rest of you I can't even muster
the words I just like feel it drain for
me and I just pass out on the ground
very like dignified but like somehow and
pass out in my in my brows still
furrowed like I'm like it doesn't rest
no no it's like you're wishing for the
sheath and you're like well uh done
grass oh yeah you're right yeah and the
last thing I do is like sorry pet that
is just like sign off on like a employee
was knocked out for not I notarize my
own will oh man what have sucks but
let's go guys you know in our bliss yes
tough but fair no rain but oh hang on oh
I know oh well I guess you don't get an
action that would right so wait so that
was the monster so now it's get you your
ass no just keep sorry I would I don't
have to do death saves I'm this is no no
exciting for negatives yeah okay
I'm trying to be better I think it prone
to nothing just 26 points assignment she
can probably die she can well chip into
a prom
so if I if I he'll do you regain
consciousness like at the point of
feeling okay so I gotta bring it back
all right
uh I've got it you can do it everything
I was going to that's true role play
that we're looking at you mean right
yeah
points it looks yeah it's like
unconscious people can't drink potions
move her jaws we try to pour it down her
mouth we end this already this
discussion yeah we could do that work um
a creature you touch regains a number of
hit points equal to 1 to 8 plus spell
casting a building modifier spell
casting a little strainer
that's your pi/3 thank you
when do you figure the juice yeah just
kind of boost you up a little bit
how did you can it sure is
Jerry come on don't you're young
consciousness is cheating it was like
two pyramids yeah I know I said that
we're learning you know which point
eight Oh where'd I go just now yeah lay
on hands I'm still on the ground
lightest team I'm very depressed with
the generosity of you funny oh yeah me
too I'm blown away by it I know you know
why I'll kiss on the forehead no no it's
because we're seeing we're actually
seeing Ryan Hartman yeah because he's
thinking about what happened last time
in this cavern oh yeah maybe tonight
just wanted something a mother for a
second yeah I do I get real real
nurturing I'm like put little bandages
you got a signal
you got little civil war bandage like
walnut there and I did yeah all better
ticked off the skull it's Chris Brown I
just take it all in what its delight to
see oh my god in action yes exactly yes
in your gullet yeah works alright I'm
going to just do let's do bring a dish
up I'm going to try my my Eldridge blast
mmm it's a premium blast it's a great
blast yeah people love it do I get a
sense though wait here's this the scene
this this pool yes now writhing yeah and
rising up these are there more of them
or it's just a single writing right now
okay as best you can tell then you have
you have dark fish and I mean you know
you don't see anything else here your
darker yeah you don't see anything else
some of us like this okay Carl a with it
in terms of volume like this is pretty
substantial right okay I just want to
make sure I wasn't wasting my my energy
on one when there's a couple more magic
missle don't miss um I'm gonna love to
do eat something different this time let
me
I'm going to throw a hex on it that
bonus
it is bonus action okay so she hexed and
then the hex hex confers disadvantage uh
yes on one of the ability checks okay
and let's make that one Constitution
okay and then I'm going to enjoy
shattering it okay Oh your new toys my
new toy
mm-hmm ooh I want to point 10 point this
sphere so we're not I'm not dropping
this 10-foot sphere where dinar and wall
mother in there is that possible can I
get it on the edge yeah okay from where
you are you can do that
alright that's what I love so take a
some make the Constitution saving throw
verses 14 and if you don't make it if we
just see a combo you don't make that
from Chris prison trout you can enjoy 3d
eights under damage that does not
succeed
wow wow that does not succeed if you
beat it with disadvantage you still take
half straight right that's right it's
just like oh no no I'm saying he lost
you know I'm just very pleased did you
make it I mean the animated yeah no no
is so I just you'd you suck you didn't
anything piece of paper
you hair great that is good because he
explored a damages are yeah damaged
index I'm tired let's enjoy each other
on all the great guys I will see we get
a little good so this is 12 plus and
that counts yes that's kind of 18 told
she 15 total I can take that blob what
am I saying
but I certainly go there those puddles
come rosy lip around oh yeah how do you
got um well show you so you you'd summon
this new this new revelation that you've
had about a dream okay easy
but I can share exactly and it does in a
moment it shatters and because shatter
and then reforms all right fully
refreshed what you got yeah yeah I've
been it just gonna drop more flavor do a
hit again I'm gonna try so it is it
shattered and it's still looking pretty
hale and hearty if it's fine well I mean
it's very hard to tell what I would a
holy uniform liquid beast rot well no I
I forgot that's very mature for you you
the shadow council has afford you some
benefit yeah forgive me I forget to add
the hex damage 1d6 is Lord forgive me
see ya I get to roll more dice forgive
me oh I'm sorry
sorry oh I'm sorry oh I forgot real
quick my 70 hologram good alright
alright drop some science on we really
do look you some grandma man see it
seems well quick grab and grip so that
would that would provide you great
protection against this against this
okay
well this augusta's is you to benefit
its grip faraman see we got it we got to
work on maybe two am panetta I want I
want more okay
no I think that's gonna be fine all
right
yeah so that's a 24 to hit yeah that's
kind of it that would not do it alright
yeah they're horrible they're easy to
hit but they're okay really really bad
I'm using flurry of blows again as you
should oh it's going to be so made for
every first doctor's first point okay
are you getting your plus one damage
yeah yeah we had his twelve well uh six
and seven twenty five wow it's pretty
big big hits for such a small [ __ ] oh
how I it so it letters now well concept
in words if my ears content attacks just
a literal flurry of blows if you will
well just a coin a phrase hmm get it
like a way like labor it yeah the ice
cream
thank you it's been recalled
on the hips and then rolls itself
forward to give you a super wack 15
likes
that's mighty cake Pat Rothfuss says
that I'm supposed to roll separate be
20s for each of my unarmed attacks
instead of just really damage like a
[ __ ] boss that's why it's which one's
cooler Pat Rothfuss thank you yeah
he's also hood thank you to help you
know I think kind of like Beyonce or
will attackers in the text says I love
you but you [ __ ] suck at this game
pepperoni up here Wow 20 damage twice
you okay oh wait you just took me to
damage yeah so your your body is too but
no I'm fine no walnut good I bought it
with a rejuvenated walnut um
now salmonella uh well I don't want to
touch it and most of this point you just
think I could do our dirty are touchy so
here's what I can do flip the tip to
slid what else oh here's what I do um I
would you want strength or do you want
like more I don't know all right so I
reach I was touched in order to thank
him and I use enhance ability whoa
and then I want to give him advantage on
chronic check okay is that good or do
you want more hit points I think well
and there's no way to gain the advantage
of tax anything you know do you want to
know that stuff uh it I guess hit yeah
bounds like this things right so let me
give you pretty hard you gotta get you
some area HP are we hurting this puddle
hold on
probably wow you have four HP for extra
HP or you didn't have before it is have
four so I'm at so we run beyond another
camp those are temporary temporary so
basically those sit on top of your
regular pool yeah and get removed first
no he gets them forever no you're right
you're right you're a big buff for mom
pill all right well and they can't be
taken away and they're right now hello
we're all learning we're all friends
here all learning just students in this
great world tell me their heart I see at
the role so I forgot it extinct would
you forget I forgot that familiar gets
initiative takes gets its own spot sort
of sneaking out a puddle
yeah I got luck so he's four I don't
work he goes after you bigger than that
okay now but then all right well I want
him to go you think you can I heal you
are you yeah you all right I think you
should probably do a slash yeah I'll do
a hit all right what do you got
I'm gonna go I don't know how long has
just come back in the last I could combo
up and really [ __ ] them up next turn I
do it do it
we're dying all right if we can survive
another attack from this thing ah then
I'll bless this mess nothing I'm the met
I'm the mess
so I'll get a d4 added to my attack and
singing tears about an action or bonus
that's an action okay you're not
actually gonna do a hit now I said next
round
yeah okay go for it I don't know if
we're gonna make it that much say you
said we're like no we need to [ __ ]
hit and you were like I left myself yes
I go and your turn oh you got to service
what do you got to frist route 75 die
Cyril no well if you guys live til my
neck attack I'll really bang that's good
I'm so upset at this thing that's still
good it's hurting your friends it's
really bad actually yeah these dopes
both of those so I can't do any of them
all right so we're do you have a
subscription to black magazine it's just
my degree and I keep meaning to re-up
you get all sort of the savings are me
yeah right now I know this will fight
fire with fire
oh yeah I'm curious about that one yeah
I'm just saying you could see what goes
in do I want to fight this thing with
what it is made of suppose it lands
directly in it yes what would it
somewhat it rise up you be academically
interested
rise up that's true let's say yeah I
mean if you're going to go and then your
enables going to go yeah
and then Rosie is going to go means
there's there's if there's a few rounds
of friends before they for the moisture
okay or mister moisture because his name
from now on mr. moisture it's in the
book some a guide yeah master manual
yeah mr. mayor you know under manual
let's do it and I'm gonna go ahead and
throw down a temp tacular spectacular
I'm going to appeal to the God that I
like not this horrible one that thinks
like oh what a favor
cuz a Holman hey do a little so one
thing that that Ryan does that I love is
that he actually cut the promo for his
oh I was like a special ability
yeah do you mind giving us like 20
seconds of flavor how do you I ran peers
it yeah that's true they can make a
funny voice do it come on just 20
seconds that's fine but yet yeah no it's
okay then this is something that only I
know you know the party knows it but I'm
sharing it with the players you do hear
me get down deep and I start with the
brewery process yeah there's not a hard
rock I know what that says to the powers
that be are come on guy
come on champ it's one time for me come
on out work mm-hmm
come on out buddy Lee job hi hey hi
friends hi and I can see like on the
periphery of my of my understanding my
perception that it's like I can see it
like tentatively linking in like yes
welcome welcome friend but then all our
tea is just like the darkest and I ain't
crying blood your you've every girl
should I have the necklace in like yeah
okay so it's an art can enroll yes right
Oh
alright everyone that area good lot
that's a 20 very good
here's what here is what you see this is
an embodiment as I said before a
cathedral to this entity and from each
of the glittering symbols in this dome
that surrounds you comes a ruby shaft
first one then two then three then ten
like crucifies this night then 20 then
30 take nine points of damage I will and
they all have you know they owe several
of them yeah three or more go directly
through your chest yeah
and they all converge on this on this
creature and then the symbols pulse and
you can see it sort of in the imagine
that the Rays or the carrier wave and
there's a single pulse of light and
malevolent pressure presses all the way
down compresses the creature down to
nothing arriving resisting little sphere
and then it's gone oh my god the times
the [ __ ] now oh yeah I'll be your slave
so this this place is still sort of
glowing and ruby red and you see the
tendrils sort of slowly pulling them
suspect like they pulled slip slide
straight through your cloak out your
back slip slide away and you see all
these symbols for the most part you know
you were filling out your document see
some information before so you you were
not paying attention you are not on like
sigil duty hmm
but now that you can see these symbols
activated and present you recognize one
of them and it is you enjoy video
sophist yeah no I'm no something else no
no I know but like okay you recognize
one of these symbols this symbol is not
legal under the laws of the Enclave
panik's anima it is never
to be written for those that don't know
that is Walnut Grove yeah it is it is
not it is it is punishable it is an
offense to even write it and it is you
are surrounded by it this cavern is just
twinkling with this symbol so it's the
anxious the ancient lore of the Enclave
mhm
is this for you action um I needed for
my I can't write it myself see
physically yeah the the ancient lore of
the EPA is that the gods of the EPA were
Maliki and maelys this is a pair of
lover goddesses that prayed created the
template upon which your civilization
thrived Intel maelys stocks answering
prayers never any explanation no one
could ever discern why and that day she
became Mela Sibbett rare and you can
this widely considered that was a point
where the enclaves began to lose its
grip on the Grove mm-hmm
and that symbol is everywhere in this
cavern that is our game oh look oh yeah
okay for Thursday yeah you're gonna take
from you at the end of the night reduce
to dude that just it keeps giving me a
cup yeah shadow council don't go away
hang out for a little bit we're going to
go time to use the facilities we will
return and attempt to delight you if
possible let's see we'll do our best
we'll come back in a second to go
you