terment the enemy the pastor threatens
the fastest weapon you were to make it
past a second land the question play a
flash and records to choose a car
solution you saw it was prudent in any
Sepulcher PO curtain will become the
putrid it's that well said are pursuing
no mountain too steep but dungeon too
deep to spend expendable marks up to the
top of the peak of beneath they see
become like sharks to win while I swim
in that money they're like Carl Barks
ruin essential national parks do it I'll
send them home in a natural box the post
time for most of the parks included save
your breath for a cleric confessor that
is a lesson and life isn't any
profession but if you speak in my
official advice sign on the dotted line
and risk of the twice real life hello I
am Tycho Brahe hey of Penny Arcade and
pax
I am also if you can believe it
benefits Hereward run of acquisitions
incorporated but today I'm cherry hope
I'm running a game Dungeons &amp; Dragons
for my friends indeed they're seated
right here the table to my immediate
right
Dragonborn narcissist dinar blitz in and
right to it knows no delay no delay the
tractor I practiced this afternoon
that's hurts my feelings that means the
other time it was not a big one could
die wrap wrap in the natural world 100
percent deep deep in the crevice of a
walnut center dark oh yeah
the moment and that's the moment a dam
crest yeah exactly the listen we're
going to give a time a table talk
alright for us to really investigate
Amy's crevice now it's not that Wow oh
it's a baby boy ha ha ha no no listen
well I am white I drew the line not and
you you don't cross the line you stay on
this side of the line with me Rosie
Basinger dr. granik's gramma
my immediate left 100% wave shadow among
four days Chris trout emerging from
something I don't know anything like
they'll process my else's sake Oh real
some kind of emergence
is a great listen to it on a symbol for
Dragon I no longer cough a little that's
right there's something there they do
their own way they do it their own way
down there yeah yeah yeah yeah exactly
wish you know it's like it's like um
like thing you learn on your own
oh yeah or it's like Angelina Jolie in
the wanted movie where it's secure
visible like whoa yeah all right anyway
oh well now I'm thinking about that
freak a book will come back listen when
last we saw our heroes they had found a
chamber deep below the strange city of
NEMA's ear and this chamber housed and a
creature that called itself an elder
brain the you know known to be the final
stage in the evolution of a mind flayer
but it was quite at your mercy indeed it
was sort of suspended on a kind of rack
almost like a drying skin in the Sun too
clearly diminished from its absolute
power but I did have a task that it
wanted the party to manage because in
its current state there was distantly
things that it cannot do now I am
skipping over a painful moment for some
something did happen to the horse
coriander and then when I went on to
Twitter people said that I had done it
you did we did do it but I but that's
not true I I am you know what I mean
it's like you're just hard to stop well
think it's into it mystery now here's a
limit I prefer if you're going back it's
like a vision
I am simply imagine that I have poked my
head through and I'm just relating these
facts to you this is all actually
happening somewhere that's the best way
to think of it I'm not arguing with you
but I'm also saying that you made that
thing happens somewhere but you don't
like listen think about the fullness of
time think about how rich and complex
all these interweaving may be
who can say in the fullness of time
coriander is dead I can say I know I
know I'm not telling you that I killed
it I learned in their own group
backdated a word I learned it from
watching you
alright I'm going there yeah BAM that's
a lot women exactly exactly you know let
it read on your leisure we've all seen
that movie I know listen
um we're gonna talk about the crevasse
now or later is that well right now
we've been yeah any no it's not like
that
um oh god that's got to be a Google Maps
plugin that's all I'm saying bare
minimum so let's think about it like
this you are now before this entity and
last time it became a sort of strange
game of 20 questions
this entity's intellect is vast and so
the thing that happened at the end of
the adventure last time was that you
used it basically to check in on things
that would happen all through your
character's careers functionally arles
truth Korean beef indeed but now you are
all together in it's sort of you know
dank fillet and you have a guy need you
have agreed to undertake its task which
consists of the destruction of what it
calls roots which I think generally
speaking would be a strange a strange
way to describe the foundation of a
building but it's never there who knows
why there are three of them and he has
offered a guide to help you get to each
of these places anytime you are ready to
explore the undercarriage of Mnemosyne I
don't have an opportunity to rest and
get our going fits all back in business
we just take a nap right in front of the
brain can I tell you guys the name of
the quest I give this across maybe even
though it doesn't have well in the
document sir it's called
rootin tootin root busting is stupid I
love it has a light flute implicit the
main thing is that you're having it fun
no amazing or that everyone at home is
having fun he said I'm having fun that's
right that's the key but it also is very
walnut it's just like you know it's it's
her book and she can write where the
she wants to in there who has no
consequence but yeah how you manage how
you manage your your time before this I
mean the reality is that if I recall
correctly the party is not doing a
hundred percent great know right now is
that what the short-run not I was going
to say why not a long rest
why not why not why don't we stay here
as were a great weeks we asked the brand
can may we slumber beneath your hey your
ambra come metagame for a minute I don't
know a lonely thing about it I don't
know anything about that stuff we're
going to run into which is fun I'm
coming in not a little rating up on
these things things you know around
you my brain my whole job it's my whole
job right as as your tour guide here is
to make sure that you see like all the
really important stuff I got a senior
inside a sense yeah exactly but really
how I got to see the loose yet got it
yeah exactly
your mind has to look like I'm scaring
them asleep plan
oh my guessing needs this oh just going
to see but you were so you actually saw
what kind of statistics these things
drop all right a little bit of reading
up on them yeah yeah you don't have to
read much I do read the first part of a
stat block if this thing's trapped -
then what's trapping it it's crazy yeah
super crazy crazy enough to trap I don't
want to know any wandering crib yes that
was your question I was like wait do we
want to kill these roots because also I
think made you if it could trap a brain
I can travel crypt you can travel
braining kappa chris that's a graphic
line yeah okay all right I got a cramp I
could go one day without hearing that
dinar I love that you are thinking in
this way but assume ours not Ryan it's
you
cars like yet dinars just thinking I'm
great I'm great hungry and tired
now it's tempered and I'll time to say
what about my sex Bush is doing right
now I'm gonna drift off thinking about
it yeah sex is the new eggy that's
exactly right
right you know we're gonna its transfer
in it so you you asked I use new 20 sex
bags a new exhibition egg so you see
your assholey you can fully we do this
work for you we need time to rest these
these pathetic corporeal bodies you know
I know how it is if anyone Oh betrayal
of the matter
wesh2 there's just one more thing I want
to emphasize I saw people in my mentions
referring to the Eldar brain as an elder
Brian huh this is not acceptable this is
my life's work
this is my novel I'm allowing you to
read it by watching the stream do not
call it the elder bit pipe client
ecology regret Oh Ryan old bride around
overlooking a hole Brian bridges are
they out the other brain says I will not
notice you can see you can see that it's
attended to by this swarm of glowing
rats and you can you can see them sort
of skittering around even up onto the
roots and over the surface dumping what
appears to be thimble sized buckets of
moisture just along the servant of the
rain ooh that's kind of food that was
for you those little gallows done those
wrinkles down there so just dripping
boom let's collect the rest exactly but
you put hate but you can see just your
lovin I hate this thing no one looks
this one's pretty good
Sarris best friend yeah I marry this but
I have one other brown friends that get
some gaudy brains we all know they're um
but essentially just even while you're
having this conversation with it
there are we imagine and think
like inside of a lava lamp just how that
serves that fluid body and then there
are constantly just sort of orbs pulling
themselves away that's what's happening
to this massive rats you can tell that
just chunks of this mass are just being
tasked with things so they're coming
back in groups and joining the throng
and then one and then two to three going
out it's just managing some psychic
network down here and no sooner have you
asked to rest then another one of these
you know little conclaves returns
pulling behind it a satchel uh full of
delicious snacks really bring friend you
bingo rat hey Bible get it relevant
press delivery service and have some
laughs there's a mattress or something
yeah yeah you do a queen-size bed for me
yeah it's not 100% clear why they would
or indeed how they would have brought a
bag like this three seconds after your
request that'll be something for you to
think about later but it is it seems
prepared to manage the physical needs of
here and the extent to which you can
ously you can sleep inside of this
glowing brain chamber full of rats I
can't think what were think I mean it
sounds great
are you gonna wash your brush wash your
teeth brush your teeth in the leftovers
you see you never know go come on are
you swishing how what whatever what's
right what snacks are in the bag never
look a gift rat in the mouth oh just Jim
Jim
okay cut oh alright I remember my
discretion cake and I get little cakes
and fruits rule strips of tender jerky
Wow a bit of moist spring air no it's
all the rest assembly I'm sorry I'm in a
super good mood great what for jerky
made out of a whole unit survival oddly
fresh fancy-pants yes interesting not
only its walnut vegan Oh
one is a very complicated relationship
no you're you you are welcome to
enunciate some EPA mythology here if you
want um they are very much into like
yeah they they they hunt it's not like
for sports for function and they are
very much into leaving a piece of
anything that they get or harvest for
their duties so Oh pouring out for my
wine out for me leaky yeah yeah nice I
love it I love it Merry Christmas
okay I'm overjoyed but yeah snacks food
there's I mean it's nothing but strange
corners in here you could definitely set
yourself up with a small area to rest
it's not cold by any means in this
chamber I think I just feel like I'm
Lulu being lured into some like is it
like you also stand too close to a
microwave if I can also sleep too close
to no rain I'm running it for the dreams
we have wellness yeah yeah a friend I'm
going to send us some good news
can I ask elder Brian if he was
responsible
it was responsible for the wraps that we
had to eliminate as part of our quest to
be here were those his wrap my rats are
those you see before you okay my
raspberry portion of myself right so we
were hired to come here and eliminate
the rat problem but that is that you the
problem of your existence I have a
theory about this okay I didn't spend a
lot of time observing mayor for Nelson
Gore because he's an idiot and I felt
confident that I would not learn a lot I
think that he dealt with the wrong rat
problem okay cryptic what do you mean by
that I think he was issued a specific
directive to manage rats those rats you
see in my Nimbus here I think that
because he is an idiot he managed a
mundane rat problem okay you are a
separate rat problem from the rat
problem that we found
I don't see a problem it's good problems
my opinion would always lovely rats okay
checking just I want to make sure those
weren't it's rat crowd surfing around
like you don't lay on the floor you just
lay on the level of rat and they just
kind of you know it's you know I
bet it's like a Mexican just as good I
bet if you're right Danny right over hey
it's just like it is just like you just
grabbed the table you're like yep moral
oh yeah with a lumbar support and it's
like those magic fingers yeah you know
what I mean much a little paw is just
working mm-hmm I am working on your
substrate it's got the side of they all
have like Slade heads open right yeah
what about bleeding and scary things
there's no there's no like normal rats
just a bunch of little cherry servitor
that's not that's not my own seat right
look around
are there any Trevor like rats or
regular runs trying to be part of like a
where red no yes you don't any any
normal rep here mostly had a little
bloom bar boy whoa - babe what are we
doing man I'm really mad I kick I'm
happy Joanna said Oh some horse meat and
I should maybe go to sleep yeah let's
take let's take a rapid do we want to or
I guess the cloud man came LT ain't
gonna kill Brian can wake up I asked for
a wake-up call yeah no Brian
if anything goes down will you wake up
with your psychic if you have a concept
of what's going down really yes no I
mean like it's cool tell me what do you
know if a crazy never newly we're losing
our California your orange would you be
like I'm fine lunch was okay sure you
want to make sure that he's not thinking
of your alien forms in a way that's that
diminishes like the physicality of your
body we're getting you know chopped up
well he says he says you will come to no
harm here oh no like NO not K and o W B
I don't want to know yeah
I ran a pan I said smell it right now
but if it's like no it's like you come
to no harm here in the harm zone no
we're going to come to no harm for
another reason
examining her everybody no harm
I will god I only have I lost alarm Oh
and that but I do have unseen servant we
know which I'd love to take the
opportunity to restore velvet the
softest ghost alive premium goes in
addition Oh more treats await I'm gonna
bring back the gaudy my my tentacular
snake indeed I'm gonna use fine familiar
and burn ten gold worth of my
ingredients required question yes you
have a third companion now canonically I
believe it's true you do have a you do
have a tiny serpent god damn in a very
they like is it that worry and that you
look at a lot of it no how did you know
like no but like so the adventure we
played it's all real it occurred that
the stream of annihilation event Erick
is simply occurred during one of your
stopovers and read large previously so
that makes been in your life I have
always had a like oh that's right yes I
do listen good as a period of time when
you had Locati
and then the snake and it was like in
the bag they just like hey how are you
doing I mean yet no obviously I can only
hurry up alright no I'm gonna rely my
precious snakes ligardi oh my god look I
got in kenosha mine my familiar is a
severed tentacle this is other ones just
the snake exactly no comparing wow
you're saying that right in front of
them alright we're just getting more and
more ashamed know that a tiny snake
slithers away along the side of the road
and the theme from the end of the TV
show the incredible home always it's
like the piano one half dozen good yeah
yeah thank you know you have a snake
thank you my knee that's make for later
not what is miss Nikki look snakes
we can eat it George okay thank you okay
so know what this is in character let's
let's let's roleplay this right now so
you are finding the Gotti yeah and so
I've invoked him one
more I got a rich was completed he has
returned he forms out of nothing now my
my tentacle is back I couldn't be more
pleased I'm come over and look at
wrestling let Michael say oh that's
right
are you this guy did I buy it donut are
you to finish that fake well yours you
want it um since we're at the end of the
day I'll beat you up burn a little speak
with animal I love you like use my
little parcel personal personal time
yeah good
um and say I hit it a little bit you
want to upgrade from clanking around
that drowse pocket go from that zero and
come on to this here oh yeah yeah I say
that what meets will we find aa little
range I don't talk a lot of rats a good
uh and I'll say it seems we have many
enemies so the meat of all them but they
don't hear it but they do it clear they
do not hear that you go ten nonetheless
yeah yes even though even though you're
certain that in snake culture there's no
such thing as an affirmative nod you see
something like that mmm from the snake
anything it goes over as it rises it
rises up to be the picture up it's like
one natural hitting membrane yeah yeah
yeah yeah I takes a little danger noodle
and put them in my stocking answer nice
we got it we got to get that treat we
got to get that sort of like prehensile
grip like you imagine a scenario to
imagine a scenario where this serpent
coils up and is like where you keep the
quill yeah way to place on the desk and
you just like right in into venom just
use it as a pen yeah anyone eat the
document yeah I use a snake paper
invisible I don't work yeah look made
out of yeah my words like secret words
whether my words actually helping me was
remedial documentary writing he helps
you cursive but yes no a it's like a
heat and he's paid for by the school
it's all your IEP so the way that it
works is ECL head poked out so you think
under ordinary circumstances a rat would
be welcome appreciated but there's
something about to use rats but is not
delicious spokesman doesn't like it
mm-hmm
no he flips right back in every every
now and then you think you might see the
tongue slip out of a little crease in
the pouch it's kind of just kind of
keeping a keeping a sense out there is
the name danger noodle no no the Aloha
Beezus know they'll have to be a very
deep involved naming process obviously
Jay what's what's my guy doing what's
the Daddy up to Michael I was make -
what's he what he did what what doing my
pocket doing cool stuff
Jay was like oh cool thing also he's
inspired to do much do you want
Christmas I can give you as much success
with you know I will tell you this I
like now that my familiars back like now
we rest as much stock worth to be done
ahead of us but I'm like absent mindedly
heading this week temple next week and
then Mike joins like that so it's been
just up by the up by the edge of the
cloak opens its mouth right by the ear
you can feel this in the hot air coming
from it and it begins to rattle off and
in its whatever its method of
communication is and you think it's
almost like it's almost like a stream of
data it's just everything that happened
time-stamped from when he was
annihilated just everything he
experienced like every state change
that's upset every every every every
medium he passed through living and
non-living every dark dream literally
stored on him on the vellum right it's
like playing a record and then and then
when he reaches the current moment he
withdraws himself that's choice all
right
but yeah so so this wrist rest Ville yes
sleepy
the dreams that you have imagined have
you ever been in a crawl space yeah yeah
all the time but yes for real yeah yeah
it's been one right now emotionally
there just like there is basically the
dreams that you have are like that you
meet the sorts of people you would meet
in a dream and you do everything that
you would do in a normal dream but it's
all on your belly and the way that you
go from place to place and do all the
normal dream things is just by crawling
place to place it's like there's some
ceiling above maybe a foot or two above
the ground that you can't get up past
all your dreams just pushed down yeah
doesn't it deeply compress not that
different for me
yeah she's her own kind of those kind of
dreams yes she's just very small I made
a bad thing but but I get that way at it
you you get not grown you get your you
feast upon your your full rest I'm
feeling you get up.get so you're hit
dice you get your points yeah you can
give you guys we're not expending hit
dice don't forget that's always a way
it's always no it's always a way to get
no okay right like it's noisy on all the
notes during a short rest
you can expend these hit nice and top
yourself up that's their purpose
yeah isn't it short rest every day this
is I think a long rest is the right
choice
I mean I need a top-off big-time
breakfast yeah you need to be route of
spells and other life okay exactly about
it exactly so you taught back up all
your spell's you ready to go you you you
wake back up and there's no alteration
in the chamber as near as you can tell
the basic ambient light is the same I
mean you have to think for a moment and
assess yourself and verify that you have
secured some kind of rest yeah this is
this is a timeless sort of strange vault
of a chamber like we all slept at the
same time we're just super trusting okay
we're going to get your OPI design evil
brain and rats oh well they won't turn
on
either just like yeah evil yeah he needs
us what is evil what is evil in this
crazy workaday world we are yeah yeah I
mean other than we are the reactions
incorporated I'm not evil read large
desperate Valley branch yeah I think
excess incorporated us a thing for Table
Talk I didn't know that it was even out
okay okay I'm done done what else all
right I got my starter stepping right
now we get it we wake right soon so we
were told about a guy are we ready to
proceed and who will guide us what will
guide us what is one of these is what am
i continues okay okay we know what you
want to follow put a little hat on them
oh you'll know we should put a hat on it
so you can see up above up above adage
chamber again like like the rest of the
construction here is is non-traditional
in shape and texture and it's even
stranger the farther down you get
beneath Nana's ear so up from as I said
you pass through multiple sort of
illusory walls on the way here along
with the rest of the twists and turns
which of course roseyd singer could you
know navigate expertly but you just see
sort of holes and passages almost like a
honeycomb in the in the ceiling of the
of Elder Brian's chamber and essentially
you see a mass of his servants the froth
and spill over beneath one of these and
then you see them form atop one another
you see them form a kind of stair that
you can use to exit in one place okay
like that
I'll go first I guess some of you
you're looking up this Shasta can I see
the daylight or it turn some other
directions yeah yeah it's just it's just
another place essentially this is a
nexus point deep in the guts of this
town
I can't stifle my mmm when I step on the
zombies plush rat yeah this some gift
but not as much as you would expect
right and it's like you don't know what
what the etiquette is as far as like
doing step on the brain right you know
what it's like you know you don't know
like like where you exist in this
hierarchy of politeness I step on one
step and it's really unpleasant for me
so I look at walnut and like can I ride
I mean I'm fine with this oh you love
destroying in my life that's not
entirely true quiet
Rosie is asking her let you like look
over and well it's like are you ready to
be put on yeah ready backpack okay I get
halfway up the stairs I'm watching
Dinaric realizing good I'm at Morty ways
I'm just wondering came through rats
like they do why to deal with it see
yeah they're like yeah I'm like sorry
sorry they died under be consistent on
grid' yeah Kevin was a cracker and
apologizing to the rappers they died as
I killed them yeah so you wait so at
least I can do it step by step as they
as they move up this stair and out into
the tunnel proper above you begin to
make your way and it's almost like
stepping on a balloon like you walk up
and then you see like the shape that
they have tried so dutifully to
manufacture for you it's sort of
distending underneath it and then once
they sort of calibrate themselves to
your draconic heft and a couple more
contingents come over and help bolster
the the lowest portions of this you're
able to get out just a couple steps past
you can see that that was probably all
they were capable of and you see you see
you see just collapse then you see more
fears of rats begin to move out here and
there but there is a tiny rat perhaps
the tiniest cranium rat who held on to
the edge and then who doesn't split up
and then he gets out in front of the
party
and begins to sort of like hiding bounce
okay
Rosie's in love yeah yeah listen heat
and he he is ready for that love he is
ready to be a vessel for that look
something you can win us over with a red
after what you did or what if it was a
really big round what if I could rig a
real card what if I could read so big
what if one of you I couldn't kill it
what if a collection rabbit a my new
horse exactly a Porsche a cluster and
even maybe like here's a we hollow out
coriander we fill up a rat like a like a
Honda 90 right work the body there good
there we are back to normal there horse
coop is like math no they quickly you
hold up the Apple for this new horse the
mouth opens rat sporatic just a precious
little mouth take it and pull it in
yeah okay it's very much I know that is
Ignasi a ting so you find your way
through this tunnel smooth balls nice
premium all night okay
bizarre mixture of stones and by a dense
root mat that clings to the walls that
you're traveling through hate that guy
yeah just intrude mad rude man but you
hear you hear something down the
corridor that sounds almost like a wind
chime like imagine if you could make
vision it was possible to make a wind
chime out of incredibly large metal
cylinders instead of the ones that are
typically done
imagine something like a free-floating
pipe organ yeah and you begin to hear
these notes sail down the tunnel and
then you can see that this towel
ultimately opens up into a room your
best guess is that it's almost an L
shape with a long part of the elbows in
front of you and then a corner extends
out to the right you can see the room
itself is loaded with columns and it's
also stuffed with a root structure so
dense in places and so fine and others
that it's almost like a spider web the
columns themselves seem to be blanketed
in this sort of fragile mesh but that's
coupled with what you can see sort of
between a row of these regularly placed
columns you can see that there is a
thick trunk that extends entirely
through the room straight through the
middle and it's its construction is you
can recall when you were with the Brian
you could see that the construction of
the roots that have sort of pierced and
suspended it in that you know and what
must be torment of some kind
they have different sort of materials
that make them up one of them almost had
a metallic sheen due to its mystic
construction so these are not so these
roots are not winding around metal
columns but I assume have air movement
or they're not like banging into each
other like a wind chime no no no there's
to be a stringy mesh that extends out
from it so just like a traditional root
how once it's once it's defined and
established there's that exactly yeah
that's sort of that sort of army of fine
that come out into the soil so this is
why I'm an idiot
this is the real room so these are the
sacred these are the roots we need to
get rid of yeah this is this is you if
you have it you have been brought to the
live in diameter
and there seems to be one central tuber
one big boy and it if stretching
horizontally toward us it is basically
cutting across the room okay I see
imagine this sort of in the middle of
that l-shape that sort of bisects the
corner that's where that root is coming
through do we have reason to believe
that this root going to follow the the
core of it would take us to Brian and
Pierce him that seems that seems
sensible okay hmm I do a perception
check on the this room he's trapped yeah
yeah absolutely you hear another you
hear another cascade of these wind chime
sounds sort of bouncing around in the
room and then commingling themselves
into tunnel that you're in a 16-time
that's great you're trying to assist I
kinda want to make sure that this room
is safe to enter so I'm looking for
obvious dangers you don't yeah you don't
you don't see any obvious means there's
nothing there's nothing clear from the
from what you might call the dark foil a
okay
what's a for you okay yeah how I get the
opportunity to Safeway yeah could we
resell them so it's great in my normal
life in that York Lobby and that's you
first oh yeah we feel it's a great just
to set up all the traps yeah exactly
hey you didn't like these damn landline
okay fine it's got it on the head here
tons of hair point really I know I'm
like supremacy of the bank
okay now would be a great children's
book the squishiest Hank I wear my blood
on the outside yeah most of time say so
you you you the rest of the party is in
the tunnel mouth itself and you sent
dinar blitz and yeah
I chopped the back of his legs with my
staff to try to get into Oh No head on
in okay I'm ready good you hello
i denounce myself as i guess it's a
freer purposes cartographer the initial
room the leftmost part of this L shape
you can see six of these columns at
regular intervals basically two four six
okay
and then beyond in the rest of the L
there is another four back there but
it's all sort of uniform in shape
hi this is what I need most from you
dinar Blitzen
I need to know what it look like when
you rolls first still not good you never
know it was rolled my little ones in are
very surprising Oh
shadow counsel I invoke your blessing
upon this ritual may our labors please
you dinar Blitzen eyelash a massive self
boy has happened not dinar Valyrian has
delivered a premium stealth experience
indeed so premium that the shadow
council will receive a reward hmm
wonderful uh so as you enter right
between Alex you can kill you can shut
it I have a twenty okay I can do give it
a fire I have to save it to work in the
Rose one no this this when you extend ei
even into the real world
I'm the zone between the two columns on
the right you you you move in expert
lessly not even a creak from the leather
straps you place your hand against it
and then you look back you look past and
you are there immediately when the
denizen of this place clearly on some
kind of
has just is just now passing out a
vision he's not looking this way this is
a that it is essentially like a massive
angry metal statue hmm my favorite kind
of message angry mob is I'm like yes
should we go okay what do you see Phoebe
we have angry metal statue nothing
Arizona you graduated anyway it I can
you fit that halfling Carmen oh I don't
know there like this madam a tax down
for that anniversary so they eat your
Pacific near the speed it defeated
something this is clearly if it is made
of what it looks you made of this is
this is an incredible piece of work even
standing absolutely still without a good
night player down them yeah even
standing absolutely still it would be an
incredible work but it is it is
ambulatory and you can see Kohl's sort
of burning in the math how tall are we
talking oh it's very very tall underdone
it is fifteen feet tall
alright towering that's a big boy you
see that already look at least 100 feet
at all yes anything taller than me is
100 feet it's like skeleton is got to be
like in our size six stories no it's
dinner size and then there's people yeah
and then there's anything bigger and
that includes everything from an
alligator to a god yeah absolutely so
you put a business a so it's strangely
the feet from this device don't make any
sound as they move but you still hear
this this musical clamor just come in
who knows what is generating it but it
seems to be generated specifically by
this
ah instrument mm-hmm and it's or it's
originating from this metal file it is
in fact and as it passes you can see you
can hear that music just sort of playing
off there off the rest of these halls
and off of the columns and is it seem to
be patrolling this room it is it is in
fact it has just moved past the route
that is hang that it's hanging under has
to duck slightly and it's going to that
shape press passing left okay they're
moving into the top of the L okay got it
could I see your map cartographer you
can but I'm not very don't that's very
good let's thank you
very good ma'am great map so all right
um so you're did you sneak back in or
are you just like yeah crouched in the
in the entry didn't see me before so
well I'm fine where I am
okay uh uh I think we need some stealth
yeah you think you know he's away
writing around the corner yeah they're
like you closest clear yeah we got to
destroy this route before he gets but
like without him detecting that's right
cuz he looks like he could kick our butt
right yeah mmm all that you say is
murder him we're very good at one thing
apparently there's okay get work very
okay one thing we do it alive
okay I'm gonna advocate we stealth in
here I give you a path up trace darkness
combo if half of that traces the way go
for now but if it comes if goes
down then I can darkness and hopefully
it will go this can I perceive the route
like I want to look at this but what do
you what do you want anime in Ruth yeah
I want to see if it's like go for it if
it rectified it's going to require a
team effort or one person can get in and
sabotage it
I am all about this let's see it Graham
eight it's a route yep definitely
organic matter it's stick I mean it's
this I mean it's nice you saw you hate
too
to cease thanks so as you're looking at
it you can see from around this edge
it's actually what happened that's how I
got sprung sound let's take a true it is
the winter listen listen if there's not
incredibly hot route fanart after this
yeah
listen how do we destroy this room this
is like this is almost like that I got
it you seen around the edge I mean over
on the right side it's sending out but
this is like a tree trunk okay like this
this root coming down like you don't
know what building this sustains but
this is this is not you don't know if
two of you could do is this organic and
it is we're going to let out palak one
yeah yeah this is in general the
materials that make up newest areas
construction our bizarre hybrid of
metals and stone okay okay that's it has
it has it has a machine concrete it has
a metallic sheen to it and is also
incredibly thick what could burn away
what could dissolve ja I bought really
like this well I know it'll conduct
electric legolas time yeah get that
summer let's have a acid she's on oh
sure let me do the whole thing
I'm obtaining ha ha ha crucify right
after their kind of kraangdroids I've
been thinking about the game this week
class headed for that vomit yeah alright
no my my okay can you do it quietly the
quick regardless I'm gonna do that race
would you give this all happened on give
yourself checks I like that okay and it
will ready from me so stick close and
now everybody has what fun stuff ray for
the next say ray one hour okay so go 1
hour I figure does that see you don't
want to barf on it I don't think that
barfing on it
with I can swing my sword harder than I
can bark like do more damage or the sort
thing that I can with a pukey puke on it
quite fun he's on your sword she's
beautiful
if you want me to vomit on this thing I
will it's going to call that look there
the Oh the Gundam over here is another
question how how far when he ratted that
corner how far is that in order for ya
he is about to from that from the
doorway itself he is about 25 feet okay
a head I mean this is this is intimate
this is gonna be an intimate venue for
stealth maneuvers okay we can hide
behind the column when and when when
john-boy comes back what if we did uh
he's a big boy she can Zelda yeah I'm
you can't again like breath of a while
yeah yeah so here's what happens
ready okay so guys that she citizen
trolls with him okay
yeah that's a big boy right bring ah
thank you so far okay that's him and
then this is the route and this is us
and we're like ah but you can't get us
dinner so something annoying Sizzlin off
and then he's like oh I'm gonna kill you
but actually he hits the roof yeah yeah
although I did just cast across that
tree yeah so if you can dispel it well
so it really is just a +2 stealth you
know check I promise that if you jump
around oh look at the rest of us could
be stealthy and then the other person
could delenn but I'm not gonna use this
word but be sure we good I can kick in
the back I'm not the most agile though
but mad most agile person should jump
out of the way right yeah and I direct
velvet to to run out and make sure you
keep an eye on this thing when it starts
to walk back this direction come back
give me a tunnel okay so we'll know give
me a gentle rise on cheeks even more one
caress other kind of kisses yeah you
call him velvet but you doesn't have the
velvet real well with it don't
yeah that's what it is the day by happy
for the soft gray five kisses if he's
coming so Laura people yeah so that's
five you did we could get more cooks you
might want to get you might want to get
a piece of fabric just to maintain this
or no in my mind I took that fabric from
the blood even a pen yeah it's not buy
anymore Eve I make sure you clean a room
good especially I thought employers keep
it pulled eyes closed and when we need
to see them yeah with my laundry right
now he doesn't see no this is a super
cool plant is also a gamble therefore
noncorporeal therefore he could distract
them sing and run right there
that's true yeah why put us in the way
yeah every time I give any alizarin
abilities like where you could like I
have I mean I've got a manifest
something in front of I have
prestidigitation I could we could light
a torch or something I have found that
Andy hold it yes I've minor illusion as
well a kid we could hide behind these
columns and manipulate this without even
showing up well he kind of far away
right now we all just go hang on we'll
see we'll see what happens you or we
could just stay hidden the whole time I
guess there is there is
wow you are interesting let's see if you
come back and destroy himself well you
can always pick on him or his feet see
this pianist can pick on all of us I'm
getting a roll around swap around in it
yeah just for lowliness looking at
excite all right what is your maneuver
acquisitions incorporating I'm down for
staying hidden and try to do this from
that is pretty remote Sandler remote
yeah I mean I'm all but ya know
ineffectual though so you're going to a
user Bailey you won't try to MIT you
want to try to manipulate slash manage
this really from the mouth of the exit
see if we can yeah okay all right
Chinese I'm looking at the range some of
this like my vomit stance
oh there this ah okay so yes so change
of plans love it return unto me your
loving father
yes me uh what do you want me to do give
them give them a little a little torch
get some get some kindling and you just
carries it over there and then and then
hightails it back here well he's gonna
he's gonna act as bait if we can get
right way to charge him yeah let's do
that up that route okay okay absolute
can make sounds I get to get bang to
think oh you can't do that velvet sing
on them so yeah he's true velvet let's
do that in a Frank and then bangarang
can write go bang clang clang go high
why my trial depressed I like it all the
way back to yeah so you saw the crew the
crew this is sort of huddled in this
side corridor while the music is growing
louder as this contraction is beginning
to move toward the foyer mouth you have
sent young velvet out dude of leaving
through I'm busy
yeah why you as soon as soon as young
velvet is sent forth to sort of navigate
this pac-man maze through these columns
the music substantially increases in
volume and the lethargy that you saw to
melts away it this is not a slope this
is not a slow frame
excellent this is not a fine size and
the oak drops so big whoa whoa so so now
the footballs are heavy behind velvet
you are sending velvet out with the
cover and the torch yeah little flower
blossom has the eye but you see
something strange as velvet goes out
between the columns and beneath the root
torch held aloft you see the you're you
know mechanical interloper stop turn and
then you hear what sounds like a like a
furnace door creeks open and then you
can see from behind
even this mass
of emerald gas that floods out and then
you can you can see Velvets tiny cape
sort of billow and you can see the flame
on the you can see on the flame the
flame of the torch become a green flame
um as it as it is exposed to whatever
this compound is okay and then yttrium
Burgess it okay I have a fine click onto
the dragon date I would like this no
listen so the bit of green flame what
was once it burns out of this compound
yeah it returns to its original color
and then you hear that Creek closing
again and then it begins to take off
toward velvet okay so it knows the drill
he's going to run over to which part of
the relief did you like just whatever is
the best in a stereo first no papers on
it Dixon what Big Daddy see yeah so he
got to get turn up the mouth done it
kind of weird there um so yeah yeah you
remember that sorry
he's just tantalizing himself yeah
like well flam is near this route is
that bad do you not like that to put it
out stamp it out you see you see but
velvet is low yeah velvet is low to the
ground and you see your mechanical
interloper kick straight through you see
the foot come back and then just go
straight through and then there's just a
cloth at the end of the foot and it
brings down he stomps on a couple times
trying to get it off of his boot but I'm
good though I don't know I might have
got involved over just still
instantiated but the cloth is gone um
but as a target velvet is very low yeah
okay your illusion okay what kind of
illusions are we are we going forward do
we want to distract him back into the
room
or do we want to have him do it well
these right here's a route right now
okay what do I put something like all
over
root like oh yeah he's on the roof okay
really no backlash
you ever see the most what looked like
he's going to go after anything that
moves do some dancing was law everything
was there doing about the little
sparkles
yeah the sparkle try dancing lights or I
could do a minor illusion I could put
another illusion of velvet even up
higher on the on the branch and as
though to say haha you didn't get much
we got was making extra angry yes all
right
okay wait let's do it what's that again
I'm going to just do a minor illusion
okay I love it
higher up and it hopes that we'd get a
hit that's okay I see like of a cloth
like yeah man that's around us it yeah
yeah that acceptable absolutely okay I
will do that
that is nothing range they're talking
about misery yeah yeah a little people
are like middle finger right at yeah
yeah yeah that's not your nose got real
king whoa I love it oh yeah it is driven
mad excellent I mean in the manner of a
bull was exactly where I was going to
exactly listen this wriggling cloth
which seats the class up here looks down
and sees the cloth down there it looks
up and sees this cloth and then in a
motion it reaches up it could have been
a stove pipe or something like that off
the back to handle the massive sword
yeah then tilts out and in one motion
pulls forward slices forward and it
probably catches half its half stuck
tank in this route okay okay well we're
halfway there
well I don't think it can destroy my
illusion so I think I'll have to work
pretty hard yeah I think I think the
illusions just gonna stick around the
quickie chance our yeah yeah yeah look
so good I look like a dodged and came
told me to to give the middle finger
whoa
this robot
Yahoo it is this working mightily to get
your sword out of it it begins to adopt
a series of behaviors that are bizarre
like it's a scenario that that maybe it
doesn't have a good answer for it parent
grab it interested give it half way and
then it in and that pipe opens it emits
a blast working workers to work on it
again he's the one hurting the root yeah
busy counsel so and you don't think you
don't think that it you don't think the
root is getting any better by the act of
removing the sword you think this you
think of this root you sort of it's like
thinking you're like chewing on a carrot
like you're chewing around to carry and
it's basically like it is it is lacking
like those vital the vital part of this
root have seen better days at this point
but you can see that the edge around the
damaged this is that it's like peeled up
in a way like bark um right around the
edge is it like it like it died around
the time you don't know about that you
just think that it's not any type of
root that you know about okay but it's
not like healing and no no you don't say
anything like that okay dummies yeah I
always make a selfie lemonade yes let's
just face it it's a neuron there you go
uh I need zombie king city the city of
the journey I'm going to you so much RG
to make the sound of hideous laughter
come out of my illusion oh I hate robot
yeah there you go about their dumb you
can't even cut this women ass yeah and
you I bet you totally can't pull the
sword out and hit the fruit again it was
lame is what why that's like Jesus
Christ like the robot seven solvers yeah
it is it is now slice another second
part of the route I yeah yeah it is now
sort of moved its attentions over here I
mean and this time it doesn't get stuck
but it is continuously trying to go at
this immortal ghost yeah
Rosie is very very very quietly laughing
her ass off by the way watching this
this is the this is the most delightful
thing when I are eating popcorn just
like it's good as it's happening this
way but I could have done it I could
have done mention that route to I was
big for the record I have a big sort to
thank you have you a nicer make him sing
cute that he got an edge of it so he
doesn't live up to past um I think I'm
saying that he's like tug tug all chummy
just it yeah okay so I you want to
collaborate yeah we're gonna we're going
to do that do you want to weld it still
out there you want to do anything with
velvet to get up there um but he could
put the thing back on I guess so but I
don't want to cause he could but I don't
think you want to distract the robot
from the work that's up that set I love
a great work yeah way to kick another
hey I can't actually use this spell
again hope okay okay um for until short
grass and burn all myself
figured hearings say that yeah
videos or something else yeah Larry says
are a her a before you understand
obviously I just I just thought that I
never seen anything like that before and
like I said well you're correct okay so
um yeah I don't have I have anything
else to great at the moment but are you
saying but you're trying to deliver yeah
I have a more exciting pray oh it's
gonna say I was gonna use some energy
again everyday almost got me that time
wait so they're pretty scared what's the
extent of minor illusion can you still
manipulate it or have you just said make
a make a dancing cloth and then that's
the end of it it is the sound image of
an object in range the last of the
duration if a creature needs action to
examine it it can use a successful
intelligence check okay that's it I I
think it's pretty sad oh it's just
wiggling around yeah oh yeah I don't
think I can yeah it's like a fly like I
have fishing fly yeah hi hi
okay okay two in one day yeah so you
think that you think that it might have
tired of this prey
oh right yeah yeah we got an every
Deepak here I've got a pretty good-sized
hack over here but it's not it's not
delivering results okay all right
I guess I got I got some some other
tricks yeah okay
I'm curious if I'm coming to when I got
a with the velvet can climb up but maybe
it's time for a different yeah what else
you guys hey guys let's going to see I
won I won in arts I want to draw extra
attention to walnut Don grass mmm
how many normal spell cards yeah is
gonna say this is what playing Dungeons
&amp; Dragons looks like yes right guys this
is how it actually works right there's a
lot of looking in books and obviously
that's the best this is this is what you
have to resort to when Alyssa gives you
just a pile of sell cards listen and
yeah yeah a lot of circle and lizards
trying to make sure you get an authentic
D&amp;B experience right um okay
here's what I do I have a snake in my
pocket gun Louise I like to hear no no
no no no I do have druid craft though I
could make uh oh I could make something
happen that's not I mean I can't get
like a whole pray I can do like a sound
of an animal or I could like instantly
light something yeah yeah Miller I was
going to do dancing lights to make a
humanoid up there
I think it's I think it's attracted to
visuals more than noise oh okay
so let's see that time you did it I'll
be there yeah okay so I'm going to go
ahead and use dancing lights up the room
and stuff so I need a moment to recover
so it makes a I form it on the on the
side facing away so that I can make it
appear as though it's crawled up and do
its eye line lick it and it is a such a
glowing man the size of a person and
it's and it's just hanging out up there
on the roof I don't think I don't think
I have any more people really man
I like this it don't describe this
glowing man uh yeah lowing boy you talk
about me what is it brother
is there a mission blowing man is rich
fanfiction IOC blowing man he's arrived
yes even waiting yeah hey load no it
basically looks like one of those aliens
from cocoon camera movie yeah yeah
that's a weird glowing man and if I have
the ability I do want to give it to
little Rick's got our eyes and I mean I
can move it but I don't think I can like
just stick you late with it so maybe
there's a little to stuff you said oh
very nice indeed he's just sort of
scintillating up on that yeah just like
a crouched figure like did you see the
you see VA making it absolutely oh yeah
I got it like an all-day little dick
nice write down stay right you see them
you see V it's like a nope I love life I
mean look at the young man reform nice
so all of the units of light populated
Laxman's
you see the you can hear the furnace
door creeks open again you see another
emerald blast go over the top when that
has no effect right you see him
hunker himself underneath the root and
then try to swipe at it from the back
okay and when it connects you can see it
the the part where it's almost like
where you cut that wedge out of a tree
and then you let it fell basically we
have a lot of damage here and then some
damage here and then when he swipes he
clears out the rest of the back of the
root and it sort of dangles there and
then you see it look down at the root
and then try to lift the root back up
but the vital SAP makes it a challenge
oh yeah and so it's sort of slipped out
and then it puts itself up underneath it
and tries to hold it up with its
shoulder feel so bad now I did all the
help a brain that's list a little bit
and then he moves over a little bit like
this and tries to hold it like this and
you think that this might go on for
quite some time
what's that SAP look like tell me about
spinal fluid but the SAP is actually not
a hundred percent unlike mr. glowing man
oh yeah it is it is it is I'm rich
well hunk is rich and vital yeah hmm
with a glow to it was a color of the
glow in my mind my glowing man is yellow
it is history okay so just look like
toxic green goop glorp you'd be
surprised if it was toxic
oh look so it looks good I you're read
under a tall rock right okay big boys
busy we could go get a scoop yeah I
could have velvet bring you to I want I
want some of this for reason we have a
son Miss amendment Oreo get get velvet
to do with this because we've got a nice
hidey hole a reason to go out there
wagging our fingers after we've already
won yeah let his supervisors think that
yeah exactly
you know the paperwork halftime but
there was a blanket and then of going
man I didn't official report you gotta
you didn't bee sting it was so
bright I had to garden I winged him
I couldn't let that live it was too
powerful I am NOT ready we're not ready
to present
uh like I sensed that that velvet is
looking at me in whatever ways it's like
it's completely you just impede all the
properties however you feel about
whatever you're doing is how we can
velvet feel we can do it so the genuine
like what I believe is the accurate way
which is I can't
actually communicate with it when it's
apart from me right it has no mind for
me to speak to right so it does come
back having finished its work yeah now
once back I said go back out there and
visible scoop up some neck green goop
until it's like think that glop in your
belly
yeah come back with a full tummy and yes
before Hawkins oh he's corporeal I
thought that allocation he can do that
because everything he could bring unlike
if you if you couldn't do it it'd be
like if there was an imaginary friend
really good job by this one yeah so he
tells you yeah oh yeah you know I was
serving you guys I told you see very
romantic Canadian and Susur chariot was
I'm sorry get me something that stuff
she doesn't like the anti Canadian
rhetoric and we need a training my
great-grandmother's Canadian so I can
say whatever I want most for that's true
so you so you so he slips out you can
sort of see slight disturbances in the
dust for strength and then you can see
that this this vital SAP has just begun
to it's flowing freely through this
injury and then this it begun to coat
this mechanical interloper virtually
from head to toe keep it up nothing yet
nothing anyway I mean I really got a
really good and so engine so you see but
the flow is rich man it's like a tapped
maple and you can see it pooling just in
space you can see it sort of following
pooling here and then that pool sort of
winds in the way back to the party I
want to get a little like I have like a
wine but not like a wine skin might have
a wine skin like a water skin can't be
entered on and I dump it out and like
put it out for the unseen server and I'm
like yeah nobody just put in there and I
see I see I see like a mouth like takes
I'm out of the thing
citizen yeah they're like oh I don't
know if I just drop it dick look in
there and I crooked my ticket
absolutely it even it's even inside the
container there's a stoppered bottle or
is it a skin the skin okay
um it doesn't sit still in there oh it's
movin
yeah it doesn't it doesn't sit still no
interesting um yeah
restless is listener what it man gonna
let it are less bad talk to talk to your
doctor about our Oh SSO huh my doctor
yes I need some help I need you're fine
just like sitting on the beach in a
bathtub flus right because Chicago so
you make you make your way back through
the tunnel having satisfied the
objective laid out before you buy the
older brand and then as you as you get
back your little pop hop friend beat you
to the edge it looks down and chitters
and then you see this staircase form
itself back up to your level and you can
then take that down through the through
the hole the tour going back to see the
brain going back to Bobby so Bobby the
brain my question is though before we
left we I mean we had a look at this
thing
do we have reason to row Boyd yeah the
robot do we have reason to think that my
life isn't is it the same metal and
stone constructs no are we waiting - you
didn't sense anything that was unified
about that okay I would addict are we
able to what might help us determine its
origin like every single thing built
like that before I be heard of something
like that before
well you've you've heard of different
types of automata okay um golems of
various kinds but you you haven't heard
of something like like this in
particular okay I just want to see if
there was any like we see if there's
more of these we have just keep in mind
if you ever if for whatever reason
during this adventure even now you might
see another one very soon okay I don't
know clearly spend more time you're
welcome
each time you're going to go we're gonna
sell the out of this - robe lights
so I guess this would be for ruling yeah
I went down to Justin yeah Cervantes
Reina all right now let's go to the
brain because we're gonna I wanna make
sure you we did it we're supposed to do
I want to do you feel better there
friend
yeah yeah exactly so you can you can see
that down from this from that direction
much as you would see ur eyes you can
see the root itself withering this is
not a natural level of decomposition
this isn't this is not how it works it
takes a little while but you can see
that it's almost shuddering with its
collapse
and you can see it shrinking in the
wound of the brain and because you
there's still there's still a
substantial cavity yeah inside the elder
brain but it doesn't express pain or
discomfort or anything like that
alright asking about how asking about
the GU gonna hold up the bag I don't say
Brian what's in this Brian
sorry Bobby I misspoke um elder Brian
elder Brian yeah brain actually yeah I
say this was flowing through the roots
that keep you bound here yes we're
talking to this um what would it be what
do you make it if shows him sure you'd
know more than I would and then I look
at it and then possibly roller survival
check yeah say how would that be figured
out amigo many forests do they have down
there
I don't know 30 I can't map what's that
parsecs yeah 13 it's still I mean it's
even inside the skin it's still full of
potentials and action okay
may I have a bright future yeah keep
going got away ideas warming in suburban
and it's a part of an after-school
program for
fluid great um and it submitted its
delivering results that's clearly I
quark it and then I queued back I also
make sure not to put it in the bag next
to the snake very concerned so what if
you tell that would be you don't want to
get James the Giant Peach scenario yeah
we end up with a bunch of like normal
ass bugs but now these bugs are
to you actually
do you want attention actually you know
what yeah I miss better than area yeah
so great ask him any time if you feeling
better I mean noticeable difference yet
as well as can be expected I expect that
the process of healing from this
inconvenience to take a hundred to two
hundred years
sounds good kind of anyway get a little
better right out the gates and us some
be able to annihilate you had a little
stronger so I can help us something
that's it you could like Triangulum yeah
give a little kiss like an actual uh on
that whole healthy yeah I get there uh I
appreciate the gesture I don't think it
would you appreciate somebody walking
inside of you to heal you I think it's
understanding I mean like lately John
little brain or out here let's go inside
and I get 100 annoyed you have yeah I
mean like used in my head one for names
in that's what I imagine the multi-angle
probably I'm gonna be a weirdo about it
how do you feel something uh why don't
you ask if you would like it yeah it
would like it I go up like this and go
give me a touch you know a little touchy
little touch you see you see a shudder
just sort of kind of good the gelatinous
surface of the Beltre bad yeah he's good
he's very good not ask me about my Bush
so like I got something to get lost in
translation this will make you feel good
and I go like this I can touch you until
it's I could touch you until if you feel
good
wraps begin to congregate in front of
you between you and the brain began to
form themselves into sort of Gears of
War style half wall and
I think you likes it maybe a massage
table couple off I go find your lost
thank you no hope for you to mantle on
I'm up I get my hands now oh yeah hats
are trying to climb like pushing me off
weird ladder brain hello can I roll
Arkana on the on this juice on the zoo's
sure you can try me just try it isn't it
magical in the club well then I didn't
need to hold one thing you can assess it
you know I mean it'd be like maybe like
assessing um you know ascetic wisdom
from a anthropological perspective right
yeah
I just want to see if I can little
vibration up yeah what was it what's
that oh it's it's seven seventeen
seventeen yeah this is this is a
profound fluid I mean do you think you
think just with your basic assessment
your basic conception of it I mean it
could be a potion it could be a healing
potion straight uh-huh nice I won't try
it but that's nice to know she had a bug
shaft come up to Gundam the other the
big old robot up there defending that
thing ya know anything about that
Bobby in case we encounter another one
of these
automata can you give us any advice on
how to defeat them I that's the only
automata that I know of
okay the iron golem right seems like it
yeah it's the only one that I know in
Chinese found I feel like you will you
will meet other presences yeah what can
you tell us about where we're going no
maybe a little prep info oh there's like
a there's like a noticeable pause he
hadn't considered it I could see yeah
it's like you think it's like um like
imagine if you had gears on your brain
like a ten-speed bike and so he doesn't
he can't tell quite which of those gears
is the appropriate one yeah he doesn't
know which knowledge is universal and
which knowledge is local of course but
we point on the iron golem what ready
yeah which was a glowing
they are Kannan he says there are
counters obviously the master of this
city doesn't would prefer that these
routes exist their countermeasures on
all of the greatest trunks I require
only these three right you will meet a
distraught Minotaur let's try okay and
another creature from our own home meat
boy gross got them nice I I don't know
if it's even capable of taking offence
but I try I do my god damn dude hey dumb
brain nice we're getting stuck in a tree
I say I say a Wow like a happy
underground yeah yeah Wow good job yes
another great tree we've got idiot yeah
I said that
do is not have some a growth for you
three times in the toilet so but I do
ask is what AK what I do ask is um
question why didn't you need our help
you have these minions could you not
have sent these these rats up to do this
work brass oh you know just just feel
what you need from the city above and
dissolve or saw through the rest would
never been able to manage the iron golem
and they wouldn't have been able to
manage the route even if they had their
in my ordinary capacity these would be
trivial matters okay and then realize
how bad of a shape use I would entertain
a scenario by which I leveraged chrono
Mansi perhaps the more in my ordinary
state this is embarrassing
I apologize it's gotta move
up there yeah this doesn't usually
happen what's the easiest way to break
these routes each of the routes has a
distinct methodology what are the
methodologies of the remaining two but
this thing's not prima guys like yeah
like yeah exactly leave a little mystery
why don't I and hey I'm all about
efficiency
what button do I match the other the
other routes have no iron sheath okay
that's good no like that
alright let's go to the next one yeah
I'm ready make sure this guy's full
strength yeah
mr. pop hop uh skitters out of his oh
yeah it's like I'm yeah and then where
he where he comes to rest is sort of
like the seed crystal upon which another
staircase is built into another cavern
that peels off into the right oh let's
do it and then I realized that
everything must be in a bad way because
he could easily provided us with a rope
of rats that were like a rung we just
hold on and it pulls us back so we have
to climb stair a rack or yeah oh yeah
now they may be a mystery is all gone
for you you're like no way they make a
lazy boy of rats then I just kind of sit
in and just take me ready to go no it's
look like a clawfoot tub yeah yeah boom
boom like a mini clawfoot tub exactly so
you make your way up this spiral rat
staircase incredibly tasteful in a way
you can that are done railing do you do
yeah it's just like but some of the
ratchet is posing just like oh yeah
right around the edge you make your way
up into this next corridor and you feel
cold breath of wind the breath of wind
that tells us
that a commercial break is upon us by
which I mean a restroom break don't go
anywhere unless you have to go to the
bathroom
in which case do that and then come back
and then we'll finish just ground to the
seating
hello i'm jennifer cail our camps when
last we saw our heroes they had emerged
up a rat staircase into another tunnel
toward the second of three routes that
they need to destroy for an elder brain
it's a complicated story but but that's
that's where we left our here Taylor
hose is one of the seven Greek classics
a point yeah they're subtle yeah all
right about that yes okay so we are yeah
we're on our way now through the
corridor it is to determine the second
humid day and it is yeah this is the
other one had a very natural bent it was
very very you know circular almost like
a direct human oh they went out very
efficient this is the all right angles
you emerge basically in a you know with
a minecraft minecraft' equivalent of a
tunnel or a few blocks high yeah you
push your way and then you arrive
basically at the end of this straight
shot of a tunnel into what looks at
least at first glance to be amazed okay
what way are we able to discern this
amaze like you see like you see has
intersecting each other at right angles
and being closed off it looks like a it
looks like looking see a little bit
further in it looks like the stone
version of a hedge maze okay okay
a stone maze Stone maze if you will I
will tell me is it is there a cap on top
or no there's no cap on top like this
can we climb up to the like walls
yeah I mean like could could one get on
top of it no it actually goes up maybe
1520 feet and then has a flat as though
it is carved with the rest of it okay so
I can't cheat okay you tried yeah yeah
no good is that what you want yes
is that what you deserve yes hurry man
line is to say but how we squeaker with
through this oh I don't know I had such
a cruel idea what is it girl at one time
though we have snakes antenna thank you
good line I know I hear you no no no I'm
so should have been as I thought was
yours no I want no yours cause mine's
still gonna take a long time go no you
hang up first
no yeah I can't you know I can't do that
so one of the things I can do with with
my familiar send him somewhere see
through his eyes and then misty step to
their because I only miss you step to
what I can see vision count let's go
sailing snake tentacle I mean we've got
web Selma and yet we've got Scouts dude
and we also need to consider a breeding
a snake tentacle breeding program
forever how's the goody ball yes thank
you yeah pretty much
nice yeah Pringles can no no scanned
it's like a it's like a Toll House how
much is episode 12 dick joke so far we
it's like it we're halfway there knowing
early what was it everything motive want
to remember
yeah wholesome the symbolic sure but how
sick of the mold offset it
yeah your guess is about five feet okay
plow through them to a sugar blast these
walls yeah
hedge amazing if you got a change
huh we don't have one yourself
blast a stone I'm a strong boy what are
we here do we here win we're you mostly
feel it okay it's not whistling around
before and you don't hear the musical
accompaniment okay that you experienced
previously yeah I don't feel like
there's a you can miss you step to it
but unless you can solve the root
problem on your
maybe again the root problem is the root
of the problems IV a great name for this
episode yes hmm you bet it's still
homecoming uh lame so so now I do want
to send my familiar out and see through
it sighs okay
see what we can discover huh God let's
do it all right we gotta go we're not
eating far friend I love you just too
much god lagari just flops down a you
know a demi sentient you know party boa
yeah drives forward silently against the
black stones let me take the wheel so my
my the white get to switch vision with
it the path in front of you goes about
20 feet and then you find yourself in
the center of a mesh of paths okay so it
is like a it's like a neck mall and
Voyager but there's all kinds of girl
offer but it's not like a huge like a
roundabout right okay how many paths
okay from here you have one two three
four
how do you made a real man it's one of
these this guy right yeah no no my back
there but I just that's the end of the
dragons has made this into sometimes
eight Jeremy and walnut which there's
with there would you say there's like a
north east south west northwest kind of
situation happening here at North by
Northwest
I guess captain sonar this yeah just for
cart cartographical purposes would you
would you mind described exactly so
imagine imagine the you imagine of the
entry point is east cranky has sent his
serpent in directly east cat but there
were from that initial point there was
also a left and a right
I think and then he passed through in
his serpent and entered into the center
of the room okay so there's a left in
the right passage that he just flew
through went the center of path yeah
okay okay
so just this I go center path and then
in the middle of this room he comes to
the big room which has five pounds
exactly five passenger described an
orientation various distress yes exactly
so directly south okay from there okay
is a room and then a little bit east and
south is a path that goes south to the
north there is an elbow that takes a
left there's also access to another room
north and then to the direct east the
past continues alright he came from the
east yes yeah yeah further east
it starts out and we're all going east
yeah yeah for now apart wait we enter on
the west and we're heading east you got
it got it oh yeah you go me something
you go incredibly wrong when I had you
this ability to make this understand oh
sorry
okay wonder I'm not going to worry about
this anymore
don't worry you know guy over yes
exactly I'm also want to try to knock
out a wall yeah good yeah it's like a
smite I could get through a wall we're
gonna really solve the mystery entirely
cheese amazed at all yeah I want to
cheat too mate well I'm just looking
where you learn you do what you won I'm
all about the remains you should shatter
that whatever you want I'm having you
relate to all of this to be verbal yeah
listen okay so the audience out there
and then you're back there with your
your map zone Jamison you're thinking
I'm taking notes based on Chris's
dictation you wouldn't you said we feel
cool breeze right you do okay it's sort
of on at regular intervals coming from
the maze coming from the maze regular in
the blossom is different story ah can we
maybe utilize that a little bit can I
assist snake boy maybe oh if I could
sniff out where the air is coming from
Kennedy yeah well not me wall not but I
could transform into something I could
okay
somebody might help I'm gonna I'm
someone to use wild shape and I turn
into you
yes 22a so we can we use those little
evil which will have keen hearing and
smell that weasel has advantage on
wisdom checks that rely on hearing or
smell comes find the guy who ran his
back well I can sound right so I'm fine
we got him assuming he just walked for
there straight straight through okay so
you're passing just listen so yeah there
is a spin-off show Oh Anakin's
incorporated the c-team that is just the
subterranea Adventures these
creatures yeah it happened a couple
times yep like it is as much of a
recurring gag I have on this share back
at it again damn it is this is a second
of the boys our bag of toys are back in
town
okay so walnuts in there and we're all
I'm assuming a weekend mind each other
yeah is go free
but also I know the kisses can see
through the guy decision so I'm feeling
like a little like in the weasel for
most waited like the little weasel
dances but that's it right no this thing
is just lifting ahead and by you staying
with me used to be panic come on yeah
but it's like only only cuz there's no
feels like a tiny tiny goofy side so
it's what you're trying to dish up I
want to first let's try and smell and
see if I can smell where that fresh air
is coming from Oh big money no I had
advantage on those rolls alright good
job okay ah and so then that would be a
plus phone so 17 yeah this is breath
okay and so I said that and I go what I
thought was fresh air is actually fresh
breath sorry I was like oh sorry
what doesn't sound right who is this
what I thought was this person it's
actually fresh breath yeah it's bad
enough smell aside my Sultana I feel
comfortable together no one else can I
say it smell that nothing I what's funny
is that I can only go through the
whistle with the hat
oh yeah this is this is breath it's
cooled substantially by the stone that
all that it's all filtering through but
this is this is definitely breath can I
spank outwork come from oh really
okay okay go which way uh it is directly
forward and to the right
okay like through that Eastern passage
indeed okay so Eastern passage I don't
know um it was a check check at urban
dictionary I like it like a D and I give
a little the nose swizzle over that way
I was checking to see whether or not a
native poisonous snake gets anything
good but he ain't good
there's a couple of there are some bull
and there's a couple reasons that this
is the best campaign of all time one of
them is that you guys still have your
fingers in your head yeah you know yeah
yeah we've been doing this every time no
I love it's our group call yeah if I if
I had had Stan she ate him as a rat then
he'd have a keen smell okay be but
there's a another great show how he's
jetting up them okay he's a cool tackle
he's rad good grab maybe I like him for
other reasons aesthetically yeah you so
arm brand you please me uh you sweetie
we're not doing the fleshlight oh no
more merchandise opportunity
yeah what no checks start coming in okay
all right so yeah I mean was that Darwin
yes are you proceeding Hey yeah I sell
it yeah and then we come to as you is
used to basically you hit like the back
wall and the left you can see goes 20
feet and then as a hard stop and just in
darkness um and then you can see to the
right that that basically you're seeing
the back left corner of a room and it's
just a wall between you and that room
you can go right around the passage yeah
let's let's go not like you know
barreling in but yeah let's go right to
the crime in Tegel you can see as you
enter I got to do a roll but as you
enter you can see kneeling in front of
wha what you assume is is this region's
root structure this one does not cross
the room this actually pierces the
ceiling and then goes directly down
through the floor almost just like a
column and you can see kneeling in front
of this root is a Minotaur oh that's so
weird you say
the Minotaur is how how much what
information do you want you should get
that information from your friends are
weird yeah we have started with yeah I
want to do a little it connects to a
perception on them to see what his
situation is an emotional based on smell
number just based on my eyeballs our
wine is to let smells upset that's real
real good 22 and I can tell it's because
of his IDs mm-hm
ask your doctor you don't need a
perception yeah yeah I like I like an
insight I'm gonna use it is the insight
as well I do have insight alright I'm
good at it I'm good at it really really
really good 23
yes another of those no yeah yeah
absolutely it's this is some kind of
active supplication you can see it's
broad it's double headed axe
it's just laid in front of it out flat
its Hansard or simply honored knees I'm
just considering this considering this
route we got a two options I can talk to
it yeah but we can a kick is a bit of a
process
yeah his name is also a guy so are you
yeah okay I don't know yeah we can stuff
like virus it's like when you're on the
phone with somebody and there's someone
that can be allowed to the whispering so
you start whispering you they can't
interview a little wafers head to be the
creepy voice traitor yeah yeah this is
my nervously voice oh my god I love that
I love that guy actually you just kept
calling me Dad like my face daddy it's
me daddy
Oh everyone looks so nice today oh
please you crane oh my god I love it
that's just like one of the seconds that
I don't find my way at their transit
yeah a lot of room over here was he
wrong big strong daddy
you know control do I mean Chris talk
about right now play this is really
gonna be your character yeah this was
almost dinar it was like a creepy or
sweet ball I have never in all my years
of friendship with you ever seen
destroyed by the video servers or now
it's kind of like no this is have left
the tremendous priority okay okay this
is like on that razor is around the
alleged cyclist the guy that's like on
one
okay okay yeah so here's a DD yes here's
all myself
I don't want to tell you Dave I have to
the Torah so again pretty high comment
to come back into it's a human of one
and I could tell a point there we could
talk to the Minotaur if we went into
trouble you guys to time after I thought
gee maybe I get you got a test 30%
sleeves oh yeah yeah you guys we got it
yeah pretty people you wrapped and like
in 1970 yeah okay so do we feel like do
we want to talk to it or do we want to
because what is okay we should we should
talk to it like I should talk to her
right I'm gonna see how has an animal I
can talk to you does anyone have that
knowledge before I bought at our Eastern
man diem oh it's not a yay Oh what do
you know about as far as being able to
use
awakens model it what do you get proxy
you know I mean can i telepathically
speak to this thing without at night if
you guys are going that snake smash
let you know anything to you think we're
all it says is communication to any
visible creature within 30 feet as long
as it
yeah yeah but you're not going dirty see
yeah I don't think so either
be stuck there yeah yeah yeah you can
get there well that's the thing I
doesn't want to have to do I can yeah
yeah yeah that's good
so you gotta fight it alone no I'm just
here to talk actually there - yeah I do
huh why are you turning also you guys
are not far away they're talking this
whole thing you can come huh why don't
we just you're not you and I are still
here why don't we just go there and then
you can miss you stuff oh yeah when you
carry carry the sack of stairs
exactly right over like I said no
grandmother I just still white Pepe just
like flopped over dinner yeah or like
ask you isn't it awkward to grab you by
the leg just drag you faces it up spirit
yeah ouch come on yeah okay yeah all
right yeah we'll meet you there so we
will all talk it out we'll have a nice
sit-down with this what's undoubtedly
going to be a friendly minute or do we
want to take the chair do we want to
take this for you guys just show up yeah
rata around the corner hey you feel all
right champ
and then just swing exactly yeah wish we
could understand it more before we
before we pop in on them but I guess
you're doing so much is bedroom anyway
you wish you were champ you got lasers
here maybe you got a dream journal
yeah wow living space for this guy that
this is a just a court over the group
well there's a couple there's only in
just a couple ramshackle um IKEA shelves
okay so the billing system probably be
damn sick is he moving soon or what are
we yeah we try to cast a spell on
something do they know that something's
been almost cast on them even if it
fails generally I thought so
generally yes yeah I like being pals or
whatever yeah yeah like when you try it
when you're I'm assuming what y'all
trying someone else and it fails it
they're supposed to know they were they
not community trying yeah yeah also I
want to just point out we have not
completed this map at all basically I've
got a lot of unexplored arms that made
its voices low
and it says it is if you stay or if you
attempt to destroy this root I'll be
forced to kill you and it will bring me
no pleasure so we good really really
love to hear that in a minute our voice
starting slowly bring your mind it's a
really pretty faces so I started talking
to her so I guess I'll all pop out us we
before me over in our way but I'm still
around the corner
um buddy knows we're here Shane over
here but I yeah but I want to have a
fighting chance of not getting cleaved
into Wayne um well let's yeah let's I'm
not going to waste misty step since
we're practically there yeah misty stuff
I feed into it just burn it just keep
your body yeah I would I realize my
vision it stands from its from you just
a sort of penitent kneeling position and
rises up you can hear the double-headed
axe scrape on the floor second Krishna
and it turns it turns me around so it's
a wet we got legate and we have a weasel
we have oh no I'm walnut as he turns
around to face you just like there's
like no loincloth it's just straight up
that's our like Minotaur 100% the but as
he turns he raises his axe and as he
sees you
the axe like the surprise of it drops
the axe he drops it on the floor do I
know him you don't know him in
particular but I
minotaurs noble minotaurs served the EPA
well over its history hmm
that's awesome okay cool so now that I
have that that knowledge he collapses oh
boy in front of you like hard hair okay
I go like vows
you look really good at a an altar Wow
and I go sand sand like the no need for
that here and I especially don't want
like these guys to come around the
corner and I'm like please get up it's
okay I already seen it yeah where are
you
yes I saw every song yeah he's freaking
out
he says tell me you're here to undo this
I said I say and I I point to that I
planted a root no I point to the root
and then I point like above like
motioning this whole thing I say I'm I'm
here to restore what was yet weeps just
hope this massive this massive ten-foot
tall
bull man huh just just shuddering with
tears and say who who's kept you who's
kept you captive here why why aren't you
gone Bendis veiled a master of this
place the father of this place he who
stole the NEMA's ear when he season you
don't respond to the word NEMA's ear in
the way that he expects and he says do
you recall the stories of old not no
it's just do you remember the tale of
how the our Enclave Ward with the
elephant in the Underdark
well it's like having a moment where
she's like I thought my mother told me
all the stories like no I got I know I
thought I knew all the tales and she's
like no it's been so long since I've
heard the stories you have to tell me
just why wouldn't she have told you well
we I don't I was really breaking there
you get her to the Nana's here as a he's
trying to build it he's trying to do
some kind of translation as I'm Emma's
ear is a war root seizure
against the Underdark 300 are our people
ward with the illicit for a thousand
years and we ward with them from the
surface we could plant our siege engines
beneath the Sun and their roots would
reach down and destroy their cities
pretty cool clearly extremely conflicted
he has a person and also well expected
just this city is a corruption of our
mystery what a war room grows down and
gathers stone and moss and water and
magic and turns it into a weapon he has
transformed into a seed that grows a
city to what end
I think he would delight him to plant
cities like this that he could dominate
and the same clauses well I've heard all
I need to hear for now we're you know
we're here to deal with it I don't want
him to get any farther than NEMA's ear I
want there to be more
Nana's ear just you have one task before
you but you need to know that as soon as
you attempt to harm this root come on
bud I will have no choice but to fight
you that is to do my then given what is
the quickest way to destroy this root to
destroy me first dang it I can't let you
do it
don't give me these Minds how bright is
the light in here not let's breathe in
yeah yeah this is this is like the
market typical
minotaurs Mays okay I'm thinking of
something hmm I think I would like to
use my new grammar Manthey whoo okay so
the new grandma Manson yeah as
established on our walk through the
literal wood is a is connected to your
way of the shadow monk abilities correct
in our conception right shadow obviously
is a place shadow exists you can shape
it you are identifying you are you see
indeed you led your adept in the use of
shadow but shadow also represents
philosophically the unappreciated work
and toils of people in the corners of
society right right right
grandma Nancy allows you to seize the
use of a target shadow as many targets
as are available and have their shadows
stop so may I describe to you what I
would like to happen here yes
okay it seems like this Minotaur has a
personal connection with walnut and so I
don't want to hurt him but what I would
like to do is call upon the plane the
deme plane of shadow to snake tendrils
of shadow out of the dark corners of
this room and twine up his legs around
to the arms and binds him in place but
not hurt him I love it you're going to
need a light source okay I got three one
yeah I'm your light source yeah shadow
shadow exists as an opposite okay where
would it help you so you could go to
most I think probably directly over like
give me a give me a long shadow on him
okay big boy
I might do it a shot yeah and then yeah
right right three three two right now
meanwhile are like kicking the axe away
from yeah well yeah my idea is like we
promise when I'm going to destroy the
root but why don't you take an hour
break and just go over there in a while
Brian's doing it okay so I'm gonna I
don't know what I'm doing this though
just goes right yeah like I'm Cyclops
I'm going to do dancing lights okay I'm
gonna do it low and slow right you're
gonna get a strong shadow okay no no
it's going to be some distance away so
you guys have to find shadows a crisp
long shadow that will slide off of the
stone of this of this floor and and sort
of infect the body of this Minotaur a
painless like I said it is not intended
to cause pain but it is caused it is
going to bind him in place absolutely so
that he cannot interfere with our tour
so I'm you're going to kill them right
what consumes you seems cool how long
going to be maintained that's a great
question
there Graham I'm antsy yeah it's going
to last for a couple rounds you should
you should be you're all working it
should be okay okay okay wisdom yeah
stop please not wait this stuff can make
you anything yeah I could do without for
dinner yeah yeah grapples gosh plan oh
yeah alright alright okay we're good so
you so you create DC shattered yeah kill
is that is that bad yeah everybody if I
destroy his mind but he's still just
standing here
yeah he's okay yeah I think dissonant
whispering all right well my so you you
you create a so the light source yeah
it's uh it's low and in the corner yeah
he's so we're all lit up and he's got a
long shadow cast exactly he has a long
shadow cast this brilliant or
casts light up low and vice so there's a
large version of this Minotaur and what
do you say
I'm really sorry about this you seem
awesome and it seems like you two have a
lot of catching up to do but we really
can't let you interfere in what we're
doing today right he reaches down for
his axe
and as he does you can see it's his own
shadow a larger even than he is reaching
down so now shadow is gripped and
wrapped around arms and almost like a
vine and if the arms are held up the
legs are held out you can see that the
axe itself is sort of been spun and
flung into a corner and clatters away
and you have a round let's see what you
can do
I want to grab his axe gas-x
well first I want to go goose him yeah
and then grab the axe all right only
event is important running life is ax
even with miss hearts in it I'm going to
use his ax ax ax not going to get to
fish out mmm he can't I want to leave it
over there tell you that if he wants it
you get it for me oh wow boom it doesn't
real dinar move oh yeah yeah say so so
let's see let's let's get initiative so
we can manage it I'm going to do it
laughs fair one Henchard okay
Oh buddy 7 8 11 16 all right take it
away nut I didn't have a move um bang
connection right well um yeah you can
delay your excellent yeah you want you
want to just go after dinner yeah okay
work on your out have a movie there
thank you uh what it is before we get in
there what is the nature of this route
like how does it look to the differ from
the other one yes this almost looks like
a this just this almost looks like a
massive vegetable okay so this is I'm
not it doesn't it doesn't have that that
sheep hey all right
the walnut can do a bite probably yeah
that's my last well truth
oh and is it and how big around is it
the trunk of this is probably four feet
around also pretty not the same of the
oh no no it's a different light all
right wait a second
I dunno what I wanted to do all right
you could do it I haven't been decided
on our yammering and then you just push
me all right I want to know well I'm
gonna die I'm sorry Tex like we're doing
this real I'm going to use my mind in
hate and my enhance ability on a dinar
oh and then I'm going to give him the
give him full strength
wait so judges so you get a advantage on
any strengths chick right so that would
help I guess you guys feel good okay
right yeah that's what I got going to be
doing a strength check when I swing on
that thing well there's another way you
can get I mean it respects resonance
active already should be a normal attack
role I don't know sure sure the scenario
I would say there is that the best-case
scenario is probably like athletics I
would think that using axe to chop a
thick trunk is in that continuum I'm a
great weapon master by those I'm talking
about
Aquarion capacity has now doubled we all
like everyone up in my shoulders and I
say we around the Maypole there's nobody
to do would you permit me to use shatter
or is that something that's for
creatures only no it's for creature self
because it has to make this target as a
creature as a creature that's America
today we grow yeah it's getting bigger
you look at it yeah let's see yeah see a
lot of the stuff I get is creature so
it's like I'm not going to hex a root
it's not a creature it could be a little
even non-match mind a non-magical object
that isn't being worn or carried also
takes damages in this those areas no I
think that Network I think that those
are the rules for creatures in terms of
like can they saving from damage and
things like that but I think that I
think that in general the shattering
force of this is bad right well I'm just
asking to differentiate it from whisper
doesn't more probably not going to do
this yeah you hear what oh you do bad
will wash out of the balls you know you
can't see you know he breaks free
clearness you could although do
something spectacular to the inside of
the root
yeah but it doesn't work as well you see
that's true
shatters great I'll do something
spectacular the inside of the Minotaur
all right so do we wanted to saving
throwing that you don't care but it
works really fine I'll handle all that
stuff on my side all right well go ahead
you what you roll your damage all right
Dumbo's kill dommage
exactly omelette du dum ah I'm going to
need one more of those if I'm a mana bar
Lenore then okay I need even more yeah
okay so you're looking at a 15 the
precious route this region it's a
premium rune experience rosy bass singer
um go ahead yeah
I'll fight it I'll speed it up as I get
walk past the Minotaur I'm going to pat
him on like I said I'm really very sorry
he is struggling mightily against these
fronds okay wow man
I'll just go pull pull like that overly
honest this trunk and do a trunk 16 yep
second I hit it is okay and then um
don't you yeah it's a nine it is and
then I'll do a punch for good measure
which is only at 12 okay that's right
okay then be sure to use your d8 okay
delicious and that is a 10
good God hmm all right
that's real real good dinar bliss in
yeah let me get his ax and I'm going to
swing it at the root for the last of it
okay so what am i rolling home at my
rolling strengthener my rolling an
attacker yeah what I what I crave most
yeah is a strength athletics check ok
seconds you're gonna Randall yeah yeah
we I helped come on hey
that's a mean I'm great weapon mention
anything up it is so when you when this
axe connects with this root it doesn't
bite in
at all as soon as the axe as soon as the
axe sort of strikes anywhere near it you
can see it almost like a cloak or sheath
of light around it basically bounces the
axe back and you with it over to the
side and what's more you see a gash
appear on the Minotaur s abdomen oh
whoops
oopsie you guys did damage to the roof
right yeah but not with the axe yeah you
know in for a penny in for a pound I go
after him now it's a crazy horse the
other way
Chaucer Majin yeah he struggles mightily
to escape the shadow bonds and is unable
to walnut dog I'll get another round
okay cool well uh I like Bernard I give
him up
hey no I'm going to do that you were all
cheering me on a minute ago I heard it
do I want to attack with my actual human
body
oh yes exactly
a thrill of in my body yet it's been a
while since I've seen walnut attacks
hunting with her too much I never
attacked anything or I get turned yeah
her elven body excuse me staunch elven
body it's all garbage isn't a thing yeah
the hot thing um the best I could do I
could set it on fire
I'll do a produce flame classic and then
it's a a little green flame ball and I
will hurl it and I got a roll and see if
I actually hit
I'm sure there's an ammo for that it
feels confident yeah probably
oh no it was just a neat really the
flame it's decorative it's a it's like
some Criss Angel Street magic type one
click will flash whoa
I heard her oh no they didn't know wall
I could do this which is like huh it's
great if I do it good joke just now but
kind of you know notice I forgot to do
ownership for my handful friend sweetie
but you know what lucky bond do you mean
it John something you can it can see
helps me but I don't know that he can
help me here because you'd have to like
distract the root I don't know Avery any
kind of head then so in dish up uh
should I just forget what we're going to
do oh I remember now let's go ahead and
show them a little can tack Euler
spectacular realignment into that wound
a blossom of of tentacles exploding out
I hate you and I hate Kip Nam I'm Anna
do them away I want to get on the rear I
don't want to hurt the Minotaur if I can
help it alright well this is in our
camera it is this is not work we'll see
you and not hysterically Mormon took a
day you know what hi sorry ma but I said
is in disadvantage yeah great so now
Rosa okay at all here hook Beast does
that fair at all wait so am I did we
kill each other out or might be okay in
advance yeah yeah I appreciate that
couple let's try so that's that's well
horrible Oh wrong for council members
please you
yeah but it is there it's been another
critical role Alyssa if you could please
a portion the treasure to the shadow
council so on xx they get stuff on ones
do we get stuff from them if you really
want expel right everybody it was the
engine no this direction so as you as
you you draw out because you know at
some level you know that these things
are everywhere that just under the
surface a driving cabal of serpents is
ready and waiting and you five-minute II
you find them inside this route even
driven down swimming down through the
vital SAP they just they begin to pour
out of the the cut that the party has
made um and just nah and you and you can
you can see it you can see it spinning
out at the top
I need some dykes to roll would you like
oh don't worry about it I'll handle it
for you okay well coming out of the
Qaeda what nagging in the Negev river
this moment well yell please with
international coffee
now the so that the wound in the root
the tentacles surged out they Bend
backward and then from within it try to
split it like this crack yeah not bad
eating it sounds like guys they twist
cracking crab leg like yeah exactly yeah
it's just twisting it and prying it open
and that that the damage rolled is
sufficient to absolutely sever this root
and as the root as the root Severus and
the bottom flops you can see that's like
both sides it's like I had I had a once
I had a nectarine in my lunch when I was
in junior high and I'm very excited
about them because they're great and I
opened it and the seed was full of
earwigs like I opened it and so whenever
I eat one now I'm always afraid what
it's going to be like that yeah now
you're not all scared of it now they
give them another chance never like
we're getting so many up all the
way through like there is nothing but
these worms and then down through the
rest there's nothing but worms just
boring it out from top to bottom and at
the moment that it splits the Minotaur
falls forward but he is still suspended
by the shadow bonds hmm unfortunately as
I was looking and warns in there I don't
want that but not your intention was
yeah Edison coil there's no warmth kind
of hoon I think he's done yeah he you
have yelled another person we meant you
have managed to in the mouth of three
routes in this current what was the
quest again oh rootin tootin the route
busting we've been doing rig busting
that's directly from the dock your
answer obviously listen it's the
irregular actually dead you can check
them check them second yeah I'm gonna
I'm gonna keep them
tied up in the shadows I wear in a
second I would yeah and and go and kind
of like evaluate because it might be
just that a curse has been the doom as
you mentioned should have been looking
from them his eyes just have like glass
okay we have a pulse
yeah can we check his vitals yeah you
can't you get you get out your medical
kit Circus medicine has been invented I
can write I have accepted a meditation
school I'm doing good I mean it's like
it's like oh I thought I discovered a
cool weed the Sun when you put it by
Obama only doctors know how to take Poli
I don't know more to my belt I was so he
is he is suspended and you think that
without the without the shadow bonds
that he wouldn't be able to hold himself
up at all yeah you're not you're not
sure he's still alive warm ok but you
don't think that you don't think that he
is alive anymore ok well then I release
the shadow bonds and let's move him I
stopped the fair while they are doing my
hands like a foreskin I mean it's like
not pretty well he handed yeah hey in
the bank exert with it yes that's it
hazel Dickey no no is there is our goop
and this final work its worms
it's just worms it probably used to be
goop I don't wait it's like it's all
good for you it's just about getting
that goop
yes as usual pretty much right that's my
thing
I cleared my 21 day long do I want on
record on the written record that's
weird ah time for me no I want you on to
a thing isn't Minotaur cuz he did
something good oh I want to do I love it
um I am going to uh he's huge how he's
big but could I like put him in a
respectable position so he's not like
flopped down like yeah yeah I'm looking
over I'll help you okay cool um and then
I'll put his axe next to him and then uh
I'm going to take some of the some of
his I guess blood from his wound and
on a forehead I'm going to draw a very
specific room I think it's online my
sheet it is I'll put it in here so you
see it but I don't want you to speak too
much stuff I'll draw this Oh didn't I
say that the EPA APD Enclave EPA all a
suggestion it is actually a a protection
room but I'll do that and then I'll
whisper something quietly that's awesome
I support that things that sort of thing
100% flavor so you you need to turn in
the other things come over and I can see
it means watch and I say in my culture
we would eat him she turn into a bear
and eat him that would be the biggest
honor it's been our just say Mexican
would be cool
yeah yeah well my kiss on the side I can
assaulting my people no you get you
actually get if someone insults you at a
burial procedure you actually have
advantage on side I my I do want to do
something no nobody will might backfire
I want to go above his head and I want
to take a very small hole and then I got
on the spoon of annihilating it into the
stone into the it's stone oh I thought
it was during here no is this this place
has been manufactured then I got the
idea was like bored out of the yeah well
never mind can you know that right yeah
will do later okay my brain will do life
well traffic of impose this imposed a I
don't garlic's my minute aren't I okay
only in this camping so I miss you Pope
Pope all right hmm the very same thank
you for helping back there hidden in the
shadows he he doesn't have a whole lot
right yet Mickey yes he he take he takes
you back through this nest of right
angles every time we hang out a drop
your pop pop I tell him everything we've
done what is it just like coriander yeah
oh yeah it's like okay what could
absolutely my new coriander you
Jerry needs a few minute listen the
fullness of time so uh he you know
hedges himself ever so gently up to the
edge
and you mean and then looks down gross
and then I like that little bit and your
stairway is reconstituted okay okay
chunk number three mmm
are we going back to the brainer we go
right to the third one with the debris
is it a central chamber okay I keep
going into pair okay this is awkward
hi again daydream what's going on again
we come back like yeah did it one more
yeah you I'm so bad like just dangling
it's like barely thing in fact like one
more root yeah swing in her yes we're
going to get that one he's a cup I
thought he was like in a pool with you
suspended in midair oh yeah oh wait back
okay I got around I have a question if
you around brain or if you like sin but
he is stretched out cuz I have a said a
doctor who it's like with lieutenant
nearly in the spaceship and they bring
out the face and they keep missing the
space like that's what I'm picturing yes
that I can't that's good okay perfect
yeah yeah oh space a boat no not face it
though oh I'm very human I could I say
we're in the same paycheck
no no it's stretchy she's the last one
here we have to say the last human right
yeah yes yeah that's it um actually
moistening is vital I know but it is
pulled up and suspended out ordinarily
there's a you know you can even see the
remnants of the pool rather be the
ordinary domicile of this sort of entity
okay and kind of negate I think exactly
it sort of it is again like a like a
skin on a rack right
desiccated to varying degrees I'm going
okay we should tell him we ready for
that drop about to get the third one
yeah get them rats ready to catch you
yeah do it
that's good old green eyes go measure
number three his coterie is still just
operating in this almost like a solar
model it's just they're just sort of
moving around each other
another group goes over
and in the southern part of the room
manifests itself up into a new staircase
and takes you into an even stranger
realm could I worse yes
yeah oh yeah I did pretty good so far
yeah yeah again you can get way worse
mhm
go ahead uh let me make sure I have on
my paper stray for this and killed one
embarrassed one yeah who then died yeah
oh yeah I remember one we meet one got
said so so what am I trying to say about
the nature of reality yeah I mean
nothing I'm just laying down is very
real
building so I'm dying to get returned
real life is finally ha these are very
small passages that allow only a single
person at a time through them it's ok
don't like it now and as you wind slowly
around you can see that it opens up into
a small room sort of like a
kidney-shaped
room and you can see that this path
continues on into darkness but these
areas are actually relatively well lit
by mushrooms of varying colors nice mmm
and in this place you can see there is a
sort of like a stream of sewage you're
almost certain and you can see several
shapes perfectly still just with their
feet planted in that sort of trickling
river and they are standing completely
Stockstill so from head to toe up near
the top and see a traditional like a
mushroom cap the rest of the body is
like a is stalks of various kinds so
imagine stove pipes that come off and go
up to other
caps of mushrooms around but they have
something like a bipedal form and these
are definitely bipedal mushroom people
like that one Japanese movie how in
Japanese monster movies in 60s really is
like an island of mushroom people
mushroom people like my favorite piece
Oak Island yes yeah that's it that's it
for me to see any evidence of the trunk
in here not in this not in this
particular room okay this this appears
to be just how they get down here
alright and as I say they're almost
completely still they don't they don't
respirate and classic since they are
napping or feeding or some what that's
poor density what's going on under the
hood yeah there's you can work there you
can eat in the in the light of the
cavern you can absolutely see that the
air is adulterated here I spores
do I like it is that something that or
am I so dryer yeah yeah I mean there's
not a lot of cohabitation between
strands and my candids but um what are
they called
like in it yeah you don't hate it you
don't hate it it's definitely like its
home adjacent Yeah right if I got in
close yeah the next town over from the
town you go yeah yeah exactly it's close
if some of the brand's you like yeah
I've been there I've been there enough
that I'm sort of they have they have
that one buffet that you used to go to
on Sundays didn't as good it's like they
have ham and turkey but not ham turkey
and beef yeah I mean uh guys it's cool I
like these guys don't worry about of you
how abouts for them we still have half
of that trace you guys on us trying to
sell through this uh I mean I'm game I'm
not talking my friends if we think yeah
if we don't see the trunk yet yeah I
don't see any reason to cause a ruckus
in this chamber oh yeah and they're
mushrooms Aiden keep me in the dark
right usual my motto did the parties I
can't claim
like dinars approach every living for
you treat everything like mushrooms all
right I'm sorry
an old self yeah everyone do stuff yeah
pressured you so we go +10 yeah yeah
wait 311 101 this this is a sylphs yeah
we get ways I know yeah wow look at help
for today delegate god damn lemons good
cat head of council may our Labour's
please you Alyssa if you could please
issue the necessary rewards so you you
pull around this corner you can see that
that that sort of river trickles off in
one direction you hang a right down into
a more people area there's a much larger
cavern here and in this in this context
the mica dens are not stock still and
there and they do not have their feet up
to the you know ankle in sewage trying
to derive minerals they are actively
moving about from place to place and so
to vary degrees you are trying to be
sneaky but there is something about this
there's something about their home and
something about where they live that
makes your position clear okay that it's
there none but they don't care we're
just placing my us force and I know a
placement exactly like you'd like they
don't have any beefs at all
okay don't think they don't they're not
they're not angry in any way so good
well mushroom a walk job no no no
exactly a you see me you don't know if
it's something like a family group we do
you don't know how it functions you
don't know how it operates here but you
see groups of these creatures actively
shaping their environment navigating
navigating space making for things or
they don't yet this is this day
live here okay um and you see you kill
all that a that is for the society so
there is a as you're sort of passing
through this this mystical chamber off
to the left you can see a group it's
very they're very tightly packed in this
room I mean almost almost body to body
and you can hear them all sort of just
like humming like their home tree yeah
just like waving around don't have a
congregated around the trunk uh you
don't know I did that's dude that just
seems to be the right place that they do
it you guys like that I got right up
yeah they're gonna so they can kind of
see us but haven't really cared we
haven't done anything you haven't done
in agra at all of them let's go check
out an iconic cluster okay yeah let's i
guess if we're going to talk to him i
think we're gonna have to be
now let's recon first as much as we can
yeah yeah we have whatever minor
advantage we have yeah so as you enter
this room as they are just sort of
existing together there's certain that
they're moving like one creature oh like
like yeah i'm a Giunta they're all sort
of swaying around a central point like
gravity is being altered for each of
them in the same way simultaneously you
don't see anything projecting from the
roof you don't see anything projecting
horizontally through the room they don't
appear to be standing around anything
but each other okay Oh God come on man
they are the root of Jesus yeah the
murder of town and the other the edge of
perception check to see if maybe there's
something invisible that they're
clustering around sure yeah yeah you're
welcome to proceed
I'm fifteen uh no no you're you don't
think is anything invisible I mean this
dude there's nothing including the space
they're cracked they're pressed together
okay yeah I think exactly um Dennard
behind you sneaking up know that you see
a small creature of this style hmm
bright green cap
um don't don't kill it I'm not kind of I
didn't say anything ray green cap it is
handing you schools like I like a bottle
yeah like a twist off just quick I tell
you Porter too hard yeah you see and it
hands you a cap oh oh well hat a
mushroom cap you can see two little eyes
on the front of it uh-huh and it has it
has a sort of Scour but you would
interpret add our expression okay thanks
Lloyd oh yeah issues say this I'll put
this on this will take me over if you
I'd be mushroom people we'll check this
out and them are you guys this all would
be so much we can I was gonna say can I
reach out to it with my with my mine and
see if I can get any language off of it
sure I greeted old friend so it's really
you know this you know that it's there
but it just doesn't need to respond okay
you got snug yeah there's an effort that
would be required all the information
you get is like emotional this
information yeah I see it is super chill
when I'm alone earth they had maximum
chill
uh they're chill is at ten okay orderly
on eleven it's eighteen a photo Wow that
may have advantage on all chill checks
oh man
too much effort to be that tail yeah
really as you're talking so it's rich
raise its raising one I like he did it
on his head are you a you're gonna dude
but he's looking around all I'm hoping I
will take me over like anything but this
yeah whatever you know you feel you
obviously as soon as the Mon from the
moment you wake up to the moment you go
to bed you're the strongest person that
you know oh yeah you anyone you are even
stronger than that
now now nice you are even stronger than
you were before you feel strong yeah
yeah yeah just it just smug you can see
it's sort of like Nestle and resk trying
to find that exactly this is trying to
find exactly the right place to be on to
be on these horns it's like I got to
find the place that's right for me smell
good forgot that back around back around
the the corner it just toddles off with
a little one like that yeah yeah yeah
here they're they're doing their meld
dance around it back and around the
corner you can see that there is a final
chamber at the end of what they're sort
of their Great Hall and you can see that
this room is entirely ensconced with
dance which is like the most kind of
mushrooms you'd find on the on the trunk
of a tree so leather goes flat certainly
I was very lucky it's a combination I
mean it's a combination of flat
mushrooms and what you perceive as eyes
and then they congregate and all gaze
upon a central structure that is itself
covered with mushrooms okay
and eyes that is all the time that is
from Frodo tell me not today shadow
council if it please you we're going to
sample the facilities we're going to use
the restroom we'll come back and hang
out I understand that long a dumb grass
has some special toys that she got from
viewers of the show and I hopefully
there'll be a show-and-tell phase
completed same word I think I hope that
you brought enough for the rest of the
class
don't go anywhere come back and tease
you