JERRY: No. Be cool. You have to be legit. This is a very serious thing...
Hello. I'm Jerriford K. Horkims.
Dungeon Master of the "C" Team.
To my right...
JERRY: is Ryan Hartman, as Donaar Blit'zen. RYAN: (clapping)
JERRY: Master of puns. We've got Amy the Falcon.
KRIS: (clapping louder and faster) AMY: That's me.
AMY: Oh! Yes. Thank you! KATE: Oh! Falcon. Very good.
JERRY: Going with the Walnut Dankgr-- Are you still going with the druid? Is that still your character?
AMY: I mean... Let's do it one more week, and see how it goes.
JERRY: We'll see if takes off the way.
Kate Welch. Always a pleasure. Not your grandma's grandma.
KATE: Not at all.
JERRY: Rosie Beestinger.
K'thriss Drow'b.
You've finally managed to put your OC deep enough
JERRY: into the Acquisitions Incorporated lore. KRIS: I self-inserted myself.
JERRY: You self-inserted yourself. Kris-ception! KATE: Deep into the hilt. &gt;&gt; KRIS: I'm there.
KRIS/JERRY: (Inception sound effect)
JERRY: Now we are jumping right into the "C" Team, Episode 3: In Good Standing.
KATE: (noncommittal sound) RYAN: Hey. I like that.
KRIS: Is that the title? KATE: Oh is that the title?
KATE: Oh! We've got a title! In Good Standing.
JERRY: We'll see if we get all-- Yeah write that shit down. AMY: Oh it's notes per episode?
KATE: I do! KRIS: It's going to be a poem.
AMY: Committed to memory. JERRY: It's going to be good.
KATE: I'm going to sell this on eBay later. JERRY: No, no. It's going to be an acrostic.
JERRY: Like, by the times it's like-- (gasp)
It was there all along!
AMY: It spells, "Omin is great." (noncommittal sound)
JERRY: As soon as it gets to "Omin is gr..." you're like-- KATE: I get it.
KRIS: I don't need to do the rest.
KATE: I'd like to solve the puzzle.
JERRY: But here's how it's going.
AMY: Not good.
JERRY: At our last-- When last we saw our heroes...
you had escaped from a bizarre prison.
RYAN: Yup. JERRY: That people were perfectly happy to live in.
Because stew was constantly reappearing on plates.
Beds were being made by ghosts apparently.
It had the nice, you know, turndown service.
And that was sufficient for them.
But you guys decided that you did not want to hangout there for an extended period of time.
And I went with it.
I mean, the campaign was suppose to end there.
RYAN: I was going to say, we should have just ended this thing right there!
We live there forever. The end.
JERRY: No. The credits would go-- Obviously there would be a saxophone...
You know what I mean? There would be scenes from happy events later.
All in the same place.
What eventually happened,
was that you had freed someone they had bound.
They left.
You took a hostage.
So, let's start the campaign off right,
with hostage taking as a policy.
The rogue was with you and you led the rogue out of that chamber, out of that final part of the Test Market.
AMY: Mm-hmm.
JERRY: But when you emerged through the portal you saw a...
fresh country road, breeze,
trees that sort of formed themselves into an arch.
In the distance a portal is visible.
But your friend K'thriss Drow'b...
KRIS: Friend.
JERRY: "Friend." &gt;&gt; RYAN: Again... AMY: Again... very loose.
RYAN: We just met. KRIS: De facto.
KATE: Have not actually learned his name yet. JERRY: Yeah, exactly.
RYAN: We spent three nights together.
JERRY: Listen-- KRIS: He keeps to himself.
RYAN: Amongst-- You're as-- I'm as friendly with you as I am with those mice.
(laughter)
RYAN: You're on the same tier. KRIS: I rode them. So...
KATE: Aww I miss them. JERRY: Same tier.
AMY: Extremely. KRIS: Don't get comf y.
JERRY: On the social scale... RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: One K'thriss Drow'b. Three mice.
JERRY: About the same. RYAN: Yeah.
RYAN: That's the exchange rate.
JERRY: Yeah exactly.
But K'thriss Drow'b, you do not see an idyllic forest scene.
If there is something that could be the polar opposite of an idyllic forest scene, that is what you see.
So...
clutching your focus,
this chunk of stolen onyx or obsidian,
with a symbol on it that you can't perceive.
KRIS: Right. JERRY: You are floating against a starfield.
And it is either so cold that it feels hot, or so hot that it feels cold.
The sensations coming in are difficult to unravel, functionally speaking.
And in the great distance you can see a red pinprick.
One of the pinpricks in this field of lights is growing in your vision and approaching you.
And you have a dim awareness that there are other people here with you in this space.
But essentially you're just clutching this stone in a sort of fetal position hurtling through this--
JERRY: expanse. KRIS: But I feel motion. I am flying.
JERRY: Yeah you are hurtling-- traversing, but it's so difficult to tell the rate of it.
Because there's nothing around you except for this dim awareness of these two other figures.
KRIS: (whispering) Two other figures.
KRIS: Um... KATE: Sounds tight. I got to say.
KATE: Had me at "starfield."
JERRY: (laughs) Yeah it's like, shit yeah--
RYAN: You had me at "pinprick."
JERRY: (laughs) Why can't I--
KRIS: It's just a screensaver.
(laughter) KRIS: I would--
RYAN: Now these pipes start forming in front of you.
JERRY: Yeah it's like, how do you interact with these pipes?
JERRY: There's some fucking-- KRIS: Where do they go?
JERRY: They're going wild.
KRIS: Let me see...
I guess the first thing I do is... well I attempt to speak.
Just to like clear my throat. See if I can make sound in this place.
JERRY: Yeah. KRIS: Am I able to?
JERRY: Yeah you are. What do you say?
KRIS: I just, where am I?
JERRY: You say these words out. You can hear them.
There's some medium capable of communicating it.
To your left you can see...
the person whose life you have made progressively worse.
Every moment.
This is the person whose bonds you clipped... upstairs.
KRIS: He's come along?
JERRY: He is somehow along for the ride.
In this alternate place.
To your other side-- imagine a...
JERRY: Imagine-- KRIS: Let me change my first words there.
KRIS: Hey, buddy!
(laughter)
RYAN: It's the naked guy.
JERRY: Imagine a situation, you know, in another universe, there would be three men on crosses.
KRIS: Right. JERRY: It's that tier of destiny.
KRIS: Okay. JERRY: Hurtling toward this increasing sphere of red.
JERRY: To your right, the rogue that you marshalled through the portal is here with you as well.
KATE: Seems like a pretty well-balanced party.
JERRY: Yeah you guys-- &gt;&gt; KRIS: Yeah I'm good to go. RYAN: Is this your new team?
JERRY: Yeah exactly we're going to-- AMY: I hope you're really happy together.
RYAN/KRIS: Yeah.
JERRY: We're going to do this-- KRIS: Spin-off.
JERRY: We're going to do this spin-off already.
RYAN: The "D" Team?
KATE: It's the Frasier to our Cheers.
JERRY: Exactly yeah. We have "D" through "Z."
You know? Obviously there's growth opportunities.
KRIS: Yeah there's plenty.
So I got... so the one on my left is the one I freed from my bonds.
The one on my right is that rogue who wanted to live in that false inn forever.
JERRY: Yeah had made a kind of peace with this alternate existence.
KRIS: So what do they look like right now?
JERRY: They are suspended in absolute terror.
And as I said you get...
You can sense that you are moving--
This is really a calculation you're making on your part.
Because the three of you seem to be in the same configuration.
As though you're being drawn into this...
KRIS: This red circle. JERRY: this increasing-- this sort of ruby orb.
KRIS: (whispering) Jeez!
I cast Dancing Lights-- No. That's worthless.
JERRY: Cast it if you want. KRIS: Nah. I'm good.
RYAN: Just let it envelope you?
KRIS: Yeah I don't-- AMY: Just give me the sweet release of death I've been looking for.
KRIS: Yeah at what point are we going in?
KATE: It does sound exciting.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. AMY: For you. &gt;&gt; KATE: Yeah for you.
KRIS: Well I am clutching my hunk of altar.
Because I feel like this was meant for me to see.
JERRY: Yeah. KRIS: This feels special.
JERRY: There may be... KRIS: I don't know why these guys are here.
JERRY: There may be a case.
There may be a case for it.
It continues to grow.
And then as the-- the closer it gets you can see that...
it seems round at a distance, but it doesn't have...
it doesn't have a true shape.
It just has a volume.
And like a gem, you can see that light penetrates it and refracts against impossible structures.
KRIS: So it has like a size but no aspect.
JERRY: That's right. KRIS: It doesn't have a shape.
JERRY: That's right. RYAN: It's a fractal.
JERRY: And light can-- light hits it and then travels via some path inside of it.
And the closer it gets you can see what look like--
Imagine like the-- like a frond of an aloe vera plant?
KRIS: Yeah. JERRY: So it's long, triangular...
KRIS: Fractal, like you said. JERRY: Exactly.
JERRY: Along the edge...
Along the edge, teeth...
that dance and sway along sort of the inner edge.
KRIS: Clearly teeth, though.
JERRY: Yeah. KRIS: Not like, oh so white structures. It's like--
JERRY: You don't-- They read-- They parse to you as an organism of, you know, with an interest in survival.
KRIS: Hmm. JERRY: This parses to you as a teeth.
JERRY: It has a teeth-type deal going around it.
And as I said they sort of dance and sway
JERRY: in whatever alien gum this exists. RYAN: Dancing teeth?
JERRY: Dancing Teeth, obviously check out my first album.
AMY: (laughs) JERRY: Jerry Holkins. DJ Jerry Holkins.
Dancing Teeth.
KRIS: It's dope.
JERRY: No. So it reaches out almost with a curiosity toward the rogue.
The rogue immediately begins to dispense weaponry.
Daggers coming from...
from-- absolutely from mysterious locales in her kit.
And they hit it and it sort of sounds like...
like if a fork were to be slid off of a table,
and were to strike a wood floor.
It just rings in a metallic way.
JERRY: But you're not-- KRIS: No purchase.
JERRY: You're not sure that...
You're not sure that these daggers are going to impact.
You think that daggers might not be the right tool in this case.
Farther out the frond...
With interest now!
Maybe even enthusiasm.
Goes around, and then in the manner of a Venus flytrap...
just cinches-- just closes.
KRIS: On the other guy.
JERRY: Yeah, and then it starts to draw them in back toward the center mass of this orb.
And as you see it get closer to the center it begins to thrash them against itself...
KRIS: It's like the inside of a Langolier.
JERRY: Yeah! And then... RYAN: (laughs)
JERRY: they get drawn in to that sort of dark mass that you can see light refracting off inside.
KRIS: No, so they don't exist anymore.
I'm not seeing them going, hooray!
JERRY: No. KATE: I don't think they ever did exist after this.
JERRY: You think-- AMY: Yeah they've been eaten out of time.
JERRY: You think-- KATE: (laughing) Nice.
JERRY: You think that there is a case to be made
that they will not be showing up at the company Christmas party.
KRIS: Okay. Interesting.
KRIS: All right do I-- KATE: It sounds metal as hell, to be honest with you.
KRIS: I-- I um...
I hold my...
focus out with the sigil side toward it.
As much as I can.
How far am I from it? I assume it knows me--
JERRY: It is continuing now until it fills almost your entire field of vision.
And you can see that it has extended a kind of pseudopod beneath...
and it has risen up beneath you, almost like two hands.
And you're now standing on a platform of this living ruby.
KRIS: (exhales) AMY: It likes you.
KRIS: Kind of just going to start weeping.
But I hold it together.
(stammering) I say...
I reach out this time telepathically with Awakened Mind.
And I say, is it you?
KATE: (whispering) What?
(exhales) (whispering) Dungeons &amp; Dragons, bitch!
(laughter) JERRY: I love this man.
KRIS: Because I'm assuming that this rune that I cannot read, even though I can read all language, is a name.
Is a name that perhaps this thing owns.
KRIS: Is he? JERRY: Is conscious of.
KRIS: Yes. It must at least be.
JERRY: "Why have you deny my precious gifts?"
KATE: (whispering) I have chills! AMY: This is very good!
JERRY: You were so close.
"Why did you deny my gifts?"
KRIS: (whispering) Gifts...
JERRY: "You were so near to it. So near to me."
"If I told you my name now, you would be destroyed."
KRIS: Got to think this through-- JERRY: "We could have cracked this world like an egg."
KRIS: You're saying everything I want to hear.
(laughter)
Even though I'm a little upset that I didn't disappointed.
JERRY: "Do you even recall my Trifold Revelation?"
KRIS: I do not. It was taken from me.
JERRY: You hear a shriek.
Somewhere in it. It's not the voice that you hear.
Because the voice that you hear is reverberating inside your skull.
This sound comes from the entity.
Says...
"The universe..."
"is nothing..."
"but meat..."
"and mouths."
"And you are one of my mouths."
"This is the pact you entered into."
"You have no recollection of it?
"You understand that that has no effect on whether you are bound by it."
KRIS: Absolutely.
I say I agree with it a hundred percent.
It may not even be language I'm using.
I hope that it can sense my enthusiasm for this philosophy.
JERRY: The entire structure...
The entire ruby structure in front of you becomes transparent.
And you can see all the pinpricks through it and around it.
You're surrounded by it.
And it says,
"We will devour..."
"every world..."
"and every star."
KRIS: There-- JERRY: "This is my Second Revelation."
KRIS: There's no other way it could have been.
JERRY: "I will fatten you..."
"with destruction..."
"until you, yourself, are devoured."
KRIS: I'm at your service.
KATE: (panting breaths)
RYAN: He seems nice.
JERRY: "But you know--" AMY: What a good guy!
RYAN: Yeah. (laughs)
JERRY: "You know that my gifts are not free."
"This is the pact you entered into willingly."
"When you forsook Lolth."
"A pitiful creatures. A..."
"local..."
"goddess."
KRIS: She sucks.
(laughter) RYAN: A townie.
(laughter) JERRY: Exactly.
KRIS: Low rent. RYAN: Yeah.
KATE: (laughs) (whispering) Jeez. JERRY: But there are...
"This is my fear."
And the blood-red reverts in front of you.
Says, "There are..."
"there are aspects of myself..."
"that can't forgive you..."
"for having cast away..."
"our precious gifts."
"If you are able to survive them..."
"we may continue."
And you can see rippling out from the right edge... just like mouths.
It's like those awful online pictures where like it shows a person's knee...
JERRY: And it's all-- AMY: Hmm!
JERRY: And it's all-- KRIS: It's like a lotus pod, yeah.
JERRY: Lotus pod. KATE: Ew!
JERRY: You see it just dips in and then there's just like barnacled mouths sweeping around.
And it rushes over you.
And completely covers you.
KRIS: I-- as it does I make the sound,
Aha!
(laughter)
(laughter) RYAN: You let out a little, yippee!
JERRY: But as it does so...
you feel the contact of it.
Impossibly hot.
KRIS: Hmm.
JERRY: But like...
Even another second of it would be too much.
And then beginning with your hand and the stone...
it peels and pulls away.
So there's something about it. It's almost like a floatie.
You're in a kind of womb of this stuff.
And it is progressively, continually, trying to counteract this stone.
KRIS: This object I have. I see.
KRIS: (sighs) JERRY: So...
JERRY: that's what's happening with you.
KRIS: (clapping) JERRY: On this path...
AMY: Literally a walk in the woods compared to you. JERRY: Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
RYAN: It's been three hours or-- (whistles)
We've long given up on you.
AMY: So more equity, right? JERRY: Exactly.
KATE: Yep. 33.3% share. JERRY: 33/33/33.
JERRY: I'll just that last percent.
JERRY: It'll accrue to the Dungeon Master. AMY: (noncommittal sound)
JERRY: So the way that it functions for the rest of the party is that...
you can hear a conversation occurring.
AMY: (laughing) Oh god! JERRY: You can't make out the words.
AMY: Okay.
JERRY: But there is a small voice echoed by a vast voice.
AMY: (high pitched) Me, me, me, me, me. RYAN: Little baby voice.
KATE: (low pitched murmuring sound)
AMY: (high pitched) Me, me.
(laughter) KRIS: Cool and powerful.
(laughter)
JERRY: And after-- RYAN: And confident!
JERRY: After a couple of exchanges bounce back and forth...
every time the larger sound is enunciated...
you can see cracks...
from behind you...
faults...
AMY: Oh okay.
JERRY: reaching out.
The problem is that these faults are not nearly in the ground itself.
It isn't a natural phenomenon.
These cracks extend directly through space.
AMY: The good kind of cracks! JERRY: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
JERRY: Yes it's not-- AMY: (chef's kiss sound)
JERRY: It's a crack epidemic.
AMY: Sure. RYAN: Mmm.
JERRY: And it reaches out-- RYAN: Plaguing our forest. (laughs)
JERRY: Yeah exactly. (laughter)
JERRY: Until there are no fewer than six.
And then there is a shift at some final moment,
where in a seismic way...
they push and then separate.
AMY: Great.
JERRY: So on one shard to the left,
it has split out and Rosie is here on a kind of spire that reaches up and out.
Walnut and Donaar are on a larger flat section to the right reaching out.
But the doorway path that was available to you...
is now sundered in slices.
AMY: Great.
JERRY: And you can see--
This is incredibly odd, but I have to describe it to you.
JERRY: That's the task I've been given. AMY: Sure. Bring it on.
JERRY: In the cracks themselves, you can see what looks almost like a...
It's crystalline in how it refracts light.
And it's polygonal. It has faces like a gem.
But it flows underneath like a liquid.
And you can see...
Again! This is strange.
Both to your left...
and to your right you see exactly the same thing.
As though it's the same space in different sides.
AMY: Did someone like throw rock in the holodeck?
RYAN: Uh... &gt;&gt; KATE: Yeah. JERRY: Right?
AMY: Okay. JERRY: And so you can see...
and you see K'thriss Drow'b...
clinging on to what you know to be his focus.
Sort of bobbing like a bottle in this stuff.
Like you can see that it is trying to wash up and pull him down.
But by the same token, there is something-- some property...
of this situation that is keeping him from being completely consumed.
AMY: And that's what we get? JERRY: That's what you get.
RYAN: Well we're on a platform.
KATE: How far is my spire from their platform? RYAN: So we can just 50/50 this.
JERRY: Right now the crack-- (laughter)
JERRY: the crack between the two is about five feet.
KATE: Okay.
AMY: That's a lot. JERRY: Like I say, each of these splits--
JERRY: So even in the cracks that you can see...
that are higher-- that are just in space--
you can see the same reflection.
You can see K'thriss Drow'b in those as well reaching out.
KRIS: Do I have an awareness of them?
JERRY: You do not.
You are completely consumed by this act of consumption.
And knowing K'thriss,
being familiar with that character sheet,
I'll be very curious to see how you spend this time...
in this kind of proximity...
to this entity that you have sought so long.
RYAN: The final moments. KRIS: (ecstatic grunts)
JERRY: Right? I mean I'll be curious how you invest that time. But--
KRIS: That's not even for the DM to know.
JERRY: No, exactly. (laughter)
JERRY: Exactly. But I would like to get-- just because I'm going to need it eventually,
I would like to get initiative rolls from the people.
KRIS: Ooh yeah. AMY: Great. I love when it's--
AMY: Hey solve the puzzle. But also just initiative anyway. KATE: Just in case.
RYAN: Fight this giant red d20.
AMY: Walnut got 18.
JERRY: 18's very good.
RYAN: Uh... 16. JERRY: Mm-hmm.
KATE: Eight!
AMY: That's almost as good as an 18. RYAN: It is.
KATE: Hey! This is a cooperative game, ladies and gentlemen.
JERRY: Yeah. I need one from you too, K'thriss Drow'b. KRIS: Oh yeah. Let's get that.
You going to love the way you look. I guarantee it.
It's a seven.
(laughter) JERRY: All right.
JERRY: Oh hey. And look at my cool initiative thingies. KATE: (gasps) Ooh!
JERRY: That Elyssa made for me. So cool!
KATE: Thanks, Elyssa! KRIS: Hooray!
AMY: That's good for me too. KATE: That's so cute.
JERRY: And hey! Thanks for drawing all the characters.
JERRY: That was very nice of you. KATE: Thanks, Kris.
KRIS: A pleasure!
JERRY: Now Walnut!
How are you going to contend with either this fractured door, this K'thriss Drow'b scenario, or both?
AMY: So... um...
knowing what I know of the drow and knowing nothing of what you're seeing,
I immediately think that he is responsible for what's happening.
JERRY: (laughs)
AMY: Like I see this focus as like-- things are you know...
JERRY: Shit is coming out of it. AMY: Yeah like things are coming out of it.
AMY: This is shaking that you've-- you know, we fallen into some dark trap of yours.
KRIS: Well wait. Let me get some clarity here.
Am I warding these mouths away with my focus?
AMY: Or are you just watching it? KRIS: Is it clear? Or am I just observing it?
JERRY: When your turn comes around, you can play Dungeons &amp; Dragons.
KRIS: But... I want to reroll initiative. JERRY: Until then play with your phone!
KRIS: No. RYAN: Yeah. (laughs)
RYAN: I want to keep rolling until I win. AMY: Me first!
(laughter) JERRY: Until I succeed.
AMY: Okay one last question. JERRY: Yeah.
AMY: Well maybe not like it's directly-- but I definitely think maybe this is some of your dark drow workings.
JERRY: Mm-hmm.
AMY: Do I perceive this as I'm actually seeing K'thriss?
Or am I looking at this as if through a projected image?
Am I actually seeing him twice?
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. I mean the way that the closest thing that you can think of--
like the closest analogy would be a broken mirror.
AMY: Okay. Okay.
JERRY: Because the movements are identical.
AMY: Completely identical. Okay, okay, okay.
Oh goodness gracious.
I have just...
RYAN: Turn into a bear. (laughs)
(laughter)
AMY: Ah! Um...
I just have nothing that I...
RYAN: Yeah. KRIS: I was going to say, try Thornwhip again.
RYAN: (laughs) Just whipping his face? KATE: Oh!
KRIS: Ah! AMY: Stop it!
AMY: Stop it! Stop it!
JERRY: Stop doing evil. AMY: Stop with that devil stuff!
AMY: No, oh. Good golly what do I even have for this?
I'm so used to playing a spellcaster where I'm like,
Ah. I conjure up a disc and I can get us out of here.
JERRY: Yeah you can conjure discs, you can use physical solutions. I mean there's all kinds of--
AMY: How far away is Rosie about?
JERRY: Right now the fissure between the two of you is five.
About five feet.
JERRY: It's pretty easily jumpable. AMY: That's nimble.
AMY: Good gracious.
I don't even know what to try...
JERRY: It isn't a true initiative situation.
So if you just want to think about the situation for a while that's totally legitimate.
I know that I have presented you with something... you know...
AMY: Yeah this is like so... JERRY: novel.
AMY: Like I'm in this crystalline Cthuluoid-dimension here.
AMY: But it's just a forest fractaling apart. KATE: Right but it's fucking tight as hell, isn't it?
AMY: It's tight &gt;&gt; KATE: Yeah, so good. RYAN: It's the third episode.
AMY: Yeah it's the third episode just with endgame stuff. RYAN: Doesn't it usually scale up to this?
JERRY: No, no. You don't even know where the endgame goes.
KATE: You stay put, because Rosie's by herself.
So I will jump to meet you guys when it is my turn to play Dungeons &amp; Dragons.
AMY: Sure, sure, sure.
Yeah so just the image of a beautiful forest fractaling apart, let's just pretend that Walnut is...
JERRY: Just stunned. AMY: (shakily) Wha-ah-ah.
KATE: Okay. JERRY: Stunned by it.
JERRY: Donaar Blit'zen.
Approach this scenario and generate solutions.
RYAN: (sighs) God... JERRY: Create a plan for Q1.
RYAN: Yeah so I guess in this sort of scenario I would be like,
Hey, vagrant!
Can you hear me?
KRIS: Are you talking to me? RYAN: Yeah.
RYAN: Can he hear me? KRIS: What do I hear?
JERRY: It sounds like you're underwater.
RYAN: Oh. KRIS: So I can hear a voice.
KRIS: Can I tell it's him? JERRY: Yeah you can tell.
KRIS: Oh okay, okay.
RYAN: Just can't see me. JERRY: He has a novel cadence.
RYAN: Yeah. KATE: I'll say.
KRIS: Ah! Suddenly I'm in the void.
RYAN: Dulcet tones.
JERRY: The first words you exchanged followed a similar pattern.
JERRY: So... KRIS: Okay.
KRIS: (laughs) RYAN: I don't have any more money!
(laughter)
AMY: Money... money... money...
KRIS: This isn't necessary! I don't have any...
KRIS: (stammering) Why are you here?
I'm offended that he's present for this.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, yeah. I had a cool thing going. KRIS: Yeah.
JERRY: I had this evil god. AMY: It's like your mom walking in on you.
JERRY: Yeah that's what it is.
JERRY: Mom! KRIS: I wasn't doing anything.
AMY: (shuddering)
JERRY: It's just my evil lord. KATE: That's why I want a lock on the door.
JERRY: Yeah exactly.
KRIS: Yeah. JERRY: Used to have a lock when I was 16.
(laughter)
RYAN: I get the internet on this thing, you know.
AMY: I didn't realize we can try talking to him. That makes sense.
KATE: (laughs) KRIS You did it.
JERRY: You were overcome.
JERRY: There was an idyllic forest and you were annihilated. RYAN: I did it!
RYAN: Problem solved. So wait.
So can I hear him? Are we conversing to an extent?
KRIS: Yeah I literally was like, why are you here?
JERRY: Yeah, no. You hear him perfectly clear.
RYAN: I say, stop whatever you're doing!
You're messing up the forest!
KRIS: (laughs) Smokey.
(laughter)
I'm...
I'm not...
I didn't do anything. (laughs)
(laughter)
RYAN: Do you need help? KRIS: No, no. I say...
KRIS: Not now. (laughter)
(laughter) KATE: I'm busy!
KRIS: Yeah.
KRIS: I'm all right. JERRY: I'm so pleased.
RYAN: All right.
KRIS: Things are good.
RYAN: Okay! JERRY: You think that that might not be true.
KATE: They don't seem great.
RYAN: Yeah from this end they don't seem that great!
RYAN: I have divine sense. JERRY: Exactly.
JERRY: Divine Scents from L'Oréal?
RYAN: Yeah. KATE: Wow.
RYAN: What will that get me in this? KRIS: (sniffs air)
KRIS: Vitamin B. RYAN: It'll confirm what I'm seeing, I guess.
JERRY: Divine sense is basically... KATE: Can you read the spell for us?
RYAN: Until the end of turn, I can sense undead, fiends, and celestial presence.
KATE: Oh!
RYAN: And I can uh... KRIS: That's very important.
AMY: You can do stuff?
RYAN: Yeah. KATE: Holy crap.
JERRY: Yeah do you want to use it? RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: Oh yeah. Every one of these-- all these cracks-- every one of these cracks...
are the same fiendish entity.
RYAN: Hmm.
JERRY: When you have trained to do this...
you know it was with minor artifacts...
You know what I mean?
Like you're not...
You have never experienced-- you have never been in the presence of something this all-encompassing...
AMY: On the level? JERRY: Yeah. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Mm-hmm.
KRIS: I'm telling you, he's the real deal.
RYAN: Yeah.
AMY: Didn't I say he was great? RYAN: Oh! Ew. Ugh.
JERRY: But you can feel that in this medium-- RYAN: This is worse than the goddamn magic house we were in!
RYAN: When are we just going to fight like regular old orcs and stuff?
(laughter)
JERRY: There's a period of time where that occurs.
But the sort of slivers that you're on, these chunks, they sort of bob in it.
Sort of feels like a floating dock.
RYAN: Hmm. AMY: Ugh.
JERRY: So they do shift and move in this medium.
And then before you in the distance are the different pieces of this gate.
Which you can try to resolve.
Rosie Beestinger. What's going on?
KATE: I am fascinated by everything that I see.
because it looks like some crazy astronomical,
meteorological phenomenon that I never read anything about.
JERRY: You think that you can see...
You think that you can see...
stars reflected in it.
KATE: Mm-hmm. JERRY: They're warped. I mean they're the...
they're the...
constellations that you know, but they are shifted--
just out of joint in the surface of this sort of canopy.
KATE: So I have the sage background
which basically is just I know where to find almost any piece of information,
I also have this meteorological astronomy thing.
I don't know that those things would help me understand what's going on here.
But I thought I would ask the Dungeon Master.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. If you can-- You want to know if...
KATE: If there's anything that my background in research,
in my monastery reading many, many, many books,
if there's any kind of religious text or sacred knowledge that I might have run across that would be familiar here.
JERRY: Well let's take a look. AMY: Is "sacred" be the right word for what we're looking at here?
KATE: Yeah, I mean he seems like he's in some kind of religious thrall, so...
JERRY: Exactly. Well here. Let's dish up a history check. Let's see what you get.
KATE: Okay. Let's do it.
That's not great. That's a five.
JERRY: Now, Rosie... KRIS: Do you want to try...
KATE: Oh!
KATE: Yes. Sure. Yeah! JERRY: You can absolutely do it.
KATE: Thank you for the advantage dice. RYAN: Forest Friends.
KATE: Here we go. JERRY: Forest Friends are back huh?
KATE: Ten. Not any better. RYAN: Yeah. &gt;&gt; AMY: Oh yeah!
RYAN: Nice.
KRIS: You get to fill these mouths with squirrels! KATE: I'm like, mmm...
RYAN: (laughs) KRIS: Feed them!
KATE: I read about a god or two.
JERRY: You know about stars, exactly.
KATE: I know about some stars. JERRY: So let me see...
JERRY: in terms of...
Okay. Here's how we'll go.
You know...
you have...
heard stories-- you don't know if this is not--
There would be a lot more detail for you later. It might be something you can research.
KATE: Okay.
JERRY: But you know that there are...
constellations that sometimes lose stars.
Or have stars replaced in them by other stars.
JERRY: And that process isn't fully understood. KATE: I see.
JERRY: So when you look at this surface and you see these...
you see these astronomical phenomenon-- or phenomena-- you are...
It's as though they're from another perspective.
Like this is not how they look. And you know how they look in different hemispheres.
It's the shapes that you know but they are warped.
KATE: Okay.
KATE: So the knowledge that I gain from this is that we are observing something
that is not anywhere on the plane of Earth that we find ourselves in.
JERRY: Yeah it is not-- this is not how things look from--
KATE: It's not motherfucking Kansas, is what you're telling me. JERRY: your perspective. Yes.
RYAN: Let's get this Elder god off this motherfucking plane.
(laughter)
KATE: So I don't know what that gains us
except that I don't that think K'thriss is in a very good situation.
I think he's very far away from us,
and that potentially these cracks are about to splinter our very existence.
JERRY: That's your feeling. KATE: Yeah.
JERRY: That's your read on the sitch.
KATE: That's my instinct.
RYAN: As I'm shuddering and vomiting from the divine sense.
JERRY: (groans) RYAN: Yeah can confirm.
RYAN: (dry heaving sounds)
KATE: (nasally) From my studies, I can tell you...
AMY: Well actually.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, exactly. There's got to be a hashtag.
KATE: Can I also take a movement and jump over to join my friends?
JERRY: Easily. Easily. KATE: Or is that too many? Okay.
AMY: The icebergs are drifting apart.
AMY: We're going to have to polar bear it up soon. KATE: So do I even have to roll?
JERRY: No. God.
JERRY: No, no. KATE: (laughs) Stupid question.
JERRY: No, no, grandma. So...
So straight off of the staff.
Just the easiest thing in the world, but when you push off...
it's like a gondola.
Like you push off the other one and it sort of widens.
AMY/KATE: Ooh.
JERRY: And Kris, even more of this false daylight is cast down into this thing.
And you can see K'thriss just sort of bobbing in it.
But it's just darkness.
Underneath the ruby's surface it's just this black expanse.
K'thriss Drow'b.
Let's play some Dungeons &amp; Dragons.
KRIS: Ooh yeah. Can't wait. RYAN: Wait so is she with us now?
AMY: Yeah. JERRY: Yeah. She's popped over.
RYAN: She lands and I'm just like, so 50/50-- I mean...! 33/33/33!
AMY: She's been there the whole time.
JERRY: You are also real and you can be part of it.
K'thriss Drow'b. What do you got?
So you are basically suspended inside this...
JERRY: entity. KRIS: Right I'm enwombed by this mouth.
JERRY: So you can approach it in any way.
You can reach out with arcana.
You can...
KRIS: Boy! JERRY: You know what I mean? Like--
JERRY: You have the-- KRIS: It's a smörgåsbord. Can't wait.
KRIS: What a feast! KATE: Yum yum yum.
JERRY: Yeah I'm excited to see how you contend with it.
KRIS: I want to-- well first of all I want to attempt to speak with it again telepathically.
So I ask-- I'm speaking to the mouth ball.
JERRY: Yeah. KRIS: Are you an aspect of it?
JERRY: An aspect-- Oh of...
JERRY: You want to know if it's an aspect of the-- KRIS: Right it spoke of certain...
KRIS: portions of itself as being disappointed.
I want to know am I dealing with a specific aspect of it right now.
I'm not talking to the big boy, apparently.
Or maybe I am.
KATE: Is your god named Big Boy? KRIS: He's Big Boy.
JERRY: Yeah and André 3000.
JERRY: It's like-- this is the-- in the pantheon of the Acquisitions Incorporated universe...
they're in constantly opposed poles-- No.
KATE: They fight at their whim.
JERRY: That's not canonical. KRIS: He's an Outkast.
JERRY: That's not canonical.
KRIS: It makes sense.
KRIS: That was for the-- KATE: (laughing) That was good.
(laughter)
AMY: Just to clarify.
JERRY: It says...
"I am its unified heart."
KRIS: That's good news for me.
AMY: Aww it kept you in its heart. RYAN: Yeah.
RYAN: Hearts love Valentines.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. KATE: Oh! We can solve this puzzle. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Yeah.
AMY: With love. KATE: Candy.
AMY: Oh. KATE: Right. Love.
JERRY: So like I say, do you want to reach out and try to assess it?
KRIS: Yeah, let me-- let's try and do some of that.
Now that I-- It's good to know that it will correspond with me.
KRIS: So let me... JERRY: Yeah pen-pals.
RYAN: Are you still fighting it off as he's doing this?
AMY: No, he loves it! Look at him! He loves it! RYAN: Is it still like...?
JERRY: He's soaking in it like Palmolive. Or whatever the opposite of Palmolive is.
You are not being moistened by this.
KRIS: Ooh. JERRY: No, you're being desiccated.
KRIS: Let me do... deception-- No.
KRIS: Let me do arcana. JERRY: Yeah. yeah.
KRIS: Let's see what I got.
Actually let me try religion because I'm a little higher there.
Let me see what I get--
KRIS/KATE: Ooh!
KRIS: It's a 20, my friend. KATE: That's a nat 20.
JERRY: It's a 20? Oh Jesus. KRIS: It's a natural 20, my friend.
KRIS: Get me up-- Tell me the endgame. KATE: You're going to write it.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. AMY: (laughing) Tell me the endgame.
JERRY: So when you're 20th level... here's what happens.
KRIS: Here's what goes up.
JERRY: So it's-- you're holding-- it's almost like a water wing.
Like you're holding on to this chunk of the altar...
and it is always trying to get between you and it.
KRIS: Oh it's not just warded away by it, it's trying to take it from me.
JERRY: This is the only thing that is allowing you to be here and exist in this context at all.
And you can tell that there is a part of it...
whenever this fluid passes over the symbol...
it retracts instantly.
JERRY: But it seems to forget this every five seconds or so. KRIS: Right.
JERRY: It's always trying again and always learning that that doesn't work.
And...
what you perceive from the iconography-- from the religious iconography...
you think that the symbol on your stone...
can't possibly refer to this thing.
KRIS: Oh... yeah.
Seems like it wouldn't mind its own name.
JERRY: Yeah. As a relic you're like...
As one of its artifacts it would adore it.
It would protect it and nurture it.
And what it's actually trying to do is...
port it out and forcibly separate you from it.
So that symbol does not reflect--
That symbol is not the name of this thing.
KRIS: Oh. All right well... JERRY: Whatever it is.
KRIS: Now I'm less excited.
JERRY: Yeah.
KRIS: So I go from adulation to like, whoa! What?
JERRY: No, no. It gets worse. AMY: Yucky.
JERRY: Yeah. Walnut Dankgrass. Let's play Dungeons &amp; Dragons.
AMY: Yeah... Walnut's like...
Wow the AI screening process for interns is super rigorous!
RYAN: Yeah. AMY: Huh!
AMY: Um... Okay! JERRY: How does anyone get through?
KATE: She goes from stunned to like pithy one-liners.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. KATE: Damn it, Walnut.
KRIS: May I add a little flavor by the way? AMY: Yeah.
KRIS: Like you've-- after this has occurred and I'm now aware that
I don't audience with what I want to have audience with.
AMY: Yeah.
KRIS: I go from like,
No, no. I'm doing-- Let me see what's going on.
To I'm just like shouting. I'm shrieking.
KRIS: No! No! This is not what I want anymore. JERRY: No, it's the worst. It's the worst.
JERRY: Now. Walnut, I want to emphasize a couple of things to you.
Okay? So everybody has got cool shit.
AMY: Hmm!
JERRY: Boons and banes from the channel...
AMY: Ooh so many Forest Friends.
KATE: So many Forest Friends.
JERRY: You can kick in-- People can put in cheers and those bits work up towards specials.
So Donaar gets a re-- get you re-juiced.
Just sacs of acid filled back up.
RYAN: Yeah because I'm still empty right? Because like we jumped right through the portal.
JERRY: Exactly. KATE: You blew an acid load.
JERRY: Waln-- So to speak.
RYAN: I need a nap.
JERRY: Walnut-- Refractory period!
Walnut, Forest Friends.
It looks like the Forest Friends were pretty entertaining...
KATE: (whispering) Oh my god. JERRY: to them last time, so you got a couple.
RYAN: You're just a squirrel geyser.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. KRIS: Pour some Friends into this.
JERRY: Squirrel cannon! KATE: Squirrel geyser.
AMY: Yeah. JERRY: Squirrel Cannon. Squirrel Shotgun.
Rosie has Back in My Day so you can basically grant her
a skill roll proficiency in one skill or tool for one roll.
Just remembers her prodigious experience.
And then K'thriss can consult his icon and gain the effects of Augury.
Which is basically like, "Should we do this? Should we not do this?" type thing.
KRIS: That would be-- RYAN: I was going to say that'd be great.
JERRY: It's the Cthulhu version of the Magic 8-Ball.
AMY: It's called a hint!
JERRY: Exactly. AMY: And I didn't even get one.
JERRY: But the main thing, Walnut, that I wanted to emphasize to you
is that you have got Forest Friends.
JERRY: I just want to make sure you do not miss them. AMY: Oh I'm lousy with Forest Friends. I see.
AMY: Let me ask you a question with the Forest Friends, because I don't know.
Is there a limit on what kind of little Forest Friends?
Do they have to be tiny? What's the size class?
JERRY: It is a sudden swarm of small animals that scurry out of nowhere.
AMY: Scurry out of nowhere. JERRY: If your suggestion is cool I can take it.
JERRY: But we can also go-- KATE: How rad is it?
KRIS: Small compared to us or like a god?
AMY: Have you seen the movie Up?
And can birds airlift him out of there-- (laughing) No! I'm sorry! I can't!
KATE: Continue down this path,
KATE: It's Dungeons &amp; Dragons. JERRY: Yeah continue--
JERRY: to investigate it. AMY: Can we Operation Dumbo Drop K'thriss--
RYAN: A bunch of snakes make a rope... AMY: from his...
AMY: (laughs) Yeah. No. I mean I have rope.
JERRY: Yeah but that's not snake rope.
JERRY: Fuck that. AMY: No I'm just wondering if I have like you know...
AMY: a bunch of like birds that can lift him out.
KRIS: I like-- I like-- the snakes. You're like, grab the snakes!
And I go, always!
(laughter)
JERRY: 100%! AMY: You bet! Nom nom nom.
AMY: No, no, no. KRIS: Okay what are we doing?
RYAN: I like the idea that they're loosely tied together
RYAN: and you throw them they just come apart. AMY: I'm trying to think of a helpful animal--
RYAN: And just drift in this... AMY: that would be good in this situation.
KATE: What's the muscliest bird?
AMY: The muscliest bird? RYAN: Oh the muscle bird.
KATE: Amy knows a lot about birds!
RYAN: From New Zealand. AMY: (sighs) What would be a good one?
KATE: A good, buff bird. RYAN: It's like a flying bicep.
KATE: You know those birds with arms that they would--
JERRY: A bicep with two wings?
AMY: Yeah it's like a sparrow but with-- KATE: Yeah, super jacked.
JERRY: So like a ripped-- AMY: I don't know, something like...
JERRY: A ripped ass bird?
AMY: Just like some-- I mean I saw some eagles fighting on Planet Earth 2.
KATE: What about a swarm of eagles?
AMY: Yeah can I just get nasty with eagles?
KATE: Just some really gnarly eagles. AMY: I don't want to waste it! I don't want it to be like,
AMY: I summon a bunch of eagles. And you're like, cool. Two sparrows come out.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, yeah. No, half of one sparrow. RYAN: And they claw his face.
JERRY: No, no, no. This is the sort of thing that, you know, we want to use.
AMY: Mmm okay. JERRY: I want this to happen.
KATE: What's your favorite kind of eagle, Walnut?
AMY: Um... Oh I mean there's so many. KATE: That's a tough choice. I know, I know.
AMY: I mean I do like golden eagles the most.
Also in fantasy stories, a lot of times eagles help out people that are in trouble
and don't know what to do when you need to retcon ourselves out of the situation.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. It's like, oh shit yes. Send the king.
Why not? Why not send the king of the eagles?
RYAN: Deus ex eagle?
AMY: I would like to try and do this. We'll see what happens. We'll all learn together.
I'd like to search deep inside of myself
and summon up these Forest Friends and wish so hard for eagles!
(laughter) AMY: For big birds!
KRIS: Please. AMY: Come help my good, good drow boy.
AMY: Who is just drowning in goo.
JERRY/KRIS: Yeah.
AMY: If you're screaming and also I think that maybe you being in there is like a wrench in two cogs of a clock.
And if I can just get you out of there--
AMY: it'll just go back? KRIS: Yeah maybe it'll go back. &gt;&gt; KATE: Maybe, yeah!
JERRY: I like it so-- KATE: (straining) I wish for eagles!
JERRY: So yeah exactly. So...
So like from the vanishing point of all these shards...
you hear a screech.
And seven eagles... come out.
You can see them sort of reflected against all these edges.
And for whatever reason they don't seem too weirded out.
(laughter)
AMY: They're used to this.
JERRY: You'd think there'd be some reaction.
AMY: Yeah.
JERRY: So they come out and they perch on the edge and they're looking down at the situation.
How do you want to guide these Forest Friends?
AMY: I want to...
point to K'thriss.
And I want to say, you know,
Bring him to us! Get him out of there.
KATE: Get him. Get him. AMY: Sic him! Sic him, boy! Sic him!
AMY: No. &gt;&gt; KATE: Get that drow. KRIS: These eagles are biting me!
(laughter) AMY: Ah!
AMY: They get excited about your sigil and take it away! No.
AMY: Ah! K'thriss is devoured.
JERRY: They bring it up into their nest. AMY: They bring it to me!
JERRY: And they just rest on it. They feel good.
AMY/KRIS: Yeah.
KRIS: The sigil, you're like, that's a good thing to have.
Those mouths don't like it.
Let's get it! And he gets what he wants, we get what we want...
AMY: No, I want to point at K'thriss with urgency.
Like almost psionically imploring them to help.
KATE: Right. KRIS: Yeah.
KATE: I'm going to watch you and be like, man I should have gone to druid school.
AMY: (laughs) KATE: This is so cool.
JERRY: So they leap into action at your direction.
AMY: Please don't kill these eagles, Jerry.
JERRY: Oh they're dead.
(laughter)
JERRY: Yeah this is like a chipper shredder but just for big birds.
AMY: Mmm. Okay.
JERRY: It gets advantage on liquifying birds.
(laughter)
JERRY: It has bird liquefier... KATE: It's written there.
KRIS: Smaller birds might have made it.
AMY: That's also on the menu right next to Jim and Tonic.
KRIS: Just the right size.
JERRY: No, no. It's like a conical burr.
One part of the bird goes in and it's goes-- (grinding sound)
No. Nothing like that happens.
AMY: Good because that's my nightmare.
JERRY: No, so the first one...
swoops down and is able to sort of catch the hem of his sleeve...
and sort of drags him through this...
JERRY: It's viscous, but it's not solid. AMY: Mm-hmm. Okay.
KRIS: And I don't know where this eagle suddenly showed up out of.
JERRY: No. All of a sudden a bird grabs part of your robe
and starts dragging you toward this dark shore
that you can sort of see in the edge of this field.
KRIS: And I say, g-good bird!
(laughter)
JERRY: The next one-- RYAN: So the birds are swimming?
JERRY: Yeah exactly. So the next one flies down...
and then it almost like it gets ensorcelled by the reflection of itself in the surface...
and just smashes headlong into it.
AMY: Good bird. JERRY: So it gets up briefly.
JERRY: Sort of like, have you seen like a puppy on a...
AMY: Yes of course. JERRY: frozen puddle?
AMY: Yes. JERRY: Like that.
JERRY: And there's a few of these scratches, and then it just disappears...
AMY: Oh no. JERRY: into it.
AMY: You're rolling for all my eagles? KATE: I liked them. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Ugh.
JERRY: No, no. It's all right. The next one is able to swoop in after the last one.
Grab the hem and continue to drag him closer.
All right. You're good.
KRIS: Whew. JERRY: The last one was able-- they're basically like...
JERRY: pulling and letting go and the next one pulls down. AMY: Ah gotcha.
JERRY: Like it's-- It's like they drilled on this somehow.
AMY: These are actually from different fantasy IPs.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. It's all the best eagles.
AMY: All your favorite eagles! KATE: All-star eagles!
AMY: Now that's what I call eagle.
AMY: Seven.
JERRY: Volume Seven. We've got like Gwaihir...
We got them all! We're ready to go.
AMY: Marahute.
JERRY: You pull...
KATE: I hear you. I see you. RYAN: I don't know what that--
JERRY: The last one pulls you toward this sort of like border.
You can see like a dark mist border.
And then as soon as you're pulled to the edge of it...
you can see-- sort of again, like sort of like off of a dock...
Like you can reach up and see this sheared edge of the reel.
You can see sort of like a forest canopy,
but you can see everywhere inside these furrows this entity.
This creature that you have somehow sworn yourself to.
KRIS: Yeah.
JERRY: So on your turn, you think that you can possibly grab that edge and pull yourself up.
KRIS: Okay. JERRY: Donaar Blit'zen.
RYAN: Uh... so you're almost out?
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. AMY: I'm so nervous.
RYAN: I don't know if I want to reach in there and get him.
JERRY: Please do. &gt;&gt; KATE: Just get him! AMY: Just grab him by the scruff of his neck.
JERRY: Please do! I want that.
RYAN: I'm afraid I'm going to get sucked in or something.
JERRY: I've been waiting for this.
RYAN: I have a climber's kit. KATE: I turn to Walnut. You got to boss eagles around.
KATE: So I turn to Donaar, I'm like, sic him.
(laughter)
KATE: Get him, boy. RYAN: You got that rope, right?
AMY: I do. RYAN: I say, can I have that rope?
KATE: Is it made of snakes? It's a normal rope. AMY: 50 feet hempen rope.
KATE: Normal rope. Wow. Okay RYAN: 50 feet of rope. All right.
KRIS: I'm so touched you guys are going to come in here and all that.
The eagles did a lot of that work.
RYAN: All right I say...
Do you still want to get out?
(laughter)
KRIS: Yep! Yep! Yep! Yes! Yes. Yes. RYAN: Are you good? All right.
(laughter) RYAN: And then I dangle this rope.
I say, here you go!
RYAN: It's just like... JERRY: Here so...
RYAN: Grab it. KRIS: I need more than the end.
JERRY: So as you near the edge and dangle the rope over...
something glints off of the undulating surface of this.
It's all right. It's cool.
JERRY: I need a wisdom check from you. AMY/KATE: Oh no.
AMY: Not from Donaar.
RYAN: No, my wisdom is all right.
JERRY: It's great.
RYAN: It's normal.
RYAN: 16. KATE: Hey!
JERRY: It's great.
You can feel yourself on the edge of this as you dangle it over.
You can feel yourself just drawn into it.
And like for a second your foot moves...
in preparation to...
swim in this.
And then you sort of catch your back foot.
You dig your heel into the edge of the strut that you're on.
JERRY: So that's-- RYAN: Could have been bad.
(laughter)
JERRY: No it's supposed to be bad.
KATE: Whew. AMY: Lucky roll.
JERRY: Rosie Beestinger.
How can I help?
KATE: Okay so the situation is that Donaar is dangling a rope that K'thriss has yet to grab.
JERRY: Exactly. Kris-- RYAN: Yeah the ingrate.
RYAN: Got a rope right there for you.
KATE: Okay.
JERRY: You've-- I mean you've seen a lot in your 120 years.
KATE: I sure as hell have. JERRY: He is not present.
KATE: Hmm. JERRY: He is just-- sort of like a bottle.
JERRY: Just bobbing in this muck.
KATE: I see. Okay so he doesn't look like he's got a consciousness to him?
JERRY: Well he just looks like he's just not... like he's checked out.
KATE: Okay. JERRY: Like he's just completely on some other shit.
KATE: Can I reach down and just like slap him?
KATE: Try to-- RYAN: Don't reach in.
KRIS: If you can reach down to slap me why don't you yank me out?
KATE: Okay-- JERRY: Please do that.
KATE: I'll stick my quarterstaff there and try to like bonk some sense into him gently.
JERRY: Okay as you reach over the edge with the staff...
I need a... wisdom... ability...
KATE: Yeah I got some wisdom. RYAN: Don't go crazy.
KATE: I got some wisdom. KRIS: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
KATE: I got that. I got that. RYAN: Wisen up.
KATE: That's an 11. JERRY: 11?
KATE: Yeah. &gt;&gt; AMY: Aww... JERRY: K. That's enough.
RYAN: Oh... JERRY: That's enough. That's enough.
KATE: Whew! Skating right over-- AMY: Well she lived a good life.
JERRY: You know, it's the crevice. Right? It's the crevice.
KATE: I see. JERRY: You're exposed to the whole thing is a different story.
JERRY: So rope is hanging out...
there's a bo staff...
This is a very important decision for you K'thriss Drow'b.
KRIS: (grunts) JERRY: Whose aid will you accept?
RYAN: It's redundant. KATE: Oh I'm not trying to help.
JERRY: Oh!
RYAN: Oh you're just trying to hit him in the face.
KRIS: She's trying to like prod me. JERRY: Oh you're trying to poke him?
KATE: Yeah I just want to like wake him up a little bit.
KATE: I want to make sure that like-- you know just slap some sense.
JERRY: So you just give him a tap on the head?
RYAN: Just don't let him know who's boss.
AMY: Like a kid poking a dead body by the sea.
KATE: Yeah. So I'm fascinated by this.
So I'm like, huh! (laughs)
JERRY: As though from a great distance...
from you-- in your perception...
you just see this rod, just coming at you.
And it's like-- have you ever seen the movie Antichrist?
KRIS: Probably. JERRY: Like the initial shower scene?
KRIS: Yes. KATE: Missed that one.
JERRY: It's like that.
JERRY: Like this rod is coming down forever. RYAN: I don't get that reference.
JERRY: And then it comes into contract with your forehead.
AMY: Oh. JERRY: And then it nudges you back.
KRIS: (laughs) JERRY: And then...
JERRY: when it pulls back away...
Now you're in real time again.
KRIS: Oh okay.
KRIS: (sound of surprise) Whoa!
JERRY: So you're just slipping and bobbing in this muck.
Right above your head is a-- like would play with a cat, I assume... you're dangling a rope.
KATE: Do I see any difference after my...? RYAN: Just smacking you in the face with it.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. He's blinking. KATE: Okay.
KATE: Nice. KRIS: We're back.
KATE: We're back. JERRY: He's remembered how to blink.
KATE: Okay. Excellent.
KRIS: Okay. On to me. JERRY: Yeah, yeah.
JERRY: It's on to you, K'thriss Drow'b.
KRIS: I swim back to that mouth cave--
(laughter) KRIS: so I can get some more of those secrets.
(laughter) JERRY: Some more of that juice!
KRIS: Just get this rope out of here. JERRY: You can if you want.
KRIS: No I just... pull you down. RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: This is Dungeons &amp; Dragons.
AMY: Join me! JERRY: If that's how you want to do it,
JERRY: that's a legitimate thing you can do. KATE: Is that K'thriss' thing?
KRIS: If this was my--
AMY: If we were all playing abysmal characters. KATE: If it was your Big Boy.
KRIS: If it was my guy I would have gone for it. But not this time.
KRIS: Um... Yeah I'm going to take a hold of this rope. JERRY: Yeah, yeah. Get a hold of it.
JERRY: He's massive!
JERRY: And strong. If you-- KRIS: Yeah. He seems like it.
JERRY: get a hold of this rope, we're not talking about rolls and checks.
We're talking about you coming up out of this fucking shit.
RYAN: Saving throw because I'm going to pull you so hard you're going to fly in the air.
KRIS: Let's get it done.
JERRY: You're going to take damage. KRIS: I'm going to do that.
KATE: Let's get the hell out of here. JERRY: Yeah he wraps his...
JERRY: he wraps his...
RYAN: Little noodle arms around it. JERRY: Yeah exactly.
KRIS: Like I'm not big.
JERRY: Yeah exact-- No this... It's... KRIS: I'm still an elf. Of sorts.
JERRY: It's... irrelevant.
Like he has an irrelevant weight to you.
KRIS: In fact the only you pull on the rope is to get the rope back.
RYAN: Yeah. An eagle can carry you. They're not that big.
(laughter) JERRY: You just drag him through.
AMY: That's a good rope! It was my grandmother's rope.
JERRY: Just like with one hand.
It's just like pull him up and you're aleady done. You're already done with this shit.
RYAN: I say, everyone, watch this! (grunts)
And then I say...
Look at how strong I am, everyone. I'm so great.
(laughter)
KRIS: And I come tumbling out of there. RYAN: And I say, right?
KRIS: Ye-- RYAN: And you take too long and I dip you back in again.
(laughter) RYAN: And I take you back out and I say...
RYAN: I'm the best, right? KRIS: I think you can get--
RYAN: Too late. Sorry, back down again.
KRIS: Any-- any kind of-- RYAN: And I wait and I say--
RYAN: Who's the strongest and the best?
KRIS: This... boy-- RYAN: Too long! Back down!
RYAN: We'll do it one more time.
RYAN: Who's the strongest and the best? KRIS: (strained yelling) Donaar!
RYAN: Ah ah that's better!
(laughter) JERRY: Good stuff. Just over!
KRIS: I was going to say, any confession you could get out of me at that point.
Like you put-- Who's the best?
You! Anybody! Yes. Not me! Whatever you want me to say!
JERRY: Any non-me entity!
KRIS: Is it me? Do you want me to be it? I'll say yes-- RYAN: No!
RYAN: It's me! I'm the best! KRIS: It's you. You for sure!
JERRY: So you have dragged him out.
Just flopped him down. I mean like a...
like when you keep all the fish just sort of on that chain and then you just like-- (grunt).
You're done with that. Now you're on to your next shit.
JERRY: K'thriss is out. Walnut. RYAN: And I take a nap.
JERRY: We are back at the top. AMY: Sure.
JERRY: But there is something about that...
AMY: That portal. RYAN: Mary.
JERRY: that does not-- There's something about where Kris was drawn up out of...
AMY: Mmm.
JERRY: You can see it creeping over the edge...
AMY: Mm-mmm! KRIS: Oh...
JERRY: and moving in.
But your situation right now is that this is creeping up.
And you can try to find some way...
to get this configuration back together so that you can get the fuck out of here.
AMY: Yeah... Okay so we need to get to the portal.
AMY: Where's the-- is this like... JERRY: It's job one.
AMY: Job one. Right.
How far is the next thing? Jumpable?
JERRY: Well these are all like slivers.
They all sort of erupt out from the vanishing point in the middle.
AMY: I'm trying to get this-- JERRY: So you can--
JERRY: Imagine there's all sort of like...
pie, like pizza wedges.
JERRY: That's sort of joined at the point. AMY: Oh I'm imagining it.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. KRIS: Yeah.
KATE: And it would be very illogical for us to run there.
JERRY: Well you can run there, but once you got there-- you can run there and get a better look at it...
Once you got there, there still needs to be something to arrange these slices that are sort of bobbing in this fluid.
KATE: Okay.
JERRY: But yeah, getting up there and investigating it is a great plan.
AMY: Okay great. Well one, I...
Walnut just whisper a little prayer for that eagle that got sucked into the thing.
KATE: Moment of silence?
AMY: Yeah just a moment of silence-- (laughs)
JERRY: One moment. One moment please.
AMY: And then-- KRIS: I'm still screaming by the way.
(laughter)
AMY: I still respectfully bow my head, then I just look at you kind of angrily.
Okay so then I want to look at the-- I mean I want to start moving towards the portal.
And I want to get as close as I can in my-- You know my speed is only 35.
JERRY: Yeah absolutely. I mean it's not far.
AMY: It's not far? Okay.
JERRY: Because space is not working. AMY: Because of the way that it is. Right, right, right.
JERRY: It is not-- The green light is not on this device.
You are walking out sort of on these long, sharpening pontoons toward this.
And then near the-- obviously near the end it's almost like pick-up sticks.
It's just like this ring of sharp points that are just offset a little bit.
AMY: Okay.
Would uh...
AMY: I'm so scared to touch them. JERRY: Yeah. That's reasonable.
JERRY: Impossibly sharp teeth of the universe.
AMY: Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. JERRY: Maybe. I don't know.
AMY: Can I do a perception check to see if there'd be a place that I could feel like I could nudge one with something?
JERRY: Yeah absolutely.
AMY: All right. Cool. I have good perception so let's give it a shot.
17?
JERRY: Oh yeah! Absolutely.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. You think that-- I mean...
It's strange, but these shards are physical.
AMY: Okay. JERRY: They could be bound together,
AMY: Okay. JERRY: the cracks could be sealed, I mean--
JERRY: you have a bunch of ways to approach this-- AMY: Okay great.
JERRY: as a physical problem.
AMY: Okay.
So then I look back to the rest of you guys and I go,
Uh... Let's get the hell out of here!
Help me put this thing--
(laughing) Help me put this shit together.
(laughter)
RYAN: Put the world back together? AMY: Yeah. Please.
JERRY: Yeah. Walnut does not sound a hundred percent okay.
KATE: Hmm...
AMY: Suffered another terrifying animal loss today.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. Everyday is harder than the last.
Do you want to make some attempt to resolve this?
AMY: Yeah can I try and lash it together with this goopy rope I got?
JERRY: Yeah! AMY: Cool.
AMY: What do I do? RYAN: I give you the rope back.
AMY: Yeah. RYAN: Here you go.
AMY: Literally my grandmother's rope.
(shudders)
RYAN: Came in very handy.
RYAN: We got our vagrant back. AMY: Smoothing down some of the fibers.
KRIS: Frayed edge? You're like, there you go.
KATE: I'm sorry, meemaw.
AMY: I'm sorry, meemaw. (kissing sound)
Yeah can I try lashing it together. Can I like roll for it?
Would that be something?
JERRY: Yeah I would say survival. AMY: Survival?
JERRY: Yeah. AMY: Great. Something I'm proficient in!
JERRY: Well it's a net sort of knot continuum.
AMY: Uh... nope! That's all I got. Seven.
JERRY: All right. So you're looping it around these edges.
And then you make the knot that you remember going this way.
It's like forgetting how to tie a tie, type thing.
AMY: Yeah and then it just comes apart. JERRY: Ordinarily you would look at YouTube.
JERRY: Right? AMY: Sure.
JERRY: But it hasn't been invented.
JERRY: So as you cinch it-- RYAN: That's how they get you.
JERRY: It shreds and splits on the teeth of these--
AMY: No!
JERRY: Just the front part. It's okay.
AMY: Okay. Done with Walnut's turn. JERRY: Donaar Blit'zen.
RYAN: Uh... god.
JERRY: So there's different situations. You can try to cinch it up back here.
Try to cinch it up front.
RYAN: What does cinching it up entail?
JERRY: Basically we have physical objects-- RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: that have to be shifted and/or moved. RYAN: Well I'm big and strong.
AMY: Do you have glue?
RYAN: Do I have glue? No.
KATE: I have a bag of sand. RYAN: I have a toothbrush.
AMY: Can I summon animals to make... glue? (laughs)
JERRY: Just summoning horses? KATE: (laughing) Oh my god.
(laughter)
KRIS: Into the fisher!
KATE: You know it has only been like one day and you've killed a lot of animals.
JERRY/RYAN: Yeah.
AMY: There have been zero animals that have died except that.
JERRY: You are animal killer number one. RYAN: No. I think I killed every single squirrel--
RYAN: that was on the wizard. AMY: Oh yeah they did turn into meat.
KATE: You did kill a lot of squirrels. AMY: That was a squirrel smoothie.
RYAN: Yeah. AMY: All right nevermind.
JERRY: It was a pudding.
Oh yeah, yeah. You can approach this, you know as you would a physical problem. If you want.
RYAN: So is the rope slightly damaged or--
AMY: It's only slightly damaged.
JERRY: Yes. AMY: There's 50 feet of it to fuck up.
JERRY: Yeah there's tons.
RYAN: These are floating like pontoons.
It's like...
Well you need an anchor point right?
So like go here. Give the rope to Rosie.
RYAN: Jump to the next one since you're the most agile. AMY: Oh it's like getting drunk on kayaks with friends.
RYAN: And then yeah. And then try to pull them together.
That's my suggestion.
JERRY: This is a solid plan. Do you want to start initiating that?
RYAN: Yeah. I say, there you go. KATE: I'm with you.
KATE: Huh!
JERRY: All right. So on your turn, you enunciate this.
RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: This pontoon scenario.
RYAN: You're going to have to adhere it to something over there, because otherwise I'll just yoink you right off.
KATE: I'll adhere it to this guy. So it's going to be fine.
JERRY: So Donaar you have tossed the rope to Rosie whose turn it is next.
KATE: I'm going to jam my quarterstaff into the ground.
Into the soft earth of the forest floor?
KATE: That I'm standing on? JERRY: Into the loam?
KATE: Yep. The loam. Right in there.
And I'm going to use that as the anchor and grip onto it.
And then go, giddy up cowboy.
JERRY: K. So you begin to tug that closer.
RYAN: Mm-hmm. JERRY: The quarterstaff holds.
JERRY: You're able to draw these together.
You're a little agitated because the seam isn't exactly right.
(laughter) RYAN: Yeah. That would bug me.
(laughter)
JERRY: It might-- We'll see.
We'll see if it's okay when your turn comes back around.
Right now, it's not okay.
Right now it's a little wrong.
It's like if the fork is a little bit off from the knife.
JERRY: You don't like it. Right? RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: That's not how you were raised.
JERRY: K'thriss Drow'b.
KRIS: The universe might not like it either. I don't know.
JERRY: Exactly so... Rosie. RYAN: Me first.
JERRY: Rosie, you held this as the anchor. Do you toss the other end...
JERRY: Do you toss the next part of this link to K'thriss Drow'b? KATE: I believe I will.
KRIS: Okay.
I see what we're doing now and through my sobs,
because I'm starting to stop screaming now, I go,
(sobbing) It's like a tugboat. Toot toot!
(laughter) KRIS: And then I grab that rope.
And what's on my shard?
What's on your shard?
Dot com.
JERRY: What's on your shard? KRIS: Yeah. What can I anchor it to? Let me see here.
KRIS: Because I'm assuming if we do them all like that...
JERRY: Yeah exactly. Come up with... AMY: A rock?
KRIS: Yeah if there's a rock or a tree stump or anything like that. JERRY: Come up with a plan?
KRIS: Yeah then I want to lash it to that.
Would we have enough to send it back over there?
So with one pull, we're just knitting the whole nest.
JERRY: You may have to make something. You may have to...
KRIS: Hmm... Let me see here. JERRY: use something.
AMY: Now would have been a really good time for something that didn't work so well last time, but we didn't rest.
(whispering) It's Thornwhip.
(laughter) JERRY: That is a premium whip experience.
RYAN: Yeah. KATE: Why don't you just hug your island?
RYAN: Look nothing's bads happening right now.
RYAN: We're just floating. Let's all just take quick naps. KRIS: What if I just float in the water? Down the stuff?
AMY: Everything is creeping.
KRIS: Uh no. Let's see here.
AMY: Let's take a quick nap in the abyss. KRIS: Aww shoot.
RYAN: Quick nap. KRIS: That's not the thing I was thinking of.
KRIS: I thought...
Phantasmal Force is not an actual object.
I cannot create a thing.
JERRY: Yeah. KRIS: Can you tell me...
JERRY: Yeah.
KRIS: Would Mending have any effect?
KATE: Whoa... RYAN: You're forever trying to Mend.
KRIS: I got to Mend.
AMY: Oh my god! KRIS: It only works on objects of...
KRIS: like one foot-- Where the rift is a foot.
Like a tear or what have you.
But would it work on these facets?
Could I do it at the center point?
JERRY: Interesting... RYAN: Going to Mend reality?
KRIS: Yeah. I might I have to do it six times if that's how many shards we have.
KATE: I think it's officially rad.
JERRY: I-- Yeah well it's definitely-- KRIS: Because we're talking about math now.
If I can Mend those points, the rest of it would line up.
AMY: A level three character using Mend to fix the fabric of reality.
JERRY: Yeah. Welcome to my campaign.
AMY: This is what we like to call homebrew-- (laughs)
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, yeah. (laughter)
JERRY: I like it. AMY: But it's good!
JERRY: I think there's something interesting there. KATE: Don't question it!
KRIS: Okay. RYAN: Yeah. Stop trying to talk him out of it.
AMY: Sorry! RYAN: It's a solution.
KRIS: Ah let's see.
RYAN: All I got is strength and rope!
JERRY: Yeah exactly. I am going to demand... AMY: My rope.
JERRY: I am going to demand...
an intelligence ability--
KRIS: That's permissible.
JERRY: You think you can use Mending to sew up some of the physical aspects of these points.
KRIS: Right. JERRY: But...
JERRY: getting it properly dialled in is going to require an intelligence check from you.
So what I'm looking for is that dice...
plus your intelligence number that you see in the upper left hand corner.
KRIS: I'm going to love to give it to you.
Oh I'm going to take an advantage by the way.
KATE: Oh. Don't know if you need it. KRIS: Ah... ah...
KRIS: I don't know if I need it either but I did say I would take it.
KATE: Okay.
KRIS: Yeah so this is going to be an 18. JERRY: Okay.
JERRY: Give me-- roll the other one. KRIS: Let's check it out.
KRIS: No, it didn't get better. But 18 is pretty good I feel like.
JERRY: So you can see up close it's almost like a...
it's like a palette or a color wheel.
You can sort of see like slight differences in the color of these points.
And you're trying-- use the Mending spell to sort of attach this bit of bark...
you know, to the tree that exists in this.
It's like making a really sophisticated puzzle.
KRIS: Right. JERRY: Basically.
And you're able to get a couple of these pieces, you feel like, in a solid place.
But you don't think you'd be able to pass through this door yet.
Or you don't know what the result would be.
KRIS: I see, I see.
Uh... shoo-- let's see here.
I don't know what else I got.
JERRY: That's your turn. KRIS: That's my turn! I didn't get it.
JERRY: Walnut. &gt;&gt; RYAN Oh! AMY: Um... okay how many--
JERRY: I saw you shaking some papers. Do you have a good plan?
AMY: How many shards do we have that are still separated? A bunch?
JERRY: Right now he has attached-- you think two or three of them.
And so we have another three over here that we can try to--
JERRY: squish together. AMY: Incredible.
AMY: I turn into a giant spider!
Using wildshape.
JERRY: (shouting) Are you for fucking real?
AMY: An invariable rope machine. (laughs)
KRIS: Yes! KATE: It's just ropes for days!
KATE: It's all you are! JERRY: They have a rope gland!
AMY: I have a special sac just for ropes.
JERRY: Yeah. &gt;&gt; RYAN: It's in the butt. AMY: And I would like to-- Yeah.
AMY: I would like to make some of my good, good butt rope.
RYAN: That's how spiders work. KRIS: It's near the butt.
KRIS: It's not in the butt. AMY: All right.
AMY: Sorry we have a spider expert here. RYAN: All right Doctor "Doo-litter."
JERRY: What you going to do with that rope?
AMY: Um what am I going to do with all that rope?
So I can do...
I have a web attack so I can just shoot one of these things.
KATE: Your sticky icky.
AMY: You know, use my little... my little mandibles.
JERRY: Your little pedipalps.
AMY: My pedipalps. Sorry you know all about-- JERRY: They don't bite it!
AMY: Right, right.
JERRY: You know what I mean? KATE: Just bite it!
AMY: Then I want to put it-- RYAN: Use your haunches.
AMY: Yeah. JERRY: Here...
RYAN: Put your haunches to work! AMY: Do you want me to roll--
AMY: to see if I get these spots or something?
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. I would love that.
JERRY: I want a wisdom check from you.
AMY: You want a wisdom check from me?
JERRY: I want a wisdom check. AMY: I'm very wizzy.
KATE: (laughing) Very good haunch. AMY: Ooh!
AMY: 21.
KATE: Ooh ho ho. RYAN: Ooh.
JERRY: So you see it.
It's this circular pattern...
basically sort of splayed out almost like a floral icon.
AMY: Whoa. JERRY: Right?
KRIS: (whispering) Or its internal web! JERRY: No, no, no.
JERRY: And that's the thing. Your awareness as a spider, you know where the problems are.
But you know where each...
AMY: I can see the Matrix?
JERRY: Exactly. Where each of these seams, you just know where it's wrong.
And then she becomes bulbous for real!
AMY: I'm hacking the web. JERRY: Yeah exactly.
JERRY: And she just skitters-- KATE: Dark web.
JERRY: like effortlessly skitters around... RYAN: I get all these references.
JERRY: And even up and around this partitioning. This shattered partition.
And sews it all together.
And then with a final tug you see everything sort of slide together.
You can see thin seams...
But the portal is there and ready to go.
AMY: And unfortunately you still see a giant spider.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, yeah. KATE: How big are you?
AMY: Giant spider. It's the size class large.
JERRY: It's not a small spider. RYAN: No.
KATE: I want to ride her.
RYAN: It's a venti. JERRY: Spider rider?
KATE: Yeah. JERRY: Is it just for the pun?
KATE: No! I would-- No. KRIS: This is amazing!
AMY: If it was Rosie, yeah Walnut would allow this.
KATE: Nice. Okay.
AMY: As I duck down. KATE: I jump on.
KATE: I'm riding a spider.
KATE: Crossed it off my bucket list. AMY: Hmm.
KATE: Thank you. AMY: That's fine.
AMY: Remain in spider form.
JERRY: I love it.
RYAN: All right.
KRIS: I'm so pleased.
RYAN: Yeah. AMY: Great.
JERRY: You pass through now-- This portal is not a hundred percent designed for spiders...
JERRY: But it's fine. AMY: Okay.
JERRY: You're able to make yourself portal compatible.
AMY: Oh like I do.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. AMY: Where I get all...
KATE: Ew. JERRY: It's like the gull wing door.
JERRY: It's like right here. So legs are higher.
Yeah going to high-knee it through the crack.
AMY: Mm-hmm. KRIS: So you're kind of hugged in tight on the thorax--
KRIS: by these barbed legs... KATE: And I deeply believe this is a nasty thing that I'm doing.
JERRY: Gaff thorax. KATE: Get that thorax.
JERRY: You got a grip on it.
KATE: Yeah. Scaly.
RYAN: The most necessary thing to have done.
JERRY: You cast--
KATE: Yeah like teabagging your friend? Is that-- RYAN: (chefs kissing sound)
RYAN: That was to establish, you know, the pecking order. JERRY: No, teabagging them...
JERRY: in an unknowable... ancient evil. KRIS: Right.
JERRY: Probably never happened in a campaign before.
KRIS: No. Needless. JERRY: That's the kind of material we deliver...
RYAN: I got to prove I'm strong. KATE: Do that in Call of Duty all the time.
JERRY: So you push through. RYAN: When we're voting on leader.
JERRY: Donaar. Do you pass through this arch?
RYAN: Well yeah if everyone else already has.
Last. Hesitantly.
Because of doorways and whatnot.
JERRY: Yeah, K'thriss… (laughter)
JERRY: As you pass through it you sort of wonder idly...
what those hairline fractures in the portal might result in.
KRIS: Hmm. AMY: Ooh.
JERRY: And as you-- KATE: Oops. &gt;&gt; AMY: Cheese wire.
JERRY: As you pass through...
RYAN: Party wipe.
JERRY: Uh party wipe.
(laughter)
As you pass through...
you emerge in a place that is...
profoundly abstract.
So you move from different versions of the same space...
into a shattered version of a natural space.
This does not have an analog with space.
The realm that you have entered...
is defined primarily by a gray mist.
You, Rosie, and you, Walnut,
are sort of hugging--
You have your legs around the edge of a staircase...
that is slowly spinning in place.
RYAN: This... AMY: (grunts of exertion)
KRIS: It's Hogwarts. AMY: Yeah Hogwarts.
AMY: Are you telling me Jim Darkmagic passed this--
AMY: AI initiation test? KATE: No way.
AMY: (laughs) &gt;&gt; RYAN: Yeah. JERRY: Hogwarts...
JERRY: Hogwarts is an incredible visual cue.
That's exactly what we're talking about. Specifically the Gryffindor...
RYAN: Okay.
JERRY: scenario right? AMY: Staircase.
RYAN: I get this reference.
JERRY: But when each of you emerge...
you are on your own versions of these...
geometric objects. These staircases. That are in different places.
So it's vitally important that from here on...
that I know when your character is speaking and when you are speaking.
AMY: Ooh okay. KATE: Sí.
RYAN: So... this is... KRIS: Yuck.
RYAN: Up is up and down is down, though right? This isn't like M.C. Escher...
JERRY: As near as you can tell there is an up based on how you're standing on this.
No one-- If you look around you can see your fellows,
but they are not coming out of the fucking side area, if you know what I mean.
RYAN: All right.
RYAN: It's not like I'm standing here and you're standing there.
KRIS: I'm standing there yeah.
RYAN: Boo bip bip bip. JERRY: Exactly.
JERRY: But this swing does require...
some concentration to maintain your position on it.
Obviously you got-- you are just gripped around it.
That abdomen is just laying down on the top of this thing.
KATE: Kate speaking. Not Rosie.
How close do our staircases swing from each other?
JERRY: They do not intersect each other's arcs.
KATE: Okay. KRIS: Hmm.
JERRY: At all. KATE: So we're orbiting very different--
KATE: planets? JERRY: Yeah exactly. And there are other shapes...
JERRY: There are other like primitive shapes that exist in this space...
KATE: Such as? JERRY: as well. Spheres...
KATE: I like that. JERRY: Pyramid shapes.
KATE: Okay.
JERRY: Dodecahedrons. &gt;&gt; KATE: Ooh. KRIS: Toroids?
KATE: Wait. Do they have numbers?
JERRY: No. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Parallelograms? (laughter)
(laughter)
AMY: Ah! We're in the table. No. JERRY: No, no.
RYAN: Yeah, yeah, yeah. Now you're in the deep web!
(laughter)
KRIS: How are we like-- KATE: Whose turn is it?
AMY: It's Donaar's turn. KRIS: Oh okay.
RYAN: Is it?
AMY: Yeah I did all-- I mean-- KRIS: Yeah. She's a spider.
JERRY: Yeah. Walnut went. AMY: I did all my web stuff.
KATE: Yeah she's spider.
RYAN: So wait we're all on little spinny stairwells.
RYAN: This is Ryan talking. JERRY: Revolving. Right exactly.
RYAN: Independently. JERRY: Mm-hmm.
JERRY: Their arcs don't converge.
RYAN: Wait. How far apart are these? Just roughly?
JERRY: Roughly probably...
JERRY: 45 feet? RYAN: Okay.
RYAN: So we went through this portal and all popped up in our own little stairwells.
AMY/KATE: Mmm.
KRIS: Do they look like they-- Oh sorry. You go ahead.
KRIS: It's your turn now. RYAN: No. I guess I'll be like...
Hey guys!
Everyone okay? Going to the top of my stairs!
KRIS: So you speak. JERRY: Yeah, yeah.
KATE: So you speak. RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: So you say, "Hey guys. Going to the top of my stairs."
And there is an image at the end of your staircase...
of you walking toward the top of the stairs.
RYAN: Hmm.
KRIS: (laughs)
RYAN: Hmm. JERRY: What are you delighted, Kris?
KRIS: Yes! RYAN: Yeah.
(laughter)
RYAN: Does everyone see that? Or do I just see that? JERRY: Yeah. No, you see it like it's a real thing.
RYAN: Okay.
(laughing) Looks I'm going to do that!
And then I do it?
KATE: Okay. Great.
JERRY: So you walk up-- you follow this other version of yourself to the top of these stairs.
RYAN: Yeah. JERRY: And then you wait.
JERRY: The farther you walk up the stairs,
the more stairs there seem to be at the top,
and the fewer there are behind you.
RYAN: Hmm. KRIS: Bleh.
RYAN: I don't want to get out of eyesight of anyone.
JERRY: That's a good plan. RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: That's a good plan in a place that's completely beyond space and time.
RYAN: Yeah. &gt;&gt; KATE: I'm going to whisper-- JERRY: Rosie.
KATE: Rosie-- I'm Rosie.
JERRY: I'm Rosie!
KATE: I'm-- (laughs)
KRIS: I am Rosie. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Wait, I'm Rosie. KATE: But I'm the one that wrote the essay.
KATE: I'm Rosie!
Walnut, do you think we should just go back through the portal? This place sucks.
JERRY: When she says the word "portal,"
the top of your staircase flattens out, smooths out...
and a portal appears.
RYAN: Oh. KATE: Tight.
KATE: (whispering) It's Scribblenauts.
RYAN: Oh...
JERRY: Hold on let me take a moment to wink at the camera.
(laughter) RYAN: Cheeseburger.
KATE: It's not your turn. AMY: This is Amy talking,
Say "more equity!" (laughs)
(laughter)
JERRY: Better contracts! KRIS: Yeah.
KATE: Graduation from internship. RYAN: Yeah.
(laughter)
JERRY: So it's there. Previously these portals have had a dark cast. A gray cast.
This is a pearlescent white portal.
RYAN: Ooh. AMY: Well on my turn maybe I can do something about it.
JERRY: Yep. K'thriss Drow'b.
How will you enjoy your whirling staircase?
KRIS: I don't know. This is a refreshing respite from what I was just at.
AMY: Say "one true god" and see what happens.
KRIS: Oh uh... AMY: I'm joking!
KRIS: Back at the mouth!
JERRY: (gargling noises)
(laughter)
No, it just-- (gargling noises)
No, no. It goes down-- (gargling noises)
And when it goes up there's no more K'thriss.
KRIS: Yeah, but it'll go-- (slurping sound). Licks its chops.
JERRY: (gargling sound).
KRIS: I did see that what just happened.
JERRY: Yeah. KRIS: But I didn't hear it apparently.
KATE: No, I whispered. KRIS: Because you whispered,
KRIS: so I'm not sure how the portal showed up.
But I do say, I'm not sure how they got a portal!
No, I don't do that.
KRIS: Um... JERRY: Do you say the word "portal"?
KRIS: No, I don't actually said. JERRY: Oh.
KRIS: That's me metagaming. But it doesn't work.
I'm curious though, do the stairs match up at all?
JERRY: Mm-mmm. KRIS: They don't look like they match? Okay.
JERRY: No, no. They aren't a part of a single architecture or anything like that.
Theirs is sort of marble in nature.
JERRY: Yours is rustic woods.
KRIS: Oh! So completely different. I see.
Um... Jeez!
Fascinating.
Um...
JERRY: Listen, the main thing I need to ask--
the main thing I need to make sure is that
I know when K'thriss Drow'b is speaking and when Kris Straub is.
KRIS: Exactly. Right, no I will proceed his words.
Um... let me...
I want to just do like an insight check and see if I get a sense of like...
JERRY: Yeah absolutely. KRIS: just the nature of the stairs.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah.
Insight-- This would be-- I would say this going to be more on the arcana.
KRIS: Oh, okay. That's fair.
KATE: You do have Neuveunomicon.
KRIS: I do...
RYAN: Mmm. KATE: If there's a--
KATE: Magic-8 Ball like question. JERRY: Yeah you could. &gt;&gt; AMY: Yeah!
KRIS: Oh it is-- and I get a single one, right?
JERRY: Yeah exactly. It'll be like-- I can give you-- basically a mystical Magic-8 Ball.
This is a good thing or a bad thing.
Weal or woe, I think is the usual way it's phrased.
KRIS: Ugh.
Nothing that would assist me.
KRIS: Because I'm like-- JERRY: Don't worry. You'll have plenty of opportunities to use it.
KRIS: Yeah let me hang on to it then.
That one's too important. So let's do again arcana.
Ugh. That one is going to be a ten.
JERRY: Ten. KRIS: Yeah.
JERRY: This place is shapeless.
It has ephemeral things that appear and then leave.
But you saw with Donaar. Wherever he goes on this it just sort of goes with him and follows.
You want to think about it for a little bit?
KRIS: Yeah let me-- JERRY: You want to sit there and think about what you did.
KRIS: Let me... JERRY: Donaar Blit'zen.
AMY: Wrong. JERRY: Oh yeah. Walnut.
AMY: This will not be Walnut speaking at all because Walnut cannot speak as a spider, so...
JERRY: Yeah! AMY: Getting you out of that.
AMY: I would-- seeing the portal...
Can I look at...
Hmm.
Can I try and shoot a web onto K'thriss?
And like get him?
KRIS: Oh yeah. JERRY: What's the range on your web?
AMY: (whispering) I don't know.
KRIS: As much as you want. AMY: So I guess I can't do it. I don't have that written down.
KRIS: It's a good thought though. Let me see what I could have done. AMY: Yeah...
AMY: Shoot. Okay.
RYAN: I still have the rope. I have your rope.
AMY: Mm-hmm.
So I mean we could go through the portal but it seems like...
I wouldn't want to go through the portal with everybody.
I don't want to turn out of the spider because it seems very helpful.
KATE: I think Rosie has caughten on to what's going on here. So you can--
JERRY: Yeah you can broadcast. KATE: show what you want.
KATE: Yeah. Can I just like out-of-turn broadcast?
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. If you want to you can say something. KATE: Okay.
KATE: It's Scribblenauts!
(laughter)
KRIS: (whispering) What?
KATE: Say whatever you need!
AMY: Oh okay. KATE: To get out of here!
AMY: So then I'm going to turn into Walnut.
KATE: Yeah you probably need to turn into Walnut.
RYAN: Still on her back.
(laughter) JERRY: Yeah! &gt;&gt; RYAN: Still--
KATE: It's no problem! JERRY: On all fours.
KATE: I weigh 29 pounds. KRIS: Yeah that's true. Yeah.
AMY: Okay. No more spider.
JERRY: Yeah.
AMY: I'm now the dashing devil-may-care druid that you all love.
And I say...
We need bridges to connect all these stairs.
KRIS: Hmm. JERRY: Okay.
JERRY: As you say, "We need bridges to connect all these stairs," the staircases stop.
In some configuration.
And then you see stairways joining from tops to bottoms, and bottoms to tops.
But the space is rapidly filling with a geometric pattern of stairways.
AMY: Okay. KRIS: I see.
KATE: Oops. KRIS: It's like the end of Interstellar.
AMY: Whoops!
AMY: Okay. JERRY: It's Interstellar Scribblenauts.
KATE: (laughs)
KRIS: (dinging noises) AMY: Donaar?
RYAN: Is it me?
RYAN: I say... JERRY: There's a clear path, yeah.
RYAN: How'd you get a portal?
(laughter)
And I look around.
JERRY: You hear a sound-- almost like a sound of a xylophone.
It's got a resonant ping.
And then their portal sort of flashes inside the middle of it.
RYAN/KATE/KRIS: Hmm.
KRIS: Oh my god.
KATE: Got that hit marker.
RYAN: Yeah.
So when these bridges are being built,
JERRY: Yeah they're still clacking together. Different materials--
RYAN: Are they built or are they still-- JERRY: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
JERRY: Yeah it's fast, but like I say, the place is rapidly filling up with them.
RYAN: Okay.
Cool it with the bridges!
JERRY: It's trying to join every vertex basically. KATE: Don't say "bridge."
KRIS: Right yeah.
AMY: (whispering) Run. RYAN: What's the opposite of a bridge?
RYAN: I just run over to their-- towards the portal.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. You just go through it past them?
RYAN: No, no. I don't go through the portal.
I just huddle up.
KRIS: I want to go through that portal. JERRY: The team-- All right.
RYAN: I'm the last to go through all doors.
JERRY: Rosie Beestinger.
KATE: Is K'thriss set up to get to us?
JERRY: Yeah there is a thicket of stairways sort of growing together.
but there is still a path for him to get through.
KATE: Okay. I'm going to say...
Cup of tea. Just to try it.
Cup of tea.
JERRY: It appears. But about a foot higher than you'd like.
KATE: Yeah.
JERRY: And then falls but not too fast.
KATE: Okay. I'm very agile, grab it.
JERRY: Yeah. Oh yeah you just--
KATE: (slurping sound)
I'm very happy.
AMY: That's it? KATE: That's it.
AMY: Oh that's your whole action. That's really good. JERRY: K'thriss Drow'b.
KRIS: Amazing. All right. If there is a path for me, then I would like to join these fellows.
JERRY: Yep, yep. As you are moving across this path--
I mean, the space behind you is rapidly filling up...
KRIS: With stairs. JERRY: with additional stairs.
JERRY: Of every conceivable manufacture.
KRIS: (whispering) Stairworld. RYAN: Yeah.
KRIS: This could be valuable. Hang out here and just farm them.
(laughter)
JERRY: We defeat elite stairs.
KRIS: (laughing) Yeah.
JERRY: That's the key.
KRIS: Do I-- So yeah--
As I approach them, like I have enough space to get to them before my stairs die out.
JERRY: Yes. Absolutely. KRIS: Okay.
KRIS: So I've done that...
Are we all now at this--
JERRY: You stand before a glowing portal.
As so many Dungeons &amp; Dragons parties before you have.
KRIS: Yuck. I hate these portals.
AMY: I choose death! No.
(laughter) JERRY: I just jump off. No!
(laughter) KRIS: Yeah. Me dying.
JERRY: But you'd like fall two feet. Because there'd be a set of stairs there.
AMY: Yeah, yeah.
KRIS: Uh... oh man.
I kind of just want to go through.
KATE: Go through it. Pop your head in. AMY: Go ahead.
KRIS: I feel like maybe we go through it, guys.
KATE: Don't be afraid.
KRIS: I give you each like a look like...
I'm just going to do it.
All right!
RYAN: This is Witch World, man.
JERRY: Yeah! RYAN: I say,
JERRY: Now you found a world-- RYAN: Gold pieces and health potions!
(laughter) RYAN: I say that out loud.
KRIS: No, thank you.
JERRY: It's like Vegas.
RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: Just glinting light-- like a school of goldfish. RYAN: And I'm like...
RYAN: Nice!
JERRY: Just clinking down, like gold rolling down these infinite staircases.
KRIS: Oh it's so noisy.
JERRY: Yeah. AMY: Cacophony.
JERRY: The sound is awful, but you hear breaking glass, you see drips running down.
AMY: Oh. KATE. Look what you did.
JERRY: The party has gathered before this portal.
What's next?
AMY: Go through! &gt;&gt; KRIS: Yeah. KATE: Go through the portal.
RYAN: I want to take-- I want to try to get some gold.
KATE: Oh before I go through the portal, I have a missive from Viari.
JERRY: Oh yeah? KATE: I have to say, Jim Darkmagic.
And hold him hostage until he...
KATE: agrees to our demands. AMY: (laughs)
AMY: (laughing) No. RYAN: Ah that's clever.
RYAN: You say, Jim Darkmagic? AMY: Well-- let's hear that out.
JERRY: And he materializes.
KATE: Let's see where this goes. RYAN: That's actually really funny.
KATE: Let's see where this goes.
KATE: All right. Rosie, I guess, I-- AMY: You're on my back.
KATE: I am on your back.
I remember Jim Darkmagic from the inn and for some reason I think like,
he'd probably know how to help us right now.
So I say, Jim Darkmagic, out loud.
JERRY: Jim Darkmagic? KATE: Yeah.
JERRY: Okay.
There is a sound like a slap on a bass drum.
RYAN: (laughs)
AMY: (rimshot sounds)
(laughter) KRIS: (bass guitar sounds) &gt;&gt; JERRY: Exactly.
JERRY: And a purple-garbed wizard...
is sort of descending through space.
And he says,
What the--?
And you see two parts of stairs...
grow together and liquify him.
(laughter)
RYAN: Ah...
KATE: Rosie says, whoops!
Yah!
(laughter)
KATE: To the portal! AMY: You jump through the portal.
JERRY: You keep fucking with my game, Pat Rothfuss.
You keep fucking with my game and--
AMY: I loved it. RYAN: He'll kill characters!
RYAN: He'll kill beloved main characters.
JERRY: I don't even care. KRIS: Was it a purple-robed wizard?
KRIS: Or was it a lithe rogue with red hair?
JERRY: (laughs) Sensual.
AMY: I want to jump through this portal and I got Rosie on my back.
JERRY: All right. Absolutely.
AMY: I take her through. KRIS: Me through also, please.
JERRY: You-- RYAN: I say, handful of gold.
JERRY: Yeah. RYAN: And I take it then I go.
JERRY: Yeah and it goes-- (sputtering sound)
RYAN: I just want to see what happens.
KRIS: Nice. Nice boy.
JERRY: As you walk through, Rosie and Walnut...
JERRY: You're holding on to each other physically? AMY: Mm-hmm.
JERRY: You do that. You both appear...
in a warm bed.
AMY: Together? JERRY: Together.
KRIS: Whoa. KATE: Finally.
RYAN: Slash fic.
JERRY: Listen. It's what the fans want.
AMY: Walnut's intimidated by her experience.
RYAN: Geriatric...
KATE: I'm a lot-- RYAN: action.
JERRY: Exactly.
AMY/RYAN: GeriActive.
RYAN: There's something there.
KRIS: We'll think about it. &gt;&gt; RYAN: We'll workshop it. AMY: I definitely...
AMY: heave a huge sigh of relief and then I look to Rosie and I go,
Are you all right?
KATE: Oh yeah. Never better. JERRY: There are...
on the bedside table there is a pot of tea and two envelopes.
AMY: K. Well...
I want to pour tea for Rosie--
I don't see these two clowns?
JERRY: No. KATE: Nice. &gt;&gt; AMY: Great!
AMY: Honestly... KATE: This is perfect.
KRIS: Saving the best for last.
RYAN: Yeah. AMY: That's what Walnut wanted all along.
(laughter) JERRY: It's a huge win.
50/50 split.
AMY: So I pour some tea for Rosie because she's an older woman who I obviously respect due to her years.
Pour her some tea,
make sure she's all propped up in bed okay,
give her the tea-- I'm still in bed the whole time with her.
JERRY: Oh yeah. You aren't leaving the bed. KATE: We're snuggling.
AMY: And then decide to read my-- open my envelope?
JERRY: Mm-hmm. Exactly. AMY: And then I pass her hers.
JERRY: Inside there is a document that says,
Walnut Dankgrass of the Enclave Pax Anima is a member in good standing. Acquisitions Incorporated.
AMY/KATE/KRIS: (gasps)
AMY: I did it! KATE: You did it, darling.
AMY: You see me talking,
(breathlessly) I'm in Acquisitions Inc.
(laughter) AMY: It's awesome!
(clapping) AMY/KATE: Yay!
JERRY: You have a similar one. It says,  Rosie Beestinger, member in good standing. Acquisitions Incorporated.
KATE: Yes...!
JERRY: That is it. You're in a-- it's a darkened room.
This is a room that's been prepared for sleep.
It's simple, but homey and comfortable.
KATE: Let's take a long ass rest.
AMY: Yes. KATE: Just a long one.
JERRY: The longest ass rest.
KATE: (gasps) No...!
AMY: What? KATE: Look at you, you little dork!
AMY: (laughing) This is to make it official.
JERRY: Oh you're putting the pin on?
RYAN: Aren't you a little worried about us? I mean--
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. So as a-- AMY: Ping!
KRIS: We're still inside that membrane. Let's discover...
RYAN: Yeah. We're back in the mouth.
KRIS: what's occurred. RYAN: And they're celebrating sleeping.
JERRY: So as you pass through...
you go through this--
I mean you're still pretty hurt, I mean you're--
KRIS: I'm not well. JERRY: You're not doing well.
KRIS: This whole time I've not been good, yeah. JERRY: Right?
JERRY: You emerge...
under the covers...
in a soft bed filled with dry straw.
JERRY: Straub. KRIS: Straub now.
AMY: Dry Straub. JERRY: K'thriss Straw'b.
KRIS: Straw'gob. AMY: I wet the bed.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. Yeah! I pee! I pee!
KRIS: As a bonus action.
JERRY: Your bedside table has an empty wineglass, and a bottle of dark wine, and an envelope.
KRIS: Oh I... KATE: Got the hard shit.
KRIS: I throw the sheets off.
Afraid to like-- I look-- I check the envelope to see if it's roiling with teeth.
(laughter) JERRY: No. &gt;&gt; KRIS: All right.
JERRY: There are so few teeth.
KRIS: (sighs)
RYAN: Like three.
JERRY: Like-- Max! Top!
KRIS: The usual number.
JERRY: Three writhing saw teeth.
JERRY: For an envelope. KRIS: Well I'm very careful with it.
RYAN: Way less than what you were dealing with. JERRY: Exactly.
AMY: Howler. KRIS: Yeah, distrustingly I open the envelope.
JERRY: K'thriss Drow'b.
Member in good standing. Acquisitions Incorporated.
KATE: Yes! &gt;&gt; KRIS: Whew. JERRY: 25% share.
KRIS: (whispering) What a relief.
JERRY: As you emerge through,
you appear in a bed,
with the covers up,
and then almost immediately the bed shatters from the middle.
RYAN: Yeah.
Where's my gold?
JERRY: Just goes-- Your hand is empty.
RYAN: D'oh! (laughter)
JERRY: Basically it...
Like a trap-- like a bear trap, the bed just goes-- (impact sound)
Like this.
KRIS: Like two Murphy beds. RYAN: Yeah.
KRIS: Just claps shut.
JERRY: It's not a mimic.
JERRY: But it is-- RYAN: I'm going to freak out, wha--!
KATE: There's a close-up. And like, why me?
RYAN: I know. Wah wah!
JERRY: Zooms right in. RYAN: Too big and strong I guess.
AMY: What kind of drinks does he have?
KRIS: Ooh. JERRY: Well he's going to have to escape this bed!
RYAN: Oh. (laughing) Okay.
RYAN: Do I have to roll to escape the bed? JERRY: No.
(laughter)
I pull out my sword...
JERRY: (grunts of exertion)
RYAN: Just start hacking at it and I sleep on the pile of whatever it is.
KRIS: The lumber? RYAN: Yeah.
RYAN: Lumber support? KATE: Loudly to no one,
KATE: I prefer a pile anyway. JERRY: Yeah exactly.
JERRY: In the corner. You just push all the pieces to-- RYAN: Yeah.
RYAN: I don't trust any furniture after all this.
(laughter)
JERRY: You reach up. There is a bottle of Jinaari silver wine which is a vintage--
RYAN: Hmm. (chef's kiss sound) JERRY: from your...
KATE: Jeez.
JERRY: your city. Your eastern-- in the eastern peaks of the Sword Mountains.
Thoughtful. Tasteful. There's an envelope sort of resting against the front of the bottle.
RYAN: All right. I drink the bottle.
JERRY: Wandering around, looking out the window. KATE: You're not going to get those notes or anything?
RYAN: Yeah I look around...
Take a nap.
(laughter)
RYAN: Then I read the-- (laughs)
JERRY: You wake up in the morning to read it?
RYAN: Yeah I wake it up. I fully rest in case in case it attacks me.
KRIS: All right. Good. (laughter)
(laughter)
KRIS: I will deal with this in the AM. RYAN: Yep. Yeah.
RYAN: I had a long couple of days.
KATE: See I love what you're doing. You're like, nope!
(laughter) JERRY: Later.
It says, Donaar of the noble house Blit'zen.
Member in good standing. Acquisitions Incorporated.
(clapping) RYAN: I was waiting for this to curveball here.
AMY: Member in questionable standing. RYAN: You're like, goddamn it.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. Some kind of dragon person.
JERRY: It's weird. RYAN: It's the tea-dipping thing, right?
JERRY: That's where you fucked up. RYAN: I'm sorry! Yeah.
JERRY: But yeah, simple rooms...
You know. Not-- Comfortable, but nothing out of the ordinary.
AMY: It's a bed. It's more comfortable than whatever the hell you came out of.
RYAN: So I'm like in a room by myself?
JERRY: You are in a room by yourself. It has two doors.
KRIS: Shh.
RYAN: And I go...
(shouting) Where-- Hey where are you guys? Anyone hear me?
I say, what the what? Really loud.
JERRY: It is entirely possible to hear the sound of Donaar Blit'zen
talking to himself and someone else, he hopes, in a nearby adjoining room.
AMY: I offer Rosie more tea.
KATE: I turn to Walnut and say,
Man I'd love to not hear that guy's voice for like-- (laughing) five seconds.
(laughter) AMY: And how.
RYAN: I start thrashing against the walls with my sword.
Another trap. I'll save everyone!
(laughter)
KRIS: Yeah I hear you and I say,
Yep! Got to go to sleep.
Got to-- Still hurt. Got to go to sleep.
Time to sleep.
RYAN: I like how like I was the fool for just grabbing a door to open it and everyone's like,
That's crazy! Why would you do that?
And everyone just immediately says,
Oh beds in a confined space! This is all fine and normal!
Now I'm on edge now forever!
KATE: (laughing) You got some trust issues, yeah.
RYAN: Yeah I do!
JERRY: Trust issues, but like for plants, food...
KRIS/JERRY: Doors.
KRIS: Yeah. RYAN: Definitely doors.
AMY: I want to-- JERRY: Door marriage!
AMY: Do we feel rested or no?
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. After you wake up? AMY: Yeah.
AMY: Do we feel-- Is it?
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. You have actually slept.
For real.
AMY: Okay.
JERRY: For a night.
KATE: Nice. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Yeah. AMY: Fantastic.
KATE: Get those hit points back! KRIS: For four years.
AMY: Change my spell loadout.
KATE: Yeah! Long rest. KRIS: Yeah. Get rid of this.
KATE: Ooh ki points. Get refreshed. JERRY: Spell loadout. You get your shit back.
JERRY: K'thriss Drow'b. Your big guns. KRIS: Please do.
AMY: All right I want to say that I pocket the envelope somewhere safe.
Put it somewhere on my person.
JERRY: It's on your person at all times?
AMY: At all times. I'm putting it on my character sheet. JERRY: Okay. There we go.
JERRY: Some interior pocket of your--
AMY: When we stop somewhere I'll have it framed.
JERRY: of your drui-- (laughs).
Exactly. But as I said, your rooms have two doors apiece.
They have a larger door that you remember from having--
You've seen doors like this very often for what seems like a week.
And a smaller, more simple door on an interior wall of your rooms.
RYAN: I'm walking around door.
AMY: I want to go try the tiny door.
JERRY: Yeah. The tiny door opens up into a room not much bigger than, maybe like,
four small closets put together.
There's a tiny table in the middle with a candle.
And a bookshelf sort of against the far wall.
And there are four doors leading into this room. Four small doors.
AMY: Dude, is this our base? And I go,
Uh... Big guy?
You in here?
RYAN: (laughs) I hear that, I assume? JERRY: Oh yeah.
RYAN: I go, yeah.
JERRY: The second you fall asleep.
RYAN: Yeah. (laughter)
RYAN: You gain one hit point back.
JERRY: You've been awa-- RYAN: I thought I was sleeping!
(laughter)
RYAN: Other guy said we were sleeping.
Still not catch his name, by the way.
KRIS: Okay I'm sleeping now. I'm not talking. Actually I am asleep. No? Okay. We're--
AMY: No, we're all rested. We're good. KRIS: We've rested. &gt;&gt; RYAN: All right, yeah.
KATE: I'd like to try the other door that Walnut did not try.
JERRY: That door opens into a-- sort of an upper-tier...
of a homey inn-- of the type that you have seen many times before.
But there's no ear pressure, there's no rush of cold...
KATE: Thank god.
JERRY: And it's different in a few key ways from the inn that you recall initially.
This is not a Jim Darkmagic-themed restaurant.
AMY: That's great.
KATE: I don't want to think about Jim Darkmagic right now.
RYAN: Yeah. The guy you killed?
JERRY: People are dressed in simple, comfortable attire.
I mean when you entered into Red Larch you got a sense of the--
of where this town was at in the grand, you know, economic hierarchy.
It's not up here.
It's a town that does well because it's on the Long Road but, you know, this is a simple town.
Over the fireplace, where there was a portrait of Jim Darkmagic,
you actually see a picture instead of three children.
You see what looks to be an older girl with her hands on a boy, with a striking resemblance to her,
and then another girl on her left.
JERRY: So-- AMY: Wait. There's two girls and one boy?
JERRY: There's two girls and one boy. AMY: Okay.
JERRY: So there is...
It's like a nice version of the place you have spent an eternity in.
The cauldron chairs are there.
KRIS: Oh! (shudders) JERRY: Warmed by that central fire.
JERRY: There is a bare stool on a small stage that adjoins the fireplace.
There's no one currently seated at it.
KATE: Well I think I should-- I'm going to grunt in satisfaction. Hmm!
And throw open the doors that I believe belong to my companions.
JERRY: Yeah you see other rooms similar to yours.
With people in various states of repose.
KRIS: Whoa! Whoa, whoa, whoa! RYAN: No, whoa!
KRIS: Okay, okay.
Let me get my cloak on.
JERRY: So the central room that adjoins these is comically small. Like--
KATE: Like halfling small or-- JERRY: it's hilariously--
KATE: something smaller? Okay. JERRY: Not for you.
JERRY: For you this is decent.
The problem is that you hang around with a lot of larger people.
This would be a family reunion. Like you would rent a place like this for events.
JERRY: For Donaar, it's hilarious. KATE: Got it.
RYAN: He's like, uh.
JERRY: He has to like brush the candelabra away and then invariably it swings back. I mean it's...
JERRY: It's complex. KATE: What kind of booze you seeing there?
JERRY: It's complex. AMY: I was going to say, is he drinking like...
KATE: yeah do you have-- because Walnut got tea and I bunked down with her so I got her drink.
But maybe... AcqInc knows my brand.
What kind of drinks do you see in there?
RYAN: Oh in my room? KATE: In my tiny room.
RYAN: Oh. Wait in the small chamber room?
KATE: Uh huh. RYAN: Oh I thought I was still in my bedroom.
AMY: I'm in there. RYAN: She's in there.
KATE: All right. Whoever's in there. Find the booze.
(laughter) KRIS: Just get it to me.
KATE: Tiny, tiny halfling booze.
AMY: I go, I don't know if we should be drinking right now.
KATE: (laughs) So disappointed.
RYAN: Should we do the-- Is now do we do the formal introductions?
KATE: Yeah I open the door-- JERRY: yeah, yeah.
JERRY: In your batcave scenario. KATE: Yeah.
KATE: I'm going to plant my quarterstaff and say, I'm Rosie.
RYAN: Okay.
Then I guess I groggily get dressed. (laughs)
KATE: Like fine.
KRIOS: Laboriously.
RYAN: Yeah like ah... KRIS: You make us watch.
RYAN: Put all my plate armor on.
RYAN: I don't like anything about this place.
KATE: It takes 25 minutes. AMY: Shining each scale.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, yeah. Oh yeah. Individual scale polish.
RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: Toothbrush? RYAN: I do the nails up.
RYAN: Oh yeah I brush the teeth for sure.
KATE: I'm clos-- I'm clearing my throat. I'm like, ahem. I'm Rosie.
KRIS: While you're doing that--
RYAN: There's other people that can go before me.
KRIS: I was going to say, while you do that I say, I'm K'thriss-- But and you go,
Eh no! It's my turn.
(laughter)
RYAN: Bup, bup, bup!
(brushing teeth noises)
Rinse it out with wine. (spitting sound)
JERRY: It's a bottle of Jack.
RYAN: And I say, okay you can go.
(laughter) And I don't introduce myself.
KRIS: It's not even done, yeah.
I'm K'thriss Drow'b, partners.
RYAN: Yeah. I show everyone the letter. I say,
I guess we're all partners. I'm Donaar, by the way.
The leader.
(laughter) And I guess we're all partners.
KRIS: That's what it says on mine. Fold it up--
KRIS: and never see it again. RYAN: Yeah, mine says I'm the leader. Did you guys' say that.
RYAN: I guess not. It makes sense because I'm the dragon and you guys aren't.
KATE: (laughs)
RYAN: So, what's good?
AMY: Oh. I very begrudgingly at this point say that I'm Walnut.
KATE: Like the nut? RYAN: Sulking.
AMY: No, like I don't want to say it.
KATE: Mm-hmm. AMY: Like, (grunt) yeah.
KRIS: Oh. RYAN: Walnut. That's a good name.
RYAN: Like the nut?
AMY: The very same.
KATE: Like the nut. RYAN: That makes sense.
AMY: Sure.
KRIS: I've-- I've had some of those before. RYAN: Yeah I had those. Those are good!
KRIS: That's a darn good nut. RYAN: Those are good.
KATE: I like to put them in my zucchini bread.
AMY: All right you don't need to make me feel good. I know.
(laughter)
With name like Walnut, you know.
KATE: I've heard it all before.
JERRY: You done heard it. AMY: Not my first time.
JERRY: But like I say, there's enough room for each of you to stand around this small table.
Right now the shelf is bare.
Who knows what your adventures will stock it with.
In the middle of the room is a small round table.
AMY: Now this is a far cry from other bases that I know that people from-- (laughing) this brand has though.
Just want to-- Looking around like, hmm.
K.
KATE: Okay. So we each have our own rooms. JERRY: Mm-hmm.
KATE: We have a downstairs where there are presumably drinking and making merry.
JERRY: Yeah it is by all accounts a roadside inn.
KATE: Okay.
Let's go find our person, I assume.
RYAN: Do we report to anyone? Yeah.
KATE: Omin? Probably is around here somewhere, right?
This is the Dran &amp; Courtier after all.
RYAN: Oh wait, I mean you guys report to me. Is what I meant to say.
AMY: No, no, no.
Do you think that...
Mr. Dran would be here?
KATE: Oh I think there's a chance. Certainly.
KRIS: At least there's an envoy or somebody. KATE: Stranger things have happened, my dear.
(laughter)
AMY: Well let's go meet him.
KATE: Indeed. I hop on your back again.
AMY: I go, I guess this is happening.
RYAN: I say, this is really cramped in here. I don't know about you guys.
KRIS: Let's go find out-- let's go verify that all of that was the test.
Hopefully that was all-- 100% start to finish was it actually.
RYAN: I'm with you man. I don't trust any of this. KATE: The test is over. And there's no more test.
RYAN: I have a lot of bad memories in this room.
AMY: Yeah... I mean did reality... RYAN: In the big room.
AMY: shatter for everybody that takes that test?
KRIS: I don't... know. KATE: Let's go find out.
KATE: Let's go downstairs and find out. AMY: Okay. Let's go downstairs.
KRIS: We all go downstairs. Except for you who's barking at us like,
I'm the man! I'm the one who gets to--
RYAN: I didn't dismiss the meeting.
(laughter)
AMY: I'm still holding the talking stick. JERRY: Who's taking minutes?
RYAN: Yeah. Who's taking the minutes?
JERRY: Absolutely. So you exit your rooms.
Groggily. You can see a few other doors up here.
RYAN: (shuddering sound) JERRY: Four additional rooms.
Yours are the-- No don't worry. It's okay.
KRIS: Did you shudder out of fear? Or delight?
JERRY: Yours are the middle four. RYAN: First one then the other.
JERRY: But there's several additional rooms on each side for other guests.
You head down the staircase.
It's a little strange because all the first times you encountered these things,
in shape if not in the reality,
all have bizarre memories associated with them.
This landing, you did battle with and made love to a door.
RYAN: Mmm. AMY: Mm-hmm.
RYAN: And murdered a wizard.
JERRY: There was a wizard, obviously. RYAN: And a bunch of squirrels.
KATE: (laughing) The tears and vomit.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. The staircase was dangerous. You saw these things over here.
You have a vague memory of having to get all the way from the bar to the door at a completely different scale.
But this homey inn melts a lot of that away.
It's not-- you can tell that it's nothing like the weird reflections that were summoned up for this test.
AMY: So I don't see a cat anywhere? RYAN: I was going to say, look for Onyx.
JERRY: Do you look for a cat?
AMY: I would like to look for a cat.
JERRY: There is a cat.
AMY: Is it Onyx?
JERRY: Do you want to go examine this cat? RYAN: (laughs)
AMY: Sorry, buddy.
AMY: Yes! I would like the examine the cat! RYAN: Do whatever. Go talk to him.
AMY: Perception! AMY: That's what got us into this mess!
AMY: Dang! Ten. (laughter)
JERRY: As you round the stair at the base and move in,
you can see behind the bar a woman of about 6'4".
AMY: Mm-hmm.
JERRY: Clean but obviously well-used plate.
Cleaning a glass.
She gives you a nod as you round the corner but you're looking elsewhere.
AMY: Oh okay.
JERRY: You can see a cat sort of lacing its way through people's legs and chair legs.
As it moves out to where you can see it as it emerges from one of these little meshes,
you think that this is probably Onyx. And in fact when Onyx sees you....
she...
approaches your leg...
and then...
does that cat cheek thing...
AMY: Oh the--
KATE: The good stuff.
JERRY: on both sides of the boot.
KRIS: Oh yeah. Getting that musk on.
RYAN: Different than last time.
AMY: I definitely pet Onyx although I will choose not to speak with her at this time.
(laughs)
AMY: Can't ask for a favor if I can't talk to her.
JERRY: Exactly. Yeah, yeah, exact-- (laughter)
KRIS: Yeah. Price is high, my friend.
AMY: But now that I know she'll be lurking around our base. RYAN: Yeah. Kill everyone in this room.
JERRY: Have you ever seen-- AMY: Probably.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. Have you ever played with a cat--
Or have you seen a cat that can see a bird outside of a window?
AMY: Yeah and they do that noise?
JERRY: That chitter. &gt;&gt; KRIS: (chittering sounds) AMY: Yeah.
JERRY: After the rub it's the chitter.
KATE: Oh! AMY: Great.
AMY: So I use (laughing) Speak with Animals.
KATE: Uh oh. AMY: So I use-- I cast Speak with Animals.
And I see Onyx and I go,
Hello, friend.
And I kneel down and put my hand out like I'm going to pet her, you know, more.
JERRY: She withdraws a little bit.
AMY: I go, what troubles you, friend?
JERRY: "Bring me a chicken."
KRIS: (laughs)
AMY: A chicken...
KRIS: The price has gone up. RTYAN: Yeah.
RYAN: It's bigger than a mouse. AMY: I... I...
AMY: look up at the-- am I close to the bartender?
JERRY: "Not as your kind eats."
AMY: Oh.
KRIS: (whispering) Ah...
AMY: You want...
a chicken.
A whole chicken?
JERRY: Just cocks its head.
KRIS: What other kind is there?
JERRY: It doesn't have a concept of a partial chicken.
AMY: (laughs) It wants a chicken.
Okay.
Okay. I'll--
JERRY: "You will do as you promised."
AMY: Okay.
AMY: I do owe you-- I do owe you a chicken.
Okay. I will be back with a chicken.
Then I walk away from Onyx then I look at these guys and I go,
I got to be honest, I thought it was going to be a much bigger ask.
(laughter)
So...
I have to get a chicken for this cat.
RYAN: You're going to kill a chicken?
AMY: No! I'm going to give it the chicken.
KATE: Like-- KATE/RYAN: A live chicken?"
KRIS: Sure then they can eat-- AMY: Cats eat chickens.
KRIS: Yeah.
AMY: It's fine. RYAN: Cats eat mice!
KRIS: But an old person at the table besides you says,
(old person voice) But chickens are forbidden in Red Larch!
(laughter)
RYAN: (old person voice) Next will be dancing!
AMY: We haven't had a chicken in 50 years! KRIS: What is a chicken?
KRIS: Not in this realm.
(laughter)
AMY: And I use Plane Shift! No, I'm joking.
RYAN: We broke reality and made chickens nonexistent.
JERRY: Yeah it's like everywhere you're going it's like,
Chickens, right? Like bawk bawk!
KRIS: You're like, the beat! RYAN: What? &gt;&gt; AMY: No.
AMY: Oh you mean the cockatrice that lives in the woods.
AMY: No. We didn't meet a chicken. I didn't make a promise to a chicken.
I can provide a chicken to an animal that eats chicken. Yeah, that's fine.
KRIS: Yeah. Yeah.
AMY: I'm not a vegan. KRIS: Idiot.
KATE: Did she say that she wanted it for eating? RYAN: Feel like you play fast and loose with these rules.
KRIS: Say what? KRIS: Did she want it for eating?
AMY: I look at Onyx and-- because I can still talk to her, and I go,
Friend, I assume you want this chicken alive?
JERRY: "No. For marriage."
(laughs)
KATE: Okay, now is the cat being sarcastic?
AMY: Walnut keeps it together!
(laughing) Walnut keeps it together!
She goes,
AMY: Ah-- JERRY: "Yes, I want to live with this chicken."
JERRY: "And be as one."
(laughter)
AMY: Friend, I have to ask...
Why?
KRIS: (whispering) Oh sweet Walnut.
AMY: Is-- KATE: Are you yucking the cat's yum, right now?
JERRY: "Bring me a chicken."
AMY: Okay. JERRY: "I will decide what happens to the chicken."
AMY: Okay. KATE: Holy shit!
AMY: That's-- That's-- That's fine.
RYAN: You're getting cat-sassed.
AMY: I'm just curious. KATE: Cat shade! &gt;&gt; JERRY: Meow!
RYAN: Yeah. This kitten's got claws.
(laughter)
AMY: Um okay so...
AMY: Walnut is bound by her oath to do this, yeah. JERRY: So you're hunched down in the middle of this inn,
JERRY: meowing. AMY: So you guys can do other stuff.
KATE: And you have to conduct a cat-chicken wedding ceremony?
AMY: Or it's going to eat it.
AMY: But Walnut did promise the cat-- RYAN: It can do both.
AMY: so at some point that's going to have to happen.
JERRY: Yeah. Absolutely. It doesn't have to be job one.
AMY: Sure. &gt;&gt; KATE: Side quest. JERRY: You know what I mean?
JERRY: Yeah exactly. AMY: Ding.
RYAN: Are we even at the right level for this yet?
JERRY: Right now it's green. No, trust me the chicken-- that's not going to be the hardest thing you guys do today.
AMY: I'm going to write it in my side quest book. JERRY: Yeah exactly.
JERRY: So...
RYAN: Get one chicken.
JERRY: The door to the inn opens.
And a woman in leather armor...
very functional, put to work, leather armor;
with skin the color of a chestnut;
comes in.
Gives a quick nod to the woman behind the bar.
And then off of her shoulder eases a satchel...
that is emblazoned on the front of it with the sigil of Acquisitions Incorporated.
KATE: Do these people bear any resemblance to the portrait over the fireplace?
JERRY: No. Not that you can think.
It could be a very old portrait.
KATE: Okay. KRIS: I have my suspicions.
AMY: What color are the people's hair in the portrait?
JERRY: In the portrait? AMY/KATE: Mm-hmm.
JERRY: Blond.
The boy's hair is cut very short.
AMY: Okay.
JERRY: And brunette. AMY: Yeah. Got it.
AMY: Cool. KATE: K.
JERRY: So as I said...
she eases this sack off, drops it at the bar.
And then: quick nod, turns on her heel, and heads back out.
Like even before the door has closed,
she's thrown it open, come in, dropped it off.
And then, as she is sort of silhouetted in the doorway,
the woman behind the bar says, "Alby."
And Alby turns back around, you assume.
And the woman behind the bar sort of underhands her a roll.
She catches it and then proceeds to leave.
You can see through the generous front window
Alby, or whoever it is,
hangs a small sign underneath the Dran &amp; Courtier sign,
that is the symbol of Acquisitions Incorporated, below.
And then as she hangs it, she gives it a quick pat.
It sort of sways in the wind and then she continues down the road.
AMY: (gasps) We have a base of operations.
KATE: Yes! RYAN: I go to the bartender and I say,
RYAN: What is this place?
KRIS: No, what? JERRY: Yeah.
KRIS: So we're here from-- We're the-- We're them. We're the franchisees.
KATE: Show them the letter. RYAN: Oh. I was gonna lead her down that road.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. She says--
KRIS: Why are you asking like you don't even know where we are?
JERRY: She says,
"I want to apologize in advance,"
"for whatever my son put you through."
KATE: That's not really in advance then, is it?
JERRY: "It's before-- ahead of our conversation. I can understand, Grandmother, why you might be..."
"displeased."
"I have told him on multiple occasions, not to use the door..."
"of the Dran &amp; Courtier for his hazing initiation torment palace that his friend Jim made."
"But..."
AMY: Did she say her son?
KATE: Grandson. AMY: Grandson. Okay.
JERRY: No. Son. AMY: Oh son!
JERRY: Son. Yeah. KATE: Oh, son. I thought you said-- Okay.
AMY: (whispering) This is awesome.
JERRY: "I've told them not to do it."
"I received a letter yesterday saying that I should prepare the rooms upstairs."
"It's been a long time since he has centered a team out of Red Larch."
KRIS: Oh hmm. JERRY: "But..."
"I have a guess why he might be doing it again."
"Once you've come back from a couple missions, maybe it's something we can discuss."
KATE: Ah. we're not high enough level yet.
JERRY: Gah. Levels aren't real.
RYAN: So do you like, work for us?
Because I'm the leader.
JERRY: "You should open the satchel."
(laughter)
RYAN: Is that a yes or...? KRIS: I'm already opening it.
RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: So you know that there are roles, duties responsibilities that come along with the license.
So the advantage of the license is that it gives people...
You know, if it comes down to two groups, a lot of times they're gonna choose the group that they've heard of.
KRIS: Right. JERRY: Right?
JERRY: So it allows you a little bit of leeway in a new market.
Right? If you're just starting out. There's an advantage to it.
Obviously, you need to give up some of the gold from each job.
But there are also four roles.
You know that each of these franchises has four distinct roles.
Just like any corporation.
KRIS: Of course. Yes.
JERRY: And so the first thing you need to do is actually to establish
who is going to take on which of these four roles.
And all the documentation is present.
As soon as you open it up, it's like when you get your passes from Disneyland.
You open it up and then all the papers and quills are all lined up, ready to go.
JERRY: The documentation-- the first document you get out is basically your...
is a finalized version of the license with space for signatures.
But each of those signature spaces is associated with one of the four tasks.
So the first task is the Cartographer.
Second task is called Hoards Person.
AMY: Wait, Hoards Person? JERRY: Hoards Person.
KRIS: Sure.
JERRY: The Hoards Person maintains stocks, keeps track of coin.
The Decisionist...
is the tie-breaker.
Their task is whenever there's a vote, they get two votes.
KATE: (laughs)
KATE: Oh my gosh. JERRY: Right?
JERRY: And the final one is called a Documancer.
So a Documancer in Acquisitions Incorporated...
You know that...
Obviously any contract has a mystical aspect.
It's like...
You know, it commands things of people.
KRIS: Yeah. It has its own weave. Yeah. JERRY: Exactly.
JERRY: But the kind of documentation that comes from Acquisitions Incorporated is a step above.
It has parts of the document that would fill themselves out.
It can take dictation.
So the type of stationary that comes along with this pack is a step above.
And it requires someone to focus their corporate efforts
specifically on making sure that all this documentation is going back up to the head office directly.
So every time you take a job, every time you leave a job, certain types of dungeon entrances, plants.
All these things-- information of this type is all sort of agglomerated together at the head office.
Which keeps a substantial storehouse of data about the regions it operates in.
So I need to know who is signing which of these things.
KATE: Okay before we start...
AMY: Fighting.
(laughter)
KRIS: Hold on I'm the Decisionist!
You sign this part. You sign this part.
JERRY: There's no bar fight aspect.
KATE: I have been advised by Patrick Rothfuss,
Don't sign anything without reading all of it.
Find a fantasy lawyer.
Do we have a fantasy lawyer who can review these documents for us before we sign them?
JERRY: I don't think so. KATE: Okay.
KRIS: Having never heard of a Documancer before,
KATE: Yeah that job sucks. KRIS: I assume we need one of them.
KRIS: And we don't have that.
KATE: Okay well Rosie is going to read it very carefully.
Every word.
JERRY: Absolutely.
KATE: Is there anything untoward there?
AMY: Did Omin write this?
JERRY: Are you asking me, Jerry Holkins?
AMY: Yeah. Is this like a-- RYAN: I've never even heard of Omin.
JERRY: Yeah do you want to examine it?
AMY: Yeah I want to examine it.
JERRY: Yeah. Let's see some perception.
AMY: Oh! Popped out of my hand.
15?
JERRY: Down in the lower right hand corner, in very small type, it says,
This document prepared personally by Ominifis Hereward Dran.
AMY: I'm immediately grossed out that I'm holding a contract that Omin had anything to do with.
JERRY: It's vile. AMY: I know he views them as pornographic.
KRIS: In the other corner-- JERRY: Yeah exactly. Sensual.
KRIS: In the other corner, C:\Documents and Settings\
(laughter) JERRY: Yeah exactly. It's the raw printout.
KRIS: Right.
JERRY: But even the document even smells magical. You can assess it if you want to.
KRIS: I want to just to see what level of magic is being dealt with.
JERRY: Yeah. KRIS: Like what have we gotten ourselves into?
KRIS: So that's all right. It's arcana, that's not going to be great. Uh it's 11.
JERRY: Okay. Yeah this is...
This document, it doesn't seem malevolent or nefarious,
but you think that writing on it...
happen twice.
You think that when you write on it here,
you think that there's another document somewhere
that receives the same inscription.
KRIS: It's so valuable.
These magics!
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, but anyway. So we got some documents here to check out.
AMY: Does Cartographer-- that's just like keeping track of where we went?
JERRY: Yeah exactly. Tracks where you went. But it's specifically mapping for the corporation.
AMY: And the Hoard Person, they just deal with the whole loot.
JERRY: Yeah they deal with loot, but they also provision jobs.
They make sure you got the supplies to do a specific job, but they also keep track of the gold and treasure.
KRIS: This sounds like a you thing.
RYAN: I see everyone sniffing at their contracts. And I go,
Isn't this what we were all shooting for?
And then, eh? Time to make a decision!
And I grab the decision maker sheet.
RYAN: And I say, yeah! I wave it around. AMY: And I go,
AMY/KATE: No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
RYAN: I don't even know what the rest of the words mean. The only word I know is, Decisionist.
KATE: I'm still reading. And I'm like, why did he type out all the moaning?
That he has this feeling while writing this contract.
JERRY: Hmm... Hurr…!
KATE: Hmm. Uh... JERRY: Eh...
KATE: Mmm. It's not pleasant.
JERRY: It's gross. KATE: Gross read.
AMY: Um... KATE: Nasty boy.
AMY: I look at Donaar holding the decision maker and I go--
RYAN: I'm waving it around. I'm not just holding it.
RYAN: (paper waving sound) &gt;&gt; AMY: And I go, KRIS: You keep it out of our reach.
AMY: Wouldn't someone of your economic stature be more at home keeping track of all the gold and...
RYAN: (paper waving sounds)
KRIS: He's making a great hoarder. AMY: gems.
JERRY: "In-wealth-inations?"
Yeah, yeah. Dragons specialize in hoards.
KATE: It's true. It is kind of in your blood. RYAN: Eh...
KATE: Is that racist?
RYAN: If not me, then who? I don't know.
AMY: Well it should be someone that's you know...
RYAN: That is willing to sell us out to mice? AMY: Impartial.
AMY: No. Maybe someone who sticks to a strong moral code or ethics.
KRIS: That's... Yeah. But, I mean, I feel like wisdom could be taken advantage of here.
Certainly someone who's lived a long time.
Not me.
I'm a youthful, sprightly drow.
Not that old.
RYAN: I'm noble! KRIS: Sure.
RYAN: I'm a nobleman. KRIS: I believe you.
RYAN: You're-- KRIS: I'm saying--
RYAN: I thought we laid this out. KATE: I'm not interested in making decisions.
KRIS: Ah I see. KATE: I do like mapmaking however.
KATE: So that's where my eyeballs are at. KRIS: I see.
KRIS: I think that's fine with me.
KATE: I think that Donaar would make an excellent Decisionist.
RYAN: Hey!
That's two votes for Decisionist.
RYAN: And because I'm Decisionist, I get three! KATE: That's actually three.
So this is easy.
KATE: That's a majority already.
(laughter)
KRIS: Okay.
AMY: I'm ready to-- KATE: Up top!
AMY: I'm ready to roll to try and get it away from...
AMY: To get it away from Donaar. RYAN: I'll try to persuade.
AMY: That's fine. KATE: Ooh.
JERRY: Let's see it. KRIS: Oh yeah!
KATE: Here we go. &gt;&gt; KRIS: Let's see!
KRIS: This is real combat. RYAN: All right. So I roll for persuasion?
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, yeah. AMY: What do I have to roll against?
RYAN: I want to take an advantage too.
KATE: Oh nice. Yes! KRIS: Wow!
KRIS: This is a nightmare. JERRY: (laughs) This is the best.
AMY: Walnut would never want to be in charge of loot.
That makes no sense.
JERRY: You got to make a case. RYAN: That makes it funnier.
KRIS: Yeah.
KRIS: Oh you know what-- AMY: She would just give it away to poor people.
KATE: You get provisions too. KRIS: I was going to say--
KRIS: I was going to say, I don't either.
KRIS: But suddenly I remember that I do. JERRY: Let's see what you got. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Oh.
KATE: Yeah I think you would an excellent Documancer. RYAN: That's a 17 plus five so...
KATE: You're very brand-oriented. RYAN: 22 or a...
RYAN: Well no. I'll take the 22.
JERRY: All right 22. AMY: What do I have to roll against that?
JERRY: Well take a look at your sheet and tell me what you think would be a good match for this incredible case he's made.
AMY: Can I do insight to view his true intentions?
JERRY: Yeah. AMY: And can I also take advantage?
RYAN: True intention? My true intention I just told you what it was.
AMY: No, can I roll to know like, oh no, no, no, no. You're trying to--
RYAN: It's very vapid and not very smart.
JERRY: It's like is he going to implicate that is really what you want.
AMY: Yeah, yeah, yeah. JERRY: Right? Yeah.
JERRY: So roll two of these dice. Let's see what you got.
JERRY: That's a shit show. AMY: That's a one. That's a one. Come one.
JERRY: That's a toilet dice. AMY: Bigger!
AMY: Ah shit! 17.
JERRY: All right, now how do you convince...
Tell me about the case you make to Walnut
who does not want to be the Hoards Person.
RYAN: I say, you don't have to be the Hoards Person.
That's fine with me. I'm not arguing that you're going to be the Hoards Person.
I'm arguing that I'll be the Decisionist.
And then I say, maybe I didn't make this clear earlier.
So, just a little insight, the pecking order goes:
dragons;
dragonborn;
and everyone else is tied for third, at best.
AMY: I mean--
RYAN: I mean we all know this. This is comm-- I'm not telling anybody anything you guys don't already know.
Right? As I sign.
(laughter)
KRIS: As I sign. RYAN: As I sign the document.
RYAN: You know I'm just-- We all know this.
KATE: I kind of want to convince you that Walnut is a dragon.
KRIS: Hah! &gt;&gt; JERRY: Has draconic-- KATE: Yeah.
RYAN: I begrudgingly admire all of you. We gone through this together. KATE: I take you aside,
RYAN: And I'm like, there's probably a little dragon-- KATE: Do you understand? She's actually a dragon.
RYAN: There's probably a little dragon in all you guys. There's more in me, though.
KATE: Hmm.
RYAN: You know. I mean, you couldn't have gotten through that without having like--
RYAN: 1/32 dragon. KRIS: Now hold on a second.
KRIS: Me thinks you doth protest too much.
Maybe you're putting on a dragon front and actually there's more dragon in somebody else here.
Because you make a big fuss about it.
RYAN: I say this as I scratch my scales, I say,
All right. Go on.
KRIS: I didn't say it doesn't look good.
(laughter)
It's convincing. Maybe even real.
JERRY: All right. Now do we have any other roles that people will take?
KRIS: I will... I am interested in Cartographer but I would take Hoards Person if nobody else wants it.
JERRY: M'kay.
AMY: I guess Documancer's fine because Walnut's name would be on all documents that go to official--
JERRY: That's true. It would go all the way to the top.
AMY: I just want to point out-- This is now Walnut speaking...
Have to deal with this person being able to outvote every move that we make--
KATE: I think it's great. AMY: for the rest of the campaign--
AMY: (shouting) Why?
KATE: Because I'm chaotic good!
KRIS: It's not outvote. It's just a little extra juice if there's a lock.
RYAN: Yeah. A little extra strength.
RYAN: Like being a dragon. KRIS: We can form a bloc.
RYAN: You know? Just a little stronger than the rest of you lot.
KRIS: I don't like it either. But I think he's--
AMY: I just think mechanically it's-- KATE: I think it's fine.
KRIS: Here's the problem. He's already written most of his name on it.
RYAN: Yeah. I've gotten to the L.
RYAN: I've gotten to the "Bl." JERRY: He's gotten to the "Aa."
AMY: Okay.
JERRY: Okay, now... RYAN: We don't have erasers.
KRIS: We need to have-- present the home office with a unified front.
KRIS: I don't want it scratched off. RYAN: Yeah it's just all these different names--
KRIS: We need to solve this. RYAN: scratched or rewritten.
JERRY: Exactly. So...
KRIS: Yeah. It sucks. KATE: Real test.
JERRY: The Red Larch chapter of Acquisitions Incorporated is:
Cartographer Rosie.
Hoards Person K'thriss Drow'b.
Decisionist Donaar Blit'zen.
And Documancer Walnut Dankgrass.
Obviously there will be things that tie into that stuff later.
But in the farthest back pouch inside the bag,
underneath the rain flap,
are two scrolls sealed with the Acquisitions Incorporated seal.
KRIS: Hmm.
AMY: Are two scrolls?
JERRY: Two scrolls. KATE: Sounds like a job for the Documancer.
AMY: I'll take those!
I look at Donaar like...
AMY: Look what I got. RYAN: And I say...
RYAN: I'll allow it.
(laughter) RYAN: As the leader I will...
AMY: It doesn't say leader. It says decision maker.
RYAN: Oh we're going to quibble over terms now?
KRIS: I love it! I love it. KATE: Decisionist.
KRIS: You will open them.
RYAN: Yeah. AMY: Sure.
JERRY: So there are-- (laughter)
AMY: Sure. JERRY: Each of these--
JERRY: It's a black wax with the symbol glinting on the front.
They are both equal in size, weight; they're virtually identical in every way.
AMY: Cool I crack one open. JERRY: K.
JERRY: You crack one open and it says at the top--
the document is laid out in a very, very clear, established, didactic way.
And at the top it says,
Party Security for the Vespertine Order.
300 gold pieces.
AMY: Oh... okay.
JERRY: Below that it says,
Sombar Blood-Drinker requests professional defense specialists for a midnight soirée.
Inquire at the Doomgate Inn.
AMY: Hmm.
KRIS: Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. AMY: Okay.
JERRY: You could ask around about that. You haven't heard of the Doomgate Inn.
AMY: Yeah. I have feelings about somebody with the last name Blood-Drinker. (laughs)
JERRY: That's-- Listen, that's--
It's 1492.
KRIS: Yeah. Not only bad people drink blood.
JERRY/RYAN: Yeah. JERRY: Exactly. &gt;&gt; KRIS: You know?
AMY: Hmm. KRIS: That's an old idea.
RYAN: Lot of iron.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. AMY: All right. Well...
The second scroll, once unsealed, says,
The Raiding Must Cease.
AMY: Okay. JERRY: 200 gold pieces.
AMY: Okay.
JERRY: It is signed by a Lord Vizgig Cartinwheel.
AMY: (laughing) Okay. RYAN: Hmm.
JERRY: It is offered as a job between the town of Beliard and something called Stone Bridge.
There's a small chunk of the map here.
And in addition to the 200 gp it says,
Partial payment in the form of a cart.
KATE: (gasps) &gt;&gt; RYAN: Ooh. AMY: Oh yeah!
AMY: Oh yeah. KATE: (whispering) Oh yeah! Oh yeah.
AMY: Sure okay.
And so I want to read these out loud to the group.
Or at least the important part.
And when I do it I want to be like,
Party security. Yep okay.
JERRY: They have date ranges on them as well. AMY: Oh they do?
JERRY: Exactly. AMY: Which one is closer?
JERRY: The more immediate one-- the Party Security, is physically closer.
But the date on that is about ten days hence.
AMY: Ten days. Okay and what's the cart quest?
JERRY: The Raiding Must Cease from Lord Vizgig Cartinwheel...
AMY: Mm-hmm.
JERRY: That is a range of time.
And it appears to be an open contract that other parties may also be able to partake in.
KRIS: Hmm.
AMY: Hmm.
KATE: Is that range sooner than the Doomgate?
JERRY: Absolutely. You think you'd be able to do both if you were able to knock this first one out.
JERRY: Especially if there's a cart involved.
AMY: Okay so then I turn to the party and I say,
We have two missives.
And this is our first one! And I hold up the cart quest.
(laughter)
KATE: I believe you a hundred percent!
AMY: I go, this one doesn't start for ten days.
So we have plenty of time.
KATE: Crumple it up, throw it in the garbage.
AMY: I... then put it in my...
KARIS: Little bit details?
AMY: docum-- KATE: Document sack?
AMY: document sack, apparently. JERRY: Yeah exactly.
RYAN: Satchel.
JERRY: Yeah the satchel should probably be carried by the Documancer.
AMY: Absolutely. It's already on my person.
JERRY: It's ready to go. The branding? Strong!
AMY: (power up sound effect) JERRY: On the back.
AMY: Got an item. KATE: Mm-hmm.
AMY: It's my own special bag of holding.
Document holding that is!
KATE: (laughing) It's so perfect.
JERRY: It's all quills inside.
JERRY: Like it's just-- AMY: Oh absolutely.
KRIS: It's so tasteful. AMY: Yeah I have a roll out--
and it's all just different kinds of quills.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. You choose the right one for this document!
AMY: Oh exactly. I'm already commissioning a special stamp.
KRIS: They say that the quill chooses the Documancer.
(laughter) AMY: (laughing) The quill chooses the Documancer!
Yes! I said it. And it was funny when I said it.
JERRY: No, it's premium. RYAN: I thought of that. It was great.
KATE: What's-- The name is Vizgig Cartinwheel?
JERRY: Vizgig Cartinwheel-- Lord Vizgig Cartinwheel. KATE: Lord Vizgig Cartinwheel.
KATE: And we get a cart? Isn't that a funny coincidence?
JERRY: Mm-hmm.
AMY: Well he probably has them rolling around. JERRY: Partial payment. &gt;&gt; KATE: Partial payment.
JERRY: In the form of a cart. KATE: And that's upfront.
JERRY: Mm-hmm. KATE: Perhaps? Okay.
KATE: Maybe we need it to-- JERRY: Yeah.
JERRY: It's established. AMY: What kind of cart? Like wheelbarrow?
JERRY: It's established.
JERRY: There is a voucher... RYAN: Like Ghostbusters?
AMY: Okay.
JERRY: on the bottom that says,
Waelvur's Wagonworks.
And then below that is says,
Not Thelorn's Safe Journeys.
And below that it says,
Prince and Princess.
KATE: Ooh. RYAN/KRIS: Hmm.
AMY: Huh. Okay.
Okay.
KRIS: Sounds pretty--
So I put away Party Security for Bloodsuckers Inc. away.
JERRY: Exactly.
Vampires 'R' Us.
AMY: Yeah. JERRY: Midnight feast!
AMY: So in ten days we'll have a party with some vampires, but not today.
KATE: I don't like vampires.
AMY: Nobody does. KATE: I don't know why. I just got this feeling.
KRIS: Is that known to us though? RYAN: Yeah you got his false memory.
KRIS: You said...
We know that the other tasks are--
JERRY: No. I don't think she read the other task at all.
KRIS: That's what I'm asking. AMY: No, no, no, no, no.
AMY: I'm saying I did not read anything about it. I said it doesn't start for ten days.
AMY: This is our first missive. KATE: The cart enthusiast.
KRIS: Okay. JERRY: That's right.
KATE: Can I open my Cartographer bag?
JERRY: Yeah. KATE: Is there stuff in there?
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, yeah. Imagine there the--
On the side of it there's something like where a bedroll would ordinarily be,
this is a roll that has a thick vellum in a waterproof sort of spiral case.
And it detaches from the main bag.
KATE: So I just got some vellum. You got all this cool document bag? Okay. That's fine, that's fine.
I'm a monk. I live an ascetic lifestyle.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. Austere.
JERRY: It's not about possessions. KATE: Exactly.
JERRY: Know what I mean? It's not about possessions. KRIS: You'd have been more upset if there were more in there.
KATE: Yeah if there were more stuff, I'd be pissed off.
JERRY: But give me some shit! Right?
KATE: Give me some fucking-- JERRY: Give me some fucking shit.
KATE: Yeah.
JERRY: All right. That's the situation.
Your parents have gone away for a week's vacation.
(laughter) AMY: God!
JERRY: It's going to come up a lot. KATE: I love that joke. I love that joke.
RYAN: We're at the beach house. Bernie's dead.
JERRY: So the woman behind the counter has been making drinks and serving food this entire time.
But then every now and then definitely casting a glance over at the party
with what seems like a-- almost a sadness, like a wistful look.
AMY: Can I...
Since we're in her inn running our business out of their--
Can I ask her her name?
JERRY: Yeah. AMY: Oh. Ma'am.
AMY: Thank you for letting us, ma'am-- JERRY: "Oh. No 'ma'am.'"
AMY: Oh sorry.
JERRY: "Well my name is-- my name gives people problem also."
"'Propha' is fine.
AMY: Propha.
JERRY: "I was born Prophetess Dran."
AMY: Oh!
Oh.
KATE: Oh! AMY: Propha. Okay.
KATE: I like it.
AMY: And then I just say,
Propha, thank you for allowing us to use this base of operations--
JERRY: "Oh it's all paid for."
AMY: Right. True. JERRY: "It's all paid for."
JERRY: "As long as you're alive."
AMY: Right. JERRY: "There have been challenges in the past..."
JERRY: "keeping this branch open." KATE: What kind of challenges?
JERRY: "It's something we can discuss..."
KATE: I'd love to. JERRY: "It's something we can discuss later."
KATE: Oh. JERRY: "He only sends people..."
JERRY: "He only..."
And she steps back from the bar for a second.
"He only operates franchises out of this inn for one reason."
"And it's something he and I have fought about for years."
"He..."
And so she turns around and starts absentmindedly just cleaning glasses.
AMY: I see this-- JERRY: But they're not even getting clean.
AMY: Yeah I see that this is a-- I stop pushing.
Because I see this is a sensitive subject and we'll probably see her again.
JERRY: Does anyone else want to approach this?
KATE: I will definitely keep pushing.
RYAN: Yeah. By "he" you mean Omin right?
KATE: For what reason does he have groups operating out of this inn?
JERRY: Persuade. KATE: All right.
KRIS: Hmm. KATE: I can intimidate. But I will not do that right now.
JERRY: Just mother to mother?
KATE: Yeah, yeah, yeah! Totally. KRIS: I feel like that's-- Wow.
KATE: Do you think-- Like I mean I can do that--
JERRY: No listen, hold on here. Kate, Kate, Kate.
We're playing Dungeons &amp; Dragons. Don't let me guide it.
KATE: Okay! JERRY: Right? You can use whatever skill you want.
JERRY: Whatever you think Rosie Beestinger would do is okay.
KATE: Okay I'm going to try-- KRIS: I mean we have to work here.
KATE: I'm going to try Good Cop approach first. Yeah. AMY: Yeah don't crap where you eat.
KATE: I'm going to try persuasion and give her just like a little like,
KATE: Come on, I know... AMY: Just don't make our rent go up, please.
KATE: I know exactly how sons, and grandsons, and great-grandsons, and great-great-grandsons are.
And I rolled a ten, but...
I'm very old.
And I look very wise.
(laughter)
And I just have this extra maternal instinct that I'm just trying to project super hard at her.
Even though I know she looks tough. And she's got the armor on and everything.
And maybe she doesn't have a super great relationship with her son, sounds like they fight a lot.
But I'm just trying really hard to just be like,
I know... I know how they are. I know how this is.
My son...
Uh. Driebus.
A hundred years old. Still has not learned how to listen to his mother.
Right there with you.
Driebus Beestinger, wherever you are, I swear to god.
AMY/RYAN: Driebus.
KATE: Ugh. Don't get me started on Driebus.
KRIS: Started thinking about calling my mom.
KRIS: I'm going to see this as some error. AMY: Call her on the sigil?
KRIS: Feel a little guilty.
JERRY: Yeah, her face hardens at this.
And says...
"If you're around in a week,"
"we'll have this conversation again."
KATE: Sounds promising. AMY: Walnut's in the back like,
AMY: (whispering) Told you!
(laughter)
RYAN: If we're around in a week. KATE: Cool.
AMY/KATE: Great. RYAN: Ominous.
KATE: Another great sign. JERRY: Yeah.
KRIS: So whatever this thing is it happens at least weekly.
(laughter)
RYAN: Thursday-ish.
JERRY: Once a week. It's Taco Tuesday!
(laughter)
KATE: Gets you every time. JERRY: So you...
JERRY: You collect your things.
What do you do?
How do you approach this situation?
You have a direction.
You have a job.
And you're ready to go.
AMY: Should we...
Can I say to um...
Oh I already lost it. What was her name?
KATE: Propha? JERRY/RYAN: Propha.
AMY: Yeah, sorry!
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, yeah. She is wheeled back and she has casted the occasional hard glance.
AMY: Yeah, yeah, yeah. So I say,
Propha, we'd love to get out of your hair and let to continue running your establishment.
Do you know where we could find a Lord Vizgig Cartinwheel by chance?
KATE: There is a map.
AMY: There's a map in there? KATE: And I am a Cartographer.
JERRY: Yeah-- AMY: And I go,
Propha, nevermind. You got it.
KATE: (laughs) You seem really busy.
AMY: You seem really busy. JERRY: Exactly.
JERRY: So on the document...
AMY: Oh there's a literal map to him?
JERRY: Well there's a map that covers where the actual job is.
AMY: Oh okay. JERRY: It doesn't say where it is,
JERRY: but it says Waelvur's Wagonworks.
And has what you think might be a local address.
But it's on the same street actually.
AMY: Oh okay. JERRY: Right around the corner basically.
AMY: In my head when you said map, I thought video game,
and thought map of the dungeon that we have to get into.
KATE: (laughing) Sorry. KRIS: That's very nice of them.
AMY: Wow that was really easy. Yeah, that's why I was like,
AMY: Well this is a no-brainer! JERRY: No.
JERRY: In fact, so you leave. You can tell that she is relieved.
She has had to think about something that she doesn't like thinking about.
And it keeps coming up.
AMY: Sure. When we keep bringing it up over and over? JERRY: Exactly.
JERRY: You go out. The last time you have been out here was before you came into this place.
You can see the Acquisitions Incorporated sign below the Dran &amp; Courtier, gently swinging below.
AMY: Little swell of pride.
JERRY: That's right.
You make your way out into the main road and across the way
you can see Waelvur's Wagonworks.
And you think that you probably don't want a ride in any kind of caravan that this person is offering.
But we will get to that stuff next week!
Next Thursday.
It's been an absolute pleasure!