time is the enemy the past addresses the
fastest weapon you will that make it
past a second and that the question play
a flash and reckless to choose a course
in solution you saw was prudent and any
sepulcher poker - will become the putrid
it's that well said I pursue in no
mountain too steep but don't in too deep
to send expendable marks up to the top
of the peak of beneath this thing you
need they come like sharks - and while I
swim in that line again like Carl Barks
ruin so send your national talks to it
I'll send them home in a natural box the
close time' most of the parts included
save your breath for a cleric confessor
that there's a lesson and life isn't any
profession but to speak in my official
advice sign on the dotted line and
listen the twice yeah hello i'm Tycho
Brahe hey of Penny Arcade and pax I am
also a menace as hair were drawn CEO of
acquisitions incorporated but today I am
Jerry Holcomb and like a terrible father
I'm just going to leave the entire party
I'm going to put a nickel in to that
little horsey machine they have out in
front of the store and that's going to
be your dad now I'm going to run out for
any smokes I'm going to run out for some
smokes in another variable ever so slow
playing no no I have got a good
babysitter for you to take care of you
while I'm away shadow council may our
Labor's please you it is my great
pleasure to introduce Jim dark magic who
is also my crew who thank you very much
oh thank you
thank you Carrie I was very nice all
right
I'm not your Dungeon Master uh so don't
you know don't play like you're playing
with Jerry don't catch I don't like any
not even realize don't catch feelings
yeah well anyway can I introduce us to
just for the summer though no oh yeah
Julian do his introduction right Who am
on is my friend Chris why are you
starting alongside feels off
no drink drop the stream here no
this is much better I know who they are
I like to my right
Dragonborn narcissus dinar blitz in okay
all right now repping the natural world
walnut dog grass to my left not your
grandma's grandma rosey B singer and
then emerging is though from a mister
out her strobe all right now that I
really hope he does not do that again
yeah all right every five minutes he's
going to run out I understand that you
guys have been having your own
adventures I don't super care about any
of that ah Jim wants you needs your help
and just imagine in the middle of the
scenarios that you are involved in when
Jerry left you you sort of start to fade
out of that and when you come back you
are standing in what looks like a very
well appointed Wizards studio a study
and there's a large desk in front of you
there's a young man sitting at the desk
he's got a big mop of curly black hair
he's ringing a silver bell that says CT
on it s what time of day or night is
this happened you can't tell you're
inside a study there's no windows I
don't but what are we wearing are we in
our Jam so it just happen oh you're just
a middle end okay like I'm worried my
wife really really what here in the
middle never vote yeah yeah and you
faded out and when Yuri materialized you
are now in this magician study okay
please ring the bell puts it down into
one of the drawers of the desk and
closes it and he says C team I am so
excited to see you guys here are you
familiar with Jim dark magic ah
anybody heard of him everyone I've heard
of him got all bubbly negative emotions
towards him I were you did he had a lot
of great things to say about you
actually really yeah
Jim has had a bit of a magical accident
he removes like a little wooden box from
one of the desk drawers and sets it on
the table he looks down and he says
Jim's in a real tough spot right now but
he's got a solution and you all are
going to be able to help him out you
he's sort of cursed himself in trying to
find a solution for that the magical
ailment that is re killing him right he
had he had a bit of an accident he looks
at the box again anyway there is one
wizard in the entire world
with the knowledge and the willingness
to help Jim remove this curse
unfortunately getting to see him is
tricky once a year he provides an
audience to the champion who wins his
tournament held at his wizard tower his
Wizards neck the four of you will need
to infiltrate his wizard tower confound
his army of guards take the place of the
for actual champions battle each other
the winner will then have to take Jim he
looks at the Box to the wizard and have
him resolve the current situation so at
this he points to a portal that
magically appeared next to him it says
this is going to take you right out
front of the tower I put you right there
but then it's up to you guys to do the
rest so anyway any questions never had
kind of a votive this yeah what is
creeping right yes you are in a
dimension right now from what I
understand you had some experience with
Jim's pocket dimensions
yeah yeah assumed yeah hated them
they're great assuming everything goes
according to plan which I don't know why
it wouldn't I'm going to put you guys
right back in all your spots and it'll
be like no time passed at all if there
were like some I'm gonna I'm gonna
present
third party it would be like nothing
ever change for them yes someone
watching they doesn't know they wouldn't
know right wouldn't know it is it work
Oh Jim is in that box yes
one of you will need to take Jim one
like Ranson yes
I'll take care of this it's official
okay clearly an official good at saying
okay can we can we see the
contents of the box we'll have a look in
the box yeah yeah well shakes it you
hear cheeps like I don't know oh okay
and then opens that credit there's three
baby chicks oh you're so come I got all
my little sweeties oh okay she hates and
yeah oh he's gonna okay you're gonna
kill them they look a little rattled
honestly they're kind of stumbling
around on their tiny chick feet one of
them is just on the ground laying on its
side Oh God oh okay diagnosis chicken
concussion yeah I know is it does it I
mean does it just look dazed it looks
day yeah it's fine I reach into my
pocket and give it some of my life I'm
just assuming birdseed sir yeah I will
you that I does have they perk up and
they sort of walk around in the box
they're cheeping very happily are those
Jim yeah yeah Madge Acton this these are
Jim those are Jim those the three of
them are Jim there were you disappear on
oh-oh I'm Jim's apprentice dude I know
he had an apprentice lovely took me you
didn't you haven't heard of diz ever on
and then she was immediately as
disinterested in your um a pleasure to
meet your acquaintance are in a branch
obviously you know do you might be
pretty high to code signatories anyway
I'm gonna take very good case what do
you say like okay this is really
important because this is like I think
I'm mrs. omens best friend so we need to
you know absolutely maybe everyone's
super trusting here I don't know you and
I don't know these birds
well that C team on that oh you got me
there yeah no team all right there is a
large portrait of Jim dark magic to your
right on one of the walls near
bookshelves
yeah and it's and I get PTSD okay like I
remember the good goddamn and that's bad
get a shudder of disgust and behind this
sort of there's like a big framed piece
of art it looks like a very elaborate
cross stitch very floral lettering
sparkly sort of thread it says a wizard
did it and he says if you guys have any
questions points to cross
stitch are you an acquisition think no
unfortunately I am not Jim will not let
me apply for acquisitions incorporated
he says it but my skills are best used
under his tutelage hmm how long have you
been with the process 16 years one yeah
well you'll get there one day
I believe so if I if I keep my head up
and the right attitude I'm going to be a
wizard as powerful as Jim when he's not
you know chicks yeah David yeah it seems
pretty strong normally he expects hugely
is yes there way to do a perception
check just to see this is all [ __ ]
yeah yeah absolutely we have to see yeah
okay you wanna make a perception or
Arkana
I'll do it makes definitely something
sure will do I don't have our cleaner
you have Arcana insight is like you can
tell if somebody is I think like lying
to you yeah I'll do insight yeah
absolutely okay all right I'll do I'm
awful do bad 14 yeah I wish would have
been I wanted timeless unit perception
needed insight yeah
16 did is 100% certain like he is
honestly telling you the truth okay he
is Jim's apprentice Jim is those chicks
this portal will lead you to a wizards
tower well you have to compete in some
sort of tournament the winner of which
needs to help you this is really going
to impress home and when we do this I
cannot wait to write to him about it
alright honey if you're excited about it
with honestly a master dark magic would
rather foam and not know all the details
about hey oh man I'd like to leave some
that doesn't heal me but it would be I
mean it would be a personal very nice
thing to do for Jimin and he would I'm
sure reward you I get out all right no
no I'm not allowed to keep anything like
that at ease he specifically said not to
write anything down we're not even
allowed to do anything without four
forms in triplicate right sure the
alternative is we just hang out in this
pocket dimension forever all right you
know I actually have thanks get back to
okay with Nova Condor and I would just
really love to find
was responsible for that yeah as soon as
he is fixed I'm gonna put you guys right
back where you belong
Jim's a good kid all right look he uh
though what would you add he's tense now
has man's level wizard making his way up
so yeah I do
we asked you one question about of Jim
could we create a calm yeah uh Jim dark
magic sir if that's you can you cheap
each each one of you just cheap once do
you get three distinct cheap okay all
right all right yeah
Tom said something the cheap Morse code
for anything yeah hurry up idiot okay
checks out yeah we're off to see wizard
okay thank you
yeah so this has the portal set up as
soon as you step through it it's a sunny
day you're on a dirt road wide dirt road
leading up to a ridiculous tall White
Tower
it's ringed by a wall and you can see
that there's a line of people like going
into this doorway in the wall it's like
a big wooden door that's open and people
are just lined up to get in and above
that you can see there's a sign that
says spectators okay and so you could
you come out onto this pass to write it
to end of this line you can see some
people are just now coming up and
getting into it what would you like to
do he didn't come with us
no no as soon as you step through the
portal what okay uh
did we ask if this was like combat to
the desk we should have asked that oh
let's go find out we'll see well alright
I brandy done concerned yeah
across that bridge when we get to whose
goods bearing like they know where we
are
who's raised a good bearing no you're
not I'm saying I won't know where this
tower is yeah yeah would that be
somebody maybe the lake is good Maps or
like has a good sense of direction why
uses the Stars my entire game is looking
at you and I said it I was just
wondering if you could yeah you know the
nature
yeah I'd help somebody comes up and ask
you dinar
are you live yeah all right behind me
all right get behind or we're
this guy and he gets his whole family
he's obviously dressed he's got a
wizard's robe he's got his kids and his
wife and they all sort of tuck in behind
you yeah we don't wanna be in line we
want to go we need to yeah there's like
a long gap between me and the difference
I just create a crowd for Celina yeah I
know what partha all right usually I
roll a history check yep figure out
where we are 13 there darlin you cannot
discern where you are the the it's
daytime you can't really see any stars
but nothing around you looks especially
noteworthy there's no landmarks or
anything like that it's just a wide-open
field there's this tower that reaches up
it's going through the clouds and it's
ringed by this wall you think that
Wizards sort of like to have their
residents in their own little pockets
sometimes this might not even be
anywhere specific to the Material Plane
we need to find this service entrance
yeah thanks of mention I'm going to ask
the person in line in front of us excuse
me geniu where the competitors go sure
if you're here to be a champion well
championship shows in at a time uh well
I think we've been chosen but um we just
don't know which door to go in Oh
probably that one he points and there's
a smaller door to the left and above it
there's a sign that says champions I'm
going to guess you're right that looks
like the right way out you so very much
you're very welcome and good luck thank
you we are so excited
everybody here we're very excited these
guys no chance me of you guys who the
champions is this to the death you know
obviously last year there wasn't a
winner because they all died okay crazy
is that crazy is this really cool yeah
oh yes thrilling oh yeah yeah I'm rich
spectacle I don't fear Jesse suddenly I
think about how much more of a
percentage I would get just if one
person were to go down yeah in this
we're bad well something about being in
Jim's pocket dimensions we all just
think about when one of them dies we all
get this yeah I'm gonna pair this is
like like the quickening like whistle
you do I get stronger
it's like Highlander so a key comes up
and strip tug on you and he's got a
little note patty
he wants your autograph yeah of course
your your ears down yeah yeah kids love
me and I just scroll it you're gonna die
what hey what is Reza way okay you first
use a piece of chicken throw the
autograph a large smartphone yeah okay
and magic release yeah all right campus
Dorothy story okay yeah anybody in front
yeah oh yeah simple wooden door okay
swear open it yeah yeah it opens call
great all right
sort of a long straight hallway maybe 10
15 feet in and stares down okay so it it
looks like you know it leads down into
some sort of underground well-lit oh
yeah there's torches all along okay walk
in like we own what color I purchase
they are red right now
I'm sorry right now right now I do have
some energy I can change yes you hear a
voice from down the stairs say blue you
have the big annoyed sound championing
uh why hi thank you
you go to champions yeah yeah friend
we're legit told me I'm gonna die I'm
already late
we're here now ready to take our place
in the champion circle you can do it
here yep alright we get down there
Curnow name a tree so down down the
stairs sort of widens out still
underground torches there's a guard
their armor sword he looks at you hey
goes you're not the champion I'll be
like the hell I'm not
but you don't have your champion
medallion the hell I don't
yeah yeah I can do a minor illusion
because I haven't given you your
champion yeah
[Applause]
putting my knife back bak you guys
excited yeah time being champion so and
because the autonomy puts like this
medallion it's a big gold medallion it's
got an eye on it looks really cool very
official
what's it around your neck guys been
been fans of that tournament for a while
totally I guys went around wanna take it
do my sisterís since I was a little
champion you hear the door that you came
in slight like opened up and then slam
shut you hear armored footsteps running
down the stairs here don't let him into
the arena yeah not them
yeah yeah okay sounds like you guys have
somebody that yeah yeah so when we will
just get your way by the way I don't
want yeah hold on thing we should we
should see what this is now at this
point two more guards come around the
corner and they're drawing swords okay
oh okay here in trouble doesn't sound
like business for a champion though yeah
let's get on our way and then we'll just
we'll yeah ah
they both scream and now the shores are
out okay yeah great
alright I think they're talking to you
yeah what did you do what'd you do
what'd you do seriously are you looking
in Georgia oh these guards are now up
with you guys could you guys tiny swords
I just we don't get a lot of
opportunities to meet the champions yeah
before and obviously there's not a lot
of opportunities afterwards oh sure guys
gonna sign these it would be a lot to me
champions don't have time we got to go
make a little sense I totally understand
I wanna mess with you guys before
tournament I'm dinosaurs and I do I've
always got time for a fan that means a
lot to me he signs for us and so when I
sign all your name yeah usually we're so
much more when you're dead that is how
we feel about it whether you know the
value always goes up just that's the way
I work and you look kind of big and slow
so alright good luck
it is holding a key condition wow those
two guards leave this were commiserating
about this awesome sword autograph
session that they just had the first
cards is her rights you've got your
medallions
I think we're ready to teleport you guys
to the arena you any question ice you
can give us about yes
yeah absolute amp Ian's come through
here I've been doing this a long time
it's totally cool to be nervous oh yeah
tips let's see you know got to be quick
you got to have the reflexes um yeah you
know yeah we're gonna have cable in my
house growing up so I don't know what
this is I'm a first time I mean you know
you're gonna love it the most what is it
it's the tournament man yeah I don't
want to spoil the surprise it's yeah but
you know no you're gonna like it the
most right guys oh right yeah the love
it he said I believe oh my god you're in
her tree if you survive I guarantee
you're going to be in the seats next
year watching this hmm
and we can't wait to ride that I say he
sort of learns and guides you towards
what looks like a big summoning circle
he says each of you guys in order to
have you step onto the circle you're
going to be teleported into the arena
and then from there I make you kind of
know what to do at that point no I just
said and done ourselves and just be the
way told you with my words thank you
only go first all right Rosie
yeah so you step up onto the portal into
the circle yeah you can feel yourself
being teleported you're sort of lifted
up into the air and and when you appear
in this new area you're on a raise Dyess
with a sort of ramp that leads down and
you are lifted you're rising up above it
and magical sort of tendrils are weaving
all around you and after a couple
seconds you realize that they're
actually weaving a little cart and it's
got four wheels and it looks something
like this haha Oh fancy wood paneling
down the side there's a car seat in the
back and it sets down onto the Dyess and
you sort of roll down the ramp and you
can see that your what looks like a
checkered line and you and your cart
automatically stops you there okay who
would like to go through next I was
where did she go what happened she's in
the arena now how do i boy otherwise in
it's great in here we don't worry about
it tell me your part walnut so you feel
the same thing as you look down you can
see sort of wooden twigs and stuff that
leaves sprout off of the end here within
weasels form and we're in you're in this
little tiny wooden cart that rolls down
the ramp you actually notice down at the
bottom where the little pebbles are this
is a squirrel down there nibbling on an
acorn come on
hey buddy I try not to kill you today
we're head was going through next even I
I showed okay now say no yes yes risen
you step through the portal and you can
feel that tentacles
sort of reaching down out of your body
so as a dream again and and and they
they erupted from the body they they
pull you along rather than having wheels
driven by this massive writhing
tentacles oh yeah this is the best on
denier you're the only one left
well yeah all right I guess I gotta go
through I I gotta go this guy I'm like I
am like what give me he'll give me a
little something here it's something
like never seen before all right if I
survive this I'm gonna come back here
I'm going to kill you you go through the
portal pretty normal what looks like a
little cart appears around you and you
look down and you can see that they're
all the little carts and there's what
obviously is some sort of race setup and
I this is [ __ ] and you punch your
legs through the bottom of the cart
and you hoist it up around your waist
you know I'm faster than a car accurate
Oh God the leg ease the my leg you see
stick the light there you are down in a
very dark done part you can see the path
before you is very dimly lit and you
hear magical voice amplified through
this dungeon say prepare yourselves for
wizard card
I don't I don't play Dungeons and
Dragons like normal people I guess what
I've done is I've in a game that uses
sometimes dragons rules to recreate a
game like you've never seen before
yeah I remember you've never seen
anything like this no I guarantee it
what the [ __ ] have you done this is what
I do great season
like I hope so cuz I work really hard on
it yeah now I'm going to explain some
very basic rules to you because I'm some
very big never played anything like this
on your turn go fast you want to go as
fast as you can
your speed is your character speed + 1
d6 ok so divide your speed by 5 to
figure out how many spaces you get to
move ok well it should be easy and
you're going to your speed is going to
be that plus a decent yep I'm going to
disobey everyone keep everyone guys
normal right 35 you cannot move
diagonally ok and you cannot move
through other racers ok
if you pass over one of these question
marks mm-hmm you will draw a weapon
spell ok if you are in 1st through 3rd
place if you are in last place when you
pass over one you will draw from this
stack which is heavily weighted to get
you out of last place man you even did
the rubber banding I don't know what
you're talking I know each of you has a
little card yeah yeah on it you see that
you have an AC of 14 everybody has the
same Kart AC and you have a Kart power
that is unique to each of you so why we
go around the table you can read your
Kart power and I'll break it down for
you if you have any questions walnut
vine whip once per turn you may swap
places with a player within 3 spaces of
you watch your head Wow
Big Daddy you may move through other
racers when you do their move back one
space
nobody else can move through but you've
got a special cart power lets you go
right through people tip you out of my
way
sorry Rosie shadow step once per turn
you may move one space
really yeah so that's very helpful for
cutting corners getting around people
super useful highways RIS I have arcane
knowledge my hand sizes too when I would
draw a card draw up to two normally you
guys can only have one spell at a time
Chris just to have two spells that's
good yeah but on your turn you get to
move and you can action which is playing
a spell or making some other kind of
check there's things to explore in this
dungeon and also if you guys have ideas
for how you want to use these powers
sure do let me know and I will
adjudicate them on a surface by case
basis all right now ideally we're going
to do three laps and roll for initiative
okay Oh believe me I'm in front okay oh
so what we got here fifteen holy moly
five whoa she will not hit cars bottom
well one time I did well one time yeah
I've been driving the cart the whole
time anyway we have nothing expecting oh
that does be fifteen it's more he is the
only time I ever go first
I always be related would you have a
relax with three just gonna take me
[ __ ] really three bad boys all right so
now okay
oh but on you back so I should start
like a bunch of spacing ahead uh no you
guys so right there
donor your speed is what six plus a v6
so roll a d6 your speech thirty huh /
five like alright yeah I'd only thing
about math but I trust him
sounds ever Wow a huge box how did you
manage neither role I'm sorry go ahead
I'm excited let's find that I've got
Jerry normally friendlies you know yeah
yeah I say I've got a real dead and
you're not it okay I understand dad yeah
when I'm talking you like
okay doing ice cream or you've got nine
spaces total to move uh what
six plus four 6 plus 4 is 10 yeah okay
yeah you've got 10 spaces so luckily I
got a bonus one thank you all right yeah
yeah hey hey can we get some of those
like World War 2 like those little treat
yeah yeah that was one two three four
five six seven eight nine ten you passed
you the thingy oh yeah you got your
thanks you get your card
what are you guys referencing looks like
magic not oh yeah you don't have to show
that to anybody with a woman and they
should be very self-explanatory even
though you've never played a game like
this before I haven't I don't know it's
wildly unique yes you can play it right
now if you want or you can hang on till
you can hold one stone no I'm gonna hold
my stone
yeah hold yourself that's fair I have no
problem with you holding your spell
what's hang on do it then hang on to it
okay when are what else can we do on a
turn sorry did you say to me like mm-hmm
okay
there's some crosstalk happening I'm not
gonna call out who's doing it I didn't
my turn but it needs to be it needs to
be taken down alright so if I can't talk
on my turn what do I talk you don't ever
get to go okay all right Rosie indeed
all right it's my role and here at home
I got a seven plus three okay also a
times that's a million here we go and
you can't stop and grab your card and
then finish your move oh goody I know
you think they're just cool did you
throw him yeah what is that I wonder can
you tell me not without you making up
some kind of chick if you have any
question as you draw a card let me know
okay okay um liquid I do have lots of
questions yeah you I will get to it
we'll go guys with me my guess is what
happens when walnut pie the seven leave
my d6 roll
eleven you want some help I do I can
reach a previous a one jewelry for you
just do the thing for me you just want
to sidle up next to dinar here I do what
up hey B yes okay
would you get it I don't know huh
yeah but not least to thrist but least
though I really yeah I live in Amman
probably not most so it's going to be a
nine for me man that right yeah cuz I
was on that yeah you're one up all right
if you get some the large file oh yeah
you were last place I'm sorry okay
absolutely
alright so any go to look at the top of
92 I didn't leave that one yeah a
cheater
are you happy now yeah you have your our
campaign or anything you get you take -
yeah yeah yeah maybe should have been
nice to me I could gone your a sooner
your stepdad favorite I see you've got
those any more tender yeah you can play
one of them you only play one per Carter
look okay okay um gonna see how this
goes just yeah okay that's sure good
then we're background to janar so what
else can we do on our turn sorry you can
make chicks so you're not anywhere near
doesn't enough this statue but once you
get within range I would absolutely make
a check - okay destiny strange - Jill
over here me and and then we get to do
one action actions per turn
yep card is an action checking
investigating is an action I'm going to
do it three times yeah oh it's a Rollie
so if that's the case then may I as my
action just like I want to observe like
the contours of this room is it just
like a tunnel it is a tunnel
yeah they're like spectators around or
there's no you're not sure you know that
there are people watching but it must
not be physically must not be physically
present okay okay
that just looks like regular stone and
all that okay I guess that's fine a
little dot some little I'm going to do
this and then roll
gonna do that in and move yeah yes that
works all right I'm going to do three of
them yeah so you can see what I do to
have as Denar drove through that
question mark three green orbs of flame
appeared around him and are spinning
orbs of wagon plane plane plane plane or
yeah the green ones the cards called
green flame or so
I mean I'm something times three times
three would you want to hit all of us
everybody yeah do it roll so range ten
attack plus six to hit so just D 20 plus
six yeah and everybody has a ACU for
camp yeah okay all right it's easy-peasy
grab it
well call out who we are not again huh
Chris no wait I definitely wanna hit you
yep I think ya okay so here is Miss
Catherine sweetness lady yeah I am a
last-place who's this this is any wallet
on it
you're on Simon 13 wow do that missed by
one weird this is Krista if you describe
to me what your green ball does as it
hits her I will give you that one Wow
Wow how I would deflect yeah what does
it look like you're letting off this
ball of green energy so and it's it was
gonna miss her yeah I'm driving so I'm
kind of kicking these because I I don't
have wheels so I'm kind of running and
Kay yeah and I'm kicking the ball to
people and I kick it at her cart and
then when it wobbles over it gets like I
get like a ricochet like it falls short
Donna grab short pass five yards if ever
you're down down up yeah yeah okay with
you yeah we're gonna take it - which
bases oh it's really not yeah yep two
three and this one's for you
sweet boy this could close and BAM
that's a hit - nice three three
yeah okay and then oh your cord to the
discard okay look I want to be in less
and then I get to roll and you know what
were the rules on movement and can't
move I am you cannot move diagonal okay
you're the only person Rosie can one so
I'm just stuck on this
oh I guess like once I get in here I can
sneak okay that's not a great roll no
limit five six
okay we can't we can't take diagonals
nut but Rosie can once per turn
okay and when she takes a diagonal I
want you guys to know she's going up on
two wheels I got it oh yeah yeah so when
you come around this corner now right
you can see that it's a straight shot
down to this wide room at the end and in
the center of it there is a large stone
Dyess with a statue on top of what looks
like one of these carts sort of it
tipped and an eraser behind the wheel
it's all it's all white marble just
beautiful okay can I you already did an
action card to share with auntie hamster
Jaime yep Rosie okay hmm for I guess for
my action
kind of like what consisted I'd like to
perceive see if I can perceive any
shortcuts that may not be visible just
to the naked eye by looking yeah look do
I can I kind of use my perception role
to like Hydro Thunder go through the
waterfall kind of thing I see what
you're saying yeah yeah you don't see
anything in your immediate vicinity that
is a secret passage or a shortcut of any
custom okay all right well keep that
spirit alive anyway all right so it's a
good thinking thank you all right that's
the 12 that's a big role he will help
help in 2 3 4 5 6 7
no oh no Tim you're late yeah yeah 8 9
10 11 12 the other yeah nice
you can only have one card a time oh
geez joy can I look at him both no no oh
geez oh geez leave okay all right
Oh see but you can hold on without
that's what makes Christmas power so
cool suspect yeah okay okay
Rosie's done yes unless you want to are
you starting your turn with action hello
Walnut great and don't forget your vine
whip oh I know
again in these towers up here too we can
figure out how those work if you have
good ideas oh sorry
some people know I thought about her you
didn't know okay and then also I would
like to use red flame or an auto hit to
make somebody back three spaces I had
this idea where there red flames hit
like they track yeah but the green ones
don't I don't know where I come up with
I don't know where I call them out
fascination dairy game design yeah so
the flavor of this is I come around the
corner and I'm like clearly really
hating everything and then I see Dan are
and I knew I know he took a shot at me
and then I wait I'm like ha ha ha ha ha
and then as I pass I must go suck on
some others are breaking at me yeah I
got real excited
no that was my special way yeah I know
I'm just looking at this oh hey mind if
you know where it's pretentious mind
your business
alright everyone go to hang three yeah I
would go back now you go back that way
yeah you go back to where you can't get
where you Jane uh all right walnut you
done I'm done okay cthe RIS you are
currently in last place you have to
spells though just where I want to be
what could those be well I can only use
one of them you can only use one of them
mister yeah that's which is fine thank
you
you gotta love it I do I do
let me go ahead and do burn one of these
first which is a blue flame Lord Oh blue
flame Lord above target auto hits a
first plane really yeah which right now
is roni means how far back is it's
really thanks it's really you guys to
see this blue flame snake between you
shoot around the corner and then you
hear rosy painful yeah yeah the worst
movement will not trigger the spell
effect okay
that would have been cool okay with that
done
hey let me see what I get got that's 6
plus 5 so that's good that's a given one
two three four five six six need
somewhere to go seven eight nine and 11
after a go and then I race so am I am I
still last them I guess no no all right
last yeah okay so then I would draw one
from that you didn't want Oro that's
right
I thought it for some reason I can try
cheater oh well maybe you get up daddy
nicely all you wanted I guess I
accidentally took a you're the one that
got the plus one I guess her I don't
remember that
oh oh so discard your blue flame over it
as a rare as a bonus action yeah I'm
going to reach out with my mind to
everybody else just saying we actually
gonna do this thing go away through it
I'm gonna team up and try to break
through walls or what where is this I I
say eat my dust
yeah shouldn't eat all of the [ __ ] I
shouldn't you've asked that before you
hit Rosie with your blue flame yeah I
got to blow our cover
dude still first place we're getting
that hang out you hear dial tone yeah
prank caller prank caller whoo I don't
know you where you guys like go back to
daughter alright my turn
you need to play catch-up here mustard
my friend with what what is that foreign
ten several hand remember you can go
through people too oh no my friend three
yup four five six seven one sound like
that that was seven eight nine ten and
draw your card it is why didn't you look
at what we see in you then have to be
Reena yeah everybody around statue hmm
and I want to observe this okay make me
uh make me history check you want to see
who if you recognize it or I want to see
what I want to get what can I say you
want to make a statue what's your deal
uh yeah history okay works just well
read persuade yeah I said I can i uh
cyberbully it alright plus two
so for all right I like marble you can
tell that it's made of stone and it
depicts some sort of racecar driver
yeah second pal yeah it is a cool ass
statue
you also know that I imagine it's me
yeah that was your action Rosie
okay my turn
yes uh I'm gonna do a I'm going to cast
me a lightning bolt on Chris ristretto
lightning bolt hits everybody Oh target
is all and you move all your spell they
get to make a saving throw this is a
dexterity 14 yeah I don't have anything
else but how much do we move back or is
it you just blew those girls in your
hole I find out you're not holding a
spell right max right yeah all right now
don't worry about it and then roll
frisky 1411 what's your next plan for
honor oh good question
come on Dexter it still didn't propose
to you as a discard your spell card
yourself
mine was a 9 right when it saw what it
was another another blue flame or mine
was a 9 I lost mine Hey okay okay fine
so lightning strikes all the other
racers except walnut because want and I
blow your kiss finish this okay and then
I'm going across the line again um
that's yeah absolutely I can trigger it
out of here all right move me 12 yeah
just in a straight line
ah two three and then you wanna go the
diagonal she can go through 30 I gotta
go
you can diagonally up two three four no
day I go me look at you one diagonal six
seven eight nine ten eleven I'm gonna do
it 12 12
oh yeah 12 I'm sorry that's like a some
light cycles yeah okay
don't spur turning okay if it was one
for a little and I fiddled with once per
lap powers but they were kind of hard to
remember if you had it in a box eight it
go I'm sorry
all right breaking all the immersion of
the motto Rosie you had an action and a
move so you're good yep and you're in
first place right now
walnut hoorah let's see I'm sorry
Rosie's you come around this corner you
can see ahead of you the spell strip on
the ground these sort of purple glowing
schedules yes but behind them you can
see a larger blue sigil on the ground
that is also glowing okay but it seems
to be right up against the wall right in
the corner there I'm only playing em
right still hot um okay so I can go nine
one two three four five six seven eight
why um oh then I guess like this and
then for my action I would like to UM
you can see the statue I can see the
statue um I guess I should perceive it
okay yeah I want to inspect it what we
have to do history without it uh you
tell me what kind of check you want to
make history is a good one you see
statues I guess I mean I'd love to just
do a reception what if I make a statue
all to dedicated what's your plus two
statues yeah I mean you may have a point
in statuary now um you make an argument
for perceptions yeah why not why not
just a procession I can let you proceed
the [ __ ] and I was alive a thirty year
roll oh yeah so you you come around this
corner and you can see the statue and
it's like a zoom focus boom right on the
bronze plaque at the bottom of it and it
says a buddy scorch racer one nine two
two three eight seven right and as you
look up at him you can see that you know
it's made of stone but you you can see
him wink yeah and you've gained the
racers boom Oh which means you may look
at the top two cards and pick one Oh
forever
yes no for now it'll temporarily
increase your hand size
um okay and then what do I get to put
the other one back on the bottom so for
but for a brief moment I have to yeah
until you decide to use one but you are
using action mister I do I'm more I just
don't want you to cheat like I know you
like - that's sir alright and now that
you look at it again you can't imagine
how he possibly could have moved your
wing because it's obviously marble yeah
but you feel energized next discuss is I
call out Toby this is a farce this is a
game they have work to be doing did I
want there's a cool car best car if
that's what we're trying to determine
either the best car let's talk to more
dragons yeah you're allowed you look at
the your car you can see you in front of
it
red lights sort of flash out in either
direction - right I in school Oh buddy I
didn't know you were alive oh yeah keeps
a car is that the winning head kid no
yeah and he says one more time we can do
this if you like slash out of here I
believe me I don't no one who's ever
believed it um I like my Rick like if I
had a hat I'd push it forward see your
dick your bonnet is your son up and it's
true yeah I tie it a little tighter I'm
gonna do the move for though yeah I got
nothing on my hand
Kevin Olivia thank you okay so simple
why won't movie night that's good roll
don't count with me
I'm sorry for livin it up but I was
saying the same number six seven eight
nine yeah I'm gonna do that you get when
you get laughing laughing yeah all right
I did it I get to see I didn't have with
everything your hands your anything
Leslie's noxious oh I guess your
inability to race is paying off great
didn't you can play one of them if you
like maybe I will
maybe I'll do just that sure all right
I don't want to alarm you know I just I
didn't have that I didn't do an action
that's right I know you have another
market this is ridiculous we had whoa me
and kit we're gonna make it to the end
red flame orb times 300 real them do
auto hit yes I do
knowing three spaces back but who all of
us
yes everybody gets one well I'm I love
to just hammer one you could ever what
we're definitely not unless I'm gonna
sprinkle Jeff it's you nice yeah really
mess up Rosie if you want to do three on
two literally could really mess me I
want actually really gather this yeah
that's if you cheat like that but you
like my alright good turn castration
good job all right
it's another site if I got her okay
another ten so you're starting your turn
in a leg one okay exam yeah yeah guide
ways math now you know what I'm gonna go
take one now wat take 100 you're last
oh yeah it's a good poker face
one two so next time you are just making
sure the movement into it no card but
starting a channel you five six seven
eight nine quick pull ahead
the car's name is Katherine I was trying
to think of a name you said kid hasn't
wanted it so it has to be yeah there was
one there um yeah I on the letter I'm
gonna hang onto it
I want to perceive them okay statue you
perceive you can history whatever you
tell me what you're best at
actually history is better than
perception yep 10/10 you what are you
you cannot be here to stand out on me
your secrets
this is the greatest riddle I've ever
seen
that was dinar Rosie so Dan our just
screwed around the corner and past you
probably gave you a hand signal on the
way by what you avoid it rude yeah I
understand the throw is that it that
must be not to dragon painful to echo
dragon boy yet happy
it's dubs asking all the time wow yeah
okay well I'm going to try to pursue
this thing - I'm I have a pretty good
history but I'm actually better at
intimidation the statues got a high will
I will tell you that did you finish the
shuttle does marble yeah
all right history m3p oh yeah absolutely
hell yeah this is very clearly a statue
of the Scorch one of the greatest kart
racers who ever win 197 to 387 exactly
and he looks down at you recognizes that
you recognize him mad respect gives you
a wink and you get to pick two cards
from the top which is one you can't
figure out like why it is happening with
this statue that's the best statue you
guys I don't care ah keep one you asked
me to get your question like this one is
just superior oh absolutely it is all
right if this were to be in some sort of
video game context you would definitely
want be how you wanted me how many men
in this family I don't know how it
wouldn't be modeled at all but yeah okay
and then you are education you got oh
okay mmm
gonna be Sidney the balls 12 mm what a
minute
one two three what's our live in Vegas
four people seven times I'm taking back
a record nine and you eleven twelve
okay you drive into the the seal and you
can feel that it's it's some sort of
trigger but you don't know exactly what
for okay hmm you'll need to inspect it
further okay which I can't do right now
now right now come here I take an action
duh that was Rosie walnut' so I can't
take me cuz I already have them mm-hmm I
can't swap I just know physically can't
take it cannot take any more else stupid
hey who made it who made this car behind
mrs. angry as you are brilliant I'm
going on board game geek who put you in
that right in a bad review so unbalanced
I was like it was made in a week so I
really want to get back to the concert I
really want to get back to it my
girlfriend I've been thrown into this I
have to do this thing with the box of
chickens one was just like
so mad at this point and then on top of
that she ripped a she's in last place
yes she is and now I'd like to use
forest friends who put a swarm of bats
to just get up in everybody's face oh if
I could cause them to you veer off like
yeah basically you I'm in a cloud of
bats to come through the whole dungeon
just like oh yeah just like full blast
bats just a circle through the port
after my favorite backstory so for
everybody on everybody's next turn you
can tell me remember this yeah I'm gonna
take away the modifying d6 you'll just
get your basic yeah thank you shadow
council yes you have to take away one of
my things on the magic thing oh yeah I
do this is so high-tech over here oh you
had two of them we saw one left and she
had three don't tell you that I three
what oh I did the wrong thing
Wayne advantage yeah okay this is so
fancy gangs how could we use advantage
every role article Nick it is yeah I got
walnuts down to two okay public oh yeah
they're alright yeah you want to use
your vanish to reroll okay great good
could you burn all of Jerry's advantages
even do i all right that was no that was
walnut now no d6 are you complete are
you all done complete oh you need to
move right yeah you are you are playing
a game I don't think that you are
affected by your my own barkeeper is no
that's right there's a pocket around you
know I see them and I go key please do
something about this and their life like
in Batman when they're all just like
spinning around we got yeah yeah yeah
you just told ovoid you yeah one two
three four five one two three four five
six seven and then back in the mix
walnut thank grass the cave hi Maya
oh is it really yeah yeah don't hold
back the home line uh Chris nice very
tightly to me and my buddy tight race
anybody's race sup a little turbo boost
almost am i right
mostly frozen face I yeah let's see
oh wait I'm sitting on your net so I
will get up I want everybody to see this
view bad camera I didn't wear these
pants today so nobody would see them
when I hang on to this guy
don't roll let's just move oh well you
have no wrong you have no roll you just
get your base moment as a bad guy going
like this the whole [ __ ] time but I
love bat I it's in our back like I see
the only genetics fat story oh okay well
they're not it in that case I will be
taking my full regular mo just your
normal of six spaces
you go ahead yeah we already know okay I
wanna see okay now we'll do this four
five six I aim to get nice and tight all
right looks good we'll take a look at
that thank you good tank now why would I
care it's just a statue on camera then
okay is absurd dinar so Chris just came
up right behind you yeah with his
leering creepy eyes yeah and you can see
wala in front of you with this tiny
squirrel hanging off the back just for
dear life ah that Nixon ah alright fine
red flame orb oh no come on
and we're gonna go Auto hit one two
three Auto hit one oh yeah I'll hit one
two three yeah yeah yeah oh boy howdy
that was back over here my golly gee one
two three four five statue I love you
back watch you just made yourself an
enemy my friend IO that is talking all
that chirping about being the first
place I can't even say a penny arcade
joke before you do I just say you've
made the enemy of the birds I read one
or two yeah you good yeah you pretty
good yeah I did my action kept looks I
mean uh [ __ ] you just lay this card on
the track it's difficult ring that oh
yeah you didn't you really played D&amp;D
right so
in old school also a fourth edition
difficult terrain meant it took two
that's basically to move through that
space so you can drop that card that
mature magic banana peel yeah Matt as
well just tell her yeah no not this turn
not this turn though no thanks tell us
what you got though really
you'll see it soon enough all right I
can only catch one spell for timing
correct yeah well then I'm gonna do a
red flame war on Bernard hmm he deserves
it just one just mi mi mus play second
ship right now are you well you won't be
when you go through the right yeah I'm
just wondering how you would I would say
you are in less well I think Chris is in
last place
okay yeah I see how you would measure
yeah right your back further on the
track that way yeah I guess he'll okay
[Music]
two three four five six you go Joe oh
you already have a car wreck oh [ __ ] -
you're good uh walnut it's me okay so I
see the guys around me and then I sit
Robin is racing
Robin is racing there you go I said that
accrues I'm glass and I've seen movies
uh and then I throw down a shock wave
which is the close first one and I do a
+62 hit and the damages to space so I
start with we weren't hit first soon our
dinner first
mm-hmm okay hmm oh you can't desert and
then do you feel great with maintain the
hecka hit it
alright okay and then I'm going to hover
all and I want to use my advantage on
this roll okay which I have I do so
you're going to roll two dice and take
the best one I am so we're moving one of
your advantage roll that was a four not
bad spending a while shoot then I get
ten of these bad boys right one two
three four five six
you can also see this blue schedule now
but she did the action all right
yeah she didn't care about magic yes
okay oh this is a discard and that was
my turn all right Chris thank how much
of a I don't have any line of sight can
I do a check on that sigil yeah
absolutely
you can shave from my yard all right
Arkana what do you want to do let me do
in our camp okay if I may yeah all right
I guess is that a roll yeah as 14:14 is
good no yeah you recognize that this is
a sort of magical activator and that it
probably opens up a secret passageway
I keep that now and now is now that you
understand its workings you believe that
were you to drive sort of into it it
would do work for you but only France
only for him but right now I but I want
to role play it like the car told me
it's like yes I trust you in this you
see that so Joe what I've never seen
that before yeah take moving that buddy
drive right into that wall it's you mean
Michael still many me right one let's do
it
I open my my clothes a little bit to the
chest air system yeah nice oh yeah like
- yeah just - - just - like this white
would you I don't want to are you going
yeah let's hit it
I might feel like we're gonna keep
talking about Jim Miller that's are gone
now I'll get the chest hair talk silent
really smart I roll out numbers okay uh
we left your folks yeah it might be to
the tables on a fine it's gonna be ten
so let's move me one two three okay now
pour - it's going okay and then I heard
Niall asked I'll do the other way uh
yeah you have one car I have one okay
I'm gonna wasn't last we started turn
does that matter
yes if you're in last when you cross you
the plane okay okay so I'll get it all
right yeah okay you want though could
you have one already
well I'll drop it before I do let's talk
what really roll one two three four
drop a banana five magic banana peel
six seven eight and you mean though tell
me about the metal this is our didn't
you just we're not helping them the car
now takes up these four spaces okay and
they're difficult terrain so if you move
into them you be going one two three
four five oh six seven it costs more to
move through those spaces as soon as
it's hit as soon as somebody moves
through it it goes away
okay well so you're just gonna leave
that there on the track nice did you
take an action I guess you did you
investigated this deal yep and you know
how it works now yes
yeah but and I did all mine so it's
who's after me it's Rosie Rosie okay I
want to investigate this a deal um but I
don't have good Arkana
we used inside dad oh it has to be our
can well can't you make me a perception
check okay garbage day said no way I'm
gonna need the bans on this too okay
yeah so that's what good thing
Big Mike won a yeah so looking now back
it's over the central you can see the
wall behind it is is in shadow but where
you thought it was stone you can
actually see that it really is just
shadow
there's nothing material there and you
believe that were you to drive into it
you would probably just keep continuing
through some sort of passage excellent
if you don't mind me jumping on top here
I'm going to role play it such that my
car told you okay that's good secret
wall oh god what found your car felt bad
sweets I'm in last place
no okay she's a Jill over there let me
tell you about it good long look at that
one alright so I know if it's a glyph
for sigil to figure that out digital
unique so it's definitely said Jill yeah
okay um so I'm just going to do my
normal movement and just go straight on
through yeah well should happen okay
that's ten whoo so that's one two you're
destroyed your character dies you don't
realize came up
wah-wah-wah-wah four five six
and you guys just saw Rosie drive
straight to home Oh vanish and vanish
eight nine Tests 31% she'd be wrecked
she clips into the wall yeah peace out
and he just drive straight of the
shadows that was Rosie walnut ah yeah oh
my god
is this passage now available firmly
well they saw you drive into the wall
and not die right well I know that yet
till I turn this corner yeah I see a
walnut doesn't know that I'll do my move
actually didn't even see you drive into
the thing so I would not even know it
exists you come around and great good
yeah yeah so you want to get Ivan seven
to three left four five one you show you
three four five six seven oh well yeah
and you need a card I know yeah we
already have one um and then I look at
Rosie I go ahead amazing yeah it's a
second ago she was behind you I have my
ways and then I go apparently you should
know better than to cheat and I use a
more oh let's say was I do that DC
gesture was plus six seventeen yeah yup
I see for sure so you go back three
spaces one you nobody with a nut I
thought we were friends
I know I've got a miss with a nut just
walnut when you come around the corner
here you can smell like a raw sewage
coming from around the corner and you
can hear sort of a gurgling sound how
could this get ahead of me I'm not Wow
or Footwear
that's not good sorry bud but you guys
are supposed to be friends fresh not on
the quarries yeah
all right Chris you know how the seal
works and you saw Rosie drive into the
wall yeah obliterated I don't want to
beat that pace
no instead of doing that powered by
shadow no thing is nice dry seems like
something you'd because true what do I
want to do here now we're going to do
this one uh so I friend Dena I'm gonna
do shockwave was my right knock now I'm
going to shock his wave +6 to hit let's
try it oh it's a hot hit is a huh gang
bang tune-up one to one that sounds been
moved is not going to walk through yeah
that's a terrible move alright for me
now whatever I roll I'm going to try it
I'm going to backtrack and get in the
you wanna gain to the secondary I have
when I get roll out 11 so get me do I go
1 2 and now it's 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 you can
draw one because you only have one your
handle that's true we're going to burn
this one or I think cuz then we're gonna
lunge up to this oh you're not I'm not
like that one yeah where we at 9 10 11
10 yeah let's do it like 11 or now that
yes just 11 I love yes there we are
let's go I'd better like this better
like this I don't know I'm glad that's
it alright and you've got two cards you
use an action so back to dinar times
right and you saw a fish you three yeah
so that is seven and then I'll go this
distance defense Benson in an efficient
sense different buildings are how's that
do what to do six spaces to movement
anyway I can move through racers any
when I move through moves back to ha so
they move back free for you haha so
that's six 12 13 total one two three you
regret five go me out here 7 8 9 10 11
12 13 right on the mattress goes back
three one two three two three perfect
okay uh and I went through the question
mark but you were not I was not last
place cuz no you're right okay now
that's that question mark that I moved
back through a mound behind board move
million when you go through it yeah okay
asking man nice nice all right that was
- now Rosie hey you guys are all just
clustered up right here yeah ma you sure
don't start with me don't act like we're
friends nut okay
wow this is the dynamic so ten was
already yeah right well you also really
okay the wizard kart Cup is on the line
we're both we're all very competitive
yeah I'm going to do a quick red flame
orb on you your ass okay so that'll
touch a factory speed up you want to go
back oh right in front one two three
yeah that works
got you yeah I'm just a big old very low
okay then you do my movement which is
gonna be terrible seven plus one that's
plenty of - yep I got you listen ending
thank you
I feel healthier with this game look
actually I'm standing up and doing some
words yeah give that calisthenics oh
yeah nope yeah okay so now when you come
around the corner you can see that
there's this trough of sewage flowing
through the center of the dungeon here
and it disappears into a grate in the
floor here you believe that were you to
try and drive through it it would be
difficult
yeah and probably take maybe twice as
many spaces to move through hmm looks
like difficult terrain over there maybe
and it smells horrible
it smells really really bad okay this is
undeterred I'm gonna go right through
all right in that stage I mean uh all
right that was rosy and yeah
walnut yet don't forget your difference
of your screens so I can summon small
animals right Lulu huh maybe something
that like sewers like oh I know think
about sea turtles yeah seven boys you've
got four sea turtles
um okay so II know what you're doing
here I would like to go a lot of dragon
boy in front of you I do I have a lot of
Dragonborn in front of me um so do I get
this as a bone
section or is this my action that's a
bonus section so I'm going to do that
can you saw me with dinner
vine whip yeah now I don't have that
animal channel command and then I would
like to use forest friends to summon
sewer rats
anyone from the burbs no are scary big
rats okay and I want to ask them to grab
the tail end of my vine whip and see if
they'll pull me like a lead and get any
kind of bonuses Oh what like I will let
you treat that as normal train sweets of
the sewage yeah she's being pulled
through like like they're lucky I did
yeah I did arrived via I will get there
but [ __ ] but as they run it's just
sprang up sewage that's all over you man
yeah I don't go oh what is Brahma gonna
think of me now yeah smells that is
liquid but then there's chunks in it
which you're weird
no no chunk of what China that's the
question yeah roll gave me an organic
shape I've seen a [ __ ]
eight nine yeah and I'm in the slap your
and up you're in the mix flip-flopping
away or if he gives you this look more
is good
I love the slop I was born in the flat
yeah you're merely adopted by it
Chris alright let's see what my options
are here no it's not worth it no wait
that one might be I don't even know who
is what the situation is in the front
because I can't see if you can't see
around the corner but I do a blue flame
Oh Oh as soon as you get in the first
place isn't that the way in horrible
however I always seem to go back three
kind of get you one filled a bumpy line
three okay with that let me get this
over there let's move Wow hooray I agree
roll I'll help you Evan that's only one
scene all about the last three please
card oh yeah thank you for
survive
x7 God we cannot get out of this
collector yeah well designed for as
unbalanced as it is I'm surprised
they're so close to each other oh well
girl endgame well nothing good I had a
lot of fun fun it'll be available never
yeah all right three nine
I can help you where do you want to go
just bulrush simple I'm more like
bowling pins I was debating whether it's
worth going back and getting a car you
get beer over and then come back and
take that little bro first place a fire
in your mind you know yeah well I'm
gonna do that anyway yeah lightning bolt
so everyone loses their cards well they
have to they have a saving throw
oh yeah I'm sorry savings girl oh look
what a car no card think about 14 you
should roll for each card it will
correct out the Dex Dex okay well then I
not know unless you have some other way
of avoiding lightning oh please view
that's not that Wow's in the first place
yeah so I left this morning yeah okay
getting a twinkle in the round news
about girls it's funny I think it was
another cellphone like a wasn't the
service the crappy hotel piece a tape on
them okay nice classy it's like a real
games yeah I lost my oh oh you lost
wizard boost oh now we'll never know
what it is alright no yeah I'm gonna
play one two three four five six which
one I guess I just got a pound minute
gosh you're a seven eight nine yeah okay
put him in the poop he goes in the poop
chute put enough in the poop your
shipment Robins racing alright shipments
it is I came up with me Rosie it is
Rosie
so dinar just blew through you sure
blunderer knocked you into walnut is
water not into that I just kind of I can
only go diagonal once right I can't go
woot-woot
you can just go Boop yeah yeah let go
Boop but then you have another for the
Canopus yeah the only other booth guess
loudly but you can minimize your time in
the slop get sloppy grandma grandma man
I gotta play like that I don't like that
multi-angle no amazing angle I'll be
grandma seven male for today's what I
have well that's like 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9
point whoa whoa wowie Zowie hard alright
Oh your close-up that you can see that
there's sort of a raised platform here
in the middle large room and it's
surrounded by a blue shimmering
forcefield okay and inside of it is a
wizard working very diligently at a desk
that's all you can really make out can I
can I use action on him was I'm action
action yeah what do I do yeah yeah um
can I uh
timid ate him good you hear me alright
yeah something something I'm seen with
him oh yeah that's that 24 320 23 yeah
so he hears you yeah yeah he does okay
and he looks at this is oh I didn't
realize you were here already he starts
going through a scroll I'm very fast he
finds bring us yes yes this should do
the trick
and you can see that two big balls of
fire erupted on either side of his
little room here and they start slowly
spinning around this chamber no and they
are super difficult terrain so it's like
one two three four I said oh my god
right now they're right there but
they're gonna move that sucked
yeah nice she left him alone okay don't
work with Wizards meant to do that
uh next is walnut it me hmm I can just
go right through the floppy
you got your rat cord still yeah to a
rat
I know when movie just ate right you too
sloppy
one two three four five six seven eight
done and then I get a card he's not boys
and you are just coated in sewage now
that's completely 100% fine preferable
finally um can I try so I see that
there's the wizard in there and he did
that thing yep um can I just can I can I
just try to persuade him like hey buddy
turn off the way haha right yeah yeah
because you can be ready when intimidate
or what are you trying to do hours well
I want to try and um well yeah I don't
have a bonus on either show it doesn't
matter and this is just shot in the dark
said I want to use my okay my thing but
yeah I'm trying to intimidate him and
let's just maybe see it for my bedroll
tornado Greyson be less though everyone
just hurling insults disguise
you know our fireballs no no my job
alright I'll persuade him I'll go okay
great
coming through just turn it off one
second common through buddy nevermind
that's not that would work yeah want to
flip them off the squirrel flips him off
Wow what do I need older foot care if
you got rounded this corner yet no so I
know what's a wait are you here here
everyone failing I think I'm in the
front there young yeah I'm pretty sure
I'm probably probably there thank you
thank you bright quick frame yeah I'm
doing that order but okay let's open it
yeah already he's got the trophy right
you should be at home
seven-thirds out of here alright
everybody oh man he's rolled like an you
have an advantage and Chris don't you
have an advantage you have an advantage
when I lie you advantages I'd love to
use it but do it now you have none okay
thank you a little better way I
appreciate oh thanks everybody thanks
Matt I'm for us you buy them more
advantage Oh yep here we go this night
let me go do you have anything to
counter him to mitigate
no I don't like you do there are five
six you have an eight nine ten eleven
that's a good point I have a friend I
have now used my action yet what would
you like to you can see two giant
flaming orbs sort of slowly rotating
around a change lowly roach
as they move past you can see that there
is a wizard working diligently in desk
poring over ancient scrolls and books I
have an idea but you're not going to
like it
you're going to probably you might like
it did you say our aren't yeah I don't
know what you here we here we go I'm
gonna pop can't Acula spec test Oh show
me how now normally this comes out of
something dead like organic matter sure
and I have to do in a can of check just
to you're surrounded by raw sewage I'm
going to try and make a writhing mass of
tentacles in that sewage hole hmm and
hope that it puts out some that spray is
going to put out one of these plier
balls Oh otherwise a condom I get an
explosion of do it just a huge waste
back right right now okay market it
right on mom essential well yeah I mean
why not yeah as close as close as we get
to here so that's not canon yeah let's
make it our kind of check okay sure this
Morley usually because it goes really
poorly awesome real recycle big money
not bad well that's gonna be 16 total
wow that's solid yeah so there's an
eruption of sewage and you thought that
you were coated like you're like oh I
have sewage in every place there could
be sewage now it's in my record you're
learning about any places by which and
this this boys Bremer and does go away
from the wetness what are you really
that's what the wizard shouts from his
little room I already have pinkeye both
eyes I like that your wizard which is
very similar to generate is sort of mine
alright that's the trick okay that's my
secret I have never been Bob King thing
is yeah okay
so that was Chris you put out one of the
orbs yeah that was an action in a move
so you're done yeah and I shot at him I
say now I'm covered in your waste old
man so this thing is going to move one
two I liked it really intimidated and
let it on 12 mmm you just want to shoot
up the right here 1 2 3 4 5 6 7
come on clam 11 well you can see that
finish line yeah Oh hungry for it uh
traffic name is peel my head oh I'm
going to slide in that waist it's a
magic banana peel it doesn't make any
sense it would be a regular one we're
we're covering it's a waistcoat I liked
it
I don't like you Wow anymore opposing
dinar just willing pass you guys and
Shannon mostly please now it's very cool
use your grandma's skills to clean the
floor Wow Wow okay um I'm just gonna
roll barrel one groan amazing could
possibly help me that oh I do have an
idea
now you grandma man see to confound the
vision of my of my competitors Oh dad
out you want to pull shadows up around
them yeah so maybe they don't know which
direction to go on the next turn oh
that's interesting yeah like maybe maybe
they have to roll to get something yeah
go forward yes I like it yes
so shadows are wrapped around you guys
on your next turn you'll make a saving
throw to see if you can even perceive
the right direction to go Danya monza
okay just a mantra I did ma ma ma ma ah
ah
800 amazing the shadow step around the
magic banana peel right well played
Thank You walnut
did you take an action I did yes it was
there I mean yeah growing into you Oh
yep um this is you you're the only one
in this poop why make sure you know you
know you're the one that's toilet cover
oh I'm an employee
and I belong look this event is mores
coming down yeah right guys five okay
you can poop in the whole time I will be
three four five so just below the banana
peel and then I would like to use vine
whip to switch with dinars Oh anymore I
am lovin then I still get my seven
spaces a one yep two three four five six
seven bang credible I'm using um but
that was my bonus action yeah I still
get an action yeah that was just your
vine holy cow don't you do it
[Music]
whoa dead anywhere don't worry about it
my friend
I'm going to use my action to and I
realize I don't know I took me this long
to think of it to use um
stupid animals oh I don't want to talk
to us would you do to seventh row to
even determine whether you could move in
the right direction
hello that's right let's go back guys my
whole cool thing I'm gonna say over back
yeah oh no all the way back Francis oh
my back oh no no actually I'm gonna let
the vine whip go I don't think she needs
night to do that to originally written
three I wouldn't know I see what you're
saying yeah many is my advantage to the
other I hope you make it good what I
wanted taken her again ah you say
perception if you can see through the
shadows oh yeah that oh give me your
perception Botanica wisdom yeah okay I
got this
ah so the twelve when do you want more
don't forget to take away my advantage
ah oh yes yeah yes I think the whole
thing that so bad if I go so yeah here's
their hair and you were like right there
yeah yeah and then I would like to for
my action talk to the squirrel oh go to
school yes
and I'm sure guys it took me that long
and I look back and I reach back I grab
them to the note was hanging out the
back and then I look at him I go sorry
thing you can do to help me win this
thing
right after I squeeze them like a little
too hard
Oh his eyes kind of bulge out a little
bit yeah yeah
coughing little blood comes out of his
mouth and I go are you sure there's
nothing you're killing me I like a
little bit she's had guys our race and
then I look I look at our egg open we're
going to get clip something to get close
to us and when they do you know you
could get out of this car I'm not
allowed to leave your cart Oh
and then I go what are you good for and
I guess I just put him down basically
doesn't have win a race go on
damn next up is kotharis oh I think do
we need to do that I mean a stop for
commercial break and potty break yeah
you do a great break come back in two
minutes
console timeout Thank You shadow council
visit the facilities and never go back
sure all right guys
walnut done your squirrel is not a lot
of help grain it turns out yeah RIS
bringing up the rear
I'm ready like difficult loose I bid for
a well than my sweet chaos trophy the
yeah yeah yes moose it's a stretch I
don't know yeah it's not bad habitable
all right I'm gonna do it's difficult I
don't want to do it I want to go through
these four one yeah and I want to avoid
a flame which way was this guy going it
was like going to the right yeah it's
going clockwise all right I don't know
it doesn't mean we can do about that I
haven't taken my my cards yet what is a
one-song you have anymore you know you
used up your nautical you have one I
said I'm gonna hang on to my one I did
okay I didn't want it bad enough for my
both coach you wanna a card though as
you go through to I want to you're Emily
absolutely I do oh my god guy getting my
last place you guys seven that's it for
me Brown conveys your oh [ __ ] by your
own banana he yeah that's how they get
you kind of done that that was total one
banana yeah yeah whenever you try to
throw it out ahead of you yep yeah I
always did it I raised in this game
anyway yeah that's how whenever I play
wizard card yeah oh also shadow council
wizard card is 2x it turns out that's
how Wizards play it it's only 2 left
yeah yeah free game yeah and
resting right uh now I'm gonna hang on
to it
hang on to it both of them okay yeah
yeah back to the top this is going to
move to one to film that heat you're
feeling the heat it's not consuming you
yeah okay but it is breaking the waist
your flesh it's sort of cooking it's a
shell yeah crap magic show at 5:00 so 11
[ __ ]
it's splashed up own room so you want to
go through your banana peel I assume no
choice right so I got to hit that corner
1 2 2 3 3 4 you want to go 5 6 the edge
stuff mentoring 5 6 7 8 9 10 11
Wow yeah that works for me yeah and then
this goes way to accept it yeah so you
went through it yep thanks for clearing
that all right that was Denar Rosie
Rosie there's these first connect a
lightning bolt everything all their
spells they say oh yeah yeah kidding
sure burned it um don't got none didn't
have to do a saving throw to make sure
right correct
I told you oh yeah none of you guys we
all got yeah everybody forgot next time
all right we'll do it next time we'll do
a next time extra took some yep I'm
gonna make a note beep boop beep or you
could just read to get back I guess just
saving cars the decks you have to beat a
what 14 14 1000 count
okay don't go away put those go away
really bye-bye okay yes yes yes to do it
twice if you want alright okay
yeah crit so good that you think yeah
good
we which one of those ha thank goodness
that's the one I didn't might have these
networks okay all right that was your
arm yeah I'm going to move now okay big
numbers big numbers big round really
nitrous around that corner through to
finish line you can you can diagonal I
don't want to like tell you how to play
your game 5 6 7 8 9 10 12 to 13 damn
grandma go grandma fast she's small but
she she protect she's she also attack uh
that was Rosie walnut mmm
again not again um so Oh to create four
five six seven right in by Rosie I have
one more thing I can do yep I'm gonna
red flame or Rosie out of my way
that's my action okay Otto hit three
spaces yep so you've gone down that to
do it straight and then I get to go win
so yeah see you fired off of her car her
car just flips over yours like that
serious style but it's cool and I land
on my way and that time like slows down
when you're above me and you're like
what Emily you did it to the Top Gun
yeah exactly yeah have you seen my
squirrel going help just hey Leon yeah
alright uh that was walnut Don grass
cthe RIS do I do I use my move to burn
this that's the question or do I use it
to talk to this this guy we have to roll
to make sure your is the shadow
yeah shadow over what I beat in uh
thirteen right all right I'm gonna do no
then do it
nope so I'm going to go back to the food
you go back right I don't think you go
backwards
you're gonna lose your modifier I think
okay they're your best there yeah I see
I see you did like a little 360 okay so
yes go backwards like third yeah thanks
an opiate lost it
I'm gonna take your modifier from still
connects plane to come while I'm taking
my head up at this guy
what is he what's he doing laughing at
you he's laughing hahahaha no come on
just come my dreams you're you're bad
man and I don't like it and I'm going to
use a wizard boost oh oh well that'll
help me who is it most that's right
hey you can you feel better after 12 so
that me doing this by the gods watch me
learn twelve not like that well a sweet
eraser like all right you and me to
thread we could do this we could still
win it legend spoke of a racer like him
so that thing it slides in right behind
you just as you scoot across the finish
line you can feel the heat from it as it
passes behind your cart my cheeks are
the first dinar does anything changes on
know maybe when you make your own
[ __ ] board game you can have this
pain no laughs oh there's a stack of
chips here yeah alright three plus six
nine so I go for mmm card we got here we
have working on interesting how exciting
summer you've got poke up two three four
five six okay and you're hanging on to
that gets a long honest Rosie I'm gonna
end with a card yeah I'm gonna green
flame orb oh that that wretched nut at
the top sure oh wow how far I go I get
six plus three in trash no 23 person
says I am I good by three I only kind of
say I have a cousin let's say go back in
time dude everyone save against my
shadow a [ __ ] no no do it you have an
advantage
oh the shadow just yeah yeah there's
nothing left in the store three prizes
sorry guys
okay so um nut yeah you got still a neck
even army even on that yeah well so now
what happened you go back to you go one
two and then I'm gonna have you go three
the worst okay and then minimum one I
said I was gonna take advantage even
though I didn't want to oh three I'm
taking it from you yeah hey good
sportsman - I have four disadvantages I
should give you disadvantage yeah are
you all of them yeah just you know just
so even me so just to burn is
disadvantage role what I please
yeah um wallet you have disadvantage
well Brett hit really messed you up I
love ya you got hit by nine you took the
right your cart you thought you disgust
me but the little purple cloud comes
over like a fishing pole it's like a
nice bike you got knocked out you got to
run back like yeah so that was a - um
okay I like excited by reference words
like yeah absolutely I can run fashion
this is not take tho um and instead of
going this way I'm just gonna push my
cart up the back of Rosie just rev my
engine ah you can swap with her if you
want right here mommy oh yeah it's on
with Oh ciao deft amazing forgot about
my own secret powers line we've got cool
power oh yeah
good yeah and there really is only way
to close oh great did you kill my Amex
right so yes it's us - yeah yeah my
whole thing okay doesn't open let's say
yes
next is cthe RIS and I can hang out with
this old man there's no point
alright let's see let's see what I got
side it's really your as far as actually
going I set you yeah I think it's from
that it's not wheels they're all the one
again Chris traveled of one again goes
seven and you're doing last place I'm
still uh well I don't mind because this
has been working out for me the whole
time yeah I pick up these last cards but
then I get stayed all right Dan Arnhem
and I'm sorry and use them pop a spell
yeah I can't I can't take a break as
something a lightning them out of mine
exactly haha nice but my spells in two
pieces
you're gonna go yeah let's do I'm going
to do a a red flame ward okay and it's
not okay three that's three of them and
I'm going to spray them across everybody
gets on all y'alls everybody look under
your seat for we get savings over or no
right or auto hit that's my bottom here
this game we all are you want value it
has we can persuade me one two three
ever been a kitchen so no one's ever
played anything like tuna for okay
I've fantasized about this game yeah did
you make good yeah I did my I'm done and
so I glower each one I want to be around
each one yeah one happy family breaks
like one two one three
oh there was no reason to do that that
works out well for you like an army yeah
and I'm gonna be fireballs behind me
okay we're gonna start with get three uh
odd he walnut first
okay so attack plus six to hit man I
missed well it again I don't give me
just a minute today thank you for for
all right that was a good one okay so on
sixteen uh
so back three one two three and then and
the grandma use your last one right yeah
yeah
hi guys all right yeah I'll do Rosie
oh nice on cue 3 the sniper yeah I just
I did it because I felt good right
middle of the screen or just shooting
out the back of your car Rosie yeah you
take a green or bright had a face I did
sorry my life now um I'm just gonna move
I guess I can't do much
I am 512 here we go Mike come on Mike
you some help yeah you guys moving you
want to go yeah I want you to choke up
through the three back four five and
then around town six seven eight nine
ten eleven twelve twelve yeah that
diagonal is it's a good one that's a
good one okay that's good not moving
through people and knocking back the
Buddy Glade bunched up as we've been
that's been really yeah I have been good
everybody can't fart on command but she
makes a noise all not going right for
gotta go Kathy I have you whirring right
there great yes one cheese you guys have
been spending too much time with Jerry
rubbing off on you
Jerry somewhere crying uh okay uh so
where you going what you talk about it
like that he'll be back then two three
four vine whip em six seven and then one
and then as my action the vine with cows
of space I think you just find what and
then cute and then you keep that space
so you point you went from four to six
but I think vine whip vine whip does not
take away from your movement right so
you get one more oh yeah bingo happy
noise hey remember that ever forget
gotta hey thank you Mr Tarzan you all
along slide in front like this is
hailing out and then for my action I
would like to just really think about
what I was doing an hour ago versus what
I'm doing yeah yeah go back to your
happy place
I'll give you the evidence kid yeah I
watch it and I think about it baked-on
yeah
you on board somewhere mmm smells like
strawberries okay yeah my games aren't
like that
next is kiss RIS all right well let's
see what all those cards did me uh-oh
I'm in the back again all right well
buddy what are you doing back there I'm
just gonna keep being mad that's what
I'm going to do right cuz I meditate
yeah man well there's a green flame orb
times three oh it's not Auto heads it's
time to see some rolls yeah yeah let's
do yes they're all sized avi yeah let's
do the two using the front date card
look at you walnut first login yeah oh
that's not great look at those clothes
it's one to one Jessa get to yeah yeah
think of off of the one at least you
have to set them down so that they they
know how to sit from there's a power one
right here how I want that hit you do
you go back gosh it's off the wall and
ricochets back okay so you're fine
walnut now Rosie gee I'm so fine okay I
have a great if Table Talk reason why
these rules you have an advantage these
people have paid for you to have it
oh okay well that's for you dinar and
I'm going to I am I I don't know is 11
plus 600 plus KB dungheap take your take
your step back three steps three steps
hey buddy so we're he takes threesome
and everyone but you okay okay I'm gonna
need to hit me you do is your movie you
want a conversation no yeah I pull you
back unlike Mike what are we should
killing this man probably know he could
be the guy behind this thing I don't
know I was it sure he's that great
feeling frizzy that's true a natural
hair king he wants me to call Britney
Spears one more in that column you're
speaking very loudly in gospace cat all
right that's it
okay my movement is complete and you
don't miss spells or anything right yeah
okay no you did it I burned it one what
is with you guys and he's one of your
number one here
connectin I can I have one Wow I'm
necessary three four five six seven so
because I felt like it okay ah be
blessed again
so what asked us with this a lot is on
the under last I just want to remind
everyone a Denarius canonically running
yeah holding the car passing things out
of their own yet Rosie yeah I kicked the
item can I hold the card up okay well I
was how is that even like just across
there it's not even worth of people
talking worth because of this it's great
you got your [ __ ] animal I made the
focus you made the focus I made beer and
larvae today and I look at what you've I
was saving it for Table Talk but it's
here yes could you move me diagonal next
to you yes and then then six more spaces
for class six you want one of these oh
yeah that's right yeah well looks like
it okay I feel that dark residence you
got hang on to that it's really one now
I'm gonna use this oh I'm gonna use it
well on cenar what's a red flame work I
don't have my history spaces
could you sit on you nut could and I
remember that you want
I forgot area that's happening another
one power
I'm resurrection will use my advantage I
roll a dice does it come up one I go to
okay one two three
should I should I see what I got you got
it demands tribute four five six seven
and then I want to look at that statue
again but a torch yes
okay um and I know a lot about
dome rocks so I'd like to inspect
just the general construction of the
rock with a survival check okay we'll
just see that does anything really shoot
in the dark mmm-hmm that is a fourteen
uh it seems like it's been run into a
number of times
like it's a little loose on its base oh
I look at the I look at the scroll and I
go home all of a sudden you've got
goggles yeah I have goggles I'm really
just bandaging you know what yeah I got
happened to live for him this pocket
dimension
mm-hmm yeah though if walnut has seen
that this is off its base and then
someone like say Rosie were to ram it it
wouldn't with that change I can't tell
the future so all right I just have to
see interesting all right cool but I
don't think you communicated that to
anybody else sure and what she did to
the squirrel oh very close to her okay
yeah you turn here I go
all right you didn't say in that
language am i right or whatever I'm sure
[Music]
it might do something this kit thread
yeah I [ __ ] everybody
I mean looting us what is keeping the
team together nothing at this point
enemies race is my goal yeah
I'm the one that's what everyone did he
did it
so there's gonna be total of 10 whoa
here you want us to yeah let me try all
right make your big boy 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8
yeah you won't learn if you do it fine I
will do never learn I think you did a
good job moving your piece oh yeah okay
good job gold star good jealous ah geez
as an action because the only thing to
do other than a race yeah I'm going to
look at the statue yeah under under what
- what type of check do you want to make
on oh okay let's see on oculars I have I
how much of their actions with it have I
seen all I know is that they look at it
and then they suddenly yeah that's
really all you know okay well then I'm
gonna I fix up with that statue so I'm
going to do in our kind of check okay on
it and see what if I can is it is it
alive
can I wonder can I make a request of it
not what is up with the statue you guys
I thought I talked to the wrong statute
I assume it's another another crime yeah
you don't know anything about that
statute dinar hey five that's a good
roll maybe he's gonna pass right by you
without going through you you can go you
can i woody yeah
why would I do that you just try to look
at the adjuster I look at anybody else's
cards because I mean sent me this unlike
yeah wait till you get your last place
ones and it'll take them from you uh
that really I'm happy ready Rosie okay
[Music]
okay I'm going to do a perception on
this I can do a history on the Statue I
guess except but I already do it
I really buddy scourge can I do it what
do you want to do can I get out I you
know buddy you're the best one that's
ever lived and everybody knows it yeah
so buddy stone hands that are on the
wheel ever so slightly and you can draw
the top two here I hope you're up early
thank you pick one pick one we're gonna
do the fastest second half of this lap
yeah maybe it's movement is your
movement plus a d20 v10 let's try it
again okay
whoo let's kick it into Nitro mode I was
going to say if we weren't well flex in
fighting then maybe we should we feel
like overcome rifice magical you do you
feel overcome by a master presence
wonderful okay and blue flame shoots out
of all of your carts you're older well
starting only man come on me ten-four
well let's start at the top with dinar
okay okay okay so I got five I got you
man
yeah good game player
seven eight mmm oh that banana peel huh
pick one nine ten here yeah
yep discard perfect thank you and you do
you have a card perfect yeah okay
walnut ha ha hmm
not a one dot yeah yeah
little victories yeah okay do you want
take a picture I want to stay close and
then I want to use shockwave on it oh I
like that I was going to ram it yeah
okay so it's a +6 to hit please I want
to vanish okay nice burn it for me I'm
so than I've seen oh and Wow yeah you
slam into this thing and it it crumbles
yeah
so I love it this is all difficult
terrain now hold on okay when your enemy
sent no way well now here we'll go like
that I'll give you this tiny space
all right the furthest the m45
they're gonna seven eight oh wait whip
whip time that weird encapsulate there
janna date no yeah you don't understand
on my own power works sorry you just
transpose yeah and you can be within
three spaces so yeah I get three away
flip and then keep counting it hit me
right on understand mm-hmm think of how
anyway for next week yeah
when Jerry runs thanks wheeler car 500
okay so that was walnut cthe risk you're
the last person to go without nitro oh
do I oh I do not have you did you you're
still a g6 okay v6 my specialty no
worries that's gonna matter be rolling
on Oh so fancy I guess it's going to be
nine give me one two three four five are
you sure you didn't have a spell that
can throw this boy back I don't know
your stuff I'm I know I would you yes
you're in super last place wait why do I
want so that you can move past them oh I
see giant canine anything like enemy
weapon out of the way
for so long I like no matter one of them
is way yeah and then you get the last
yeah you know what
Thanks that makes a lot of sense into
the past that sometimes uh yeah you're
right
wait a minute Vegas laughs Chris I want
you to play your game all right you're
all too smart I wouldn't have thought of
it that way so I'm going to do I'm going
to do green flame or that isn't that is
a attacking that the rule is they're all
to hit all three all right for each tent
oh but all in time oh yeah you guys are
next we wouldn't get hit no after all it
first roll on him can't hit it so that's
minus three yep this week I was going to
seem to it I didn't before
one two three yep well now 1200 no Nigel
to show hey that's a nice thanks nice
flame orb snotzax
yeah 9 2006 equals 15 which all I want
to know yeah Sam's here sorry ok perfect
so this one's already moved three so
that how many do you have in your
eternal movement Oh Avery I did yes I'd
so give me another 6 1 2 3 4 5 6
Thank You friends all right very helpful
all right row now nitro mode each n
nitro you roll one I'm going to be
really upset goodnight hi I'm okay a
lightning bolt
don't wait don't I get any saving at
this oh yeah Avon lightning bolt
lightning bolt over here oh it's not a
strong very sorry there you go
and then I get one of them late to save
14 with deck of a 1914 decks again yeah
look that one's not in the bond of
laughs yeah okay all right bud nice I
lost it
another good one good okay Oh take it
one wizard boost I did I did what all
right are you moved in are when you're
gonna hang on to your spell well I use
the laning bowl I use the lighting bolt
right Rosie D 10 plus your speed
and this is okay no 7 to 10 plus the
speed number 2 plus 7 1 2 3 right into
the Shadow 2 plus my speed nut okay cap
did you get your car sure do you have a
lien over you FL you could get walnut
whoa Hana cheerio Pelham l ma to loose
park for 5 can we help yeah perfect nice
love it hmm quick do a flop for direct
you should swap slob okay and then I get
occur nowhere Decker um 7 8 9 10 11 12
13 14 15 16 17
yeah I'm feeling it okay with nitro you
never know blue orb blue fire one or
quite lovely warm wha cthe RIS is not a
ruling I have a I bought a really
weirdly shaped d-10 it looks like it's
off brand yeah so there's a 12 oh that
wanted us a misprint that's or they
might roll it to I'm good I'm bought us
really big deep it's over son
got some extra numbers on it yeah it
doesn't matter okay
nah hey I'll help you out where you want
to go just bring me bring me one too in
line with you and then let's straight
away three four five six seven eight
do you need card as usual Egret oh yeah
thank you up that's eight nine and
another five two four six
oh is it because it's almost way yeah
Wow thank you dr. Ramos okay can you
handle it if you want to go then you
through though yeah bring it you're
there so you how you get another six yes
one two three yeah four five six
all right print okay so our next to
Rosie in this dark secret cavern here
I love gonna love this she's can come
from me I should send ya what I read
yeah hi
one two three four like that five th I
am eight nine use this get explicably in
capsules yeah weird so I'm going to use
this to get six more zealous star stars
the door assistant or no I do know one
that's a little different is putting on
the wrist a minute everything's
copyrighted hmm
and then Vanegas one two three four five
six
sure back 1 2 pi out of honey and then
one you've got to start yeah yeah we'll
see two three four five six
wow it's sweating wowzers got it Rosie
yeah
Rosie you do I that big dice oh boy okay
I'm real sorry about this one but I
don't think I didn't have a chance to
use it I'm gonna do a shock wave on your
mommy my boy
Wow Wow six minute just cuz I can and it
is Jaco stretch access it I got that
hold that you're gonna have to go back
one two later we got another you're
gonna be laughs nice going through
though I make sure all your know you are
full up you'll need to burn it burn it
after you all right seven plus three
five one two three four five six seven
eight nine I don't want to use the norsu
yeah who does walnut be three minutes ah
seven three and then three in a now
seven seven yeah um you have a card I'm
not going to use it but on my turn real
quick uh there's like a blender in here
and I look like I start getting ready to
make like celebration jakhary
and I'm like just around four
ingredients but I like a look at the
very unhelpful squirrel I'm just like
yeah that's used for one glass
[ __ ] glass there Adam Wow are you gonna
make decorative Custer if you have a lot
of catching up to do I'm not gonna say
it's impossible I attend oh okay
I never seen pounds what about yourself
what kind of spells do you have I was
find out I didn't even look because
what's the point right
any of this matter blue or would be
really like in my heart in my house yeah
what does anything matter he chairs you
know what it's called lighting bulb
everybody can lose everything
anybody got anything good did they love
ya Amy set something on to get onto it
oh good we really roll boys head Dex Dex
on trying to hit Oh 14 well here I lost
my spell of Stein oh no that was it
going to get me to the end might have it
might have all right and then as far as
know I counted the space antenna I would
have got there I deserved that
all right eight moves to a round so
drawn through two three four five six
seven eight that's it okay and then I
just put her in park yeah turn the car
on yeah stretch out a little bit around
the radio one gray one plus six six uh
you lost your spell of star no matter I
needed yeah I needed a ten anyway um you
could attract draconic entitle me to get
me to like stop I was thinking of it
yeah how would you do it so how would
you do it from here to here that's where
you let me dirt on ik entitlement to
skip her turn like to stone her so
you'll see what you do what are you
trying to do here okay waited yeah
that's the one time like my powers just
skip a whole turn I didn't even say it
would skip your turn I'm trying to see
what he wants to do oh well am too
bristling this yeah Lily so let's just
show you force work up with your kind of
teittleman like it's called to establish
the pecking order so I go walnut you got
to know one thing
he's crazy and dinar is the cream how I
feel echoes to the janitor like an echo
chamber Joe honey is it good luck xuan
are you impressed by that at all I mean
shouldn't you roll Monica it's not like
all of our time I roll - yeah roll so do
I have it what do you want I could be I
guess I what do you want I don't think
that affects you know this is a race car
game like I would say anything stuff you
know I don't know why does yeah logical
choice where it's a board game or wizard
did it yeah all right mark our roadie
mine doesn't
yeah that's weird even took her foot up
so yes even for his role yeah on my next
turn I know I was going to use acid you
roll to see if your if I move so he like
rooted you in place but you can break
out of it like you want it what you want
to do it oh I mean all this should word
and bone it never works it's the worst
Alton history of LF I had to read you
mine are you go sickly
alright what's not everybody can have
animal murder on Kamino hmm
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 ours I get
okay man walnut you wanna cross that
finish line I mean I do yeah I want you
to do this yes yeah okay yeah Oh got 20
minutes left
you got a beaut well the pleasure I
don't know a deck so via 14 yeah you can
see where you want you want to finish
this race you are way over one and he
would've been like yeah yeah okay um
yeah actually no wait no sorry hang on I
want to do it even though it's really
painful I can't do it can you do it
nonetheless class oh not the last five
okay let's make a circles yeah fun you
know and then I immediately like pull
the e brake on it get out it out and
then I go what are we doing
yeah question you are holding gym too
right
you got the box yeah you are doing
yeah after all of that this has been
rattled around inside your car you guys
all eventually across the finish line
coming down out of the ceiling is a
beautiful golden cup Thank You shadow
Council for choosing what the prize
would be here there's a huge golden
chalice okay
and it says wizard Kart number one racer
on it
okay I'm sorry it is always full of a
random potion Wow
should you scoop that potion out it just
fills up with another random potion mmm
random program like a big thing that
like we'd keep enough you would keep it
on your shelf Becky you're okay would ya
absolutely I say it for everybody
that's nice is for the family but it has
us as walnut is in great everyone over
at camper yeah yeah for everyone it's
just like I missed everything what
happened and you are now greeted by
guard who says that you would like to
take you up to meet the wizard Abdus
yeah absolutely
okay lovely and Abner see you climb some
stairs at the top of which is a wooden
door you're led into this wizard study
he's behind another giant desk piled
high with books and Scrolls and he says
my champion I go what up oh pretty good
well not everyone gets to bask in my
glory oh you have been granted an
audience what would you like to do with
your time here and then one looks at the
box and here's the soft peeping of the
chicks me cry-baby
and for a second she she looks and then
she goes and looks back at the box and
goes I have an associate here who's been
afflicted with an unfortunate condition
and I need you to turn him back to
normal
let me see and then I bring it over work
the box Adam and I opened up and I
opened up the did you open up you look
two goes Jib dark magic is a very thing
have you done this time gotten ourselves
into quite a pickle and I go actually
wait a second
and I leaned down I go
tell you Fran Hellman who got you up
here then I hold it on I go magic stuff
all right
he takes the box from you and sits down
behind his desk and he pulls out some
sort of different sauce yeah you
definitely fireside sauce as a grantee
and barbecue sauce yeah by McDonnell
they've got he's going to want always
with you waves it over the box a couple
times and you can see the chicks sort of
slowly merged together they turn into
one purple chick and then that chick
starts growing until Jim dark magic is
just sitting on this Wizards desk Pete
he slides off the desks or brushes
himself off he looks at you and he says
walnut Dan grass nice no hay a silent I
have something for you hold on a second
just patting down he goes oh yeah here
it is
he pulls out from inside of his club a
huge bag it looks very much like your
doc you Nancy bags short but this one is
much nicer this is this is super nice
mm-hmm
and you can see his heat because he
pulls it out it opens up and all the
[ __ ] inside falls out oh it's like well
you can pick that up
ah but you can see that what fell out
was like a ledger but it's all gold foil
all these new quills came out 6:00 to
midnight a man like we've never seen
before it's just stunning Jim steps on
one of them he says oh and there's
something else he winks at you and you
feel like a bulge growing in your hot
yeah okay okay I reach in it's soft
I really I look I pull it out and I'm
like it does and tied to his leg and a
tiny little scroll walnut what is it
well oh it says nice work kid by the way
the handwriting is incredible I says
nice work kid looks like I owe you some
money and hey be careful with the
secretary and they know a lot so don't
ask any questions you don't want to know
the answer to
Oh menaces with a little symbol how did
he know you were going to win hmm
you've been promoted to the next level
of documenting congratulate hey drink
all the mystery potion just chug it
yeah I was like I had kind of a rough
day do you want to go out and celebrate
though I actually have some celebrating
to do
I'm down yeah it's not for you no I'm
doing that anyway thank you
I'm shot on you I'm in Atmos okay oh
great I'm gonna give you this and she is
holding the Dove yeah I felt like a
death grip on the judges this is for you
so there you go take him back and he
just releases it inside getting like a
wall a couple times and it just falls
into the thud um I want to go so this
has been great and I'm really happy with
all of this and she's scooping up all
the stuff from the ground she's like can
you like just get us back - yes my man
did is gonna put you guys back don't
worry about it
great so fantastic job you've got my
number if you want to call me nope
you're doing some tonight I am I can't I
could if you want to I'm gonna pass this
I can't either
yeah I come on Darren read large though
look us up I probably won't be cool all
right so you got news you guys are
escorted back out of the tower you find
the portal that led you here yeah back
through it into Jim study and diz is
there and he says oh you guys did it
this fantastic master Jim is back thank
goodness now it's time for you guys to
go home and so he picks up his little
silver bell and rings it and you guys so
slowly start vanishing and when you
reappear you are back on the ship
exactly where it is got you oh sweet did
I admit a swipe anything on the desk
well oh yeah did you try to down meat
real quick yeah give us a make a roll
try real quick okay while you're away
I'm there and I realized Johnny yes the
hair study yeah okay
oh hello a troll alright what was on the
top of that absolutely oh you snatched
is the mechanical little bird that he
keeps it can either play back a record
it's a little brass like clockwork bird
yeah you can use to record message back
yeah nice with the duration how long can
I do that for okay 30 seconds it's a
minute and switches at this one minute
in its fantasy time I go to like LP and
I didn't get to yeah it is it play my
game I'll see you guys have fun hey you
guys you're back nothing even happened
and Jerry can pick up next week with
only two disadvantage roles
I actually know at one dance we're back
for fact where we are and a bird did he
doesn't know about yeah you have a bird
you guys have a cup it refills with
random potion I know we have we have a
room yeah in our base that has nothing
in it and now it has a assault cup well
we have to you more minutes and I'd
really like to know about the shadow
cake in the Dead King is it alright yeah
sure yeah yeah
you put the shouting needs an heir for
the dead King isn't willing to give him
work his son why would the problem that
we're facing yeah
so the dawn lariat showed up and I got
sliced to pieces ingenious Lee by a
shadowy figure that he referred to as
rosy B singer which is my name
interesting and yeah now we're just I
think we're a little confused and we're
gonna I thought like we're going to roll
initiative was where we were headed yeah
yeah yeah I mean I don't have any
monsters for you right okay so and what
happened we got nothing before maybe you
could just give us lose our I gave you
two pieces of lunar I feel like so good
so this can we can we really quickly
show this I want to know is this like a
little special omens like that's the
only symbol yeah oh he has his own
symbol yes I'm dead this is so special
uh alright so I will not with pride if I
were you able to like ah but the
teleport when you return there's a break
oh yeah Table Talk Thomas this is the
telling point do you feel none of us did
this you're able to move for 12 12
minute yeah no we're going to
we're going to take a commercial break
and we can go potty then we'll come back
for Table Talk yeah thank you
you