time is the enemy the pastor threatens
the fastest weapon you wouldn't make it
past a second and answer the question
play it brash and reckless to choose a
cautious solution you saw was prudent
and any soccer poker - don't become the
putrid it's that well-fed I pursue in no
mountain too steep for dungeon too deep
to send expanded remarks up to the top
of the peak of beneath they see you be
they come like sharks to it while I swim
in that money build like Carl Barks
through it so send your national parks
drew it I'll send him home in a natural
box with the clothes tie the most of the
parks included
save your breath for a cleric confessor
that there's a lesson that life is at
any professor but if you're seeking my
official advice sign on the dotted line
and wish of the choice hello I am Tycho
Brahe hey if penny arcade in packs I am
also a mini fest Hereward run CEO of
acquisitions incorporated but today I'm
Jerry Hawkins and I'm running a game of
Dungeons and Dragons for my friends
indeed counted among that number to my
right dragons for always the Primark yep
Dragonborn narcissist dude or blitz him
nor blitz and everybody to never enough
to the right you're already my
game up man listen you haven't me
introduced yet it still time to load you
into a catapult launch you into space to
the right of my right Mikey Newman
coming in as Kiwi be steer he would be
stinger everybody right now oh
absolutely yeah you will find that that
Ryan gets with with a great
regularity around here and to know I am
the
I am people
so to the right of my right right that's
the left is three months unless it works
are you do you want me are you okay yeah
already here well not dog
reppin the natural world that beef to my
left in this sparse corner of the table
so much room I know yes that lovely bar
mm-hmm
not your grandma's grandma bro CB
stinger yeah yeah yeah yeah fanfiction
favorite if you're keeping up with the
other edit Wow lot of content there good
content to the left of my left the
emerging as though from a mister out
described
first job just grab everybody the agent
of the tentacular spectacular now I'm
done
y'all we just moving right into the
second one I throw this one too okay
here's how it works when last we saw our
heroes they had returned from their
fateful expedition aboard the Dragon
Sword a river going house of chants
operated by lizard folk they made a new
friend
specifically cthe wrist drab now appears
to be wearing the lizard king and soon
all my friends well join yeah exactly
that whole encounter went exactly as we
planned
exactly possibly doesn't end well me not
because after the game I looked at the
plan you had written it out it's all
written that he was talking almost all
exactly extra dimension it was just like
item by item it's like what we want
extra dimensional pin free mmm you know
it was right in there but there was also
you know that's let's take a moment
obviously to recognize some of the
emotional turmoil of walnut on grass
she's fine
everybody's great dirt of the Enclave
panics on Amash yes the same thing
that's 60 years of sex torture same
thing it's in the mix it's in there we
determined well we determined 60 years
but in sex terms what we're talking
about yeah we're talking about 20 so
here's how it goes here's how it goes
we're really talking about a pool of
slime full of rising orbs salmon yeah
you know how amy and salmon do it it
isn't like some of the fix you've seen
let's just say that it's largely
involves slime on slime action and you
know that's that's denied latents
contribution just more slime to the
swine pile the exact I can't even tell
them apart exactly certain point so that
is the scenario we find ourselves in a
sticky scenario but they have returned
back to the drama and quartier their
home in red large the rooms above the
inn and they have just I repeat just
received control / command of an entire
in presumably you've been told that
there is a festival lasts stones day
mm-hmm
that was just that is right around the
corner and that there are going to be
specific requirements that are asked of
the party there's gonna be expectations
obviously the drawing courier of course
being a center of community here in red
larch a place that's been established
certainly since the days that you know
almond run was a child he grew up in
this town and you know so for a few
decades at least it has offered these
services and I recall because I went
back in
listen to the other episode you
suggested Rosie that you had full
control of the information regarding
last stones day and were prepared in
fact to deliver any services that might
be required naturally no holiday is all
that different from any other games I've
experienced so very many of them last
stones date and perhaps not in
specificity but I feel like I have a
pretty good grasp on how to throw a
party but I don't know what the hell
well sorry to make some meals yeah now I
prophecy nondenominational she seemed
like she needed to hit the road she was
she was stressed out she left her
gauntlets she borrowed your daughter she
brought my daughter yeah yeah tomato
tomahto so I just wanted to let her know
that it's like everything's gonna be
locked down but I have been since her
departure like going through every
cookbook I can find and trying to find
anything that says okay don't stay on it
well you have you have a heads up in
that regard Rosie because you have
already dug through this this recipe box
once before as you'll recall wedding
cake indeed before you went south
Indian deed right before you into the
barge right doc yeah and boarded that
fateful moment of silence obviously for
Brahma Brahma Lu da no so as I said
before you have you know Doge through
this a bit obviously this is like any
grandmother's you know cookbook box its
scraps of parchment there are you know
egg some of these some of these are firm
mm-hmm
firmer than you might like flour is
represented throughout so you're saying
she has an untidy box well I'm saying
that this is a box hmm
yeah all right Chris you yes okay
I'm saying that it's this
box that's seen use okay a lifetime of
use yeah okay but it's better than the
other one moving on exactly but but as
you've dug through before you had access
obviously to the proprietress yeah of
this establishment right looking deeper
into this box of scraps it is clear that
you know that she is you know lived in
different places at different times
she has gotten recipes from friends and
it is basically like a it's like a who's
who of languages of the Forgotten Realms
ah this is this would be a master's
thesis linguistics course okay well I
can speak a few languages if there's
anything in common elvish halfling order
chronic I can read it yeah the issue the
issue is that sometimes the numbers will
be in elvish and then sometimes the
ingredients will be in common she has
developed a kind of sophisticated multi
linguistic shorthand that may require
something on the tier of warlock the
language of velocity maybe or even
document see like it's a it's a complete
fest all right what do I invite to
my fest let's see not just our
bears this is my way this time all right
how much how much times this morning
right now you were just looking through
that you were just looking through the
you were just looking through the bugs
right now my perception is that is that
time has not passed
oh you're picking right back up now you
can go to bed obviously later there's an
opportunity for that to occur no before
let's just address real quick the
elephant in the room which is the
elephant the elephant what's it doing
here I before the end of our last
episode I received
a delivery indeed edge i plump it well
it's real gotten wealth
it was plump and I assumed that I have
secret did it away in my room to be
dealt with later that is that is what
you have suggested before okay alright
and so now I am back to it doing grandma
stuff just normal grandma stuff just
look into recipes and I need even are
you are you are you within shouting
distance let's see where was i before I
think I was just oh I had been yelled at
for not helping clean them exactly so
her armor has all been retrieved
obviously the gauntlet very tastefully
placed in the baguette basket but this
place is not ready for service right but
she basically commandeered the the
common room pushing all the tables
together and as I said this place is not
ready to serve people at all well you
know it's already a mess you know who
could help make it more ready me know
plenty of things that I have on my body
and there on my person it's gonna get
Disney up in this mix yeah do your thing
cuz you're gonna help me with with
recipes so yeah when you come upon me
out there if that's what you do actually
come out or just yell I'm trying to get
the tables and chairs back to where they
were because there's so much dirt on the
floor there's so much dust and garbage
shake but I could see where the legs
stood good idea totally exactly I can
only seek if it's like the showroom
right I can totally see Chris just like
it's like a skirt and it's like it's not
right but he noticed like deep down that
if he doesn't set the table is exactly
right like there's consequences we can't
even begin to envisage to this table of
a fifth leg yeah I think it might have
so I need a there are other tasks though
that we were given indeed indeed would
you like me to run back through those
tasks well the one that I've got that I
zeroed in on was
cleaning out the carriage house m.d.
really needed it for some yeah there is
a carriage house that does require a bit
of cleaning as well right
there is obviously the maintenance and
operation of the inn and then whatever
particularity --zz are involved in these
recipes that are specific to last stones
day depending on how bad the carriage
house is is it adjacent can i peek my
head in yeah you can peek your head
right around the edge so if you if you
go you open the door
and then as you open the door there is a
person actually reaching for the handle
of the door and it's the stone right
here
Kiwi bee stinger you don't know that yet
okay but that's who it is
so you've so right within the frame of
the door and as the light is darkening
outside as evening as is approaching you
were just standing face to face with the
person who is doing the reverse of what
you were trying to do seconds ago so now
you are a little too close to each other
you're a little too close you're more
clothes than you intend to be with
strangers generally speaking what do you
see can you can we describe his is he
the shovel disease like he emerged this
the size of my head or shaved and I have
a tight and bun pulled back but it's
bleached by the Sun which goes nice of
my light blue skin though I am I am
scarred by my many years on the road and
held in features though right is there
yeah yeah I may I am a moon Lt ants the
bluish skin at first I think I'm staring
into some sort of a twisted mirror no
Hannah this is the wrong yeah
but for catharsis you no conception of
the universe perhaps sometimes when you
open doors you see alternate maybe this
is just how it works this could be a
message yeah I don't think we need a
role in anything but our look is like
we're thinking about it it's possible
like we're not saying no friend was oh
I'm sorry I didn't know anyone was in
here
not a problem at all where were you here
about who are you here to see
well I I I heard I heard the woman that
raised me was around here
Oh Myron always I was looking for her
fortunately a prophetess drawn its left
on on business but you're welcome to
stay I'm not sure how long she'll be
away but this is no place for a guest
this is a I understand a literally a
horse's toilet unsuitable so return at
the carriage house or this plane of
existence you said the magic yes or this
this won't do no come in come in but
unfortunately profit has gone but a
pleasure to meet another sibling of the
drawn family I look at you and clearly
that was not the name I was expecting to
hear Oh as that as it is not the woman I
call mother I'm actually looking for a
rosy bee stinger oh yes if you have
heard or know of her we have heard of
one of those we are familiar with that
familiar did not do not more forget
there says weave do you mean like you
and all of your family
the teller Russell no I mean you have
and you literally have a Lizard King
sort of sniffing out here and then
you've got some kind of eldritch serpent
right your Avinashi man of nightmares
that's with it yes so yeah and their
Lizard King keeps giggling because it's
not venture he's oh yeah he's having
never been in the carriage house no he
doesn't know about believe it yeah why
am I still learning in this strange all
right I'm gonna take him on that he's
like yeah I'm just standing there like
what is it happening push Shh Hustler's
describe we were talking about nice talk
show some day no come in yeah we do have
Rosie back here I was loved it's been so
many years since I've since I've seen
her many many years um she does not yet
know and I'm telling you this very
quietly that that my brother has
actually passed on oh because she had
helped raise us when we were kids our
parents died quite early the natural
causes and were they were they horrible
I don't remember much about them I just
remember Rosie I mean the dance the
deaths
I mean I don't I don't personally enjoy
dwelling on them in that in that
particularly to each his own I am now
finding the nearest I wants to pray
about this man that is how I conduct you
back into that into the main I want to
bedroom just naturally in your in your
leg no okay you can see as you as you
enter into this venue from the sign out
front
the drowning courtier yeah um you see a
tiny white tiny white bun of hair sort
of moving back and forth industriously
behind the bar I know it immediately
yeah yeah you are you are you are
familiar with
this hair sphere yeah I'm talking I'm
definitely narrating everything in the
kitchen like prophetess
what do you how do you defeat this movie
don't you don't keep these pans next to
that why would you do this you have a
melt eventually everything is gonna turn
some for this is a fire hazard
it's to no one it's to me and it's all
fine like no one cares but it's just
like there's a grandma configuration
yeah and it's like every gramma it's
always perfect but every grandma has one
that cannot coexist yeah and sometimes
it's like somehow it's worse I'm like oh
you do it that way huh the judgment
interesting but there should go dramsay
should be here yeah I mean I agree with
you they're just coming out of the oven
oh I'm sorry to get that I don't watch
television
no braces all right uh so we yeah how do
you want to do it because I'm not I
wouldn't presume we may want to just lay
a tarp out here preferably in in a
private manner oh well yeah I think I
read that and I am I didn't like
I'm not much of a show business to you
to your business can I do I recognize
your voice okay yeah I think you I think
you would all right go ahead please I
returned to you just so I get it in
place I returned to the carriage house
and I invoke though that the softest
ghost she's off just goes as I unseen
servant and you can work for an hour you
can work all day recast him yeah no I
want him to go ahead and clean that
carriage house make it shine and get
every gear every nook and cranny my
friend and then I'll go do something
upstairs
okay it's you can't get any flood what
yeah
it's shut Kim the door I just tried yeah
yeah do think the door to the carriage
house is shut and luck yes Bob elbow in
the door I'm messing around sorry you
see a soft hand brush on and around the
keyhole
come on this is so gentle I like that I
like the approach of all its industrious
pin in it so we can have this scene yeah
yeah yeah hi so now I'm trying to figure
out how I'm lock-picking next to tool I
just have blank so I got no doors can
hold me oh that's nice we're worried
about that okay we have fire so my balls
then I loves doors yeah yeah should I go
lay on hands yeah okay so I hear a voice
that sounds familiar and I come
rustling out of that kitchen and you can
barely see me over the bar yeah yeah
what I come out I take my little apron
off I put my hands on my head and I look
at you like it's been a very long time
it has been a while how long has it been
nine years I think yeah nine years
where's your brother
so about that um he he died about three
years back we were we were doing one of
the things you had taught us you taught
us music and and we were we were
traveling Bart's together and I used to
be what I was but uh he was he was
killed in a bar kerfuffle what bar uh
the dancing dragon do you are you aware
of that
yeah I know it so I make a note I make a
note just dancing very cross he's gonna
burn the bar deck they seem very
interesting
they're lying there was a fight between
two other patrons and he got in the
middle of it and they killed him
he was terrible but he knew how to fight
he was an excellent fighter okay he
actually can't block knives from two
directions it turns out it was
so one skill I didn't teach him yeah so
I guess yes yeah it was it was rough so
I make weapons now I'm I'm a ranger
traveling to - oh boy I can and I heard
you were around here so I thought I'd
come see if I could say a lie a ranger
yes we worked on that together yeah okay
and I say I don't know anything about
archery really but I say something that
like is is reminiscent to you
immediately of drills that we used to do
together that like puts you in some kind
of like preparation stance tried just to
like test your memory yeah and you're
like it's immediate and and I'm just I'm
like beaming with pride like aha you
still remember after all these years
that's that's practically all I do now
operation efg best one next one right
well we you've caused a kind of an
interesting time there is a festival
coming up and I really want to catch up
with you but we have a bunch of chores
to do so can we enlist you in in helping
that's not generally what I do but
anything you need of course okay
all right how long are you in town for
really just the next couple days okay
are you selling weapons here in right I
tell you a bow if you need one or one of
a couple short swords I have I don't I
don't have much more I try to be very
light okay is there is there something
that you needed from me that you you
came to read large for just a hug all
right oh my god is that Rosie's face
just like her eyes closed and her little
like old lady cheetah rays and she holds
out her tiny little arms yeah I hold out
my big man on it yeah very muscular as a
bargeman oh yeah
a big hug and I give you a sweet little
kiss on that how's that giggle okay
that's when when I was much smaller she
used to do that to me oh nice yeah
lettuce now it's
first yeah
we are you and I need to drink and we
need to talk but we will do that later
yes we will get extremely up and
we will tell story so that's that's I
don't I don't drink
okay well I'll drink for the both of us
I bet that's fine we will trade some
stories about your problem I my brother
again was murdered in a bar so I am for
the verse - yeah well this is kind of a
bar again I am I do not walk into a room
I don't know how to walk out over here
do you know how to get back into this
room because I know let's still into it
after a couple of drinks
well I don't do that I don't need it oh
you'll be quiet
who's but you got any heroin I stay
getting high yeah I'm gonna head back
into the kitchen and see what I can cook
but you might seek out we have a drew it
in our party and it sounds like she
might you might be a weapon Fitch that
you you might be able to sell her some
gear that would be useful to her so I
think she's upstairs if you want to try
to find her I not got fuse Italy and I'm
to make your favorite kind of moon elf
cookies snorkel blast yeah this is this
is Rosie to a tee yeah so you are still
dig you're digging through this box
you've you've sort of gone back and are
trying to categorize a lifetime of
recipes and you find you find a couple
recipes that say LSD at different points
on the sheet what and I think yeah
alright LSD exactly okay so
I'm gonna assume that these are the
right ones indeed well now so they're
both they both claim to be cornerstones
Oh cornerstones wait for rooms oh but
wait you have to you have two different
recipes cornerstones and you're not a
hundred percent sure which one of these
is would be the actual one I say thank
you I'm not do I still need his help
translating well let's see you need to
know Goblin ah I don't have it
I can read any language so I usually
know it but I'm strolling over the door
right now okay although yeah party
indoors man so this is a carriage house
can I go is around the front what do
they do they lock the carriage up or is
this like a stable but it's basically
like it sounded like it hadn't been
cleaned out for a while you think that
it is a carriage house it has two broad
doors in front and a door on the side
but you think that it has not seemed
carriage house use in the traditional
sense for a while you think it's sort of
gone more to storage you could did it's
free with free we ran out of the ground
corner itself as well kept but this
doesn't seem like it's the same
obviously like architectural II it's
similar to the the main house but it's
not it isn't well trafficked people
don't get over here much do you have
knock it's not a druid thing resident I
don't think he's been I think I'm like I
do my kids can I do one father character
I could try to blow apart the door but I
don't think that prophet would
appreciate it actually I did or opens
yeah you bash that you know that door
and then you mend it oh yeah but I can
only mend something that's Matthew like
it's a foot than smash the lock that's
true I could crush I could punch a hole
in the door like it sends sweet sweet
wheezy in there to unlock it from inside
I can break the door it's just a fine
mike lizanne if you commended I can
break yeah whatever anything you need
how was
the door jam oh yeah do we have any
purchases so the thing I was gonna ask
is can I cast can I get it's a ritual
can I do unseen servant through a place
I can spy and just invoke velvet on the
other side of the door or misty step
through it maybe you know but I don't
get lost over there three singers barn
adventure I think about it Christmas
Rowan adventures Saturday mornings these
long tails yes
material yeah you'd be surprised how
many oysters you get out of hay alone
alright so with that in mind
hey it's gonna take a whole other hour
to instantiate velvet so instead I'm
gonna I'm gonna see if I can sneak him
in velvet yeah I'm gonna I'm gonna see
if I get him in under the door through
the keel but I will go ahead and look
through anything I can and peep and use
misty Stenson growing here I host a film
he's PSPs material he's ghost he is in
his glory oh yeah God yeah this is this
is sophisticated
he's corporeal he just has an invisible
body ah welcome to Dungeons and Dragons
Mikey I mean it's getting it's like I
say Knight is definitely fast
approaching here man the bar so you try
you're trying to look in yeah man but
can I see anything you can you don't
know you can there is actually yeah yeah
there is a there is a light inside
it's a carriage house that should be hey
everybody I might work on cleaning out
the carriage house but I think somebody
looked like a lit a lit
lantern or match in there I gotta get in
there before the whole place burns down
can I see the side of the size of the
light yeah just it's soft and sort of
just rushes along the surfaces inside
you can see
I look like bed frames old sheets pulled
over so even though I can't say stories
or pots like a candle light yeah it's
just a soft cast yeah uh all right I'll
be in there if anybody needs me I shoot
through there misty step okay we will
come back to this night as I said night
is coming through roar once I went to
here in Ireland so my experience with
Ireland to deal with it okay so my
experience is with Ireland it's like
nothing would happen until like in by
6:00 the town that I was in was like a
ghost town everything closes and then at
7:00 it's like more people than I
thought lived there are all back and
that is basically what happens like you
haven't been here for very many dinners
and people love this place but they
don't see profit and they don't know
what's happening they're coming in and
sitting and taking seats at what you
presume must be the places they're
accustomed to sitting but they're
expecting some things that aren't there
and there is some confusion sort of in
the common room the casting glances over
it addressed little place the stew the
sort of chill breeze that the fireplace
is not going like this is this is not
the this is not the venue this is not
the drowning courier that they know
about okay customer satisfaction it's
not good right now oh it's like exactly
I'm so seeing everyone come in like this
and so you can be used been sulking
upstairs no no I had a vibe at stairs
and then I came back down and I was
staring at the fireplace right oh you
used to be stood on the chair just there
had been a fire so just staring it not a
fire going but seeing as people come in
all right look around see that there
crumbly the only thing I could think to
do would be to fireball let's you
produce flame laying in the flake in the
chair like that
produce the flame I just hurl it and
then the fireplace I'm assuming just
goes the flue is probably open the flue
my college is going green flame very
good that's in the natural color it
looks like just what is this yeah listen
you sold the but no I mean
basically it's like a sulfurous eldritch
flame that you sort of nonchalantly
throw into the belly of this furnace
there's no pleasing like I know it's
crackle it's like that from some corner
it gurgles yeah that flame well normal
gutters it's like the cysts thing of
like a tallow candle yeah mr. hasting
and popping everyone scrambles for their
Applebee's review cards at their table
like one one one one how did we do oh
it's obvious please they just don't know
what's happening like you don't know if
they're just please necessarily but
they're they're expecting people to to
treat them as though they're regulars
bare minimum denier you have high
charisma yeah oh yeah I'm dripping with
it okay yeah oh we can tell let's can
kick is it possible for you to run house
brother's mouth for uh no house yeah the
maitre d yeah yeah but where the D
stands for Dragon yeah
your Dragonborn yeah I can do that yes
so I gotta just sit people down
yeah and smooths make them feel welcome
you some 60 years as lizard royalty the
erotic lizard right start barking orders
what I am King
me stop it's quite snap out of it like
you statistically on your sheet you have
very high charisma oh yeah that's only
exactly my god yes that does not come
through he and role play like what you
just described well in 60 years my
brains all messed up but it like it
works for him that's the thing is like
whatever he acts like I'm assuming if
you have really high charisma that just
works for people to you're like all that
[Applause]
away with everything
enjoy your meal it's like one of those
like hip restaurants where the waitstaff
is always rude to you want business and
that's why people go people like oh
maybe this is keep are you just standing
around are you doing anything cueing
well yeah I'm kind of just awkwardly
trying to interact with my friends on
this new adventure all right you went in
the background just cooking um get stuff
done I'm looking at QA there you go look
back you go be singer okay we got to
keep this place from closing down for
one night do you think you could we
could probably give you a room yeah
absolutely
great let's get everybody some drinks
well it's like look looking around like
that's what people want right that's
human-like isn't it good good not quite
comfortable in the bar I don't know
because because I've never been here
before it's incumbent upon me as your
dungeon master can you help you
understand the layout of this place
internally imagine just as you entered
the door previously to your left is a
wooden bar yeah
behind it and then around a corner into
the darkness is the kitchen wide common
area perhaps ten tables in total over to
the right there is a taciturn elf named
walnut dawn grass who has just caused
the fire to start up but to the left of
that is a small stage by this stage
there is a stairway that goes up to the
rooms of this in mm-hmm
now you know the situation you can
interact with these pieces in any way
you like what
well walnut has graciously asked me to
mix drinks and whatever whatever the one
I call mother
whatever whatever helps to write I'm I'm
just I I must say I'm not very good at
it but I can I can do no it's not yeah
it's not like a cocktail bar situation
it's yeah the Kosmos okay you know like
doing drinks what do you like you're
talking to people you know talk to these
people
anything he's interacting with daria
morgendorffer
I just need help just whatever you need
that can you uh can you play anything
can do dance just I do I
I would much rather serve drinks than
play in this format again again the
thing my brother was you guys may be
dropping very specifically on this one
sorry painful memory yeah okay some
people watch like you know their whole
family is their whole society but or
sixty years of their life right I'm
sorry a singer and I will tend to the
bar yes yes okay great excellent
I walked through the bar like that's
very very cool he's uncomfortable but he
was very obliging and I'm like okay this
is one of the good kids I guess yeah
and I go don't you want to take orders
to a minute oh yeah we need a wait for
that yeah you know what it's fine I got
it
no she goes oh what do you want I'm yeah
that you can contend that I'm listening
I'm like oh you know what I don't I'll
take care of the carriage house I'm
gonna send velvet out there if he's
welcome you can route your commands to
him via my mind oh sweet
yeah I fax what I want to yeah I think
there's only I can show him what to do
but if you it see 24/7 this ghost is now
like a nest thermostat yeah exactly
it's app driven yeah he's a little I'm
an actor me yeah exactly
Alexa tell ghost they say so you you you
see you see velvet sort of waft ghostily
and to the frontal minimally and then
and then take up it's a new adjective it
just in hit ghost ghostily ghosted Todd
did he sort of sales over by the bar and
puts a hand up perfect you may want to
put a new drape over in because there's
their velvety is wearing it real ready
it's not looking hot it's on me is fine
when you make the drinks just give it to
this guy and then I put a platter on it
so you know if it stays perfectly oh
yeah it's it's a it's like setting it
like on a stone altar it's just like
right there it's like born
yeah instantiated 100% to be a moving
conscious shelf it's like 1 R 2 is
serving drinks in the large classic
scene yeah yeah that's the hole so so
what's what's walnuts as well as well
not continuing to look into the depths
of the flames no well I got out one hour
to your table and went seven what do you
want first yeah what do you what do you
want
do you know profit yeah is this profit
here now prop is not here Rob is not
here I know do you know when do improv
is do you know when she's gonna be back
a couple of days and then this you're
speaking to a man almost spherical in
shape
sure and as his wife looks at him and
says where's prophet I go prophet put us
in charge I don't I don't think she
would have I don't think that she would
have done that it would have been her or
Audra probably and want list and she
goes I cannot impress upon you how
little patience I have for what's
happening I need to keep this place
running for three days so that we don't
lose our corporate headquarters what do
you want to eat or drink she was to
place calls out to ales two pies and
points to Kiwi to ale pies coming up and
she looks at denarii she goes entertain
some of the people I don't know I
thought the door yeah I'm at the door
because mine yeah yeah I mean however
you want to yeah I mean how do you how
do you wanna how do you want to present
Benjamin yeah I'll see them turn the
charm on yeah I go around like a yeah
Jamil but you're getting good with you
meal think your guns the whole time I'm
not drop finger guys yeah it's like it's
like a reverse pollination type scenario
where it's like you're sort of you sort
of follow behind the tables walnut has
served and she has collect all
complaints when she has she has touted
them into what market researchers must
certainly believe to be the ultimate
consumers
you see so you suspect average purchases
are up you think you think that there is
a kind of terror that has been implanted
and now they're they're buying extra
items in an effort to please her from
the kitchen right you here to to round
stammers with two little pies come to
round stairs and two pies this is
marvelous though no no I just I see like
the bar like where the cameras live it
bar yeah and then you just see like two
little hands and eyes think it's exactly
looking for the Bell here Kiwis say yes
chef yeah go up and I look at velvet and
I start talking to him like he needs to
know what the hell to do here you're
gunning for him like listen you're a
party I'm like TTC these these are
supposed to go and then I stop for a
second you go cut this you need to tell
this this this little ghost to to take
the food and take all the drinks to the
people that I point to okay I'm facing
that so so as yes or says not seeing the
inside of it was like I know that do
what you have to do what walnut said
you're locked in the says to do and just
do that and don't please don't drop
anything please thank you yes so you can
yeah exactly exactly so when drinks are
set on the platter it will take them to
where drinks are not perfect
and profit only has one barrel she
always one style of ale here perfect it
could be made here there's only one
style so it's not like there's a deep
roster this is obviously not at a place
to come for craft brews everybody gets a
nail everybody gets around to you today
oh we got he's got the round steamer
hey boy nice cool ones come ones hot
ones cold steamers died in the window so
while you're while you're doing these
like with capacity that only
grandmothers have authentically
perfected you have these two cornerstone
recipes in your left hand and you are
making steamers with the right hand
right dang I haven't looked yet
yeah and at this point I need someone
who can speak Goblin neither of you
speak up with me to going I'm not very
good okay and you're the only one but
you've locked yourself in the carriage
ah I don't know that it's locked so
tight so I try the door tomorrow yeah
you giving there's a latch on the inside
that you can so you can like so I can
come out yeah oh great
did you watch out to investigate the
laser eyes don't try it no I guess I
overhear that like oh okay yes I can
come to that in just a second so but
before I do that so I open the door and
then I'm gonna go and investigate this
source real quick okay so if it's a
candle rythms nothing yeah yeah yeah so
yeah so as here is you don't you as you
are moving around this like haste this
this sort of like randomly assembled
pyre of you know ancient wood unlike I
said ancient sheets dented chamber pots
like it's just the the the place has
just become a catch-all for any you know
decorative from yeah the DNC for the
junk drawer exactly look at this but but
the pattern yes I'm a PA right the
pattern that's cast out through this
mesh of wood has this blue cast and so
the shadows that surround you inside
this enclosed space are informed by that
geometry mm-hmm is it in sight ya know
as I said it's almost like looking
through a hedge or some I see it's like
a heap a pile of wooden frames and so
forth
oh okay I you sort of maneuver around it
yeah let me attempt to do that as so I
can lay eyes on whatever the source of
this of this light is because I presume
it's on the other side of yeah it's just
it's just a big heap right yeah you trip
on a chamber pot you think it over and
just the sludge rich like mrs.
buttersworth but you can see so that as
I suggested that shadow sort of emits
through this but there is a portion
around the front where the doors were
the front doors the gates of the of the
carriage house would be there's a larger
shaft of blue light that isn't as
occluded okay am i able to navigate over
there bodily yeah I mean cuz you're
you're tripping and moving on things
you're you sort of you know trying to
sit yourself through yeah the King is
creepy ever tighter around the torso
it's not all adventure it's not all
swords and coins and sometimes there's a
chamber pot it's all adventure what's
next what's next
I can't wait the thing that comes to
mind is that I could I could send lagari
through because he's much smaller and I
could pierce through his vision rather
than throw myself in front of whatever
this thing is especially now that it
doesn't look like it's like a lamp light
sure let me go ahead and do that then I
take I find a place where I'm stable
since I will be blind yeah while there
and I whisper to lagari go seek out that
that light source we will and we will
share visions my friend together
together so Swami site
exactly so he he drips down the Kings
framework what's 100% delight so there's
and so there's down out of the pan zone
and then you know and then wriggles and
then wriggles through so this this
portion up here has a plainly
manufactured things have been scooted
aside here in such a way as to allow
passage but passage for someone small
hmm okay so look I got ele Gotti hits
the ground and starts to sort of move
himself through he can he can move very
very easily through this mesh of wood
and metal and tattered sheets yeah and
as he gets through he and he enters a
kind of chamber like the overarching
wood there is a place in the center of
it it's with like chair legs yeah
exactly but then down in the bottom of
it there is a little area of safety and
protection and then as he goes in you
can see three children and the children
are themselves the source of the light
and as ligado Rises his way through and
then arches up like this the dagger
gripped in his tail ready to work right
the children all look at lagari at once
and then wink out vanish oh the connie
would you do set that dagger down for
just a minute
I told you never again
it's a baker's dozen do I do I do I
recognize those those those three small
children but you might are they some
sort of a of a nymph
a dryad perhaps some sort of an elven
what's the form give me an ontology give
me an intelligence check you're gonna
get much on one I'm very smart
that's a 22 oh Jesus and 1906 I was like
you or a piece of doesn't it at 22
know exactly you are almost certain that
these are the children in the painting
over the fireplace oh wow like in the
ring in the form gosh what little forms
of the the drawings children yeah but
the Gaudi has that Locati it has the run
of the place now there's it's a ghost
free environ well I know most of it yeah
yeah
I always have the taste for child who's
just looking brother sounds good Ali and
to find some more feast let's let's poke
around I guess like is there like have
they made themselves comfortable they
seem to be able to vanish but do they
have like like bedding and such like
have they made a mess in there yeah that
there is there is a folded blanket it's
not ratty in any way there's a folded
blanket a pillow there is also a small
hammer with a pic on the back like a
mining tool but small for a fine use Wow
there is a dagger and there's a short
sword and they're all sort of they're
all in a pile like like ready to ready
to get with a child five yeah they're
also they're also they're all small like
even the short sword is probably the
largest of these implements geez but as
I said there's but there is also a
number of
as ladanyi was coming in they looked up
from papers papers remain parchment
absolutely Oh Scrolls some of them
rolled up let's read those papers okay
so there is all kinds of money please
so there's all kinds of papers that
Locati can can look at yeah he can steal
sort of do you just basically command
him to yeah read an deputies paper is
exactly funny use the tip of the dagger
- this is gently so gentle the best of
times it was the worst of times
so legato rears up over the papers and
spreads them out with his tail so that
he can take a peek for you in a way that
actually makes sense and a lot of it a
lot of it doesn't a lot of it without
the context that they must have had
doesn't make sense right away you have
to you have to incorporate things that
you know yourself okay I do that yeah
you have to roll no no there are there
are there is one of these one of these
papers looks like a map of the the
breathing apparatus of the wandering
crypt that the party was in Oh Oh God
the crypts cpap the crypts has a seat
bap it has it has
whatever that thing is you know claps
that's what the deuced it I only took 20
episodes I got there first
that's right this is this is our 20th
episode yes congratulations yeah we did
everybody hey but you you see one but
you see another there is another map
that has the same environment the same
structure in terms of its layout but
instead of a fountain in the middle
they've drawn a picture of a statue okay
all right I'm shook okay I don't like
that at all
so so I the guy look we gotta get out of
here the scram and now I will physically
like tear this dome open if I can how is
it how is it held together I want to
grab those you you you think that you
might be able to sort of wriggle in I
mean it's it's for children right but
you think you think you might be able to
wriggle in on the side or ligado could
pull them out one by one okay well I
mean I don't know that we're a lot of
danger of them returning what do they
look like they look like real boys and
girls here right about yes before it
looks like it looks like children
playing in a fort yeah everybody I found
some ghost children in the carriage
house and there's a map and a knife and
there's and they ran away and then right
here a mess in here ya go
yeah we're running out of bottomless
breadsticks to crank out today don't you
make me a liar porky we stuck at the bar
here every beer yeah see he's like
grimaces and this is a single dear
little malcolm mcdowell yes it's the
same draft that I said that night I have
whipped up a batch of snirkle blasters
and have slipped them to you I'm just
like beer hell yeah yeah exactly that's
the medicine right no way that's
grandmother yes there is a bit more
layers no I'm trying to but I'm trying
to go first okay well no you're right I
can wriggle my way in and and just try
to grab as much as I can including the
weapons if I can get them absolutely so
you you are comparing your your own
information your own knowledge with what
you see on the sheet
in their version of the same place
there's no Blackgate indicated okay it's
just a passage that goes deeper in and
they have maps beyond that oh yes me
take get me those are maps
I got maps I got weapons maps
it's weird kids wait they're in here we
got them what do they have maps up we
need to spray oh yeah sure we're gonna
get a good box it goes we've got kids
again they take the bait back to the
nest so I'm gonna break it's a den this
is no I'm saying like the additional I
think it's so I think this is the one
our encrypt it doesn't look exactly like
ours but they've got more info than we
had yes what are they doing exactly so
as you're relating this you're looking
at these other sheets and then you see
you see the the map that comes after the
sort of antechamber that you explored
yeah but they have it broken down by
season so the room after they have one
map for winter and another map for
spring but the internal structure is
completely different in each of these
seasons Wow
in winter it is a series of concentric
rings you can see that the central core
has three doors and then a ring around
that has two doors and there's a third
ring around that that provides sort of
like the final layer you can't tell if
like elevation but you can tell that
this is clearly a like a sophisticated
construct yeah but the spring version is
is staircases at various angles they've
done their best in two dimensions to try
to capture it and you can tell that just
parts of it have just been scribbled out
and then as you you you you flip over
for the next map and you see a picture
of a smiling boy
and a smiling girl and then a girl with
a frown and then this sheet says in
order
Miffy specious and 10t and at the top it
says drawn incorporated that got me okay
that's that wait if you said you think
you have a mouth with the wandering
crypt so wanna stop center track she was
talking to someone it just looks up
because I'm assuming that when we talk
to each other there's no and you just
hear get those pieces of paper to our
office immediately
I'm not in the dark and you can't see
that I feel the evening again and you're
missing the nodding yeah answer
obedience I grab it all and I I hustle
out of there as fast as I can
cuz I don't know what these what these
beings are spoked yeah yeah he got
smooth you know um from the exact door
yeah as you are exactly it's like ghosts
in our backyard so as you as you are
wriggling your way back out the
structure teeters a little bit yes over
you then it squeaks it doesn't like
being pushed against a horse for it it's
not it's that is not that is not what
it's about right now but the double
doors at the front can simply there's
that it's just barred on the inside okay
it'd be easy to open that up so that you
can come back and try to resolve this
try to clean it out proper tomorrow if
you wanna I mean for the other let me do
that so if I wriggle out gently shaman
hop that off this requires more than a
Velvet Touch yeah
so yeah top pop that off who go out the
front doors with my stuff
yeah apps question yeah and exam exactly
other entrance and it's like you have
you have the papers in your hands and
there's always a little bony hand
reaching out from reaching out from
inside the cloak just trying to pot them
yeah find not all that nature is meant
for you that need me you were so happy
in that dark blue this is important
stuff we want to raft or something later
yeah I entered through I have no idea
what's the scene I just I just be ahead
I find you okay so now that you've
you've emerged from the carriage house
yeah feeling 10 years older not sixty no
yeah right so nice I win not 64 a down
just like Izzy you there's an even great
a thicker richer shock of white along
the side or but the warmth of the light
coming from the end and you can see
imagine imagine that it's some kind of
like kitchen tactics game and there is
an AoE around walnut on grass so that
when she passes people are eating food
and drinking in an optimal way yeah
in a precise way that is about doing it
and not doing other things and they're
leaving so there's a place a pretty
solid churn going in there I always hate
to interrupt it like my eyes like snap
over at you why do I put these like I
see them and I use them with three
figures those of the children that I
look at that's the last page with the
drawings of the three children on it and
walnut very carefully takes it and knows
that technically this falls under
Rosie's realm
potentially and she looks at them older
maps she goes I got a document this
immediately and then she was a good
Thurston goes you're working with you're
working with beasting or at the barn out
orders you gotta go
and she's like shut up and then like
runs upstairs and she needs to go make a
like make copies mugs did so right now
right now Kiwi you sort of feel like
you're at the eye of the storm like at
the centre point where this mechanism is
just sort of whirling around you and
you're you're worried about your limbs
honestly to a certain extent you're
worried about being shredded if you
reach too far out of this circumscribed
zone your station out there do some tea
since you're not drinking any ale yeah
thank you keeping you nice and hydrated
I don't know that's what he does thank
you I wrote these hydration teas friend
could you use another set of hands
I saw I sensed there was something amiss
in whatever this kerfuffle is I I'm
ready for action like I I'm very bored
by bar work yes so I was actually
already in the process of grabbing as
many tankers as I can adjust filling
them up run them to every table last
call 6:38
do I see you like who's on the other
side of this it's yeah it's it's it's me
leaning over the bar yeah
like talons like that I should I come
over in a helper what are we doing well
I'm like dude should I continue doing
this or should I just serve everyone
free beer she won't be that bad she
won't be mad at you if you're gone we're
trying to keep this place running but I
heard about a minute children and to
think what time is it in bar time in
real bar time 12 o'clock somewhere
yeah I don't I don't know that I don't
think of I haven't conveyed to you
I have you haven't given me your mind
number yet so I've only been brought my
sleeve number yeah exactly it's about
8:30 okay what times is the place really
close you have no idea
all right maybe we're closing early for
the holiday today it's called 86 round
steamers yeah like I said I'll keep it
no one I think we need to come in on
time and under budget she was like I'm
fine doing whatever you want but my key
is like I didn't travel all the way from
Dallas ' I said I I come around
the side of the bar yeah we can't give
out more than it's been ordered but I I
have an idea I instruct I get Lagasse
out put the dagger down or keep it if
you want to maybe we can use it to open
bottles and then now do I have a sense
of how strong the Lizard King is in
terms of what like vigorous or backing I
want to create a coyote ugly scenario
with up on and the desiccated change
sexy dancing yeah to take over or help
can they do that you want you I lean to
the lizard king and I say food service
is the true adventure
the last adventure the last adventure he
has no strength in his body is that
right
no no he's very flexible as well so you
want him to you want him to do polish
how will you bow Avia's arraignment he'd
be nude as he is because I assume he's
so dried it's like a wiry piece of jerky
I think Chris is definitely out of touch
with what people want yeah behind the
restaurant yeah
what's here one is their drink and they
want it fast and they want it cold if
it's in a Soviet was dead thing I wear
sometimes I can provide that it's like a
franchise opportunities available or we
could just pick everyone out you guys
wasn't early for the holiday yeah you're
welcome - all right Christ yeah so I'm
gonna just bacon eat this situation okay
and just be like just start screaming at
everyone and be like we found baby
ghosts memories closing early and you
better tell her that this was amazing
can I get the intimidation role oh you
better believe I already other died
already
oh I do get those five it says still
loaded I don't have an advantage so that
is decent yeah yeah you're like
everybody's just like like while they're
chewing their last bites of food like
they start like the individual people at
the tables start piling up their own
plate sit-ups and they bring them up to
the bar and then they walk out and like
look back in and then look back out and
then will they walk out the front they
look back in the window yeah pushing on
one by
like thanks thanks thanks I'm great see
ya I'm squatting down never behind the
bar and talking to the Lizard King and
ligardi addressing both of them these
drinks gonna come in fast so we gotta
stay on top of things you could tell the
guy what to do make sure you hit the
ails out from here and if you need him
to run the food - from the window to you
then we and then I see that all
everybody's leave the dishes stacking
and the Lizard King he's like visibly
like oh yeah he's pretty compressed
right now I mean he can he can stretch
himself out if he wants to and he's
gonna be big if he wants to but he's
having fun okay he's doing his thing all
right
functionally speaking you wear him like
armor Yeah right now I'm imagining like
a vest yeah exactly a stretchy and a
stretchy
dusty vest oh I guess we're closing back
in the cloak everybody and I thought of
him as a second tape like his arms we're
tighter on your neck and he has a cape
you wear under your cage yeah yeah this
we looks and sequins yeah
Liberace like yeah so they're so they
are they are on their way everybody is
is moving out you can see them sort of
adjusting the tables back to where they
were you're fine yeah no no fix it okay
no as they see as they see the serpent
coiling back around me and this other
lizard thing crawling in like you're
okay to leave those there look we'll get
them it's no worries
come back soon they don't believe you
they still make me just do you think
this is some kind of test
ultimately everyone blows out the door
and it's sort of SWE's okay and then
speech it yeah we did it job well done
please doesn't burn down and I'm like
[Laughter]
my men brothers all of the mess oh yeah
come on it's chaotic the whole dorm
yeah like two hairs are out of place and
I'm a little like this campus
hi bun just come on Bund give me on all
that Davy made copies yeah I mean you do
need to have a team meal I'm sorry
no is he he he was hit a pickup line on
you and oh just you're so on brand run
it back okay it's fine it's fine
let's keep going no I say you that
doesn't mind your back how does it make
you feel which box you say you do a
pick-up line
that's how frequently you ignore it it's
okay I hear I sense that some outreach
is being made you're good to friends
Rosie shocked at your level of eroticism
whoa discovered it's a bar the bars
closed tonight and you each draft with a
minimum of head I look at you are you
are you finished with the with the rain
can we let's discuss this ain't you yes
fine I'm coming downstairs now yeah it's
done and she has definitely did it but
she was looking at something else when
they do that oh it was her letter um I
got a plate of snuggle Buster's pot of
tea set it down on a table let's go over
this walnut comes down with the ones
that she has dutifully copied uh maps
yeah yes uh yeah give me those maps yes
and it lays out that lays out the maps
each one and then she holds the picture
of the kids and she's looking at the
painting on the wall and she's looking
at the kids will hid the painting on the
wall and does this about like 20 times
and look at queuing goes like I mean
those look like the same kids right yes
quiet it's not just me
I just like to feel useful
just lives down she goes alright serious
I don't now here's the question so there
they are corporeal yeah they seem to see
me there's something pretending to be
them or some what I like that I love
that's your first your first they need a
past
yeah not an ethicist where do they go
where what happened yeah
would I be what can I roll for this to
determine what type of a thing it was
what are you are oh wow now that will
determine whatever information I wanted
lucky I wonder the magical nature of
them they seem to have yeah ha barking
ha ha sent from Arcana
it's 15 yeah yeah use do you think that
they might have been it could have been
a ghost I mean there was there is no I
mean typically typically in that setting
when ghosts don't just like appear and
leave yeah they typically are bound to a
specific place do you I mean like
they're around a Pacific place because
of something unresolved yeah do they
make maps often you've never seen ghost
hunter I'm not a ghost expert that it
goes to my ghost so I can't speak but
you you think that if you think that if
they were ghosts authentic ghosts with
the ghost seal yeah yeah exactly that
they they wouldn't they wouldn't just be
materialized or disappear right that
they would still be there somewhere so
you think that they have used this these
photographs of these children or
paintings or wherever they are to assume
a form I think it's weird that um
prophet would ask us to clean out this
carriage house which if the ghost did
not make that nest or that forth
then those that belonged to our children
and has not been disturbed in a very
long time why would she ask us to go in
there and and clear it like it was just
full of junk she wasn't aware of it
I don't know how long it's been closed
for do I have any sense of how old that
room is fine of a chamber pod with
contents that had not dried yeah a
couple decades you think at least yeah
okay you don't hold on Oh mm-hmm
I knew spectral yeah for the door is
also open at this point so we're free to
re-explore okay yeah let's get in there
we go in we see the mess on the floor
good for us here seriously
come on nano there's a there's a toilet
sighs this time it wasn't me so you got
you guys you guys are you filing in the
open doors yeah in front Kiwi you feel a
little tug on your on your pant leg
[Music]
there is a child with a small pouch on
the bar no no basically as you guys have
exited the car and are out here as
everyone else has moved in liner in the
pocket yeah that's ridiculous against
all that's regularly there's a small tug
on the pant leg and you turn to see a
half a child there with a little pouch
of money and she says can you please
give this to the grandmother I'm
hesitant but I take it right say yes as
soon you're trying to handle your side
of this bargain yeah it is but even
before you can get three words out
she is turned and then his down now he
just disappears mmm it's very trusting I
think at this point I have also my bow
and pulled out exactly now you know
there's lousy with kids yeah ghosts
all right how many maps do you have a
certain point it's just about harvesting
maps from ghost children yeah that's the
medication sure yes so you're you're
you're ready but your first instinct oh
wait when anything unexpected happens is
to be ready that's that's right you the
direction the party is not in exactly
exactly so as you as you this obviously
this structure is is not a hundred
percent stable yeah you talked about the
little fort with it yeah exactly exactly
but is there's there's going to be
members of the party for which it's
easier to enter into a place the size of
a child
certainly 100% just the legs kicking out
faster than you are
yeah do we need do we need lighting
that's not a spell that I will waste
here can we light it
torch some channel I can do a dark
vision is it better than mine well what
you have dark vision too so I don't know
wait no idea I am that's a that's up to
60 feet yes yes okay yeah you should be
able to see pretty good in there too
it sounds like but yeah you're yeah I'm
the I'm the right size yes I almost
brought it down and I haven't been a
move taught me that so I'll do dark
vision myself or no I was talking about
Gary what you're willing creature I
touch myself on the nose now I have the
ability to see in the dark duration
which is eight hours I see up to sixty
feet hang out in there as long as you
want yeah up to eight hours oh yeah
okay so I take off my cloak and I headed
to Kiwi and then I I guess I I crawl in
there yeah I have a bad back
yeah yeah my hands come on I I crawl in
yeah so you can even stand up in here
okay I mean this is this is the
appropriate
this is the appropriate adventure rich
venue for adventurous seeking children
and haffley and grandmothers apparently
we have a lot in common
it's optimal and here like untouched by
the terror that cthe RIS experienced you
can see that this is basically like a
base camp kids treehouse port yeah you
can see there's a couple desiccated
oranges some porn there's nothing like
that that's located oranges yeah just
look just like like clearly they were
massing things here a long time ago okay
um
do I see anything that causes me
interest that actually must be further
no no that's that's the best thing they
got okay that's the best thing they cut
in there all right
there's several perception on those oh I
just heard a beep from the elicit device
shadow council obviously mayor lemurs
please you we're gonna come up to our
our commercial break
obviously subscribers don't see
commercials they see cool see team stuff
so just let us do the whole thing
something to consider in any event we'll
see you shortly
bellboy hello I'm here freaky whore
camps and all the other people that I
constantly refer to myself as no when
last we saw our heroes they had
penetrated the inner sanctum of drawn
incorporated a adventuring company of
some renown specifically - three
children a couple decades ago their
their adventures are more or less lost
to time lost of time but our adventurers
have found some artifacts related to
their travels back in time continue to
turn the place over yeah grandmother
okay I'm gonna keep investigating juni
do perception should absolutely do
perception checks okay
here we go I will also take advantage on
us ho ho because I really want to
perceive the hell out of it okay and
that's it okay so a total of sixteen
sixteen on you do ascertain something
what what is it well all the papers that
he had secured viola Gotti they've been
removed from the center of this and he
had picked it up whoa can you pick them
up in great haste and so there are
things that he missed here in the center
below one of the board's of the base in
the carriage house his clear has clearly
been raised and lowered many times okay
okay
pull it up myself you can too werewolf
Trevor yeah you can hear you can hear
the wood squeaking as you pry how do you
how do you pry this thing up yeah with
my bare hands yeah you just get
down boys you see lot base yeah well it
up yeah you jacked that you find you
find a piece of charcoal inside this
hole it said you find a piece of
charcoal inside this char hole oh that
makes sense
thanks for you I did absolutely not
again never again you see looking glass
cloth like a glass inside this hole and
then you see a few additional old scraps
of paper okay I don't
oh we can grab the straps okay - treats
those scraps
of a werewolf obviously so as you're
looking through these sheets they say
each of them says a person is practicing
writing their name and so you see you
see 10 T and portentous written it must
be 20 different times just sort of
trying to dial it in sir you see a bunch
of pictures just of a girl's face but on
each of them each of them says 10 T or
portentous but the faces are not the
same okay wait what all right so do the
ones do all the ones that say partenza
look the same and all the ones that say
10 T look the same all of these they are
varied okay they are substantially
varied in shape sometimes it's the ears
okay is it skill or it's obviously not
yeah it was to be the same are these are
these skill portraits well I mean even a
child can make a circle multiple times
these things together combined with the
looking-glass it's some kind of study it
seems like okay all right what's on the
other scraps there this is just
someone's private this is someone's
private collection okay do the the faces
any of the faces look familiar to me
based on what we've seen in that yeah
one of them looks like the girl in that
in the portrait inside okay none of
these none of the faces have a smile on
them they're all either neutral or
agitated okay and we know I remember
we've talked about this we've covered
this several times but in character
Rosie knows that Hortensia is one of
Provinces children indeed
and she is a youngest one who is one of
the ones presumed dead that's correct
okay and the other her other daughter is
also presumed dead correct that's the
current timeline okay okay I know man is
also dead
who is dead we killed to me so the
charcoal use your werewolf die this
appears to be the charcoal I take it is
what has been used to draw on this this
piece pieces that's your suspicion okay
and usually there's a case to be made
there's a looking-glass
can I use the looking-glass to examine
this further and to find anything else
of note on this paper you think it might
just be a little mirror oh I see if he
looking glass not magnify glass good so
she's trying to draw herself she's
trying to draw self-portraits yeah that
is a interpretation interesting of these
events okay Amy's got three no no do I
see anything else in here of note to
grab yeah I'll just gather up all this
stuff and bring it there's a couple of
buttons I mean it's not much
can I wrote perception on those buttons
yeah sure I'll grab the buttons again
it's fine okay okay what you want this
RIS a friend too bad no you go ahead and
roll I was gonna make sure there's
nothing else you don't you know yeah
yeah
because there's nothing apparent there's
a secret inside the secret is rare
statistically speaking why even roll you
won't find it yeah do you I'm in a
wrong do wrong
roley's get a quarter you did that it's
a 13 the best the best thing is as far
as you know hi so I still have on me at
least this is how I Alyssa King he's
right here
close to my heart you just looked like
to reiterate your personal inventory so
everybody knows the role play
fifteen minutes no I have I'm hanging on
to the dagger from the that we from a
gaudy sticker right oh you mean the
small dagger inside small their geta
you're a you're a weapons man no no I
started yeah what is the quality of this
dagger is it what is it well mater's it
like that of a child should I absolutely
exception recession
yeah big boy yeah oh you're gonna love
this I mean the big night might be a
knife it's the worst finger
I could tell sharp you don't know how to
use like I'll save it for a table talk
there please I was gonna say I'm handing
you the dagger and because of my my
gentle caress yeah I I don't even notice
the dagger yeah you say you forget to
examine it where clearly what is it is
it is it a value or is it do we think
that they stole these or did they make
them it's not made of wood it's a real
metal dagger I'm just yeah it's it's a
it's a real metal dagger it has a decent
edge mm-hmm
but it is it is not like top tier yeah
but it wasn't a connoisseur this is not
a toy right this is not a toy I take the
scraps while you guys are doing this and
I bring them over to you you have dark
vision so you can see everything
everything and I hand them over to you
and I say what do you make of these okay
Dewey
know about this dice you trying to crank
up the old metagame engine there no I
look at it and I go children are just
like terrible artists huh yeah they're
bad and everything um but so it's it
just says it's it's 10t there's no like
other versions of this where it's
anybody else
she says part time is just different
like since well one sheet it's just
different like different handwriting of
the same name and then the other ones
are pictures that each say portend show
or tan Tien I would like to roll using
my design level two documents or now I
would like to see if I feel like the
same hand drew all these oh that's that
is excellent now documenting in this
case would be a wisdom role plus your
document sea level Oh
joke's on you babe I don't need it 19:23
there is there is no doubt in your mind
that the same hand is responsible for
the in smoothly inscriptions of the
names tan Tien pretension and the youth
you you are convinced that all these
drawings are from the same hand mm-hmm
so I look at it and I just say um I say
well I've heard that uh how does it
really take a long time to learn how to
see um and so this kid was just really
trying to be better at seeing herself I
don't know they're awful they're just
awful not good I don't know a lot about
sure so he says this about kids I you
can you can play - yeah what happened in
the ghost babies they disappears
vanished when they saw the snake and the
dagger in their Locati with the dagger
it's a little before that bent over
these drawings one of them anywhere are
these maps and such the papers can any
of us talk to them I try to make them
confess anything that they're oh can you
reach ours yeah I don't know that that's
a thing that that
awaken mine does its visible creature
sadly yeah well we can maybe let our dam
mitigate that yeah that's quitter talk
can I see them are they here ligado Tate
no no no you see now it sounds like it's
like when it's like when young people
try to do the Ouija board yeah yeah yeah
it's like are they here please do we
have a way to potentiate no to the boss
yeah can I do it I sense the presence of
magic within 30 feet of me and then if I
do sense magic in this way I can use my
action to see a faint aura so I I want
to cast it on all of us just in case
there's any magic going on with anything
oh yeah with all this stuff yeah I
couldn't affected me every time I do
that no I mean you're like alright roll
for damage it was so magical you got
scared
look enough times you know questioning
what the last time you need to take heat
on the stove and you find it through
your paints exactly no so using the tech
magic vids it's it's light job either of
course it's like yeah yeah it's bright I
mean it's like it's like yeah it's like
a light dusting okay a light dust of my
magic I also would learn at school magic
itself laughter let's see somebody oh no
no I'm gonna karate no it's not a Kris
not a chronic bring them on stage
Criss Angel Street
no no my my react it's not it's not
clear there is just a nice cover okay
hmm um so I I look around the Panda go
um I detect magic here
if you can select oi yeah I sense that
there's magic used here I think so when
the when the magic ghost memory babies
disappeared into nowhere
magic was involved exactly
do they have to let it link I do they
have to do they have to do you take five
points of psychic damage and you are
lingered you are very I mean basically
this is what I'm gonna do though where I
answer says I say I leaned over to Rosie
I said you've been in there here are you
and you know him yeah how much do you
trust him this one yeah
he's my child I mean this is so straight
yes is it is yeah is it is he a good one
I'm just gonna come out and say it with
EMS are you 3 ghost children I was
actually wondering if I could attempt to
communicate with the ghost children in
towards your question no of course no I
think I would have noticed that you see
a trend coming right up in the friends
of three small children a bit a long
time no no it's like you you start to
feel the the arms tighten but can I
attempt to communicate with ya please
wait you don't is it dragon
yeah I think I I may have something in
common with the timer is goofs Vil nice
in five hours
it could be ELISA that the shadow
council would be overjoyed council is
HEC start timer yeah exactly
with the shadow hex but I'm sure they're
delighted at the next five hours worth
of game although Matt Mercer might be
less delighted
we'll see look at the maps again yeah
obviously you want to do you want to
just because there are there there
aren't I mean they're not here
well okay I didn't know if they just
disappear yeah they're completely they
are not they are not presently here
visibly oh yeah well that's confusing
again I'm I try it okay I try to bring
them back I get plus one to languish for
favorite in me I'm not that place in any
way we all hate what these children
scared me I basically find a corner to
to kneel in this yes
very disgusting horse toilet yes okay I
I say are you are you the the tortured
children of someone who perhaps have
lost parents or our loved ones in an
early life and if and if so we would we
would like to help you so please give us
a sign that we're on the right path so
let's see when you say about the time
you say give us a sign that we are you
hear voices they're very quiet and they
don't appear to be responding to you and
I tell everyone - shut up off they
don't appear to be responding to you but
they're just you have but you have
entered into a place with reverence care
and concern okay and you are able to
hear a conversation between three voices
as near as you can tell are they child
voices or they seem yes they seem they
seem like the voices of their registers
is proper that draws me nearer I want to
walk in the direction of voices okay so
at a certain point you once you come
into contact with this sort of wicker
structure I see not it is not Pier one
but it's just sort of like it's
and you know would this sort of bent
over and water damaged and you hear a
boy's voice say we've we've gone there
twice this week if we go again I
guarantee you Mama's gonna find out we
need a longer time between trips and we
need more time to prepare
I'm sorry 10t we're not we can't do this
we can't we can't we can't do it as
often as you want I know that I know
that you love it and I love it too but
somebody's going to get hurt down there
and they're going to get hurt because we
can't plan okay so I'm if I can still I
will rejoin the group and share this
knowledge and and it's the whole time
it's like a whisper yeah you can hear it
barely yeah yeah yeah yeah but I mean
it's it might have been a whisper when
it was said the first time mm-hmm
so I I think we should try to find a
basement or something below this if
there is and none of us heard this
whisper just no no he entered into a
mental state that allowed him to they're
allowed him access to this voice where
was the whispering aloneness he's the
closer to closer he got to the heap Hey
they keep that I'm I was in before it
it's crying okay um okay so you think
that there's a basement that we should
trust
well I they they said they didn't want
to go down there which implies either a
well or a basement test you mean this is
the Crypt
this is the this is the crux we've been
we've been searching for I was gonna say
Christmas yeah actually actually have to
catch you up we've been tasked to search
for this thing that omen refers to is
the wandering crypt uh and this seems to
be based on the maps what they as
children were exploring uh an omen has
some
deal with this crypt he's not pleased
with it
yeah it wants us to seek it out and then
looks like I mean what was there was a
character we spoke to that did that
disbelieved the evidence of it
the thought it was nonsense yeah that
was that prophet prophet does not
believe this nonsense Rafa
this is hidding prophet women and the
killed his sister
yeah and the agent you spoke to from
drawn enterprises right they have a
completely other sort of cosmology that
surrounds the sharlee sharlee right and
anything we see they don't like the
unnecessary drawn poetry so so the maps
were of the Crypt itself there was
nothing in the maps that indicated
mentions to where the critic was
relative to town because it right seems
it seems like it's moving yeah I move
but the trick might be to lure it to us
I mean they found it multiple times in
multiple seasons yeah that's true
I look at QB and I go I gotta ask you've
never heard of a wandering Crypt have
you I've heard tales of one yes the
stories and bobs I avoid sober tales are
tastefully um well do you guys feel like
going out to the place where we last saw
it oh god I know this is bad memories
that ya know just about everything we've
ever done yeah I know let's go let's go
Chico guys what you want I got my dark
vision oh good can I try them one more
thing yeah no no you can play you can
play all the Dean do you want yeah I
should well I didn't know how we turn
over
shush everyone real quick shot and I
kneel and I place my hand on the ground
and I say if if you want to tell us
where this wandering crypt is please
make a noise or give us a sign in the
dress or you are you inside yeah have
you think that you've entered and you've
tried to enter in with your mom crawl
through into those
we're the source of the sound was yeah
absolutely
I've been trying to communicate with
this with this house so I want to
communicate directly and ask them like
if this will help put your soul at ease
please point us in the direction we are
supposed to go exactly so you again with
the same air of reverence yeah and care
and concern yeah that you executed so
fruitfully before you've placed your
hand sort of in that clearly I was
wanting to fill my touch what was a
ritual space yeah just and there's no
reduce there's nothing okay so you you
snooze you stand up and you hit your
head on on some of this it's a like a
chair leg that is bit it's a part of
this heap and a roll of paper slides out
and hits the ground I've grabbed the
paper and I say and I gather in the
house yeah yeah yeah I mean you you you
recognize it having just come down here
you recognize this as a crude you as
well and instantaneously like a very
crude iconic almost spiritual in terms
of its like abstract nature map of red
larch and the surrounding here Jessie
Mother's Day just north just north and
west of the town yeah in an area that
you know was once thick with red larch
trees now clear-cut and used to build
this grotesque parody of a civilization
there is a circle and an X and it says
winter
aha what season are we in yeah what's
the season this is the I'm trying to
make it easy for you guys yeah yeah I
work too dad no no no no I don't mean
like that I'm saying right now it's
summer okay okay okay I think that's
where it is and we've it's we're only
like a in-game time a couple weeks
removed right from when we first saw
that crypt the other day right but you
had a couple pretty long insurance right
as cartographer I would know where we
last saw the wandering crypt oh yeah you
read large writes and I presume we saw
it in summer
well that's nice trying to figure out
was it summer spring when you saw it
last summer spring yeah yeah back then
does see when it when that started up
that would still have been like late
spring okay
late spring early summer so relatives
who read large where was that this map
does not include the region that you
discovered the Crypt this map is very
local that's okay yeah yeah but what I'm
interested in is trying to at least put
another sort of point on this map so
that we can try to track the rain yeah
yeah exactly I can come back to the same
spots in this different seasons it yeah
call it right on the edge of spring
summer so was the place we saw it
relative to read larch east west north
or south far south okay far south south
Dan literally down the long road in the
Humber Hills oh really okay so this is
spring I'll put late spring just in
cases I'll get some reading done yeah
exactly
sir good is huge yeah yeah he's Bertha's
main quest wide open without a head
I've never been more proud of you than I
am
dude this quest is orange yeah white I
mean sex pee
where's worse fall in summer on the map
dude they're not there oh we only see no
overall we see the winter the winter and
I just added spring okay
and we need to find summer summer and
and autumn if we want to try to track
its whole thing well what is it right
now right now it's summer right now is a
rumor and we don't see it wait and it's
not on this map you don't know where it
is we don't know where it is
but we will go copies the available
information it's a wandering crypt sure
we have yes we know to places it's not
we have two points well you hear one
here we're also assuming that that's an
orbit like right circular linear take it
could be teleporting around yeah may or
may not come back to those spots we
don't know a lot of data
yeah yeah can I say that you know yeah I
mean ya know feel that it could be an
elliptical like that and so it's good
that's one better giant I ripped the
painting on so let's see if there's any
behind oh my god place a partner but
there's a lot of Secrets this is what
she's gone right this is what's hidden
where horses she imagine what's in the
house can we if we divide if this is a
linear path these are the two extremes
right so spring summer would be right
here so we died divide this into fourths
I think we can we determine is there
anything right here sir we all know what
a now orbiting if it but it's that yes
it's orbiting if we do assembly in its
linear I don't think it's just to
explore a little bit and try to get more
information and Kiwi Kiwi is just like
right behind you you guys are yeah
looking at the same map right like
pointing like as one person right ladder
we've we've shared cartographic yeah
knowledge that would that particular
zone yeah would not be super far from
the doone-gate in I mean that would be
south oh that's a John yeah I mean
that's that's South a couple days apiece
but but in terms in terms of distance
like if you're just if
it's purely abstract yeah in terms of
like guessing where it is in relation
like that would be about where that is
okay I'll check it out guys
hold this in here down you go down that
drawn and Cordy a and I'll just hop no
no part see if I mean it's cold days
here's what we do it's not a big deal
fine I'll come back there's a rope or
something and that's just how far it can
travel these don't already seasons if
that's an orbit and not a linear path
that'll be much more than two days no we
get it we get it
diameter wise how long would it take a
falcon to fly I think it has to be
linear because of the two seasons
someone a falcon it picks up with gaudy
my god he flies over there do the lovely
if you can check that done I just got
you to teleport the game I did I think
three moves you're stuck there I think
this is a piece of information that will
eventually lead us cigarette but I don't
think that we we don't know I think
we've now yeah we do put together two
points and we do need to figure out what
I think one more to triangulate where it
is now the kids have a map of it in the
spring and in the winter which which
implies that they they found it in the
spring
mmm-hmm wait that means that they've
been to the winter one yeah yeah yeah
the whispering said they went a couple
times
well my feels very confused that omen
has been to where her home was could you
write to omen and ask him it looks like
he there's an iffy yeah that would get
him dear nephew I found something that
may be of interest here perhaps it's
time show for the giant courtier in
person actually I think well I would
like to write a letter you can play all
the Dungeons and Dragons you want to I
know this table but but how it doesn't
care it's all your fingers so Wow long
ago
doing this um I think one that would put
in a like an official request saying
that she cracked you crack open your
ledger your new document okay I have new
quills oh yeah all new quills links all
new clothes new leaves and it has as a
custom cover as well did he read that to
you what there's a custom cover yeah
what the custom cover say do not draw -
did he not maybe I forgot just tell me
well here and if I remember on and
Gabanna
if memory serves drawing Goblin memory
serious yes no wait no it's goblin and
it says document see ledger on the top
go ahead like gold embossed read large
branch okay being a catalog of business
transacted in the desperate valley
walnut done grass document sir that's a
yeah
not read that soon feels feels really
good night I would never I suspect he
said I'll let Jerry it at the very
bottom of it so you see you you see it
and you're like I am donkey man
sir I open an it's very obvious that a
woman that has like put in the the
forward the letter that she got for a
moment and she just keeps moving for you
mark this is so writing a letter
basically saying that we found this
information in the carriage house of the
Iran Accord air it seems that and I and
well that's gonna phrase it where she's
gonna leave it open for interpretation
for him or say I know and I know you
know but I'm not gonna say it explicitly
and she goes on that three children that
had once resided here had been you know
exploring the wandering crypt and she's
saying that you know we've got two
locations we're looking to narrow down a
third location if you have any
information that would be helpful to us
now would be a
great time and then she says and then
Gina finishes off all that signs on the
dotted line initials or twice and then
attaches this is another really small
note that she'd already pre-written that
was a thank-you for her new note very
tasteful and also yeah and also it's a I
also won wizard card but that was very
interesting reading home from summers
being I met your friend Jim he was
alright he was not a small chicken with
some chickens to include this note as
well and inside you read it says get me
my memory back you note for me like
take my memory and I scribble out
and I said you nice person and I put
that in and then I take dinars yeah okay
great Rosa do you want to sell him
anything I ma you know it a little plate
of snorkel blasters just like covered
with with with a towel if you are we
back in the end now
I read still make no we're standing on
the bed night yeah nicely like all
huddled around writing letters okay
dictated but not read got it after
dinner seeing you find stuff onto the
ground and hidden me keep me hid in his
head and what I know
so like I'm gonna start looking for
secret passages to like like you hard is
even little dense just like tearing
apart a furniture like yes yes you're
hitting it and it's rattling yeah like a
lot what I find that you find larvae
subtlety of suggestion 6:11 kingster
kicking he's gonna keep rolling I go
over to the couch he's basically yeah he
is devouring this place and if you as he
he walks around the front he's not
getting whatever he is trying to find
I'm just impressed like this crazy
quickly scribble a note that says
Dragonborn her crate and when he kicks I
throw it like it's like a song and I go
oh it's not what's that in this one I
found the guys walk into middle of
conversations are we doing something
that sounded guys perhaps more of nope
we're getting the okay yes yes so since
Dragonborn are great yeah you find it
you feel good um and as you as you walk
out the front just into the night air
it's a moon up there the moon seems to
appreciate you as well it's generous
face doing but your tail catches a chair
leg and this Jenga tier just
pulled out and collapse and it actually
falls in such a way that it begins to
spill out into the street four or five
feet a wolf gave up its last secret wait
that was the fort he killed the fort
Dragonborn a great curse the forest is
that I was clean I was cleaning we're
supposed to clean that now the garbage I
don't get I think it's still a total
mess you're the obnoxious one on it's an
ultra mess it's a total I I
shall we turn in because I was gonna say
I can instruct velvet to to work through
the night well no you work for the first
hour of the night sure that might be
enough to get something done at least
won't have the street he'll pull out a
few things you know he'll
a few things and sit them out there's
there's a small clearing behind the
drying courtier that's currently not
used for must currently heaped with
untold mounds of chairs and yeah yeah
exactly yeah yeah so he'll can he'll
bring them back he'll pull out anything
that he can fully carry he'll work on I
need to know to look at these two
cornerstone recipes they have before you
get a bed
oh sure which one's the real one
certainly let's take a look yeah all
right what do i what I observe so they
are similar but one of them says in
giant disgusting and giant and it's
underlined two times is it looks like
I'm not that documents is is the same
handwriting sample maybe yeah yeah yeah
it's this it's the same handwriting but
it's just a the language it's just bits
and pieces from all over it's like all
of her personal opinions or maybe in
giant yeah yeah exactly
who knows where who knows where it
picked up it could've been her
grandmother for all you know this one
this one's the right one yeah thank you
this one isn't but I don't know why she
was saving it no why are you like that I
feel in there yeah in my spare time okay
so I don't right I got the one that's
not disgusting it's true okay it's true
but no before turning in yeah I I say to
you well at first I thought you were I
thought you were three ghosts and I I
was wrong
I had been led to believe too that you
were a maker of weapons that destroy
things including children but I now know
you to be a maker of whatever the
opposite of a weapon is that could heal
children that's the idea yes I only use
weapons when I have to I don't want to
he's single - ah
I'm just saying haha
it's Phil oh you want me to explore your
son's body I guess so yeah I only need
four hours you boys have fun
come on legardie let's all go and up we
go we're I'm wearing the lizard bling
it's the most it's the most elaborate
dangerous and eldritch Oh got a
technique certainly this in has probably
ever seen no no that's it it's
horrifying absolutely like a Rube
Goldberg dicks so you so you had
suggested Rosie that you wanted to feast
why not a long rest I think is what you
why not a long ride why not a long wrist
and this is an opportunity for you to
get a long rest although it is you have
every faith that it's going to be an
early morning okay
no one the dumb grass as you as you
drift away into the meditative slumbers
common to your kind yes a few hours pass
and as you're roused you can see well
that's good I was around yes it's been a
great night get that a feed that horse
is a horse so you I don't know you
hearing noise you hear noises down in
the common room your noises in the
common room at what hour like freedom
does the end this would be deep night
deep in the night
um 4:30 yeah
stumble out on my loss on a morning
person um looking down from the upper
looking down from the upper walkway you
can see that furniture is heaped in
front of the door oh come on no no this
is boots on and three faces turned
towards you you can see a wizard you
believe a night okay
and a roguish character wait and they
raise their glasses too you know so hey
[Applause]
they are me wait how do we get back here
I recognize that yeah I recognize them
as the people that we had to destroy
exactly as you put your hands on me yeah
on the banister that looks down if you
blink your eyes a couple times and it's
it's saying that you know it's a drawing
hornier okay and I don't nothing it's
not heaped it's not it's normal no it's
just quiet Odori we could have probably
cleaned the place up a little bit last
night all right everybody's a critic
a stake in a think that I'm I've been
under a lot of stress the past day I've
been very upset about just the turning
turn of events and all that and I think
that she might think that that was her
breaking a little bit like not
immediately being like well the place is
lousy with haunts like might just be
like spooksville like yeah why was i
remembering that and i think she would
hesitantly wander back to her room but
like keep looking back suspiciously ten
did that noise rouse anyone else really
no just a few create freely for a few
creaks sleeping of the wood and then
gasp and that's it okay I hope you say
maybe someone heard me come out of my
room but other than that you hear from
from my room you hear me saying that's
not right okay
it's like whenever you have that like
doctor scene in a show they look over at
that like that the tray that has all the
perfect tools but this is like the sex
version of that and it's like here's a
snake yeah here's an evil tentacle you
know what I mean here's a phone cue the
two foci it's like I don't know where we
can work them in it's in the seven-layer
burrito just like just so here's your
things
just try put them together in some
configuration let's see how it goes
disaffected from the world I'm like all
right yeah - evil focuses yeah yeah yeah
after an hour you leave and both of us
are like it's no white either of us
wanted but that's why I was fun I guess
wouldn't try the internet that was
waiting for that for long we ended
penance day where that guy's like it
comes down to because that guy looks
like we're finishing River Phoenix
dingoes that's the one that's the
greatest salute in movie history sorry a
few good men that's the drought no me
Rosie you see yeah you can hear you're
still lying in your bed and out if you
outside in the town check sorry crossed
bikes bikes are very first time cool
everybody you can hear out in the just
out in the town just through the streets
you can hear like a humming like a
humming sound is it but source around
what's it's yes really know
it's Birds it's very early
is it the humming sound werewolf no no
strangely enough no no no it sounds like
this would you hear it yeah here we go
and it just passes and you can hear it
like it around the around the end you
can hear it like in the streets you can
hear it just coming at different volumes
from different quarters of the town Wow
okay does it sound like many voices it
does okay I I had downstairs and I
opened the door to verify that there are
corporeal figures like yeah it's like
some more ghosts
no I throw the DES like this is ghost
again no no no it's a come on ghost
no no you think you think this is you
think this might be an OS DLC yeah it's
my last own but you can see it's just
it's families walking through the
streets do you think it different you
can hear even on site on side streets
and other places in town you can just
hear this this low song moving sort of
passing through the streets and you can
see that children have little bird cages
with little Canaries in them that's if
that's that's the that's the scene that
you see Wow and they're all walking
they're all walking past the drawing
courier this would be north and they're
been you can see them sort of like group
by group they have their own they all
seem to be going in the same direction
ultimately but they choose how to get
there okay so they're walking north past
the drawing courier and then breaking
off to the east I ask a question yes of
course is it seems like they're all
going in their own direction you can ask
any kind of question you want well I'm
gonna ask one very specific one can we
sort of guess to make where they're
where they're going to end up based on
because if they're all taking different
directions going the same place sure
they'll be sure to me yeah absolutely
but you you have not been here and so
you might need to you might need some
help for us or said
yeah I did I handed this idea to the
group although I avoid eye contact and
the serpent neither one ID I never
actually was away another day cuz this
is oblivious so he's like hello friend
but so anyway the spooky children seem
to be going in one area
perhaps we can guess where they're going
if we look from an elevated position
these these seem like they're real
people these are not yeah I think you
would admit no are we there we should
open a theme restaurant let's um let's
bundled up it's a little chilly so
everybody grab a nice misty I got my bow
minute okay um yeah so let's I'm gonna
start following them you're all welcome
to join me I follow immediately I will
follow her yeah yeah bunch of ghost
babies just coming out windows whoa
liquid ghost yes that movie goes down
are there enough are there uh the
parents with them they're my family
are they supervised yeah yeah yeah
children so you use you sort of like do
you do try to sing along absolutely oh
as you say I don't and trying to
maintain an aspect of reverence but
accidentally like if making it too
creepy and forward I approach one of the
parents and from behind I'm like what
are the Canaries for well you're too
close and my body is also too close
yes and they try to protect their
children from you and you you hear a
like just over like like brushing up
against your cheek you look down and
ligarius there
he's trying to get into this spirit
looking around the child he's trying to
get into visit he's trying to get into
the spirit of things now I'm filled with
that spirit I want to be one with his
best right mmm your rib covering in the
form of the Lizard King just has a kind
of resonance
yeah there's no hum yeah it's like it's
like one of those it's like one of those
vests that you can wear that has the
subwoofers in it oh yeah yeah oh of
course those yeah no no I look for real
gaming you you can tell you have you
have been out this way close to it once
before you are in the fields just sort
of south and east of the quarry that is
in the northeast corner of red larch
right and you can see that their family
is like damn near everyone in the town
as near as you can tell has gathered
around the mouth of the quarry entrance
and sort of coming down this Ridge you
can see that they are gathered around a
cart of a flat cart with two wheels
whatever you know whatever drove it here
has been disc and bump sends
disconnected and there is a great sort
of black sheet that is draped over this
this cart whatever is on top of it so
there it looks like there's a structure
or an object of your estate definitely
something beneath this sort of oiled Shi
okay and it's sort of like lumpy and
miss shapen I think we need disburse
this crap yes but they're they're
heading toward that thing with a purpose
yeah you're right if you can deal with
this yeah yeah exactly so and you can
tell that so as I say all the children
seem to have a little birdcage not all
of them have a canary in there but even
even so every child has a cage with them
okay and as you as you begin to approach
you see a man in like fine black Raymond
dark robes dark masks approaches the
cart and then you can see the fiddling
with something around the base of it and
they say grab the sheet and they pull
this heavy oiled tarp right off the top
and it is a massive cake and everyone
explodes in joy no pure joy everyone
everyone explodes in joy yellow is a
yellow is a big part of the and you can
see and so you see mother's or Father's
giving their children like little picks
and little shovels and children rush
this cake they go nuts on this
cake and sometimes it's like nope come
back these these they're just going Bam
Bam Bam and then you see the children
but the children not eating the cake
this isn't like in the marshmallow test
mmm they're not eating it they are
getting handfuls and scoops of it and
then they are running over to the front
of the quarry mouth and they're throwing
handfuls of cake into the shaft and then
they're going back to get
more cake I join in immediately yeah
yeah you can't wait
I am the size of a child no one says
anything yeah you jump in I'll get the
scoop you get the scoop you're going in
there you're grabbing it yeah and then
as you get close
everyone is has handfuls except the
children are doing something that you
didn't know before and don't know how to
do now each of them says a name as they
throw in and then go back what kind of
names are this thing probably into your
teacher no regular names
oh yeah yeah family names Welliver Bobby
centaur but each time but there's no
there's no sadness it's just joy it's
just they're just feeding the mind with
each Oh handful I think okay
rosy bee stinger I break my cake into
four pieces and I'd say it quietly
enough but I throw one in I said bee
stinger I throw one in I say dung grass
I throw one in I say what's on and I
throw one in and I say child a child
says when did they die oh god you're
cursed
[Laughter]
that's our game for this week
council we're dead may our Labor's easy
obviously it's been our great pleasure
to serve you we're gonna go and feast on
the facilities grab a beverage we will
return shortly to please you of course
as I suggested before subscribers c-cool
a AIC team stuff and that adds up to you
consider it I will see little bit
you