time is the enemy the pastor threatens
the fastest weapon you will they make it
past a second and land the question play
it flash and reckless to choose a cost
solution you saw was prudent in any step
of crippled curtain will be kind of
putrid it's that well-fed I pursue in no
mountain too steep but dungeon duties to
spend expanded them marks up to the top
of the peak of beneath the you become
like sharks to win while I swim in that
money go by Carl Barks ruined suspension
national parks do it I'll send them home
in a natural box the post time the most
of the parks included save your breath
for a cleric confessor that there's a
lesson and life isn't any professor but
if you speak in my official advice sign
on the dotted line a list of the twice
hello speak like I am Tycho Brahe Penny
Arcade in packs I am also a mean sir I
heard jingles I'm sorry there's a lot of
dogs running an oppressor walk by some
friends oh my gosh no I am also a
manifest Hereward run CEO of
acquisitions incorporated today Jerry
Hawkins and I'm here to play a game of
Dungeons &amp; Dragons with my friends to my
right Dragonborn narcissist an armed
with sin and hail I got all the way
through the whole thing without a pause
didn't practice me all afternoon to the
right of my right repping the natural
world
it's wounded on grass and wanna die
grass did they get so differently that
one but two and left not your grandma's
grandma unless she is your grandma's
grandma which the does happens sometimes
Rosie be singer yeah yeah yeah oh the
shake weight no emerging as though from
a mist shroud Chris drought
because this job everybody yay okay now
listen so we got a little Great British
baking show in the mix last time okay
this did happen when last we saw our
heroes they were toiling toiling against
fate trying to create a memorable dining
scenario holiday themed here at red
larch they celebrate a holiday called
last stones day so a piece of trivia you
may not know about last knowns day last
stones day was named by the shadow
Council
so their influence merely receives you
there their influence has reached out
low low even unto the dust rings Ally
was there and lo nobody died a no I have
a good day for though technically
speaking although you know theoretically
this should be reserved for table are
the other option was Founders Day which
would have been a very different it
would have been a very different the
founder of McDonald ever yes Ray Kroc
des hommes Proximus come on now hot exam
p.m. now so the way the things are going
down walnut dawn grass has almost
single-handedly rescued this dining
shift from absolute disaster handedly as
the floater her special heard heard damp
roll in these proceedings was to try and
resolve issues that had occurred at
other points in the food service chain
for example cooking front of house
maitre d where the D stands for
Dragonborn yeah right over here Chris
Chris trout operating in a serving
capacity drawn courtier or drunk or e8
courtier yeah I fucked up
I really need to pick one yeah you name
this thing you know what's the size of
your lousy yeah make a final really no
accent or reflects exactly what don't
you know
the I mean voted the most horrifying
meal service I'm God of that in the
destron Valley we're talking about a
scenario where cthis drought in an
effort to hasten the proceedings
obviously to bring a sort of ethic you
know enunciate a real system yeah to
increase efficiencies in the kitchen
Katrice tau levered that leverage the
most horrifying warlock spells to erupt
12 rising you know gem edged chainsaws
yeah
to in an attempt to deliver takes
attempt well horse success well they
were shredded by and large and maybe
that's what you do on last on the day I
don't think so
that certainly wasn't the reaction now
quick thinking on the part of walnut
dank grasp um allow Alaska not still
savvy big thing I got is it too much too
much here quick thinking on the part of
walnut dawn grass of the Enclave panics
anima allowed her to you know eat as we
suggested you know a couple feet of this
thing and then wrap it around yourself
comically not as not as an elf no no no
but as a crocodile incredibly exciting
way to leverage the animals forms but
you have wrapped it around yourself in a
grizzly sort of eldritch barbed wire you
have seen you see this rectus massive
reptile you're just in time you're able
to you know use your monk dexterity and
keep off you know what I mean like jump
over croc Thailand the thing yeah what
we see she pulls right around the corner
and it was a
moment that famed faint water deep water
Davian critic food critic min song right
along with his emaciated scribe has
entered the door talking's cruel it god
only knows what's going on with these
two maybe there will be an opportunity
to investigate that tonight but there is
a story yes who knows but that is the
scenario that we find ourselves in I
described it last time as a bonus round
and I was not kidding we are only at one
strike and as I suggested before four
strikes is when really really bad things
will happen the reputation of the
drowning courtier affected in a negative
way maybe permanently right now you know
that profit and share basting er are
down in water deep you know this is the
night of the concert that's what they're
doing in your mind you know that her
mailed foot is tapping but not along
with some music
she has no concept of music of any kind
she does not understand it she doesn't
know about the notes she just noticed
that
Audra is a kind of sorceress and she
loves her and that's what she likes
about the music know this male foot is
tapping with agitation and you know this
even even days away you can sense that
there is an agitation on the part of
prophet that is to say prophet is drawn
proprietress of the drawn and cornea no
but there is a sliding scale about what
you get and what happens to you based on
how many of these you get there are also
good things that can happen if you
succeed you have the opportunity not
just to you know
do business as usual but to materially
affect the success and reputation of the
drawing career now that this new player
minsung has entered the scene right kill
it right this is one opportunity so we
have a little bit tougher checks ok this
time around we have obviously incredible
floater opportunities for love it don't
really I could not love it more but for
walnut dog grass so alright so this at
this point just like in the finer houses
yes this dining experience is going to
start right up front front of house so
up with Denard Blitzen so you in the in
the moments before this it was a
terrifying nightmare it was it was a
cult ritual gone awry just seconds ago
and in this moment of shock that walnut
quick thinking was able to provide this
new contender and imagine imagine a
scenario a dark scenario ok darkly
imagine yes your eyes first
yes exactly where it's a three fighter
to situation on the player here comes a
new challenger and then imagine imagine
like a 2d version of this clearly
highborn poverty tourists asshole nice
walking straight in the front door he
has heard something about some food and
he has every intention of you know
disabusing the people of Waterdeep of
their notions that red larch is quaint
no this is just a shithole you can tell
that he has already written the article
and it's really just a it's really just
a way to pass the time now just a
formality
it's just a formality and presumably his
starving this isn't what Christmas Eve
what I'm in Solon he is human skin of
course
riot going against them course yeah but
no I was just going to say like do we
have to continue like what are the
numbers I have to hit I'm changed no no
that on this right here these numbers
are 13 and 18 okay and using so just
just just sliding by is a little bit
harder and the hi check is is higher if
you want to try to grant that stuff now
we do have obviously as I suggested you
know even down to the very name of this
festival the shadow council knows all
and sees all and they have the ability
obviously to manipulate the sky of fate
to a certain extent with the advantage
of this advantage scenario now these are
perfectly usable just like last time
something to consider when you're
putting your rolls together all right
okay so after the tentacles have popped
up yeah yeah I may have been gulped down
with going something around it's alright
around a and but and I'm just like hey
so far this all part of show everyone is
great and then amidst the cheers
mid-song I will turn in today Doris yeah
keep everyone goes oh he walked around
go around
yeah nice very good it starts it starts
slowly children clapping terrified birds
are inside the cage yeah well diesel
yeah so she's used to trying to take
that if I take that moment of startled
trailer yeah and transfer it straight
into an applause you don't know in a
better situation for ham yeah right
useful and I just greetings friend a
wink the kid gets deeply and yet at
least it doesn't really died he says it
are you the proprietor or oh boy I know
you talk oh yeah
and then this'll be great um
uh I say just filling in welcome to Big
Daddy dinars young you might ask you
that every time they say the name but I
understood there was a master on the
cornerstone oh sure that operated this
sure sure
hold it oh yeah come here
Stevie Breaston wrote this finger on the
table it's clean
you've disappointed quarter surprise it
should be them right away I'm like ready
to avoid your hand off I go they're mine
yum yum yum yum needs a Hut of yum yum
mm-hmm a little belly the same yeah put
some put some young girls in there fella
yeah any like that no no any more people
tell you like that and I push him into a
table closer to them you sit there now
we'll bring out some yum yum French but
he isn't dice what do you that again Oh
is your Kerzner oh I can oh you can
decorate I get to I suppose I can you
want to do it as yeah yeah Christmas Oh
scares me I go tell just now see my
touching is belly much times if you are
that and my man doctor might as I touch
his alright very difficult I ain't it is
that's what I really want you and gum do
I want to pass the luck book yeah
because she has a croc Annette covered
in tentacles right now yes actually just
are you thinking about going for the 18
we only have none you know what this is
everybody it's not around like an
electron yeah but mentally pick up the
other I've got it right so I've got an
image all right you know I'm never this
again what you do even how do you know I
would do you learn are their team always
a boy so now should go for the big boy
if you go for the big boy now are you
gonna use your yeah okay take mine too
gotta go save my oven
and then I'm going to use exactly
persuasion mm-hmm plus 6 e level you did
forgot about that level 5 HT oh that's
your and this and this is this is how it
functionally goes if you did not see the
table please oh by all means continue to
shake the dice if you've nothing the
table talk festival at the very end
there simply wasn't an opportunity to
render it in place but the party the
acquisitions incorporated franchise here
in red larch the one that has an
exclusive license to all the decimal
Valley absolutely at the very moment min
song enters the establishment in your
mind you you think about how far you've
come all everything that you've done
every adventure that you had lashes
before to that'll run applause exactly
right wait in a way that you absorb some
measure of that applause right I apply
it to your own wounded spirits sure and
you realize that you can rise up to this
challenge however so what you got not
that it's a real shittier come on merely
receive you if you would please confer
yeah upon the shadow council they're
delicious treats from front daddy dinars
yum yum hut what go through Deadhorse go
natural 20 this guy's trying to keep it
a couple of me right like he's well yeah
I'm he's literally just going in and I'm
like whoa she's realizing I returned his
thing yeah yeah yeah well no he should
because this is all started where you've
gotten him and is functionally speaking
wrestled him down into this chair like
there's um dangling yellow yeah but
there's another interpretation of these
events right and we don't even have to
go and even have to investigate that one
where he interprets all of this in this
gauche way yeah that along with this
twenty comes the idea that he
is about to have that thing that all
food critics claim to love and want
which is an authentic experience and so
he thinks that all of this wrastlin and
glad-handing and all this kind of stuff
you can see that he is he was sort of
seated as best he could in a proper way
you can see that his left leg kind of
spreads out a little bit we lean back a
little bit the scribe is behind him the
signs of comfort this game is behind him
taking notes two-thirds chub yeah
exactly what he said he's seen he's
singing more they sing more thigh you
know and then is generally available the
describers is you're quickly taking
notes about this charismatic um you know
clown like figure on a warm I have a
warm and inviting little move
that's right after welcome I'm Leo yeah
yeah exactly
now I'm challenged like this delightful
hope with that twenty has passed you the
rock rosy beasting okay what is this
this cycle starts with the front house
okay there's a alright turn order is me
now got it okay so the first thing I'd
like to do is I watched crock anut come
running through yeah and you see that
she just wrapped up around everything
she is still engaged right with this
flow so before I do anything unless you
have something particularly cool it you
wanted to do to deal with this I win
your die is inside me I'd be a charade
I press my time when a beloved family
cat eats tinsel yeah yeah yeah like and
then go ahead it spins and circle that's
covering this yeah and you pull it out
both ends yeah okay so I I feel really
confident after that round of applause
that I heard from out front yeah yeah
I'm good it went into your heart yeah I
did and so I'm actually going to I'd
like to jump on to an unoccupied by
tentacled part of coconut and use Graham
Nancy to use the shadows of all of these
tentacles and drag them off
croco nut and preferably back to the
darkness from whence they came
so you're going to get rid of this
contraption altogether floater exactly
there's one thing I know exactly now how
will you contend with your cooking
duties
oh so this is this would be my whole
turn well I mean you you let's talk
about it a lot of shadows to go around
come on let's let's eat let's figure out
I'm just saying like is this this
motherfucker out here he's been teed up
yeah Johnny
just leave me yeah I love that you're on
your fan please me it's more important
for you to cook just a floater
honestly no one else can cook anyone can
supplies is the critical part yeah oh
hey it's not that easy to get rid of
floater okay I'm just let me die I
written from last week it does say one
that has her own problems so I suppose
see that holds true alright it's because
the floater had their own problem to do
oh I remember okay okay well then I'm
not going to do that cool fucking thing
I just said
I'm just going to make me some treats
okay so do I know that mints soul is
here oh absolutely
okay so I need to I need to put some
special sleeves yeah you need to for you
to put a rosy spin on this thing okay
what the shadows inside got him ready
turn the head out I feel like you
wouldn't like it though right
it's quite rustic I do have that you
probably Cracker Barrel just like hit my
balls um okay now I do and I've always
been a oh yes just a little eyeball in
each one so one of my background feature
is rustic hospitality and that doesn't
mean anything in this context but I do
like to think that Rosie knows whether
Rosie knows how to like you know like
imagine you're at like a dark Cracker
Barrel and yeah yeah it was darkest that
like the crackles at the top of the loaf
of bread that you would get like that
that like dusting of flour and you yeah
exactly and Mama's kitchen yeah you you
know that a mama a mama may may get the
corn bread and it
it's crackling on the outside because it
was made in that cast iron you know that
they did that right yeah so Rosie knows
how to make those touches happen and she
hasn't been doing it because it's been
mass production but now now she's going
to put some of the flavor and love into
it and she's going to give a little kiss
and blend it out with love that stuff
with the residents ate garbage dr. Gill
oh yeah actually yeah I mean so - we
should get my prescribed right guys of
course of course of course
okay so I'm going to make my acrobatic
check on that exactly exactly now and
you are you are going for which role but
for target wise are you going for the 13
or the 18 has two advantages so I should
tell there's one and I will go for the
18 be thank you and you've been the
freebie Minar so you're good yeah
fabulous I will I will attempt to confer
the advantage and go for the hard roll I
got plus 6 now baby
okay let's make it happen Rajon do you
want to you want to remove your necklace
I know you I see the direction number is
a you pull it out okay and I don't want
those in there
okay here we are I'm gonna take a have
you thought and I'm going to think about
the time where I bake at my favorite
buns at the orphanage in my hometown
with all of my favorite orphans
okay you took it's not not my best not a
damn for fucks it was orphan hey cool
all right hold on when I came that's 25
all right so do you want to sure waiver
this yeah so I was taking acrobatics
check just to make these two so it did I
did go overboard and maybe also for your
benefit because you're the only one you
can see me do this so I thought maybe I
try to impress him a little bit and make
it like a stupid you know what an
alligator's is a rule I love the asking
your life you throwing something which
is trashing anything leading is blood
everywhere
under made of scales and barbed wire
yeah yeah yeah but it's not gonna sabi
for trying to impress just know do this
you know it's like here's like a
front-hall it's like rustic wood
furnishing that right right around the
corner right as soon as you get into the
kitchen take a right silent fucking Hill
it's just it was rough it is the walls
are peeling but I am let me make it very
clear I'm dancing on these cabins oh
yeah absolutely home it's beautiful it
looks a little sick because it looks
like I'm enjoying it or maybe that I'm
including the blood on the source of the
blood but I'm having really good it's
macabre a yeah here's what you're saying
yeah it's a macabre a ballet indeed no
don't
so here's so here's some black cab so
here at here's we're talking about we're
talking about the bump from dinar ya
board up up another bump bumps right
over here from Rosie yeah bee stinger I
got the crackling can you spike it cut
wrist route can you spike it yeah
definitely
take us on home yeah put me to bed
yes story I'm showing a equal concern
for you and the tentacles I'm worried
about a little bit okay Oh better than
expose the cool I uh I started that's a
good decision this isn't immortalized
it's a good sound to make it win I
didn't know if it Wilson or anything
yeah it wasn't on camera no no not like
75 bucks no one will know will record a
anybody answer yes so what do you got um
I want to I don't want to wait for less
man I don't know what I do what I did
before I want to do it correctly want to
do a good job
he'll okay yeah but I will Rolo I
promise that what I want to do is just
go for the plain old check I'm not going
to do anything every other time it's
like you're trying to like part of the
veil of reality maybe not everything
used to be injected with chemicals
but it's like what you don't like it I
hated party members maybe I could tone
it down right this is your credit
character growth yeah
maybe was wrong yeah normally I would
try to egg you on and now go for it it's
great really of it but I'm not going to
no no no son the same Robin uh yeah
we've met our great enemy French food
art yes this is an ark right so that so
the the cornerstone comes to the yeah
yeah perfect
uh I put on plate and take it after yeah
your check needed to walk yeah wanted to
eat it am I able to do that
two hands know what I was going to do is
like it so I just starts a little bit
because a bad thing that happened on
this very recent right yeah I'm not
going to do that this time what I want
to do is do a performance check here's
what I will do
I'm only what I love to do is bring that
glow man back but that but not in the
form we all know and love him but
enhance yeah humanoid form I'm just
gonna produce a light above the
cornerstone so delicate that it looks
like shaft of light cream you know I'm
saying we didn't know you you want if
you want to create feet like thoroughly
believable scenario that this
cornerstone is like some kind of
archetypal cornerstone yes you know it's
like it's you know any meaning it's like
the Aristotelian model and if you want
to suggest if not directly a slur tonic
ideal then it's coming down on this
shaft of light okay Oh on the shaft of
light on even better why I decided to
say I just try to rely a heavenly Catlow
about it I mean I could put the light
inside and I feel like just like it's
too bright things creepy yeah exactly
how that light is coming to the cracks
like it's a shrink pill man down you
like crawl in there
thank you bye I used to do like an
angelic choir speech but yeah yeah yeah
okay let's see if I can get past that
but yes but it is a it is a performance
check because as I bring it to the table
I want to de mujer and you know you just
to lose something from our yeah exactly
are available yeah how come this is the
chef right of course it's always and I
have an advantage you really need yes
you're just trying to hit their team on
to dice will fucking sing not quit the
whole month builds fault
okay all right just do it really roll it
one better just do it better you just
need it not a ramp
he had a +5 what five me point no there
were moments my performances calls for
okay what did you stroll so the stick
out of the garbage can will join what
hey hey oh my god did it it was good you
any 13 you would have hit the good goal
for see with the good roll you would if
it's a good roll even oh all right here
so you so you you were bringing this
over and then just as just a little
flower on my clothes just like I was
back there I'll beg just a little
something you barely hear it so rough
there's like I rustic as you as you put
as he as you you look like it's coming
from your own self right like is coming
from within
emerging from your mystery exactly
imagine that you are mister out right
you've pushed this thing forward the
light comes down you see in this light
fills the scribes eyes just blinking off
of the off of the irises side enough for
those cute cakes by the way watch two
kings one Avery wants to describe you
describe to describe are they on two
plates who are they on one plate up to
you later
oh I don't know what I place a new place
yeah you got it everyone's absolutely
I'm playing ask weird tough to sell is
rust in your yeah two plates usually I
definitely so you bring them out set
them down the table
there's ask you you know the described
is not seated
the scribe is always sort of in a ring
or a maroon or yeah sort of context
around just floating around in song and
that min song is doing all the things
that you were doing in this religious
context before slight turns you know
just trying to bring these cakes into
alignment with a deeper wisdom I like
that that very much because it's like
before cthe wrist was presenting it as
this religious experience but that's now
I want to play it like oh it's nothing
really
and he can exist know exactly exactly
right um he reaches into his robe and
pulls out his own implements oh there's
a jeweled fork of silver chopsticks yes
and then right on that right on the top
of the cornerstone he just taps it once
like an egg and then you see the jam hot
delicious jam a spread around the base
and he looks like he wants to eat it but
he also wants to cry he also wants to
cry and then the scribe sort of edges a
little too close to the second
cornerstone and he's told to finger he
reclaims his original position I'm
behind it now this has been delivered
and it has been delivered with an expert
way walnut dong grass you have an
opportunity here to get rid of the last
right track and f it up well yes is
brushes but you have the opportunity
here to get rid of the last strike
because now you can tell that the people
of red larch they find this very
interesting
right and a lot has happened in the last
you know 20 minutes or so as a drowning
courier it's a little more exciting than
it is typically but they think that it
is really amazing that someone from
water deep is going to write about their
him mm-hmm
that's the context that we have here you
have the opportunity so describe to me
how you can perfect this experience Oh
either for the members of red larch
minsung the scribe tell me how you cast
this experience you choose you choose
you you you identify got it identify the
scenario and at it execute okay um so I
so is there so is it it really that's so
walnut is so he told you please ding
dong dumb okay it turns up I can't cast
spells as a crocodile so but you can
UNCHR akka dive and I know yeah but I
have tentacles beside me I know I'll
take damage for this but that's fine um
so I turn back and do walnut yeah
I'm still wrapping these tentacles and
I'm still in the kitchen and I crawl
over to a window and I pull myself up on
the sill and I use sky right to right up
to ten words with clouds and a part of
the sky you can see which will last for
one hour for long enough for everyone to
leave including this off and it's going
to say say she's counting oh yeah I can
say happy less stones date from the
drawn according yeah and then I'm going
to roll for that so hopefully it's
written beautifully in a hand perhaps
more beautiful press even while it could
write okay so we're talking about
in terms of adjudication you cast these
spells off of wisdom yeah so are we
talking about something like a wisdom
check do you have a wisdom skills that
you think might be might help you
analyze this little bit I mean like
would you say I might like I don't I
don't want you to now here but this is
this is a special context like I'm not
digitally like perception or do you
think it could be like survival
maybe those are my like survival I'll
tell you why because here you know I
they act up that perception no no no no
because you are trying to do this you're
trying to execute this while being
serrated or said okay cool and I got the
event no I didn't I didn't spend enough
I'm going to the shadow council did
confer you one yeah I love you so you
must have pleased them this time your
labors must have pleased them so one off
like are you guys looking less on buying
oh yes just resourcing here and just
like you just like writing on the
windows thing Thanks for writing and
then and then like sort of like in this
in the steam of your breath on the
window you're writing these words and
then they're also appearing in the sky
yes yes ah low role right little bull
role looks tiny minimal why would I
confer advantage I don't know anyone Oh
getting dogs on it I don't even need to
do it again how about this the better in
the progress you should always roll it
twice in case week in case we consider
one up right so I'm very white both try
to do for our dinners on the show
Council now there are Roos and oz
from outside begin that you hear this so
he has taken a single bite now and it's
swaying to some silent music as the
scribe is by
like visibly salivating over the corner
but he's just he's continually writing
you don't need under maybe minson
doesn't even write these who knows but
these notes are coming in fast on this
on this thing the he goes to see what is
outside and Vincent grabs his cloak and
brings him back in and positions him
right there where he can absorb all of
this information now we are out of
initiative now the challenge has been
completed how else would we like to
texture and flavor this dining
experience at the drowning court here so
I am vomiting blood yeah all right yeah
yeah used maybe he'll take those of you
or give me like or do you come back oh
yeah I was going to feel like I'm
retreating at this point I need to see
my ugly mug in there yeah I come back in
a second where you are I'm on the ledge
like this I look and I see you and I go
you help me fix what you broke
they're inside me ah go can you be a
crocodile real quick or that how are you
did that I already did that how I dispel
these I could use tentacle lash and
lashing out of your throat as goal
showing grab them or that could end up
with another indeed and you could also
try to you could also try to seize
control of their will in the same way
you do you know when they arrive what
makes it right you could use your Arcana
check which is the same thing that you
use to control them to begin with
you got it oh I see and then to use that
to dismiss them yeah we have them go
ahead fire them not ruin your body yeah
if you roll like you always do a towel
to my face yeah then we'll try my thing
you try really game and right now pizza
Cresselia yes I want the blood
everywhere
okay it's cold how'd that do that's not
here mix everything no no they they ride
they beget yeah it is it should be
starting to rise like in the circular
way it sort of turned themselves into
sharp Springs so that the surface area
is more condensed so don't do that
that's why why did you not to do are
they were concern about the ones inside
you the ones outside you've pretty much
if you were a crocodile yeah these are
you worried never popped up with a bed
of them that it's like a an owl pellet
or something like she can't she can't be
eating it yeah as she shifts back this
is just vomited up but this is but
there's still this mesh on the out yeah
exactly okay no I so while I'm doing
like this Arkana like now boys knock it
off and it doesn't work ligado
without my knowing climbs out with his
tiger and he's just like intricately
starts like cutting the the tentacles
like a bone side like he's shaping it
yeah to cut to get those edges and
remove them hold on there's a larger
tentacle yeah so he has to he has to
assert himself he's here to destroy
these others and it's easy they don't
fight no they don't not tough to cut
through but they're not actively yeah
yeah he got EAA's ligarius back there
actively pruning from the sort of like
root clump just actively pruning it off
and the root clump is trying to go
somewhere different than the rest of the
tentacles back in the kitchen so Mincy
has been moved to tears he's had a
single bite of the cornerstone and that
appears to be all he required of this
place yet people are people are asking
him questions about water deep like he
has sort of been integrated in a strange
way into the homey atmosphere
of the drowning career lovely I have
been brewing a cup of tea to give to you
and it is going to taste disgusting but
you're going to barf up everything that
you have eaten so I hand you that and I
say aim for the window darling what
just drink it all takes it and then
drinks it while immediately walking you
need to like the back those because the
service entrance here yes the slop hole
I was telling your shot because you're
sad yeah she's drinking and then okay
but so we know I sound like when done
Arthur's I see it was telling me do you
want it sounds just like a cat so and
then you hear it Rosie go is stop it God
knows all force to it we replaced an owl
pellet bulge not like an owl pellet or
what else just a now yeah yeah it's got
a whole Mouse attack you know I'm so
impressed like Rose you can make flavors
across the whole spectrum of experience
good flavors mega that slaves of an air
flavor
you know niak exactly that's what I was
like you're the toughest kitchen have
ever khaki no but I can probably brew
some fucking yeah if the CAC impressive
and I've seen the prick okay no in a few
Shane Smith asked you at the beginning
miss would know now asked about on table
talk to you a little so this is this is
the the situation no no no what that's
why are you quoting that song because
there you went away on a three-day
vacation it's very old if you look the
keys to the drawn courrier min song in
the in the grip of this religious dining
experience you know having been embraced
by this small town comes over to the bar
and you can reach this over for your
hands behind the bar okay
and he says I think you I think you
I'm very welcome have I noticed that his
scribe hasn't gotten to eat so as as he
has come over and to stick you describe
you as you look over describe one of
them is just gone okay
and there's like some powdered sugar
okay like around here
excellent excellent I was definitely
going to help that happen right on the
sleeve good very good very good
hey this on that on that partial hmm I
say shuttle spoon you're you're great
you're very welcome
this is courtesy of prophetess John
don't don't forget her name when you're
writing what I hope is your favorable
review awesome Cruiser visitors Mathis
this is for you I was like this thing
stop yeah so they misshape of the
homework star junior Olympians right so
come on gosh that's not funny
this could be the they're they're
they're on their way out and you can see
as they leave and take a right toward
the center of the long road about ten
seconds after they leave they you can
hear them like laughing in the street
like mean laughing no no no try to hang
making fun of us pull out my sword okay
I come back to read large I I don't
think any of us know what you did so
should we follow them out through what
they're laughing at Oh
and then um yeah like I hear and I go
spell everything right yeah you
definitely did it literally it's like
squirrels leaf leaf and emojis
okay I think Abby papers and happy
family oh I get it yeah okay whatever
yeah yeah the restaurant I guess oh yeah
yeah yeah and like walnuts just like a
single tear like the most beautiful
poetry okay great job yeah yeah no
thumbs up yeah yeah yeah so it's um you
just you continue to operate the inn
well I want to know what they're
laughing at you using am i right yeah
yeah
do you crawl out the front no I don't
want them to know that I belong to this
establishment is just like working my
hair well you go check it out I can
report back yeah your eyes and I go cute
I did I think I'm sitting outside and I
see another I know everything I gotta
know look at the sky what is this can
Wow hey can i impress it alright I'm
gonna hop up to windowsill look up and
you got it almost completely right but
the are intron it's backward yeah what
immediately like I have to fix I'm gonna
have to wait to cast a spell again so
but but just you take a peek out there
you see that this is exactly there's
like pointing and pointing up at the sky
and the scribe and he sort of walked
their way back out to the center of town
okay
okay great that backwards are might have
sold some of the rustic nature too yeah
exactly and it's like all this is how
they do it yeah they do it out here no
no that was that was exquisite I have a
full list of everything that happens
depending on how many strikes you get
table talk yeah I will don't worry do we
still have clientele yet there there are
a few here but now it's mostly whispers
source 800 yeah they're they're skimping
up the last prey flakes of the
cornerstones
do you guys want some corner stones I
don't think anybody here got to eat all
right anything to get that to surprise
you
yeah feel-good good batch for my good
good friends we should take them out you
want to eat with the rest of the patrons
yeah only for a house forget oh yeah
alright let's have a little little snack
time together okay
yes good and I've customized of your jam
I see you're making notes and like
you're bringing them out almost filled
up on tentacle
I like spam so they get you I thought
you were like eating the leftovers from
other people yeah well they are very
good she's just like no concept of like
a social construct this is so proud of
one you know the garbage I find yeah
good while those are cooking can we come
to close up shop it would be an
appropriate time to close shop but I
mean right now there's still people
there's still people there if you can
get a couple people might want rooms oh
oh jeez nice I'll take care of them
yeah you got any want money yeah I'll go
up a lot of people and also silly this
concludes our dining service for the day
any of you need lodging for the night
I'd be happy to take care of that hands
are up you have you have a total of four
rooms and there there are five hands
like this isn't a few people a few
people it must be a firm out of town
maybe they want to take a pool cue
bringing it right here okay um can i I
have absolutely no personal effects
could I rent out my room
Wow you could get all five people in you
could take some doing
obviously you'd have to go up there and
move some stuff around I think you might
have one personal effect you want to get
rid of some of those filthy leaves is a
Melling us room is long yes it was the
nicest room possible can I don't have a
bed cuz it's August and I'm Catholic
sighs oh yeah and yours is mine special
alright you know what it's fine
um so what were to do I look at them
does anybody look like they maybe you
gave me funny there's four rooms and
there's five people okay how about this
I go for the five who are the five
and kids decide people and oh they
definitely should let in anyone together
yeah I'm just you you have like two
families and then you have a couple and
then a handful of change hmm
okay and then I say well okay so I
pointed that like the family and a
couple anyone that came with multiple
people yeah
and then that I'm assuming there's two
stragglers and I look at them and I go
so we're running a special for last
stones day if you pay past a normal rate
and if you can have normal rate and go
in together
you can have our luxury less stones day
camaraderie sweet so whole Wow
what's that well in the spirit of last
stones day you know where we all end up
together in the beyond you will really
get this protection I go and I say so
you will you know in turn yourselves for
the night in the same bed and enjoy the
camaraderie become Rodri sweet does the
deal were three ways no no sorry I know
see everyone wants this room but I'll
offer it to you cuz I came to you first
take two of them and then though they'll
try to get together I mean they don't
this is where they want to stay do they
want to stay together yeah yeah give me
that - David they will do it they will
do it so everybody takes the full room
is five silver and then the half of the
half rates are two silver five copper
right so though though they will hook
all this up coins will exchange hands
iCup ticket there's my girl I have like
a thousand gold Wow how much dough
actually like there's gotta be a ton in
here open up the till
so 27 okay yeah so as you so you think
everybody else up to the night make sure
that their bedding is secure if you find
bedding I tuck them in oh you even if
you give them the full experience yeah
yeah I have absolutely no nurturing
skills so it's just like what and then
tuck them in way too tight and I go do
not move until it's time to get a
bedtime
no bathroom breaks stay exactly hold a
start you see the Sun yeah for then no
Gavin just care it out yes don't get up
and leave until later all right so as
everyone as everyone is basically
strangled in their beds well yeah
exactly in turn make some more money
um okay I read in cold blood tareka
police hey um there is another guest
that you did not see of course at all
and in fact you don't think that you
don't remember him being there and you
don't see and you did not see him until
everyone else was gone
what well you come you come down the
stairs mmm what'd he look like
what he looked like he looked like a
novel unique sort of gentleman he has
high black hair almost looking on a
pompadour type shape okay um he has a
very is a very fine black vest black
jacket over the top it's describing Reza
consider snow is not the critic how is
it risky
he has no cloak of Starhawk um yeah yeah
exactly guys ready
black the deck exactly and he has pale
white skin and he has with him sort of
got at his feet near the side of his
table he is petting something that looks
like it's trying
very very hard to be a dog no animals
allowed sir which one of you want that a
service animal so you have pretend to be
dead with me in my room for half money
onyx onyx is over onyx is over
underneath the stove hmm like onyx is
not leaving the under stove sir region
like I want to make sure that it comes
like what I mean when I say trying to be
a dog starter kit looks like no no it
looks like the seams aren't it looks
like the seams aren't quite right like
we've got well no yeah it looks like it
looks like the sort of dog like Google
deep dream would generate like what it
is happy about it and it's like you know
there's a happy dog where it's like the
mouth opens up and smiles the mouth
opens up and the tongue comes out but
there are teeth down the middle of the
tongue
and he gives it a couple pass and it
rolls this organ back up and do it
scroll hmm um so bad on duty this time I
hate this place hey to the intelligent
so one little go down the stairs and
walk up to the sir and go hi my name is
Lauren is there anything I can do to
help you and it should be immediately
obvious that she is not talking to him
this is except the monster dog to the
lesser dog you have Amal handling I
don't need animal handling I can speak
to them and they all want to be handled
not thank you ma'am and and right now I
mean I have a neck I would not get
handled yeah I mean I think the handling
is default not office more of a mesh
that I had yeah he says I represent the
noble knife the dog says it know and I
go what's that boy
oh that's cool no joke as soon as I hear
noble knife I go that's great we have
business what is going on with this dog
he looks down at the dog and the dog
looks up at him and then he opens his
mouth and the job comes out with two
ways
sure and he's just like looks like I
wanted the damn vehicle for like what
what oh my god okay um well an answer
yeah god I just
okay well yet we do have we do have
business to conduct
where's our gems it up in your room
dinar yes okay you want to go in a used
phone replaces provenance
okay so you're swaddled you are and I
think the three of us are still eating
eating the cornerstones right I'm Emil I
imagine I was in the kitchen directing
velvet to clean up the blood
okay yeah excellent hello walnut you and
I are taken out so yeah I'm like
unbuckled Blake yeah yeah yeah it's
quiet down here looking breastplates
hanging off yes ISM a I'm gonna know gon
ders can I do with my tiny foot and
[Laughter]
indicate like no life
okay yeah do it if not yeah why one more
I'm sorry what is that mean I'll settle
on 100
oh cool oh no book coming out art then
our way to adoration Thank You
featherweight so I say I say to the guy
go I want to know more about all this
point to the dog in a minute but how do
I know you're from the noble life I will
be paid in full
I believe that head office has a
secretary in' is our information on that
correct it looks like these guys single
guy checks out rigorous but fair right
okay how's my head out what that dog
though yes I will have nightmares of
this dog get that yes I don't come back
here I think we got a pen account I'm
gonna put it out of its misery
something's wrong with that dog I think
a lot of dog it's just not a dog I mean
yeah okay I'm doing it I lay on hands
the dog best it looks hurt I think
they'll be cool I think you should kill
it just doing it a strike a zero
give him the gym and then I'll take the
dog to kill the top it will be long
should I get the gym and smash the dog
with it I don't like dogs and I blush in
the dog with the gem shall go
accidentally drop it on the dog like all
right I like that I'll go get the kid
like a hundred and twenty pounds just
tell ya I'll go get it
drop it drop it from the from the upper
deck I'll go upstairs I laugh a Decker
is it 120 Blair knows no oh it's heavy I
did nothing to make it nothi hundred
twenty pounds to grab yeah yeah clearly
a football it's no big deal for you so I
will run up and get in this one that
says he checks out so I go get it come
down go away and I like some debate like
big falling pieces listen I'm having him
sign the appropriate forms yeah Jesus
Lee she does he does so without
hesitation grains are payment on this
500 gold Oh 500 wing wings all right
mama when I'll saddle up next to you at
the gym I'll let a dog break for that
company we got that we got that money
you already pay that awesome its head
office so it just get it like well like
before the cut will come down to this
mmm
flopping on the table rolls off kills
the dog no that's what I try roll come
on try to kill the dog Dexter secretary
no this thing's mrs. D mo demonic it's
gonna I know it I great it's like you're
looking at like the final boss of season
three I know yeah this you guys regret
I know practice with your stomach well
you can do whatever you want you're
playing Dungeons &amp; Dragons while he is
doing this thing with the the jambwal
and I'm sure this little yeah exactly
um I want to just really quickly you
speak to animals talk to the dog real
quick and just say um can i I hope this
isn't a root but what are you it is not
an animal mmm although I just sound like
a cow
yes yeah we are I'm not sure as I'm
given the guy is the jewel I'm just like
a cute cute dog what's his name nigga
you as you talk to you're like wow
that's exactly it and it says it looks
at your face and says oh no like is that
even weird nice and worse now yeah with
very human lips
human teeth the other thing oh my gosh
the guy is things name I want to put a
name that they nightmare yeah another
major was Harry Wilson til you so you
you set it on the table
yeah and he cistern which is the
creatures name okay cistern
yeah he puts his paws up on the edge of
the table and then he sort of like puts
his mouth like at the base of the gym
like I'm imagine like a dark version of
the lady in the Tramp yeah yeah there's
no Dark Star heading on dark word Reagan
when were they going to live exactly and
so as he as he places in places his craw
his moist crop at the base of the gym
and then just starts to slurp
it and then however big his head needs
to be that's how big it becomes until
the gym is taken completely inside but
it doesn't like an anaconda or something
like that like it doesn't like when you
see their like whole gazelle it's like
it's just gone oh I had actually
wandered over with leftover commercial
clothing and I was like and now I'm
looking at the dog and I'm looking at
the leftovers and I'm thinking like
maybe this isn't the kind of food that
that sister could be you think maybe
cisterns full okay I paid a lot of money
for a food there buddy Altos way cheaper
okay
mad dogs yeah he says he says what
happened to the lizard king tada
LS let me retrieve him I go back in the
kitchen so he doesn't see me a vest that
I've been wearing him when I door so he
was my friend
he's my inside close friend but he
stopped laughing at my jokes my inside
no no I did I do like if he just you
know said well I don't know yes all
right now so I removed him yeah and redo
all the snaps yeah exactly
so you carry him back out yeah I carry
my cock like a baby hold on before I
bring him back out can I be refreshed on
what their position was so it's not like
he's gonna hide perfect you know what
was the other his that that in rabaa the
job yet that the job as the document sir
would relate it is that they they wanted
this shadow gym they did not express
their purpose
however shadowy it may be it's the right
gym yeah yeah I don't even know if it's
why would I bring them out then he
doesn't care just we want to each take
just like draped over stick all right
sounds good like as well yeah like a
and second an after-dinner mint for your
animals after jam you eat this
desiccated King are you gonna bring him
or not
that mean if I had known that prior to
exiting I probably wouldn't but I guess
okay you do that revile do it like I
can't I do it yeah he's like what like
what and what became of mi so I bring
him out and is he stiff is he vaguely
best like no it's like one of those eat
you know those toys for it's like you
push the thing in the bottom and then
the whole model giggles oh yeah yeah
okay I had envisioned him as like like a
formed jerky not like she would pee now
when he when he's like oh yeah we up in
here sure like the scene used and so
forth like that but if you peel him off
like there's not a lot of grip yeah this
is this the this was him it is him still
hasn't really said a lot fuck up days he
sort of looks down into the eyes this
all right our business is concluded then
so you go very light I was wearing a
sleeve if you watch us you just like
refix in like pushing the arms down over
the top like a sweater yeah the guy
doesn't care at all and you're like wait
really
I was wearing him you have to know I
think it does lie every morning I wear
them and sometimes he talks to me yeah
we're friends he says that clan is that
Klein is now an open war over its
leadership I had an idle curiosity oops
sucks to be them nobody I heard their
bluff lying down right here I was and
whatever you want him however you want
him to feel this specific position of
this of the skull and jaw
he is appropriate okay I just want to
call out when he said that there aren't
open wards and are mumbled I heard the
blood line got a lot stronger so yeah I
did not get it and I appreciate that
I find like that
Walter's doing okay sorry Bobby
yeah Bobby both sweet Bobby all right
well if that's it
remember we hope you'll be working with
us again thank you for coming
aggravation appropriate like us on
gentlemen Valley branch yeah yeah I
guess I'm grill yes look at the present
very elders and as you're relating this
he licks his finger and he draws a shape
on the wall comment no what is it
sailor of food Oh sanitation what does
it look like we can show you dick ah
graffiti nice to see no no it's not like
it isn't like this symbol of male
attorney okay all right so just that
yeah and he is able to move through it
along with sister and thank God just
good written ticket on the way yeah what
just a little tap just like get out
faster all the way through especially
six okay no II give you any why do you
know okay cuz I can we can make that no
I want to be a committed relationship a
factor would you would you need to roll
on what skill would not have to roll on
to figure out what if I know what that
thing is if there are more like it
because that creature would I be
familiar with yes yes I very oh I'm just
curious
I think so a GU dog would it be yeah -
Jenny's and Gouda that lets you know
let's try it yeah yeah exactly
I'm sorry good let's try Arkana just for
kicks so it's going to be Slyke a circle
of five right legacy hey alright so
that's a 22 you think so you have
encountered creatures much like this
before
except that generally speaking they
don't try to manifest complex shapes
generally speaking they try to manifest
simple stationary objects like doors
tables oh so you've never seen it before
but you think this might be
some kind of tame mimic weird ditto cool
thing yeah that was a pet it was just
like a dog but it had two little dot
eyes instead of like regular dog s I
could tell the bit of like a Pokemon
joke I said yo c'mon yeah yeah I kept
small another one we catch as many as
you can
yeah like don't don't get stressed
getting them all is a tall order you
don't have to get high you ain't get
more tips here is for mastery anyway so
there's you can hear some snoring get
that coin though right uh I go to the
hell's head up as our 60% but I do like
I do like that you are this is the
second or third time in this adventure
where as soon as an object or item comes
into the party you are immediately
asking for it and then taking note that
is that is actually very important that
I hear you doing that okay now in the
bare minimum I'm going to make up this
role he has internalized the role and
that is vitally important and you'll be
rewarded so this day is over we are
starting in on the third day but it is a
much simpler day obviously the people
upstairs will expect breakfast but
there's nothing like the type of
sophistication that was required of you
before okay then they shall have no
suspicion it can be rustic it can be
rustic again now just ask why we rust
they exactly
you could eat some rough rocks and
sticks yeah
what we're talking about now in terms of
tasks does anyone want to tell me what
tasks remain from prappas oh yeah oh so
jess is gonna be any old business
cooking cleaning carriage house out for
storage purposes decorating it we look
at original cleaning of the carriage
home
we did surely need in trouble so I think
all we managed to to cooking and
operation at the end thus far
yeah we still need a cleanup care towel
and I don't know if we did any
decorating do we decorate we didn't need
to you decorated with food so we're done
their words and mirth okay okay so we do
need to clean advocate I would say
that's a that's in order to satisfy
absolutely every one of these
requirements I think it's going to have
a the ghosts in there was you get a good
Jost easier on G yeah animator just
backwards Jean yeah alright so if we
give everybody to breakfast everybody
out
lock up for the day or for the moment
for the eight for the a.m. right um we
can go try and tackle this sure carriage
house and you were in there before and
you guys have locked in for days I'm
still in it because in my image I've
never come out no but we can go in the
even lava announcer enough yeah yeah so
we can there were ways in now okay I
think there was some concern though
because that we didn't know whether or
not Hoffa knew exactly what was in there
especially not like a little fort that
seems to have been built by her children
that collapse there anymore yeah hold
this right yet dinner was junk I
remember that like okay I read a lot of
it out fit it to the alley we got all
the clues out oh yeah I'm not worried
about that
oh you maybe we just need to we did say
that velvet like took all the crap out
and he just sports and crash and rub it
yeah yeah yeah okay let's head in there
happy throw open that front door let's
get some light in there get out roll de
scrub sure look velvet Bella's doing all
that hard work right yeah Bell but we
provide him with a you know a mop and a
pail and he is not wearing the velvet so
you just looks like the mops it's like
it's Sorcerer's Apprentice I just you
would say it's peaceful on Fantasia yeah
songs one yeah I don't crazy because I'm
music although although do I recall
correctly that I could instantiate
multiple Velvets because this ritual
takes me an hour to cast
uh but am I only allowed to have one at
a time does it require concentration I
don't know to maintain truth no I think
that's the case now what is the spell
it's called unseen servant mm-hmm now
we're showing people some real Dungeons
and Dragons right uh all right open that
yeah I'm throwing open all the windows
in carriage house trying to like get
some dust and out of there no I'm trying
to get more light in here exactly yeah
it's what kind of what kind of cleaning
tasks do we have is it just the huge
that is exactly just dusting sweeping I
mean you think that your cart could fit
in here if it were all cleaned out I got
their shelves in the back right now
really so it's a lot of old wood okay
and fun old furniture sheets I don't see
anything that would cause it's not
concentration yep for several
conjuration ritual yeah mm-hmm yeah yeah
no this doesn't require yeah if you
really wanted to I mean I can't see us I
can't I can't see why you couldn't just
instantiate one per hour a bunch of help
you do this so what do you do do you
oversee this process they are ignore so
where I could go into town and just
round up one of the kids who loved me no
my little sparrows here's some money
the second area is trying to say it yeah
that's my little can learning to get
down here on our hands just six hours of
meditation and we have our yeah you're
from the dirt zone and your tissue
Buddha connealy character no I actually
like it the way it is but if it makes
you get cleaned I'm not going to do I
realize dirt than blood
well y'all are squabbling over that I'm
going to use my speak to animals for the
day and just get in the middle the
carriage house and go all right
everybody get out for a second and then
like I will get out there's a bunch of
rats with mice echo out some little
trash pandas jump out to weird
neighborhood cats I've never had the
pleasure of meeting them crawl off to
some corner look around I'm like I did
what I could
[Music]
there are either there waiting just
button and that's mine yeah I had your
group I know I cleaned I cleaned this so
we have wood furniture you sheets all
would you say all this pretty flammable
quite see I see big money is the
building made of wood deeply so yeah
drag it all along yeah especially dry
wood okay okay yeah let's we'll just
haul all of it out and have a bonfire
unless it looks like stuff that you
would like no a hoarding situation
really it's just like this this is not
what her her life has not been about
cleaning this space her life has been
about other things it's you only does
anything especially mystical and you
don't have any reason to believe that
she knew about that fort oh well what is
make sure there's no personal effects of
the children yeah and then burn the
whole thing down yeah I know is fire
yeah let's do it so eat your sponge I'm
going to use let's go fashioned some
like a pull a pull type thing creatures
eat a full horse doubtful creature
supported stone full creature um just
throw a sheet down there all the stuff
on it grab the sheet with big boy
muscles if you don't mind and pull out
into the yard where we can burn it and
dance around it mm-hm
I'm good to keep the last stone say
treasures coming yeah yeah yeah that's
my plan
got sacred flame I'm ready torch the
shit all right well y'all do that I'm
gonna do a produce my stupid water thing
I was gonna say came with some of the
water yeah I have a personal thing we're
coming so yeah I can create wait 10+2
lemon Dolan gallons of water always own
abstruse off his hands it says would
create water I can actually create rain
Hey yeah they are great
a foot cube so I'm going to just make it
rain inside the the oranges to get the
or the carriage house yeah just to start
getting the juices flowing and then
we'll come back in it give it a scrub
scrub brush it out okay good now you
ever mess up skywriting you can just be
like listen I mean it race that was okay
go anywhere very localized right so this
thing is starting to this is starting to
look like a functional functional region
again so where is our cart if it's not
in the typically speaking tours
typically speaking you sort of park it
alongside street parking parallel yeah
we could use a space again do we have
the club it's not stolen a club no kind
of that sweet honor yeah but we under is
a boot that's you claim it does has that
mobile
protection is good exactly but the cart
when parked in the carriage house gains
a speed boost around amazing so you're
able to travel farther with the rested
horse and cart maintenance facility so
you can also change out your items in
here easily once per day in terms of
your customization stuff like the garage
is in GTA exactly right so when you are
know if you've reached level five as
individual characters your franchise has
reached level 100
so there's table level one before that
it's like a base building conversation
is a base building kind of situation and
the very first building that you have
yes is the carriage house stretch house
I love a feeling game this is great
here's house and a mail comes as the as
the last you know few trickles of
rainwater are running out of the
carriage house you can see that Alvie
rolls up to the drawing courtier and she
has a package for cthe wrist proud
every single time Alvey arrives I want
to do this thing in the sims where you
build house around the mailman because
the whistling so annoying it's a geyser
not really you put him in the pool and
take those ladders away tabletalk how do
you kill your yeah I don't worry don't
worry well the mailman game is killing
war narrator since are you happy it was
definitely like then during the will
write quote about that when he learned
that people were used basically using
his game to murder Sims and he had the
most fascinating response to it he said
it seems like some people enjoy
exploring the failure states and I was
like dude that's a sick burn yeah I'm
gonna remember that that's good yeah I
was like wow that's one way of putting
it again ice cold I examine it yeah this
it is a surprise because I don't know
who would send me exactly well it has it
has a label that it's been affixed with
glue and the label says acquisition
incorporated okay makes more sense is it
the minute that a package we were like a
letter ago but no it's like it's almost
like a satchel bag it'd be something
that gets a satchel that is on a belt Oh
what what's this I'm excited oh you take
a satchel that is on a belt okay let me
I'm so you so you can put this built on
even underneath your your cloak and it's
it's substantial was it once a royalty
that is now dead I don't think so okay
my interest in wearing it yes it has
been diminished it no your first
question any time you encounter a couple
poses
what if this used to be not just read
whether this is rollover anyone know
that you don't have any Dominion and
though well I got a new bag when she
leveled up in document C well that's
what I'm saying so maybe unless Edwards
person I don't know let's find out so
let me open that yellow me um do those
straps um do you know the term regular
mmm-hmm the are ad you la yeah yeah kind
of
so when you when you loosen when you
loosen the attachment at the top like
the strings that keep it closed you can
see that there is a small row of sort of
blunted teeth that wrap around the inner
edge of the bag oh yeah oh I thought
you'd like that then it seems dark it's
very dark in there it's darker than you
would expect
imagine a dark imagine it's dark sack a
dark bag
yeah think of the darkest bag you can
think of it's that darker though it's
confusing to me yeah my I guess I'm
standing why maybe I'm in the bar let me
just throw a little a little light on it
and I walk over to a torch oh yeah sure
yeah you can you bring it up you bring
the torch over and then you see a little
like a little envelope inside but it
doesn't like physically it doesn't seem
like it's in the right place like you're
you're you as you move the torch over it
seems like there's corners and depth
like inside this pouch and the letter
that are that are not 100% Euclidian you
don't think that's upsetting what I do
reach and get that letter yeah inside
you open letter and it says greetings
towards person acquisitions incorporated
red larch branch desperate Valley it
says please accept this gift upon your
promotion this is the belly of this
creature
hmm exists here it does live as a head
office and you may store objects in it
as you please and you may send objects
to us through this creature we're that's
regulated and garnished by holding kind
of kind of mean stuff to us through sky
why it's a portal so this is like the
the chest
singing resin
people yes I was thinking like we could
get our payment my staff over like a car
like an enderchest again direct deposit
yeah we should do direct deposit through
this from now on
is there a on one can we walk through it
put your head in it well that's what I'm
going to do I'll get to that head office
right quick into this beast and all
right no everybody dive and one in the
back
everybody get in here and that's at Cape
Point yeah we have anyone in the banks
do you have anything to send to it now
you're all familiar with the contents of
the letter I like so I need anything I
go I look at it and I go um I go who
write your new wrote your note oh wow
I'm gonna see the bottom here secretary
we're going to small ends up mr.
secretary in chess is good if I had hit
from almond eyes place or the bay up I
put the fag inside the bag weird the
holding creature shut your mouth exactly
well this is a perfectly good spot to
pause here and go to a commercial break
of course subscribers only see cool AI
stuff something to consider don't go
anywhere we'll be right back they had
just results a fairly substantial
milestone event the franchise proper has
gained level one you have your first out
building the carriage house that
increases the speed of the cart now you
have also you also have the pleasure and
enjoyment of a level two horse person
and that also grants you the ability to
store lots and lots of stuff inside of a
moist creature
you can count higher yeah you know a
whole new set of numbers oh my goodness
wait to get my in a minute every time
you put something you get to caress
these teeth each time there's no
scenario in which you don't come away
from this happy
yeah I'm just everything I can actually
kind of Pat the inside of his tummy and
nobody has to know this is my secret I
put the coins in it hey buddy hey stop
it out just a little bit extra love my
mom yeah you introduce yourself there I
mean not yet yeah I got to think about
how to well there may be your intimate
already yeah exactly
exactly like you're already so close
yeah so close
yeah maybe we will maybe we can start
unless you have any complaints with the
statue of arrogant our dragon the nude
the nude one no the one that we had like
two hundred time you feel yeah the ones
that were made in there I will make it
but there was our decoration in there
yeah it's like our trophy and our mating
room yeah but now we have this we have
that I mean either that's a cool but
like the wizard card championship the
one that I don't even mean I will enter
for that they will talk about uh oh I
mean it's on someone's character she's
out there the current reigning wizard
kart champion so is it my question yes I
don't know wall nutter great good ivy
good job speaking have yeah we got have
motion flushing upstairs yeah we should
probably sore that'd be kind of like it
no no we're talking about the ultimate
tailgate scenario you install that thing
on the cart you know what I mean is
there a slot on the cart there's not a
slot on the cart for this you would have
to requires fairly substantial
modifications which would among other
things require you to interact with well
so I know a guy who knows oh yeah yeah
but did not last don't say somebody sent
over well well first got a lot of family
knows oh I thought he died yeah yeah all
right now it's a it's a it's just it's
not an uncommon name Oh
the Dean wanna sing it yes procedure
alright so I mean take three seems
pretty good yes Dave day three yeah how
do you prepare this place for the
arrival of its mistress onyx is brushed
oh yeah fluffed buffed buttercup I don't
like flowers flower both ears I have
prepared the wedding cake
god I love em right her favorites lots
and lots of warm tea lemonade I see
whatever you guys are into dragon food
whatever I have anything really how she
is
to that open like that it's like this
fancy seat yeah get that here they come
paper and over actually so we've got
some so we got some brushing we got some
snacks
I mean you've prepared the place
anything else so you want to lie down
toddlers ultimate I'm like to hear this
oh yeah I'm punishing all those surfaces
you hear that Bluff out the the you know
the amethyst tentacle burns oh yeah yeah
there's some of that I need to tend to
the little mending we'll cover that yeah
and then what's the other thing I can do
now that's a trick expressive it's a
prestidigitation to hide some of the
stain but I do have to keep coming back
to everybody else asking if it's clean
because I don't realize it and this what
is this what somebody who's not me was
considered clean how about this is it
this is what we want because I went I
rubbed it and there was there's nothing
so this is good right let suppose have
some dirt now okay long as I understand
yeah can I go outside and do some
landscaping real quick yeah I took plant
growth oh yeah yeah she has she's got
like the classic window planters and
yeah so um it will in a hundred foot
radius
call any plants cause any plans to at
one for speeds they will start over
growing just getting bigger and like
more you know fantastic beautiful yes
yeah like mojitos you know in more more
Alice in Wonderland it says like you
know like a 1 mile diameter plants would
yield double food at harvest so like
that kind of thing wears like whatever
is around the drawing a corner it would
be a bigger better more lush like better
smells like she's got like a butterfly
bush now it's just like a lousy with
those butterflies this is like yeah wow
so this is the sourcing art yeah this is
the sort of thing it's like it's like
welcome to the drone and courier
postcard this is a it it can be no other
place exactly how about you
things that are nice when you just come
home from vacation and your house is
clean
it's about fridges stocks - Rosie makes
sure that all of like the grains and
everything they were used for all of
those cornerstones everything is fresh
stocked the kitchen is spotless
everything is tidy as hell within with
Indian so that like profit just comes
back and feels good to be home for
vacation you've also like do the dishes
or whatever that's amazing
we're all doing all this dinner how do
you help just going to do I
I command you to clean so yeah she's
like I definitely I like what I think we
won that pouch of dragons
I'm just like Shana Ronin like good job
good scrub many plants I'm just takin
nap thank you so that I'm well rested
the green crop when she gets back this
is all working well in hand
yeah really nice yeah I reached up a
towel by the way and just like buff one
year scale yeah like yeah that's what
afterwards and I would do he would just
clean himself like so he looks great
when she was back shine didn't she was
impressed when she gets back a gleam now
here's the situation
a car comes to the drawing Cordier and
an exhausted terrifying sweaty man
descends from his cart as fast as he can
looks around goes to the back of his
cart gets a single barrel bearing a Z
and Signia on it and he brings it over
to the front door and he says I have a
delivery oh and Ron delivery Oh prophet
Ron yep what except that right here that
got that okay bring it right over here I
had three of these okay and I don't know
a now I have two of them why because
there are displacer beasts
on the long road that's true a couple of
them and the internet I did push off
some of the barrels so that I could live
great
ah and what the entire time Wallace is
scribbling that down she goes great so
just sign this written account of what
happened and we'll be all good he puts
an X at the bottom of it
Cheyenne Amex I I don't have litters man
what's your name Steven Steven and she
goes that's great hold this quill and
then she writes Steven it is spelled
wrong Jared as you guys well that's all
in order so he looks like a Cheers
yes it was injured he says okay well I
mean you may thank me
this I've had this before have you ever
had it I don't know what it is
zag renessa ale Agron has or ale you
sound like you're a big fan
no big enough Fannie with me want to
keep a barrel for yourself no cooking up
some story about the place of displacer
beef I don't know you have no pushing
huh no you have some you have enough
haven't ya
have some of this and then you won't
have any anymore it tastes like a puddle
in a stable like you don't want it why
why did this you have no idea
ask omen drawn well I will because we're
very close friends now yeah well thank
you for your service whatever yes it's
like a plunk his cart and ride you Arabs
because I'll tear it out of here Jared
tip for you Jared as he is pulling away
another cart dusty from the road
hold on what's up it's like rush hour
huh boys are blowing up your phone phone
alright I'm a milkshake now this car
comes up and a
nervous-looking prophetess drawn oh it's
assisted out of the cart armor still
polished to a gleam you have some you
have some idea of what it must have been
like to see her on the field like you
can you can tell that that you would
work harder around this person and she
is trying to get into the drawing career
but there's a huge barrel Midori I go
it's an art prof I'll get that for you
and then I just grabbed the barrel and
put it away and there open the door and
as she sees it all clean and I go I did
all six yeah this is all me yeah I'm
looking hopeful I'm meeting Jason Thank
You Rosie know what I said no my name is
dinar I think you just came here
thank you have your ears she's old okay
I know because I'm starting to go
alright is the email boy she odd she's
she's walking around the drownin
courrier almost like going over a mental
checklist it's a it's a lung it's a long
ride north and she's sort of good going
place to place in the drawing courrier
trying to iterate this checklist of
things that she thought she was going to
have to do place by place there now and
then she might move a chair a little bit
she goes into the kitchen it's not a
nightmare a snack there waiting for oh
yeah yeah she she's trying to take it
all in and if you think that you think
that her eyes are glinting a little bit
she says Audra wanted to keep your
daughter I hope that that's ok what do
you mean keep her she thinks that she
thinks that she could teach share a lot
oh oh so like an apprenticeship
yeah Wow that seems like a big deal
I think that it probably is a big deal
ah ten wonderful
okay so Brahma was her last student she
doesn't take them often Wow so she she
must have really impressed her I new
show is better than Brahma I told her
that racial teacher to be a what why
that was that all that work wow we just
got a delivery from your son actually
oh um Zagar now sir ale two barrels and
heard that it tastes like a warm puddle
that's terrible
that's that's charitable um y-yeah I
just put it I just put it up front I'm I
don't know if there's something wrong
with it my son made some kind of a deal
with the brewery and I don't know if
something's wrong with his batch or what
but it's not for your mouth I would not
put I would keep it away I would not
drink it to narcan you take that out can
you move it outside
sure and then just put it anywhere I
just said outside I'll find someone no
problem oh yeah it can't be that bad I
know a kind of almond likes it you're
not supposed to drink it it's got a IV
horrible thing do you say bud chug it
yeah bitter great true great is there a
type of charge it is no I know it is a
better John you know one yeah I know why
Table Talk yes and dandy rosie has had a
drug some stuff in her life and so she
says now hold on I'm interested so you
and I are going to go give this beggar
Nezzer ale Pat's Riley I've not one for
ale but if ya omen thinks it's good it
must be good I just take you don't have
to have your own I'll bring a pint glass
and we'll we'll fill it a water jury I'm
sure yeah
what are germs what you sleep in dirt
you are dirt um but only on the outside
sweetie okay so I want
- I want to take of mugga this and I'd
like to do some kind of perception check
on it to see like what the hell if
there's anything giggles the shitty beer
and that's fine
drink it outside don't mess it I am I'm
Alan I'm a mess I'm outside doing okay
my perception I don't think anything
else I'm going to bed in that I'll make
Josi into craft brewing - probably - all
the way yeah that's intense
yeah I mean a lot of the things that are
wrong with this
don't require a perception check
you don't think okay um paint me a word
picture long water okay is what's
bouquet what's the bouquet the bouquet
is old bong water yeah see how can I put
it um ah that's why I left that well no
no no no yes yeah I would say that it it
has a strong note of Raccoon and there
appears to be something like black moss
sort of traveling through the liquid
okay okay ladies brooch
yeah food shows it definitely okay
doesn't smell great does it look great I
think it's good go for it
it's got moss and raccoons and get a
little slippy set to things I am on
guard to like resuscitate you want to
just scoop through their hands that's
how you doing let's do some this
konschak yeah okay bring it yeah boy
buddy uh how you like a 16 I like it a
lot that's bad it you take it and then
you did you can just feel it's like
walking through a ghost or something
it's just a cold shiver that just starts
here and then just like expands out and
if you shake your head and then you so
you feel for a very short period of time
the chiller to grave I know
Oh God cutter she's loved this yeah I
give you a sense no stranger this
alcohol anymore so yeah I mean I would
say same for you in contact it really
isn't great
you simply rolled forward you can you
take a sip and you can feel this soft
free black lozenge like you're drinking
it and you're trying to figure it out
and then it just goes straight down your
throat hold its own volition but it was
like just like drawn in and then um he
hits the ground like unconscious just
just the ground like much as you might
have seen in when you first met Oh
passed out drunk again yeah it's funny
because I think you drew the glow man
but it looks like an outline in chalk
your body just now hitting the ground
good beating
uh well I'm wandering on through a cave
Oh spirit journey and I I'm like I stand
up in this cave yeah absolutely expand
up that let's get some way I could
describe last the day whether it is yeah
absolutely
there is a passage you don't know which
way you were moving in this case when
you got here but you can you can see
that yeah absolutely you know the
traditional bioluminescence you're
surrounded by all the strange colors
that are to you normal but would be to
any other member of the party terrifying
Oh fascinating feel as a home here I'm
going to just keep walking and the
direction I'm facing right now all right
he immediately gets up and stand
straight up stock up right what ah
you good yeah man I wasn't that good
what's why do I see further down a cave
you know you're you were back in front
of the door years past what happened
oh oh ah hmm
you get some more for that sounds a
little bit more not I want to go crazy
with it
it's very strong stuff but clearly the
person knew what they were doing you
lost consciousness for a second tears I
did not the point
I don't know I forgot there hey no
fractured ribs lesson right affecting
gate in yes week it is good to get drunk
grab my feet yeah good great to the
barrel fans yeah hi well three countries
cake stands yeah I know I don't I know I
don't actually want anymore the moment
but I do want to keep a little bit of it
should I just go ahead and do it yeah
mean cheap like I say she she was young
she does not want it she doesn't want to
serve this but she troubled that we're
drinking it no okay okay well we should
I mean I mean I don't you know we should
be drinking it okay it drinks Morgan
wait on check for oh my god another one
how did you call it because all I really
had a 1 in 20 chance of it I want to
feel like angry wind yeah right over
Hampshire right you are intro you use
read don't do that you are in this this
cavern this cave system and you can see
that it extends out in both directions
and at your feet is a gigantic mushroom
that has been broken
oh and you know that you have to put it
back together how is it how many pieces
can i is it yeah absolutely
let me attempt to absolutely there's
about 18 pieces I don't know if I can I
can mend it all at once but I can't
start to put some of the pieces that
look the same you start you start
shifting the pieces back together and
that's when you realize it
two different mushrooms so you partially
built this thing out of the wrong
mushroom okay what is it can I tell the
difference between the two separate them
right he stands immediately back up in
the street and screams mmm and streaky
they walk out can you give us that
screen see how it cuts risk screen yeah
exactly if these are going to be real
high-pitched uh but I can't do it super
I'll try though I get it out in the
street like facing away from the drawing
courtier but you're all people have a
key and wing what just happened I was in
a cave just putting on mushrooms back
together I got two mushrooms by mistake
two classic rookie mushroom mistake few
mushrooms can't do it got it
one mushroom yet all right so seeing you
do a double dip and now have this
experience
Oh self-conscious like yeah like I said
it was really really good I mean we
should just you know like keep drinking
it I guess like we should all drink it
it's so good I like here's I'm just want
to be a part of it no hearings to be
understanding more like you do he's
understanding Wyoming likes it like more
Oh like that he and I have a bond now
you're like she is she drank and she's
like garbage its competitors you'll like
it
okay sure did the thing was supposed to
do to me I'm yeah but not to you like my
pride did mushrooms and he saw yeah they
were it was broken into into pieces I
knew that I had to put it back together
did it did it look like mushrooms I'm
personally familiar well yes would like
the ones we encounter no no as this is
not another my candid okay nothing like
that not a conscious mushrooms straight
up just a lower under dark you just like
point a cabbie you were there Hey well
you're supposed to be a part of this no
you had a sequence of that mushroom
Buster I shouldn't do it
I
I had more time maybe I could have done
it get back but the thing is I drank I
drank two sips yeah and both times it
wasn't a new hallucination each time I
was back in the same place well don't I
mean it sounds like the mushroom needed
mending you sound like the drunken
ramblings of an eyebrow I'm into it I'm
sorry I'm playing right into this into
it not giving you an idea
Rosie beasting yeah um you feel an
incredible heat in your pants
touch this again that's a claw oh my
pants are closed earlier specifically in
your pocket okay you reach in and the
heat is intense but you have kept the
locket Oh from the doone-gate in yeah so
we're pointing you about yeah in that
pocket right um just for safekeeping you
weren't able to do anything yet I know
she's safe with me but exactly but
that's what you can do okay is keeper
close right and we go through the heat
pouring off of this off of the chain off
of the locket itself is incredible okay
I can't touch it with my hand I can
absolutely try if you desk sir yeah I'm
going to try to yeah here here give me a
little conch at contact yeah that's our
eight second date going that great yes
clean show you dude you drop it okay you
drop it it falls and it falls in a
puddle of rainwater that had sort of
pulled it pulled out of the carriage
house and talked about there
he cheated it falls open okay in the
puddle and you can see flames inside the
locket okay ah and this happened just
after he came back from his second trip
yeah yeah okay uh geez um and we said do
we think is the girl in the locket
no right now you see I planned right now
you see flames thank you continue to
watch it or no I'm going to take your
beard and
try to extinguish the flames wet like
that with the beer yeah that you pour
the liquid over it and I mean when it
comes into contact with the locket it's
just by coming into contact with the the
pictures is just flowing off of it the
flames are inside the they're inside the
class exactly right okay so but if
you're watching you be pouring a you see
the liquid run off and then you can see
a perceiving see the the perspective
inside the locket shift so you can you
can see like in a moment that the locket
is pulling up and you can see it leaving
the flames and then you can see it being
pulled up by the chain by the girl who
looks down into the the locket
pleadingly and then she notices that she
can see someone else on the other side
and that's when she begins to come in
the manner of a camera show the room
around her I think you see a small
brazier full of coals you can see that
there are three small windows and the
room itself is circular okay and you can
see in one in one corner of the room you
can see a set of stairs that goes that
that goes down like a depression goes
down around oh so she was put in the
fire to signal us so being yeah so it
look like she pulled the locket out of
the brazier that's what it looks like
from your perspective it looks like she
put it in there and then pulled it out
and then looked in got it
okay um and it doesn't look like she the
circular stares like she's not a
prisoner in here she can go down the
stairs is not a locked door nothing you
don't see you under your notes down
there okay um but like I say this she
begins to show it around the room right
and then you can see the locket moving
closer to the window okay yeah yes yes
yeah and then she sort of holds it up
and then just like from the vision of it
as
pressed it flat against the window
anything you see a coast you see a coast
and you see a city okay what does the
city look like you can see that there is
a like a large river that is sort of
running immediately down the center of
the city going out into the ocean it
looks like okay there's a vast body of
water at the edge of this okay that
rooms to the ocean okay you're
well-traveled I am remember do I
recognize it you might kind of do some
kind of check on you might it's pretty
it's pretty famous it's not going to be
a super it isn't going to be a super
super tough check do you want to do
history yeah we've been doing we've been
using his for its micro tog Rafi and
lucky lucky
woo oh wow he'll love it
that's 13 yes you believe that is the
city of skilled hands Neverwinter okay
so what do I know about the city's build
man stuff um it's it's a storied it's a
storied city okay it's home to
adventurers and adventurer very
incredibly famous sometimes called the
jewel of the north if I'm remembering my
Neverwinter stuff correctly and it was
recently I mean almost destroyed by a
volcanic eruption but in the modern
period a lot of that has been repaired
there's many factions that sort of vie
for control of it okay but that here's
never winner when you would you bet your
life on it is this the city that Rosie
might have been to what I'm not sure
that she has been that far north okay
but knowing someone who would have been
there or one of your children have
almost certainly if you
if you're seeking if you're seeking Fame
and adventure right in the north
ultimately that path is probably going
to take you to the Neverwinter okay and
how far from red larch is it's a ways
it's a ways you'd have to travel north
to let's see you would have to travel
north to Westbridge okay and then you'd
have to travel even farther past West
bridge and the site of Nena's ear of
course is just just south and west of
that but you have to go even farther
north up to tribe or oh we are friends
with tribe or die lost girl mmm
funny how that happens you can also take
a and then from tribe or you travel west
okay until you hit the high road along
the coast head north from there to
Neverwinter where is this in relation to
Scala Scala is even farther north but
north not on the high road on the long
road so it's all north it's all closer
to a northern objective you could
investigate this process and still have
time to go to Scala if that's what you
decided to do okay if somebody wants to
go scholar tell me I mean we have to
because we got the message we do have a
missive to go to Scala true okay well I
am how are these things from my weird
broken to mushrooms that's so far so far
where your mushrooms are super far down
do you like to return your mushrooms we
do that before I don't know it seems for
a second there I said like there was a
burning house only I don't know we're
gonna make it there in time
yeah I see what your house is on fire
whoa okay we're good don't mean we have
any reason to think that these are
related
I am I just going to like enjoy my dream
sequences
solo but yeah here I'm gonna make a bee
well here's what we could do do we
really need to get let us know shadow
council if you want what would could
thrist do bracelets notepads rainbow
kind body pillows here's the thing you
drink it and then our what it is you
would drink it why didn't we if for some
reason I think that this these visions
have meaning we could take a barrel with
us awesome with us yeah keep drinking it
and I just drink it on the roads going
to Day drink the entire trip we use it
you have to restrain me so that I can
explore the Ale realm stranger so he
thinks the few thinks of ale is a place
okay so he's an experienced with was
drinking the hell did you buy NR a drink
hey those times have been weird yeah so
this is the second time or there's a
second drink of this is he exhibiting
like wobbling as he isn't hidden no
though that's the thing is it when he
comes back he's five back okay can i
duck in and ask profiteth real quick 22
a dinner about whether she's experienced
anything like what exactly so profit you
see you find that profit is excited in
there she has found like one chair that
was 30 and on now and she no no she is
excited for some reason it's like and
she is she's polishing this chair I feel
bad we have a chair to me she's a Monica
she just likes gotta clean may I go back
about what I like I've met so well but I
deprived her purpose yes yes but think
about how bad it was before it was a lot
going on now a suppliant there was a lot
going for talking about her ghost baby's
[Music]
baby name if he's good pray take line
yeah exactly
what do we want to do I want to first of
all ask her like hey my warlock friend
here is having some hallucinations when
he drinks this terrible ale are you able
to assemble the mushrooms
Euan yeah he took two sips of it and
appears to be transported mentally to a
plane where there are mushrooms that he
has to realize I think it was the other
dark I think it was I have recognized
places like that before but I didn't
recognize that particular tunnel now my
friend is odd but this is a new one for
even for him so I do trust his word on
them she says I know that the the Zager
Nezzer brewery is close to Nightstone
it's an ancient dwarven brewery that was
out of commission for a while
and it may be that they're still working
some things out where is that brewery
here you know that's all I fucking hate
it oh thank you it's in the it's in the
town of Mexico thanks so much but it's
not being the town nice one but it's
near to it where is it farther south
siren right now okay okay
no that's yeah it's about that doesn't
have the same urgency but this locket
seems to have well you just keep
drinking like Moviefone oh I'm gonna do
that yeah absolutely I'm gonna do that
we got nothing else to do I'm just
watching it right now like scientific
method I'm like don't hold me back
there's a master of the scientific years
in our bliss Ben yeah there's a two
beakers control group hypothesis I'm Pro
mushroom I want to get on the net I'm
gonna tell you them what if we all do it
so I take a drink okay let's all do it
an all roll roll low context on purpose
yeah I say so I'll take a swig good -
good - continues - powerful it is notes
of clay of multi interval notes of clay
and silky hair there's no comment all
right well oh I'll take it
ah go ahead I don't see much other
master does it another step for me
damn that wasn't cool well it yeah
husband my hair going on our Oh oh well
that's how I see nothing boyo so you
look down and you see a partially
assembled mushroom oh I guess one
well yeah me it's modeled in in
different ways you've never seen a
mushroom quite like this I look at May
out idiot and they can I roll a survival
check to see if I know how to put
together a mushroom okay I feel much
sembly check yeah I know yeah yes for
the sim on 7 that the 7 plus 12 okay so
yeah he has put the wrong mushroom part
like obviously the wrong mushroom art
into one of the mushrooms yeah and if
you take you take it out and you just
like just cursing the whole time and you
build it and then each of these
mushrooms is missing one piece
she looks on and it's try to squeeze it
together like a wiggler shake like a
pac-man like this is it yeah it's trying
to get under go in on each other and
then she goes wait what do they look
what color Italy were they look like but
one of them is almost a rainbow a
cascade of rainbow hues that goes down
and the other one is just like a like a
lightly glowing brown and I couldn't
tell those yes a little egg white I
didn't want to tell you guys you guys
see walnut rolling around good I'm
sitting I'm like I'm worried I know it's
going to be okay but I'm like a wet
cloth on your forehead can you you're
trying but it's just like feeling around
it but it's kind of fun you trying to
get to like pinch off the underside like
a part that nobody's going to mess and
like eat it well do it I get wrong with
it wrong
to wake her up you gotta kind of you
place yeah you place it you place it in
your mouth and then you wake up and she
is like rolled herself around the corner
of the building
oh I go those Russians didn't have all
the pieces I know right no you had them
yeah exactly
they were missing you're missing one
piece I'm wondering if somebody hmm who
knows like any any mushrooms because
like maybe like take a piece of there's
just kind of put it in that like a graph
so with plants I don't know if you all
know but it's a resident mushroom expert
that's not how they work and I drank it
and it tasted like hair and piss a shirt
are you sure you don't want to try maybe
another stuff on gets better the second
time I hear no hey one I die I drown it
my whole thing in the barrel when I
drowned
oh I say you can you think I'm so you
you see the two mushrooms that are happy
with him yeah
oh and ER Kathy is here with you but he
is there god no he is and he is six feet
tall uh-huh and standing next to you in
this place he handsome
yeah oh yeah yeah yeah like I got here
beautiful kisses great all night yeah
man advice tonight mustache yeah oh yeah
that's why I remember you yeah I always
pictured you he looks around and he says
this will be our home oh I can't be
quest okay like a high video of that
yeah yeah yeah yeah something really
husbands and wives and the knife factory
but yeah I mean our home me and you he
looks over you and then he sort of like
shutters and as the rain as a door that
come down and you think that that might
be a laugh OH
taming the spores brings puzzle like a
bear and then and as the spores hit the
ground they immediately in the dream
logic of this place immediately become a
nation that fills the entire camera oh
when you come back he is throwing up on
coriander oh oh wait you like you you're
okay
one around comes to I figure better at
it did me acids ahead what like that for
10 minutes ah I'm actually that's not so
the coriander coriander seals up yeah
good move Korean I'm gotten a scene so
oh boy yeah where did you see run after
you just fix um ah I go okay still there
I
yeah me and Kathy are gonna move in
together there now we are raising a
family
hey anything oh it's very weird why did
we get I knew you two had a future like
hell yes very weird keep getting pushed
me the relationship is very popular yes
always cross-species
so Dragonborn indoor yeah what so what
happened you're gonna move in together
in the cave I don't know I think he
proposed a bunch he made a bunch of
babies he was six feet tall okay what
the mustache yeah and then we made a
bunch of babies looking handsome yeah
obviously how I feel always its Dylan I
figure have a serious problem with the
mushrooms can use back it's like there's
not a problem uh turns out there's a lot
of mushrooms you want a mushroom take a
swig and we have your have your pick
every time tonight all the water it
comes back he's like I had a lot of
babies over there but there's a lot yes
gentlemen what's the song you know hero
I went look there was two anywhere like
on their face now there's a shit-ton
you're welcome we would do we solve the
al mission I guess so it's fine write a
letter to omen we just poured the ale
the rest of it into this bag can you
talk to Cathy um wait I even know his
real name was Cathy Cathy one wait a
minute
yes can you actually do it yes what a
stupid thing I said is going to slow
down your whole campaign yeah but but
but I mean I don't think I don't think
fungi are plants that is I need to get
the discrimination flag on that yeah I
think a fungi as a plant if you don't
want me talking to it that's fine
because it's like a you liking it if
it's like a so fortunately how level
three jurors get a stroke I'll speak to
plants which you know I'm gonna do no I
got a little bit ramping and we have a a
bond that is a bond it's a Miss afraid
to split on the campaign because it's a
literally every plant I'm so excited
you in glutamates me this is insane
listen to this crap you imbue plants
plural no because this is the same I'm
sick of the animals like hey what's up
animals right you imbue plants within 30
feet of you with limited sentience and
animation like straight up Disney shit I
don't like it
giving them the ability to communicate
with you and follow your simple commands
you can question plants about events in
the spells area within the past day
gaining information about creatures that
have passed whether another
circumstances the fucking AoE yeah this
house oh you can also turn difficult
terrain caused by plant growth into
ordinary train you said come on plants
I'll freak out it's a while it's like
poison ivy an event meant yeah I like
man yeah yeah secrets little rose great
because I eco-terrorism is base offense
now yeah yeah but that's all you don't
think that maybe maybe not Kathy
specific well Kathy is Kappa key
communicate yeah oh yeah not plant we
have a link but I thought he just sends
you feelings and stuff yeah yeah like
well we spent 60 years in a shadow room
let me go home we chilled I mixed yeah
rabbit so it's kind of a common-law
marriage really yeah exactly yeah that
was after your wine he's taking root in
my brain stuff much like if you remove
him I die if it's Dennis it's true
that's marriage
yeah Abdullah oblong Cappy we get asking
like what you know because he's here
after asking why I want to move in with
you
you happy did you see all this funny
thing upward yeah I can't see anything
I see the rim yes we were together in a
dream oh oh you home
oh he went with you yeah it was just a
dream it was a dream of a real place it
was all a dream it will be our home oh
man when will we find it I'm patient
alright
every lay that time you don't know this
is right I think Kenny he looks up again
yeah that's how apparently we didn't get
married Oh
betrothed though congratulations still
yeah I'm thrilled it's all happy so very
happy how much is he gonna pay us for
this quest Mama's gotta get paid I don't
gotta look I'm in no hurry ting suffice
to split you I get the vibe we're gonna
just stumble across it well that's I
mean we owe them that because we did
they helped us with the route and so
they said you know take one of our kind
to a place where could flourish clearly
had a vision of that place got it
yeah and they got happy with a quest I
thought it was just an art bad yeah
no Kathy's the embodiment of a question
one day hot to say goodbye to hear
another yeah I got a friend yeah we're
gonna move in together experts on sprout
muscles and then you kinda head drink
that ale the end yeah any chat al until
I can run out of that tunnel and get to
an open space where I can recognize some
of these stalactites chug
yeah yeah you know what's been going you
just like finish the thing and will that
grant am more time in there because we
can do it we can add you mean keep
pouring Joe this is a party yeah use my
crater me you want to create a party
atmosphere now I have taste in you want
to get it right absorbed in the
bloodstream faster why don't you do it
he's right right listen bring me here I
want to funnel a funnel some topical
only I'm doing that keep coming it this
is not by checking because he doesn't
know what it is Justin I could talk him
into it yeah I could should I try that
way you can you got your inspiration
listen I don't know that he wouldn't I
don't mind a role play it as well it can
happen I get a ruling on Chuggington
pressing the industry
yes my child
yeah he would know that's my point you
know what I have to ask it all I know is
it if I ingested the way that we've been
doing it that's the way it's going to
work it's not I'm not trying to get the
alcohol I'm trying to get that little
all right yeah I need that moss you need
to write in the Boyd I'm back
this is comeback everything about this
nothing more again we're going to well
you can get on your face
Wow Wow hey in any way did you say that
you're wasting all of them the best
rolls on this yeah well you know what
it's a taste of the problem I love : I
was another armed shag you bypass the
tongue entirely I love that this is the
check one time Chris and her all whoa
now the answer roll oh hey Carol in it
you don't understand
I'd never is like a like a prequels
thing like you were supposed to be
balance to the force
it was never that I roll low I roll
morally right in whatever context my
name's oh yeah that's true we could take
some you could take from winning well
you say let's take a look me like all
the things that I was last i fashioned
the Lizard King into a wineskin he
tricked out yeah yeah no I have a flask
and I will bring Ukraine bring along to
experiment like where wherever we may
travel nice just as we'd yeah just one a
little nail board yeah keep working on
it now two guys in the other dark though
like I think so the SEC is crystal ball
that's where the your account ian is
kind of accrued yeah
at least this seems like I could succeed
what is that drinking yeah exactly and
then don't forget I mean there's you
know along with that you know Arkana
there's a lot of you know bubbling
things there's a lot of you know
prescience yeah you know that you can
apply you need to understand yeah
exactly exactly yeah yeah absolutely so
what is the what is the plant-eating
this is what I'm saying is like is this
our priority or do we want to take a
long road trip and why not a long trip
yeah I mean we we have to go north
because you've been called
anyway well we do have time to maybe
investigate Neverwinter first you do so
we can stop by absolute the city of
skilled hands first on our way to Scala
yes I may be stopped up in a tribe or
I'm stair front oh yeah I see gorilla
I'll just go to number one and come back
well we just need to check listen I'm
gonna tell you this we go all the way to
Scala you want to stay in the cart a
little scared dragon right stay in the
muck scare it rolled down the window
we'll put on your favorite music oh yeah
here you want to crack the windows you
do not want to leave a dragon in a cart
No crank it up heat on out take care of
my frost yeah you can stay inside you
but I'm well we're going to go and you
can do whatever you want well let's
ghost go to never wonder so great we'll
tell her you were too scared to talk to
her live but I'm saying it like in a
like in a comforting way like will tell
her that you couldn't do it that you
couldn't bring yourself to speak to her
you know look you were too afraid and
chills I mean she can't make you come in
there so then it'll be fine we saw you
don't have to talk to work she can't
make you come in there catchy
no no no no I don't think so well just a
major to do what I don't want to do
right she'll just think that you're
coward and then but you'll but you want
us to deal with her and that sounds like
a good move I like I like that plan I
like this mine along that's great we're
in the winner's arms fold in here before
we go down every winner got your divorce
oh yes you well if you do please their
goal act 5 to shoot any gold ah like a
mama bird I said n Weiss what because we
actually only said it one wizarding cars
medallion we actually have three more oh
my that's true you guys want to see to
excite I don't care about my medallion
yes yeah one medallion
it is acceptable theme yeah okay I'm
turning a feature medallion oh yeah oh
yeah oh yeah she look she liked it last
time that's true yeah oh yeah I mean
it's very again it was a chewy sweet
tart I straight through the middle when
I was
like to go in and let home and let
process know that this is our plan we're
heading to Neverwinter ask her about the
displacer beasts were those on the North
Road yeah yeah they're on the North Road
okay cool
there and there - well you what you had
seen them before you would see what
seemed to be like a hunting mother
teaching her pups yeah I remember that
on the way up to West bridge of the
floor I did some dark things yeah there
it was an earlier time in the campaign
no one is holding you accountable for
those stars compute again yeah oh but
absolutely she says she says how was
last stone today oh it was amazing I
tell her about min song yeah I tell her
about the monster the flesh mouth thing
that we killed in the cave after they
beat Reed a cake I tell her about a
gorilla from tribe or oh yes mission
relative the face softened she told me
yeah she helped out a lot she's down
every year but in Seoul I I think you
can look forward to an extraordinarily
favorable review this don't stay paper
nuclear water I don't know if I want
that many people threw water deep coming
up here ah crap well if you just raise
your prices yeah I'll find something to
do with some money I guess yeah welcome
discount yes don't go yeah here we are
anyway any advice for us before we set
out on this road trip um let's see so
you you issue you have already wheeled
out the beer it's gone it's out there
right she's just like lock up the
carriage house you bet should we tell
her about the ghost babies no no no no
and I grabbed some potion from the
trophy before we left absolutely I to be
made very clear exactly so you you've
poured it into you can get two flasks
out of it I got two classic butter and
we have a speed upgrade on our cart now
you you and maybe you indeed that mean
for us it just it means that you can
travel you know much farther in a day
than is ordinary then we have in the
past
Helen you can get much farther far in
one day
you know no not like that the car still
has to maintain physical shape I guess
it's gone like the next 53 seconds yeah
yeah no no we won't have that kind of
time to look up we want you exactly what
and go and lock up yep I will make note
of the two potions that you have and you
can find out what they do when you drink
okay
yeah it's going to be a real hoot
everybody's going to have a good time oh
it's going to turn them out that was the
dogs foreshadowing cuckoo yes a potion
of owl becoming you are now it's all
really know for a generator also yes
throw your grater else ready Basinger
yeah that's our game for today yeah I
don't
hey it's been our absolute pleasure
shadow council to entertain you low
these several hours we are going to go
for a potty break as they say enjoy the
festivities and we will grab shortly for
some tabletop company where
you