time is the enemy the pastor threatens
the fastest weapon you wouldn't make it
past a second and answer the question
play a brash and reckless to choose a
cautious solution you saw was prudent in
any soccer poker to don't become the
putrid it's that well-fed I pursue in no
mountain too steep for dungeon too deep
to send expanded remarks up to the top
of the peak of beneath they see Yugi
they come like sharks to it while I swim
in that money burn like Carl Barks
through it so send your National Parks
drew it I'll send him home in a natural
box with the clothes tie the most of the
parts included save your breath for a
cleric confessor there's a lesson that
life is a tenured professor but if
you're seeking my official advice sign
on the dotted line and wish you the
choice hello I am Tycho Brahe Hey oh I
am I continue to be Tycho Brahe hey of
Penny Arcade in packs I'm also a mini
ffice era ward run CEO of acquisitions
incorporated and apparently the villain
of this campaign mister but today I am
Jerry Hogan's and I'm here to play a
Dungeons &amp; Dragons game thingamajig type
thing with my friends to my right
dragon narcissist in our blitz and to
the right of my right there I've been
repping the natural world
walnut on grass red chicken yeah
actually that was great you do a good
chicken oh yeah or a turkey
me next yeah yeah yeah to my left not
your grandma's grandma Rosa feasting you
[Music]
sure I know like I did this
yeah oh yeah Kendall making this is the
time-honoured standing the butter yes
its internationally recognized there all
the gifts and then emerging as though
from a mist shroud it's good first route
that's right it's cold now when last we
saw our heroes they were only a single
day into operating be drawn and quarter
on a mission from prophetess drawn
herself she had gone south with Rosie's
daughter share and you know to catch a
Late Show now she had polished all of
her armor and she was preparing to catch
a show of Audra courtier of the drownin
courtier now you ma'am you may recall
that you were party to a strange affair
the next morning as you awoke you heard
the singing in the streets you saw roben
figures sort of spilling through the
streets you saw children with bird cages
with or without Canaries and all
throughout this low humming song by
everyone the gathered throng which you
followed the trickles of these
tributaries over to the quarry in the
northeast of red larch and it was there
that you saw a lump something lumpy
beneath a dark oiled cloth the cloth was
removed uh it was cake it was just a fun
cake
lumpy cake yeah it was just a fun cake
that children attacked mercilessly and
then grabbed handfuls of and then threw
it specifically the children through it
as offerings into the mouth of the mine
that is in the
and each time they did so they would say
a name alongside it and one of your own
number specifically not your grandma's
grandma Rosie beasting her approach the
ritual in novel way instead of reciting
the name of a person who had died or a
person from the mine now hold on
she didn't have that information
ignorant of the law is no excuse
yeah and possession is 9/10 yes that's
true off that position of 9/10 of the
law is no excuse yep that's what they
say that's my grandma that's what Rosie
in school anyway
forestall this sort of a future for you
where five adults try to remember one
phrase poorly so in the indeed indeed no
there's no there's no way that Rosie
could have known that at all looked like
fun and she tries anything once
exactly no and again I supported with
her a percentage shot did maybe doom us
all to death by throwing cake in a hole
yeah that's classic yeah that whole cake
fable okay the cake hole is a piece
that's right since now quid pro quo now
tell me what happens in the moments
after after the child yes child has
revealed something about the ritual you
did not know okay I recover immediately
tastefully moment of surprised but it is
not visible on my face and I say oh they
haven't died yet got a run back in again
I've been wondering how she would
respond to that all week
exactly right but sweetheart we all die
someday
Rosie gets very dark yeah sure you're
back by the cart and you can hear this
as a relatively private conversation
being between two small people you have
twenty feet in front of you but you have
a pointy trout ear you can probably
catch something of it I just I just
wander up and I go oh yes thank you
and you really will you are the only
adult people very very excuse me I'm
right here from the visible in the
visible spectrum you are the tallest
least childlike person in this in this
throng see you're sweeping up in the
middle of the day cloak of stars sort of
draping around just like dragging itself
over children yeah do you if your son
that I have probably is it morning yeah
I definitely do then yeah cut quite a
figure yeah quite understand the terms
of this ritual but I died we jauntily
grab a piece of cake I just say those
lesser gods what works you must look
like like a witch on her way to Easter
brush yes so when you as you hurl this
sort of you know hardball sized chunk of
compressed cake you throw it into the
mouth of the cavern and it does not land
as it should huh it does not land in
this pile of cake it does not strike the
ground and remain it appears to fall
directly into something that's something
that's visible or not that at that
moment no mm-hmm
you can see up and around a fleshy spire
this is an image for your use yeah no I
know where you're going with this
already spire yeah I play this game
yeah erupt
we have round the morsel and then
additional spires branch off from it hmm
and begin to roll in what is essentially
a sphere made out of teeth and mouths
rolling not unlike a dark Katamari
harvesting cake be sure to read dark
Katamari oh hey hey harvesting cake and
terrifying children did you make that up
here I didn't mean to yeah oh with a kid
like that supposed to happen that
happened every time the child is been
looking at you and looks over and then
immediately screams and runs back okay
that's unusual so that starts hmm in the
same way that one can begin a howl yeah
that starts saying that starts just a
shredding wake of piercing child screams
that retreat back and then are converted
as though by some kind of currency
exchange into adult screams and so
immediately there's just like a picture
like a blast wave has gone off at the
mouth of it and in the crowd that was
moments ago engaged in revelry and has
without incident for a very long time
has sort of peeled out and are now sort
of watching the the mouth of the cavern
mm-hmm so they're but they're they've
taken it step back their essence they
have decided for whatever reason that
carnivorous sides of beef are not in
their interest or experience no they
have decided that the creature
rolling out now due to some hood who can
say its origin oh I can but it's fine I
can't play I don't need to know yeah
it's collecting itself and rolling out
of the cavern when Lee I see y'all gonna
do something about that
and I look at dinar are you eating the
cake I say loudly loud enough to
hopefully so they hear me it's like you
throw enough cake in a hold this is what
happens to you every time don't let that
thing out yeah
oh jeez yeah I want to know how big is
it it's not a size of bite of cake
initiative is great and we're gonna roll
it all right it's been a minute Wow
excuse me that's jacked he goes first
that's a premium hope that's
experiencing right now what do you have
dinar butts in Oh actually I don't get
to go first
16 okay 16 how about you walnut ten okay
leisurely day I like that holiday right
now how about you Rosie
I got a 15 that's very good how about
you Chris no I'd love to tell you about
my 19 wow it's like inquire within
yeah you know Jesus long days and
Pleasant nights all right he who dealt
it well now him smelled a yeah sure with
us melting Eric
your Miller just yeah wait okay yeah so
as it wait as it is continuing to sort
of roll its way out any time it sees
something near it that it thinks might
be good but it is casting out on a suit
of POD another craw
we're sun lashing out yeah yeah
snore fill up any delicious flavors that
might be out there such as cake we got
tons of it rocks dirty cake and eat some
rocks there's a shoe no doubt left by a
terrified child it is no it is no longer
available it's up over the lip of the
quarry already oh yeah oh yeah it's it's
about an out of this mine entrance out
into this flat area where as a ritual
historically has taken place
it's a herbivore so okay then what's far
as I know yeah well tell this cake
everybody I take my action to ask them a
cake yeah I'll do right now before we
forget it go taste nickman is that is
that Jack it's us when he doesn't get
any pluses so sixteen for young don't
forget me I go here so he'll go after
dinner
it's a I want to position this this cake
this is all we know about it
let's go out with my faux sigh because
as we your call I've got my old my old
favorite the earth yeah yeah and then I
got the clatter it's classic classic
yeah
and then I got this then you've newer
yeah which it's fine
yeah it's just got more sugar but I I
have it I might I might getting any
sense of him I immediately like slap
leather yeah yeah I'm like I'm gonna out
draw this thing yeah he's gonna feel the
vibration see whether or not these these
these people sire they they are they
aren't responding to they aren't
responding to this entity okay at all
um but they are always responding to
each other
Oh
so I place them in obviously yeah it's
almost like my body's it's like so it's
like it's like motion at a distance one
on your foot one right head it's like
it's like it's like you can move one you
can move one in one pouch and the other
will respond like they their behavior is
as odd
it's a star-crossed romance but between
dem I sin Chi and rocks yeah hmm there's
something there hot yeah is this gonna
say I don't know what that's called
if you don't know is there anybody that
likes to fuck rocks well I agree I'm
just saying like have you heard about
these rock fuckers and what Apple
gushers I'll get back to you oh I bet
people do like Goines oh look at that
shoes you not gonna break actually now
that you bring up golems oh yeah that's
stable my boys got cake peas just be
clear just to be clear yeah I want to
make sure that this is not just some
generic tentacled mouth beast and what
do I identify this as the like that it
looks like the the mouth gods soup
Arcana is it perfectly what about my own
vial that is guilt
I'll do it let's do our can your eyes
well I don't agree good it's not my RKO
yeah it's those 13 yeah yeah it seems
like it there's definitely an
amalgamation it doesn't seem like a
single creature oh okay yeah it's like
let's imagine a situation where you went
to like a grocery store evil grocery
store and I realize now that this is the
sort of thing you were bothering me
about before it yeah I want to just
apologize ahead of time no imagine that
you were at an evil grocery store with
your mom mmm and you said hey I want to
get two types of gelatinous organism
imagine that you would put them both
into sort of the same jello mold yeah
and you create a sort of dark slurry and
intermingled that's right mass mm-hmm
well I don't like it
yucky
it's bad does it seem to be interested
in the cake at all it seems to be
interested in eating absolutely anything
you can put into its mouth
all right well Kimmy's not your friend
let's not let that happen
yeah maybe with enough cake didn't
Lovecraft write something about that
yeah with strange Aeons yeah okay maybe
even cake may die yeah let's just go to
work instead mm-hmm I'm gonna text this
boy what's he got it's been so long
since we've rolled yeah I know what is
always do I don't even know I just don't
know what do even warlocks yeah let me
hit it
let me do it what are you good no it
just is he's hexed being in a restaurant
and you're like girl you want nothing
what are you going boy wait what do you
think it all looks so bad it's the
opposite so tell us about because it has
been a quite a while
Mithras trout tell us about your hacks
let's discuss this hex bring an hexagon
no let's talk about hex baby oh I get
that good and the thing over there yeah
magazine yeah I'm happy
actually it wasn't great thanks me you
know what now you know you're you're the
best you know in Michigan I'm thinking
about what I said oh so I'm sure what
you said was great I didn't hear it I
wish you all to know that it requires a
petrified eye of a newt which I do have
at all times
right yeah you know I think I don't I'm
like Triax oh it worked I do have it I
do you have a Petra diet you have a
petrified eye of Newt like stuck in your
molar yeah here's like hard right no
it's fine all right
he's gonna enjoy an extra 1d6 necrotic
damage when I hit him
that's right and then he's also gonna
take a disadvantage on an ability check
let's see what's a good one your toes
yeah what's that combo you won't look at
that's my thanks right yeah certainly
but like it's no it's the wisdom that
the wisdom is that I don't think it's
got a lot of charisma boys yeah
depends a it's very low I mean I'm not
I'm not gonna insulted my God he's like
I can't reveal all of the mysteries
behind the screens I hear the charisma
liquid a mousehole check you know house
whole decks check okay
remove that disadvantage gotcha I need a
little bit of insight on as far as what
we're dealing with here because I want
to know about how moist he is thoroughly
know I need to know if it can hear
because I want to do either a dissonant
whisper yeah I can hear yes I'd like to
hear yeah yeah it's got it's got one
here somewhere on there some membrane
that will vibrate you know exactly mice
my suspicion if we middle game for moon
don't do it they get so mad they're mad
in the youtube comments or are they mad
at you don't get YouTube man but what is
it
Mitaka yeah what it with ears ears just
do it oh I bet the whole thing is like a
drum
oh yeah that's why I'm very curious yeah
shadow Morgana for sure disgusting I
would do shatter except I don't want to
explode it all over the kid their teeth
are gone now they are not here they are
not this thing I've done a bunch of tiny
ones we're doing dissonant whispers Doha
round I don't fret
all right you're gonna do a it's a
wisdom saving throw give it a try y'all
gotta beat my 14 mm-hmm yes there's
anything else don't you don't beat it do
not well I love makes a valiant effort
so what happens good try on its part
you're gonna take three d6
that's a hold on your psyche any image
that's so many and we got here that's a
- that's a - boy get out yeah for the
heat
it's my share lots are just fine just
don't roll like restaurant like a
three-stroke but there's no way that's
statistics I want to know what the
content of these
dissonant whispers Oh would you like
would you like to know it's vital
community let's let you adjudicate okay
dude break me off a piece of that cthe
risk at bar
hey then what I'm about to say is your
reward
well I I I put my boot
on the edge of the wagon yeah and I say
I whisper to it in that in that
unnerving way you like cake go get and
he must use his action to escape this
zone are you sending him into the into
the liquori so you kicked the cake wagon
right into him yeah enjoy I was gonna do
that I don't know if I can one entity I
don't know if I have the strength to
that but it may be sufficiently greased
yeah
but part of all that is just the two
wheels a couple Stoppers I mean it's
just like you maybe I don't kick in a
satellite yeah yeah to two or three feet
it sounds cool as long as the camera
doesn't track yeah exactly a little
apart movie um but this this creature it
has no choice because it failed its
wisdom save but to slurp in a moist
fashion and forget my democratic far
away nice three so take that no it's
dead so as these necrotic
whispers just wash over it you can just
see it sort of vibrating against some
like like incomprehensible internal
frame and then it starts it starts to
roll and slurp
it sort of thins itself out on the
ground and like a like a devious fruit
roll-up it just sort of skims along the
ground can you buy devious well yeah
exactly that's that's that's where you'd
go then for your dark lunch so it's
basically like it's is trying to it's
just trying to sort of like bulldoze as
much of these snacks as it can okay
for before it's cast out but you can
tell like there's different parts of it
and they don't want to leave oh sorry
they keep they keep trying to shape
themselves like a like a trike a combine
harvester like one of the big tractors
like keep trying to shape itself into
things that will keep it yes you can see
in this structure you can see these sort
of euphemistic fingers right trying to
pull but whatever whatever is in front
of it is pulling it out I like your your
tank that kissing is like oh sorry but
like is it a real so it sounds like it
first I'm like sorry did that hurt
I'm very sorry like it's clear I'm
actually trying to be heard you may be
very interesting another circumstance
may prophesy yes so it is it has when it
gets to the mouth of the cave you can
see this sort of like slides up around
the hewn portions of the rock and just
continues to sort of like a like a manta
ray almost yeah just sort of sail and
sail smoothly down the well the left
wall so it's retreating it is it has to
right now yes
don't leave any survivors Denar do you
think it would eat a weapon if I hit it
with nothing it's eaten everything else
that's so great you're like looking over
the mouth I'm already like mouth sore
get that thing with a sword is it just
gonna eat my sword was it leaving like
lichen and stuff oh yeah yes oh yeah
yeah it's it's it's like imagine if you
enter in the evil pits door I'm sorry I
made you aware of it it's the best part
of show everything with the things
that's not you yeah corporeal some sort
of beam weapon yeah
what's your hat well you got I give him
a little I'm gonna give him a little
push in the direction he's going i say
hey mad balls you make me sick I know
hey
can I give you a pat on the back if you
have to grab my push it yeah just right
in the mouth very nice just plant your
feet does that do
oh so much damage so in the back smells
horrible like you know you can't smell
his breath is playing at dinara and
light but like calling to all the
peoples around way it's gonna be okay
it's fine now I think he ate the cake
though it doesn't do much all right fill
this DC 12 Cory yeah waiting for you
this is for you okay no it would it
would like this I do to d6 to him but
I'm also trying to get a little push
with the acid just a goose oh yeah so we
get a little more space now this thing's
gonna do yeah
that's a six hey alright that's the big
around there and a four hey this is
pretty solid that's the second faster on
yeah yeah so you you you direct and I
get sawdust out sorry anyway you direct
a high psi jet of dimly remembered
teenaged angst toward this creature it
immediately flows over it it's like
trying to travel around on the top of
the roof two flops down you can see acid
entering one mouth and leaving another
mouth and it's continuing to sort of
like just like a like an old leather
glove to sort of slurp itself down that
oh is it like baby bird in your vomit
into and out of itself
press my aunt's mom now yeah change my
mind I say none of you hurt my baby
drink of my insides it is mine
continually like so it is now ligarius
turn right oh yeah what can he that was
gonna say are you gonna send him into
this I might lose him in there into this
hole no can't you give him to someone to
give it one who's Annette who's up next
Rosie it's gonna be Rosie Yeah right
what do I get plus one to know this I'd
need to understand better you're talking
about a offers help oh yeah you're
talking you're talking about the ability
of of a familiar yeah familiar in the
classic right since like what what they
can actually do for other people is
fairly limited but it's okay with the
knife ligarius bugatti is not a typical
familiar oh I see yeah so you can
usually won the whole status on the rep
she becomes a vessel for Lagasse's right
no no you should you should tell me what
Locati what you want ligado you want to
do did want and I can and I can handle
it alright and I'll just I'll just I'll
I'll make sure that he does that he
comports himself with the maximum
professionalism I think that the knife
changes the dynamic significantly it
does the from Lagarde ease point of view
he's very proud of this blade oh he's a
mastery yes ownership does he know that
it was a gift from me I think so
I think he's doing where yeah that you
were the one who enabled this to happen
exactly there's yeah but you paid for
school yeah yes okay
so because it sees this thing it again
wants to assert
further dominance no is it's finding
something else right it's saying like
you think Europe as much of a temple as
me
good joke exactly exactly you got a up
your tentacle game in it is that the
secure where's your neck how we talk to
them oh my god they're wood pitches Joe
80 pitches it's a sweet so dinar you you
you're studying yourself against the
edge of this this wiping openings here
yeah exactly just like giving yourself a
moment to heat giving yourself a moment
to heal yeah and then you see a short
rest yeah get some wine I love it yeah
you see you see you see Locati just
shoot straight into the thing and so the
way that the camera should look is that
he is supporting himself over here yeah
but then there is a shot a low shot that
looks up from behind Locati and he has
raised his he has raised his knife high
right against the dark mouth but it is a
mouth that contains mouths oh because
these other creatures miss are in here
yeah it's it's it's one percent success
it's a demon stream you know anyway I'm
so proud about my boy and he he he he
scuttles in and then scuttles right over
the top of its flat surface Wow and then
just unzips it with the you want e knife
that you discovered in a tomb and
chilled but as he slides it as he
basically just slides it through just
fill
lays this thing it unfolds and opens up
and it's exactly the same as the outside
mouth all of the people imagine that
this body in evil Church with an evil
steeple open the door exactly and then
within even having a dark lunch no no no
no but that's but that that's how it be
in the newsletter for that week you come
in again as a dark for just kneeling
this week the dark choirs having a dark
lunch on Saturday there is a dark yard
sale next weekend so he is basically
slip this thing open it just it just
holds itself back holds open it yes all
mouths on the other side as well there's
no net mouth there's no increase or
decrease if a guy could he'd go on the
sitcom yeah exactly
oh boy everybody knows how to respond to
it but Rosie be stinger are you going to
tolerate this type of bullshit from this
floppy mouths studded Manta from the
deep no reason with it you know what
actually okay give me a sitrep what am I
looking at where's the cake exactly how
does the how does the Mantis mr. Stroud
was able to move the cake cart two
perhaps three feet okay not far enough
he didn't get the dramatic sort of
scenario that he craved okay and even
the cart has managed to become
disappointed by this I've backed away
after I kicked it to make it look like
it had traveled further
nice dinar is supporting himself along
the side of the hole as is so often the
case and ligardi bravely Gotti sweet
look at this sweet lagari has noodled
himself into a true noodle himself into
a true martial context slashing at this
creature yeah has my current respect so
how much how much how much space between
the cart and the Manta mouth right now
so all the way the cake boss yeah the
best so it it would be about thirty feet
okay from the end here of the cart in um
to reach its way inside there that's
wonderful because that my movements P
happens to be 35 feet so here's what I
would like to do i I I don't think any
less of could dress for having not
pushed it because of June he I have
judges never I have never seen this man
do leg day and so it doesn't actually
surprise me at all
so um I push the cart and I get a
running start and as soon as it gets
momentum to the point where it can move
by itself I vault on top of the cake and
I stand there and I ride it into the
mouth of the cake boss and that's my fun
within a little feet are Paraplanner it
in the well knowing grass please parse
this situation I'm doing mental math
about what happens and equity and
there she goes so upon seeing this I do
think that it's possible that maybe
Rosie is gonna get blundered and I'm a
little concerned about that we have no
proof that is carnivorous yeah just like
the cake don't need dua riding on a cake
don't need proof um hi with some low
intelligence that can cause remember
that and my speed is 40 feet causa right
so yeah okay so I summon a bunch of dogs
and I just send them right in there just
very important there with cold they
sneeze as they enter the camera that's
gonna help oh wait I know how I can help
you good get rid of those what's your
area animals
what's your good stat what's your stat
you me yeah Dex you Dex
you son of a dad it's me okay sweet
walnut runs catches up to the cart and
alongside alongside high-fives me and
bestows upon you enhance ability so you
have that's grace you have advantage on
dexterity check lender you don't take
any damage from falling 20 feet or less
also so this somehow
transy somewhere how long do I get
advantage uh one hour nice
so hopefully and then will not just kind
of Lopes around back
I never been into this oh you're on the
other side of the of the mouth you have
this mine and nerves are it isn't oh
yeah
well I did ten damage
I can't wall I can't even I can't look
at him look if I see it I smell it
exactly everywhere reeking pure yeah oh
yeah you got it you feel it on your skin
like it's heavy in the air like it hits
all five senses mommy
obviously oh yeah it hits that back part
of the tunneling I'm gonna I stuffed my
nostrils with cake so I don't have to
smell it it's the fifth taste so you but
as your as your cart enters this cavern
just this heavy this humid reek just
assaults you stuff the cake in and then
as you're rolling in the wheel of the
cart catch us catch us some edge in the
wall and a tips you're asleep Punky
Brewster yeah yeah it's just like punky
Brewster's but like an evil no yeah have
you ever seen evil punky brewster
exactly ever seen family ties but evil
so if I can get a Decker Decker Braddock
I'll do it Dex but you can add your
advantage okay I got advantage and no
damage falling I got a 13 yes that'd be
fine okay you're not able to do the type
of incredible role that you might have
like your dress
yeah yeah as you but that as the wheels
caught and you so you you roll forward
and then as you as you bring yourself up
this thing is also bringing itself up
here in the darkness of the cavern oh
man oh man okay let's see how this goes
oh Jesus okay what that is hey Jeff we
just rolled a natural 20 yeah absolutely
you know what you all we should do that
we should come up with something special
they get when I roll it they'd forget
for now before now we'll do the classic
David character gets to stay exactly in
this story incredible item so oh my
goodness
that's so much okay I'm so much healing
it's so much good cake might vomit
covered hands like why did you barf in
your own hand
Jerry are you mad it's 32 how deep did
that go with that negative negative five
negatives I can do nothing okay
I'm not anymore oh man okay so it's
carnivorous y'all so apparently the
mouth blender well can do a lot of
damage oh good yeah yeah so you you you
stand basically at its foot or pseudopod
or whatever it calls that moist
you know mouth ridden plump that the
rest of it is supported by and it
basically just falls on you like a
curtain have you ever seen Creepshow -
yes now imagine evil there at the rafter
Ari yes it is basically as I suggested
it is like flopped down on you entire
okay and it is basically it is entombed
you inside of itself and I have I have
no recourse
I am
it's true and this may be my to enjoy
them that well now we can really nailing
with the sword I'm just gonna yeah
it's changed a lot about my Texas we're
all having fun it was a nice holiday
yeah we're out in the Sun giggling yeah
in case and they get thrist
what are you gonna do in your turn oh I
thought that this thing could have been
my friend and you guys are like oh and
she hacked some minute a comes to
talking to him and I don't know it's our
fault oh yeah yeah exactly
oh my gosh you guys said to hexamer you
guys told me to do it I tried to adopt
it the townspeople on it
you heard him he said I was supposed to
do thank me I okay yeah I saw holy shit
no that's dragon speaking yeah exactly
Sokka therus yes you see Kiwi be stinger
with a shout is running toward the mouth
of the cave arrow drawn ready to attack
this creature my faithful son your
faithful son thank God I have so many
children to save me from shit like it's
always so what's the what's the stairs
he's gonna take my initiative away from
me no no no he's he's he is preparing to
he's me he's presenting interact but he
was trying to figure out what the what
the math is on this new combat scenario
up now was a great question hmm there's
I have no other option but to do
something arranged and you know what I'm
gonna do something I was told not to do
first in for a penny in for a pound
let's say it would be a bad boy I'll be
a bad boy I had I had it I had a friend
I had an argument you know they're an
elder Brian who told me not to use the
powers of my cloak
my close-up stars it's true but I
realized the only person who would talk
me out of it is inside of that mouth
I feel no pull for my necklace that she
could use to choke me and stop that from
being issued nice sweet release 100
phone Oh freedom yes I'm gonna do I'm
gonna do the magic missile mm-hmm
component of my cloak and it's an auto
hit it's a 3d 4 and a 3 for an hour old
for you to them thanks cars that come
off how many are you doing oh I'm gonna
throw all three at it that's all you
have left right huh
you have three left oh no you get four
know this I got six a day okay yeah I
don't know if I want to use that money
but maybe that's a d6 my friend yeah
that's right there good thing you live
without one you're the eggs if you want
is a one on a d4 is number on there
three two there's your one so there's so
there's eight and don't forget about a
little necrotic from you to me
that's ten yeah gentle gentle yeah okay
denial it's end this situation has gone
yeah awry so she's all wrapped up she is
absolutely wrapped up and I don't want
to smash no and you don't see any like
you don't see any like effort inside
this shape like you see any resistance
no I don't want to go divine smiting
this thing and just whacking right
through so you you whispered to it and
it understood it you know I could
command it yes bit it out theoretically
right whew
does it understand doesn't understanding
language far first I bought just testin
here okay it's a discordant melody yeah
it's a sound it right transcends
speaking so it doesn't understand yeah
yeah yeah I asked him that just because
I think it's funny
this is yeah this is a sound that
affects the mind of the thing so if it
hasn't if it has a mind it can
understand language right no rules
like maybe I questioned for jer-bear
over here yeah yeah but you'd you don't
remember that there was never a part in
your paladin training where you told wet
mouth piles what to do I say hey mouth
pile great do we have events amount I
look up ya know what does it reactor I
mean it has to know this is what this is
me this is what a stomach must look like
but letting you just see it just dark
twisting all I'm good at is smashing
[Music]
very small like you could just hit a
part that's not containing me that's
true that is true once you get toward
the edges yeah I wouldn't carve
somewhere okay all right what's that
dear one uh I got a couple different
smites wait think it's my dog I got a
little I got a barbecues my creamed
onions my ranch
yeah Cool Ranch might just Cool Ranch
[Laughter]
it's just this gout it's like 40 gallons
of ranch
all right stream laden are in its column
we're gonna go for the gusto maybe not
actually know her if you could entitle
mouths no well now if you can't
understand command I'm not getting
pedaling no I was going to weapon master
but that's a risk that's a straight die
roll commuter chronic entitlement to
stabilize a dying party members yeah is
really interesting
that's acting a bit yellow through the
membrane and get up real close fern that
gives your chronic entitlement the
little roof that it's needed
yeah I think that's a really interesting
interpretation of it it's me something
or palette what's the don't die on me
thing right and oh well we'll cross that
river to beyond is this the River Styx
yeah yeah yeah is that a feeling if I
know which metaphor are we using Isle uh
no I'm just gonna oh my go what yeah yes
a swing anybody you're being be careful
with this yes being very careful so I
won't go great weapon master and I'll
keep my plus 5 on my roll okay
and I would be modifying your roll
slicey mm-hmm big money so I know that's
that's that's good yeah how much did you
get 19 19 so 24 dad is in credit but
drop me some damage please well I'm also
gonna smite the shit out of that on top
of it and give a little ping-pong need
my uh thunder probably don't undo
although you're dead BBQ BBQ stay well
wrathful right yeah we'll just sear the
outside ball you wrathful you know well
raffles right so all right well wrathful
I'll tack that on at the end so
everybody think about what should say in
my eulogy yeah I thought about it every
single dish you can throw in cake with
our name on it
yes yeah we don't really know who's
responsible make heads or tails of this
is a different kind of thing I did just
my normal t-shirt
oh there it is great sword to these six
plus three Chipotle smite four four
eight nine ten eleven and then OH wrath
will smite 1d6 psychic damage of the
targets a creature in one week so wisdom
Sammy throw or be frightened
yes scared away yeah wisdom chicken
what's your spell II see
14:30 you see 13 badass peyote st spell
dcs 13 okay 1 2 6 psychics oh no this is
this is very very good and is it scared
shitless
yeah it's scared it's scared to death is
it so scared that it does that ya know
yeah it's it's it's scared to death
basically well no no it's like it's if a
situation where like we know when I was
at Walmart no no fucking you know what
aisle 12
we are going to the goddamn universe for
you
Rosie be stinger you know what I mean
I'm Danny we imagine an evil Cusco no
Galan cran-grape evil cream grape juice
you basically it's like it's like a it's
like a fancy-pants wedding where you
like cut the cork off of a bottle of
champagne with the sword called savoring
yeah yeah all right really
yeah nice house man I'm gonna savor the
flavor thank you
so you bet you basically you're able to
you're able to gauge just from the the
size and like where you see lumps inside
here basically you cap you ceiling in
Rosie's freshness and you crack the seal
right off the top of your feet and then
and then as the as a blade as the blade
finishes its path through the extra
divine energy in the strike it shudders
and then sort of like peels its way off
and just forms a few small puddles
around a collapsed Rosie be stinger so
it is expired
it has expired its freshness date like
an evil omelet but my freshness date has
yet to pass
hope so it's actually Rosie's it is
actually well first its legaud Eastern
is there any guys there any are there
any like God is indeed like to thank you
minute step can you like go down my
throat and like revive my heart yeah
probably I don't know if I tell you
about it but maybe yeah probably that's
later
how would lagari handle this this is the
person who gave him dick dick this is
nice gift of dominance that lets him be
the best tentacle there ever was see how
she's lying there what's the what's the
condition like what can I perceive or
what look I be able to proceed maybe not
like what led to this death to this
unconsciousness worst where's the wound
what is this well no well no it's it's
actually I mean this is this is in tune
with Lagasse's and your own philosophy
this is what happens I mean this is this
is what will eventually happen initially
we'll all be consumed by something
certainly that's the only law yeah I did
say that you like two minutes ago
yeah oh I know I'm trying to figure out
what you know the guys to be honest
might be like a cat and then he just is
like their time oh yeah I would say no
no I'll drop it take it for the eyes
first yeah yeah yeah if there is a
that's awful then we want that to be
it's amazing
good look at her eyes no no no no really
where well he'll just sort of like creep
over and then just like raise up over
her yeah like there there would be a
curiosity like there would be there are
things being struggled against there's
propriety but there's a natural and
there's the natural inclination right
right yeah so do we do we want to say
that Locati
has his own like midlife crisis I was
what I was gonna suggest was that if
there's any place on her body that say
like oh like a wound that needs a
tourniquet Locati
goes to tourniquet it with his form but
maybe he's lingering a little bit too
close to the wound he's thinking about
it see what target is he is blocking the
flow of blood which is good for now okay
in the same way that you can get those
those army ants to to bite and and and
suture a wound yes not like the army
answer like I'll help they're like huh
bite the shit out of this just wait yeah
so yes I like that so it's a weird of
morbid curiosity and I'm right like
please but I'm also like you know no no
no it's it's like it's like when you're
in the food cart with your kid like you
know that any second you might have to
do a dad voice right yeah walnut on
grass Oh actually no it's rich Rosie
she's here no we need that death safe
please fifty twenty you need ten or ten
hiya can I take it - no on a desk safe
can look I give you an advantage no
that's that is one that is my one strike
all right friend all right it's these
these strange mouths are continuing to
liquefy and pools around the party
Karev it is your turn nothing I could do
nothing grass oh yeah motion to me said
collecting I can't use enough art yeah
I'm constantly me so
haven't you done enough walk me through
this cuz I've never had someone in five
II get to might get to this point on my
watch
she has stabilized before I can actually
heal her I can't just like straight-up
heal her up or can you can heal her
sweet oh okay so so I've been screwing
around where I just gave you the high
five and I was like okay you go deal
with it and then seeing you like on the
ground all curled up I like breath
catches and then I whisper my little
healing word but I do it at a casted at
the second level so holding that juice
listen to this gamer so Italy um 2d for
plus my spell casting ability modifier
so let's see okay wild yes
three three so five plus four so nine
okay so yeah that brings you up yep I'm
up above zero of course I run over to
her side and then like absent-minded
like batting and Gatti away and then I
screw up my right I'm coughing yeah
exactly I mean well know exactly out of
this slop yeah I mean this is this is
essentially the reverse of the of the
right back on the wagon there's an
opportunity you had an opportunity to
repay very quickly on this debt I'm good
I like it yeah exactly
so square never anybody anything yeah so
so exactly but you made out so yeah look
at ligarius is looking over her there
was a wound it was interesting and now
it's gone and he's looking at you as
though for an explanation like a dog
thing a man yeah yeah yeah I was gonna
say that like the guy he would
understand that this is no longer a dead
thing yeah it has now lost interest
yeah yeah it's like I'm coils from yeah
where the wound was awake yeah and then
and then returns to me yeah it's process
he's processing something okay now the
four of you in the party what do you do
with this cake cart burn it never let
this happen again I don't know good
doing can we investigate it or yeah you
could if I see one okay before I do that
I'm gonna look up at Walnut and then it
looked down at the destruction I'm gonna
say I'm like I'm like hugging you and
then like pushing some of the muck off
in the face which I'll put your own on
my on my back see it's like doing
nothing exactly sound good
yeah backpack man do you ready back you
want to check out the cart together sure
yeah you got a good vantage yeah oh yeah
that aerial view up here on that walnut
yeah it's like having a drone yeah I'm
just like no wanna put my hands like
this is what you want right
hands and left right I know right right
right
and then just both hands right in right
in the cake
she looks so upset yeah just scrimmage
around in their wrists you if we can
find anything cool yeah this is just
cake okay how about deep looks like she
has tall gloves
yes exactly nice okay like fine
beautiful mm and is there is there
anything about this cart that is
interesting to hold no no you think that
you think that this is a it's not a new
cart okay by any means I mean it might
be that they use this cart for this
purpose they want a well verse card be
the cake card no it is it is not it is
not they have a characteristic marking
on them but you have had more than one
opportunity to discover is there any
loot - yeah is there any loot to be
found in the slop mother you can see
swablu yeah put the cart back out like
where we yeah we ask Oh would be weak to
tell his heroes yeah I'm sure they'll
throw us a party yeah hey everyone shake
the hand of the Dragon that killed the
monster this one autograph
I finally grabs right here so you you
are squeaking you're squeaking this cart
you can sort of get it out of that crook
that knocked it over
yes you're pushing the cart out and then
think the crowd is not left they have
not moto inch what's what's become of
Keatley Nordic kid he's drawing his body
he was he was he was drawing it back and
it was his feeling that he'll again
he'll tell you as much is that he didn't
know how he could shoot it without also
shooting his mother I see I see
but it was dinar who took the initiative
yeah yeah said I can do it yeah well now
with this now with this weapon now yeah
yeah yeah this massive thing yeah that I
filleted it expertly exactly and so
the kinds like this like the card is as
it emerges from the mouth of this mine
that ring is just solid around everyone
is dressed obviously for last stones day
they have not moved a single muscle and
you come out I are you sure you still
holding her okay I'm writing all my
stuff it's a nota
type of situation as you as you emerge
like as the cart is wheeled into its
position where it was like it's
perfectly silent until the cart gets
back where it's supposed to be and then
as soon as the cart does it it's almost
like there's an audible click almost as
soon as it gets back into where it's
supposed to be then everybody knows if
the party is still on and it gets it
gets loud oh I start craning it gets
yeah it gets loud I think it's about I
they are coming in fast and you can hear
and you can hear all kinds of stories
it's like oh well that hasn't happened
for 50 years and oh like they're all so
they're all swapping stories and they've
all chosen their favourites and they all
think that they know who defeated the
monster sir
out of these four heroes me love it was
me because love the time I say tell your
kids that one you tell your kid so each
person has a different degree about yeah
exactly like they'd they say they know
that you all emerged they know that you
all went in and that there is that you
came out alive right but how exactly
that came to be they can't calculate I
say I look at the crowd and I go I go
this last stone say it's brought to you
by acquisition incorporated situated in
the Turner Cordia visitors later for the
traditional last meals
oh my girl and then I go
and I look at the NAR and I can see that
he's like very much most people don't
know this credit I do the final
finishing blow delivered by none other
than did our Blitzen
why Papa for you look at it and then I
look at Rosie Interscope she would get
you back to the places are you yeah yeah
yeah you don't you don't I say I feel I
did it you don't feel for sayin yeah I
mean yeah you got a short rest yeah you
remember a very dark heavy thing
collapsing on you yeah and then walnut
on grass yeah
Savin my dumb that's all you know for
sure yeah I can't for you yeah exactly
that's that's that's all you that's all
you know so in the middle so yeah yeah
dragon it's sort of like it's sort of
like after church people are just sort
of gathered together they've sort of
like they had that single moment that
unifying moment and now they've sort of
they've it's devolved into various
cliques and groups and then these
cliques and groups are all sort of
moving back away from the quarry you can
see a woman sort of garb not not dressed
in last stones day garb she comes down
from a hill that overlooks the
proceedings with a smile and basically
walks up to the cart examines the cart
for damage scratch yeah yeah when she
says thank you for bringing my cart back
out welcome yeah like I'm still cleaning
walnut' asleep which the whole thing
you're welcome dear it's our pleasure
really yeah she she gets the wheel
blocks picks them up and then just
throws them on top of the rest of the
cake and starts pushing the cart over
toward the edge where she has a couple
horses ready okay do you want to talk to
her more seems like I could ask her
about what what was the thing weighs
yeah you should definitely ask her who
made that cake what was in it delicious
yeah attracted all sorts of too much
yeah it's the function I ask I'm sorry
I'm new here is the fart friend my
friend I wasn't going to start with
friend this time but I will by popular
demand but all that should all that
should be vocalized is the function of
last stones day to feed this beast that
occasionally rises up out of the quarry
okay can you not you don't know about it
but you you still you still came to it
we've art of the town we're always now
engineer out if you were of the if you
were if you were of the town if you were
of the town then you would know about
last stones day we very much wish to be
of the town we're we're based here we
work out of here well she lasts and she
says well you got a good start on it
this afternoon we defended your children
lady about a little yeah right here she
said she says I don't let him live here
no I grew up here oh and I make the cake
for last stones day but I live in tribe
or hmm sounds I just don't want to miss
it okay what's your name my name is
guerrilla gorilla
Briella from tribe or illa de Ville is
it a secret
what's last stone days about where girl
at prayer and she offers you she knows
that you would appreciate it she senses
instinctively but he would appreciate a
small piece of paper okay and she hands
you a small piece of paper that says
gorilla Porter
I know critter tribe or baking
proprietress
okay what did you put in that cake to
lure that thing here I said it happens
from time to time but it is not a common
occurrence that a creature comes back
out of the cave mouth I mean that's
that's the idea of that of the holiday
is that creatures don't come back out
because we're doing the holiday so this
is an offering to keep the creatures
from coming out well so this is how it
used to work in my dad's day if you
worked at the quarry
they would let you bring the last stone
that you cut out for your gravestone
mm-hmm cheerful Wow it was a it was
valuable it was you know it was a chunk
of change
yeah it's it's something it's it's it's
pay these days you know people don't go
down too deep in this mine these days
there was an accident a long time ago
where there was a collapse and a number
of men were not able to get out so they
were never able to take their last stone
and so we give them that each year we
also honor people who have died during
the year and we throw we throw the cake
into the quarry for those men hmm but
not actually they don't ever come out no
wow and they were men not they didn't
look like that no they were men no uh-uh
that's not as I said that's not a common
occurrence
how many men got trapped down there 20
it was a while ago
is this your first year making that cake
no what didn't you put in there to make
that monster what did you forget
the raspberry yeah would you leave out
yeah
well what's your game lady she's she's
situating she's a wizard guy yeah I
think she did shit you're trying to have
a conversation trying to like lately
times like there's a mask she's not
she's not playing that game at all
I want to lean down to Kathryn and ask a
quick question
mm-hmm how many mouths did the cake boss
have did you get gate count did I yeah
one other thing you would you would
figure died man none of that nobody
loves this creepy shit I know oh I wish
I knew I was I think you were a question
for Jerry via Katherine I think it
wasn't just a mouth I think it was mouth
it was just it was just about this many
how many mouths me stab I think it was a
thing that could only configure itself
as mouths that's funny what's funny is
that if Rosie actually like approached
Chris about this he would talk and think
about it way to yeah yeah yeah yeah I
think it was like my mouth fractal yeah
yeah I'm just saying if there were 20
men trapped down there
could they have somehow become this like
creepy crawly gel monster hmm of mouths
and did we count where their nice is
good thinking on your part
thank you right now we still have the
obligation of just want to bring it up
preparing the traditional last stone
standing right which is why if you have
a recipe for and currently the best
person in the kitchen among us is not
doing so well true Majesty on the back
yeah exactly you get exactly now I'm
back in that kitchen plus my protege
here he doesn't want to admit it but
he's quite handy with the oven I can lay
on hands Oh give me nice oh that's you
okay yeah you could heal me too and then
I could be off the races
silly actually she says did I hear that
you guys are running the drunk warrior
yes
improv is absence we are so you but
you've never you've never been the last
stone state you know that you know that
her cornerstones are legendary we do now
right she gave me the recipe question is
that the one that we saw the two yeah
who did so hopefully what why are they
so legendary okay
all right have you ever made one hmm
me no have you a couple times would you
like to help no what if we what if I try
to persuade with you yeah with your
intimidation yeah I'll just keep that
line don't prove to me you didn't summon
this monster lady we have by helping us
right make up for whatever you left out
of that cake by helping us villagers all
over her for yeah her poisoned cake
it'll I tell them hey summon them yeah
there you go
please no please yeah let's let's say
this is Intimidator it's played doesn't
matter so tell me how it tell me what
you say that creates this yeah they love
the threatening line that I thought
she's summon the monster you going like
I'll tell all of these people that
you're goofy cake summon that thing so
you're not gonna help us so you seek
it's like blackmailing so she is
basically going all around her all
around her wagon it's very very simple
affair yeah she's strapped the black
cloth back on top she's banded down she
scooped off the excess cake and then but
everything that she does is accompanied
by dinar blitz and
just following her around a place to
place it's just like a but it's like but
in the in the in the filmed version of
this it would there'd be like it would
like fade transfer to imply that it
happened for so now she's up and she's
do this and one of them he's feeding one
of the horses an apple while raiding her
I got something just like this horses
the monster
yeah example was your cake oh and
they're just she as this is going in
process she mounts the wagon
and then begins to ride it away halfway
through your sentence you try yeah I
mean she's riding away alright wait give
us just one more second please
did you did you want to try something
because I have something yeah I want to
try something real quick okay was I look
up at her and I go girl if I can call
you girl it look I have to deal with him
all the time and I go and Kings looking
like Rosie was gravely injured in that
battle she's the only one that knows
their way around the kitchen
we are doomed to deliver a horrible last
stones day to the whole town improv is
absence is there anything we can do and
I looked at him like money or whatever
to just get some help on the first batch
yeah after whatever she just snot at
least snorts like she's looking down at
you from the wagon and then she looks
over at you Rosie and says well you got
did you call it a new monster to come
out yes
is it all your fault yes are we about to
cause a monster come out yes oh yeah
you caused another monster yes I'll try
one so you're used to hang it up all
your time still clinging a little knot
and I say
Briella you seem like a very talented
young woman I've tasted this cake it is
spectacular I don't know if you brown
the butter or what beforehand if you
sift the flour is it cake flour I don't
know it's clearly unbleached it's very
high quality I on my way around a
kitchen it seems like you do too and I
think we might be able to maybe trade
some secrets if you want to come spend a
couple hours showing us how to make
these cornerstones just like totally a
mobile like so for your head yeah it's
like I'm making walnut like doing around
your hands to make okay guys talking
weekend at Bernie's she shakes her head
you know we can get on yes yeah we go
this way just right on the back oh she
knows where it is yeah you can tell she
turns it she's been around so I like
goes this way and the other says she
knows you say this way but it's the
wrong way is what I would say if I
wasn't stationed here we'll just follow
you exactly so she she is able to wheel
it around and you can you can tell that
she knows the you can tell that she
knows the town because she's avoiding
the main routes that people are
filtering back into town there's a few
small roads the sort of the town itself
is sort of like a set it has a central
sort of oval with that the long road
runs down and there's another circular
it's not Mela there's another
I was just gonna say right I was just
gonna say it's like you know that's that
would be the ultimate long con
let's see I'm gonna give you a map of
red large G and a map of red bar I know
that that's not what it looks like yeah
I've got it too exactly but there's
there's another there's basically
another oval around that central one and
she knows exactly where to steer her
nimble cart back through and back over
to the the drawn-in courtier kiwis also
jumped on the back of this wagon as well
he's like jumped on my back yeah exactly
walnut until the fact it's just it's
like it's like Jenga there's just this
pile of people sort of like it's a bee
stinger fully analog scenario and he
says he says I think that's I think that
might be my time here in red larch
you're going I think I think I think
that was quite enough excitement and
there's like a like a a small glance
over in catharsis direction that he
immediately sort of like reels back in I
leave - well I mean this was just a
typical day for us but I suppose if you
want to go will you come and see us
again I'll try okay I'll see if there is
some I'll see if there's some need of my
services okay South maybe as far as
Waterdeep okay maybe we'll make our way
there sometimes we'll see
he reaches he reaches back over to his
pouch and then sort of Pat's it like to
make sure that he has everything that he
needs and then you see him sort of walk
out that same road that the party has
walked out so many times out to the
corner where well versus an operation
you know you know just north of there is
truth find poultry and he is actually
leaving he's leaving he's leaving town
on foot
that down the same path that you came
into town 21 episodes ago I guess 21 Oh
Mike a drink yeah exactly exactly
alright music plays yeah yeah the
incredible mocha
so he as he leaves as he leaves town as
you're gonna be emerging from the the
southern exit indeed very near to the
tree where you had your own altercation
with brigands what was it
Oh your forehead is yeah getting tight
nothing I'm just reacting negatively
you know I'm reacting negatively to the
information you've provided there is a
cart waiting near that tree Hennessey
approaches the cart he looks up to the
driver and says hello brother and his
brother says hello brother
what they're both brothers with each
other and he says he says what have you
brought from the old woman and he says
some I was able to intercept a pouch
intended for her but she won't miss and
he gets up he pulls himself up along the
side pulls the pouch out goes through it
finds the two small emeralds in there
and thinks nothing of it puts the pouch
back and they ride south on the long
road said his brother like that was his
brother but it was dead did he like
steal my money and ride off yeah see
Robin is fucking mom but you don't know
Drita's no but I do chemistry
you got dream knew it
you got dreamed hey that is a nice place
to pause while we take full advantage of
the potty facilities of course recall
we're gonna move to a commercial break
recall that subscribers only see awesome
AI stuff they don't see the commercials
oh so I'm considering what why wouldn't
you subscribe exactly you're a twitch
prime subscriber you gotta just like a
free subscription free subs every month
one wah-wah-wah-wah-wah
when last we saw our heroes what
specifically I think technically
wouldn't last waste our heroes we were
actually looking at a villain we did of
a sort that's one interpretation of
events Kate can't believe it Rosie Rosie
has doesn't have to know but well mass
we saw our heroes they were returning
with famed Baker originally from red
larch now if tribe or tribe or baking
the proprietress knows a thing or two
about a thing or two when it comes to
last stones day knows exactly how to
make them and your you can feel just
like a like a stone in your stomach as
this cart pulls around the corner you
can tell that there are already people
maybe they haven't heard that prophet is
gone but there are some hungry ass
motherfuckers there are some kids
melting down no no they were promised
cornerstones and right now they got
precisely zero chorus I'm ready for this
front of house RP so it's gonna say no
grellus ease this this throng and she's
like
I'm gonna show you how to make these and
then I'm gonna go in that way on the
scene exactly see what the constable has
yeah okay all right so as you see she's
able to she pulls the cart alongside
that drunk courtier how do you compare
yourselves as you leave and enter the
facility how do you communicate to this
gathered throne I'm gonna have Rosie and
I'm in a very gracefully pass her off
ticket through baby
yes but it's like with all like the
warmth of a forklift it's just right
there's nothing that a lot there and I
will do this the function will be a
shelf someone confused when you hold
like hand a newborn you're like which
end I go completely limp oh I have like
clearly and dead weight
so I'm I'm now completely obsessed with
the fact that we're deep into this the
job that prophet gave for us and I'm
very concerned we're gonna like it lose
our free rent delegate right but oh I'm
gonna open the door so that everybody
can this group can get through and I say
folks we will be open shortly for the
traditional last Stones Day meal that
you all know and love from the drawn
courtier where we are
that's where we are you and then I go we
will start seeing you momentarily and
provide some refreshments while we get
those fresh piping hot old cornerstones
- Warner stone he's no just give us a
few minutes and then I go back in sweat
new things for her soon as you turn
around it's like I have a bright idea -
as as what was we're walking and I said
ah but wait and enjoy there's this show
has only just begun while you await the
cornerstone it's my friend the glow man
is here to entertain all the children of
the town and I and I manifest the glow
man using dancing lights and the glow
man appears and then in the form of the
children begins to pantomime you see
that you see children approaching the
glow man with curiosity this starving
glow man they still have their little
cages that they're carrying they've been
feeding them bits of cake oh yeah for us
the even these birds are fucking out of
their minds
hey can I use minor illusion - uh -
great miners to create miners to a go
get some more stones no issues it to get
to like create a meal for glow man to
eat so that he can look really happy and
satisfied and then the people in line
can imagine how happy and satisfied
they're gonna be like watching this
pantomime open go ahead and try they
could make a glowing meal for him I do I
make I make him a glowing chicken dinner
mm-hmm with the big conscious oh yeah
and Louie side of potatoes mm-hmm
can't wait a luminescent potato it's
floating in the air and
man he goes Oh his hands passed through
it he cannot have it now I torment
perhaps glue man is not smart enough she
took his attempting to eat the chicken
dinner and entertains the children with
his revelries no I just happened yeah I
interrupt this gross humans
Rell with the dragon that defeated the
Beast and I just start throwing him in
the air and catching them and they don't
want any throne and I'm like no you'd be
surprised
yeah I let him crawl all over my back
you are the only dragon born that you
have seen in a red larch yeah this is
highly exciting phenomenon also this is
also the hear or read large yes having
defeated the creature of the cave you
are the hero all right so there is there
is a lot there's a lot for these young
people to enjoy right that titled
Allegan I say you your titles write a
poem but I like you're like an animate
bond see Castle for these kids but one
of these but one of the children one of
the ones that has an empty birdcage it's
over still just sort of like fruitlessly
trying to comfort the glow man and I
shut the door and let dinar deal with
the key that doesn't make the gold man
do anything no no no I need to see that
little walnut face like and then do it
thank you
Briella and i are in the congestion
process alright alright alright we need
the cornerstone pants got it I know
prophets got those yep she definitely
does yeah I've already busted out the
recipe that I determined is not the
gross one I've known other disgusting
Robin discussing one I did figure out
which is which here's both in case you
have like a preference but this is the
gross one so oh yeah she's like no we
don't okay okay there's a recipe and the
cornerstone pans are there No
so the cornerstone pan is has
four spots in it okay so imagine that
each of the imagine going to so
essentially this pan it's placed right
on the heat okay okay it's a cast iron
pan are they like muffin tins no it is
it is it's like a muffin tin but it's
more actually like it looks like it
contains four square loaves okay okay
more loaves
got it right now the way that it works
as you see quickly like she comes in and
she is able to find another one of these
pans so you actually have two of them
total and each of them can make four but
I'm I'm telling you this so that you can
picture it I the mechanism is not gonna
be so sophisticated that you have to
individually fill the mini-game no no no
and she shows you how to do it so she
has whipped up its a very very simple
batter like a like a pancake batter but
it has a few spices in it which you know
indicates that it is a distinct and is
for a specific time of the year right
and here's how it works
there are also a couple it looks like a
an old like a knitting needle right it's
long it's about yay big and she has
filled each of these little square loaf
pans with this light thin batter and
then as it cooks she and then ever she
ever after she is poured all the way
around once she has poured the last one
the first one is now ready to do
whatever the fuck she's gonna do with it
so she reaches in this knitting needle
and then she's able to like lift out of
the pan a little square shape so just
the edge of it has become
being delicious and then she's turned it
over like this and the batter is poured
down into the base so she's flipped the
whole thing over got it and now that
base is cooking yes right I'm gonna make
the recipe no I will show you how to do
it oh you know this is a real thing that
you've made well they're not they don't
look like this then Tabletalk okay I'll
tell you I'll tell you about him anyway
but the cornerstone and then she's like
and then one of the ones once she's gone
all the way around a second time and
done the flip she pops him out
hot fresh delicious crispy outside chewy
inside rolls them in some powdered sugar
and then makes a tiny slit in one side
spoon a jam inside Oh
what flavor Jam it's got to be fast but
she has an assortment there this
particular one is like a huckleberry Jam
local bushes right it's like a weed but
they like it I hope that someone in
their fan art decides to manifest it as
writing out this recipe and baking it
and sharing pictures oh yeah well will
do will do and I'll show you how to get
I'll show you how to get close with a
with a real traditional recipe exactly
open the house exactly exactly so you
can open now so as soon as you start to
see a few cornerstones get popped out
you're opening the place up yeah
all right so people are outside on the
front on the dinar jungle-gym mm-hmm
crawling all around on these pauldrons
you know getting flung into the air it's
getting knocked over jail you're
juggling kids yeah the kids it's like
this is the thing it's like you can
entertain like seven or eight of them at
once that tails going this way they're
jumping over the tail yes finally
someone thinks it's great yeah exactly
yeah exactly Danny Inara is real he's
been crying all time yeah walks into the
shadows
[Applause]
like thank shipped one exactly so
essentially here is the yeah here is the
the situation imagine imagine that your
parents have gone away on a dark dark
week my parents did too soon so we need
cooks yeah I have servers and we have
morale Maitre D' type issues out front
and then we have a floater that can
support those fellows like a turn Jeff
to be flushed yes we make we make potty
humor on this show did you laugh with
you turd you need to comport your
cylinder you need to comport yourself
with maximum per joke so these are the
roles exactly so after after she's after
she pops these out she grabs a couple of
apples looks out at the people who are
pouring in looks out the window at the
additional people and says good luck
thank you we got this yeah yeah she
emerges okay she emerges from gorilla
emerges from the front you have her card
of course oh I'm gonna actually give her
the first course don't wrapped up in a
towel Oh what the heck her travel oh
thank you so much well thank you of
course she wraps it up tucks it like a
football
straight out of the front door out of
the cart you can hear the you can hear
the hooves
say are you stealing that yeah children
I killed the monster she's summon
she's the reason you should fear her at
night come get you in your sleep it's
weird that you have no friends when
Michael's got in the office there's a
tape of him as a kid he's like when I
grow up I'm gonna have a hundred friends
of another hundred good friends and no
one could say no to be my friend
exactly so so you're there they're
hearing this they're hearing this wisdom
yes and they are filing it away drink it
in in their truth English are they're
gonna get a big old dragon club pressure
than they're breaking exactly so here is
the scenario there are going to be two
big rounds okay
hmm three turns apiece cooking serving
and maintaining morale in order for this
to go correctly in order for a profit to
return to a place that has maintained
leave you yeah no we need to get through
these shifts we got a tune and polish
running this this engine now you have to
get through these rounds without getting
four strikes okay okay
exactly what strikes okay it's a mini
game it's a mini get this is now
wonderful there is no check this out
there isn't easy you know by the book by
the numbers roll that you can take okay
to get through these to each of these
checks cook serve or morale right there
is a more difficult check that you can
take to give the next person in this
sequence free advantage
hmm heading down all the way to the
morale Maitre D' type roles indeed and
so if they succeed they can confer that
advantage all the way back to beginning
of this I can just pick you pay it
forward okay yeah if you want to go for
the harder role now you get a strike by
failing a role anyone any role
okay I think you're not rolling Jerry
Wow now but you got me now you got this
advantage for all your boys no no listen
yeah yeah yeah that's no no I'm saying
like it I mean when we put together the
AI dice like I put the AI logo on the
one for me I just want to look down and
say you know what oh wait for 20 today
is it you didn't like the paint so you
could do a good job on that look Chuck
you go yeah he go okay so how would it
what constitutes a fail is the best
check does not not succeeding not
hitting the target DC what is the target
the target DC for the regular cooking
roles is 12 okay you can difficult and a
difficult one is 17 hey and do we get
any bonuses but I am open to suggestions
about how you can use your skills to
create a cool Anthony Bourdain esque
kitchen adventure okay to entertain the
shadow Council
okay who you know who our labors should
optimally speaking to be pleasing I've
got a natural Asian and intimidation and
I've already got the crowd on my side
ways so they're loving me your morale
yeah okay maybe you are server got that
decks are you floating with velvet I
guess yeah yeah his feet don't touch the
ground I am I am sort of the utility
remember in the group and then so and
then 12 and 17 are the checks for across
the board yeah basically if these things
get crazier out at the end hopefully
you've got the advantage by then
wouldn't use a floater exactly truly
hate that word if someone messes up
their role does he have a chance to come
in and do that yeah that round like you
can pick one person to float their job
they have their
problems oh nevermind yeah what's the
turn order and let's hear about the
other rules
exactly the turn order is basically you
guys are gonna choose it all so you're
gonna tell me who the cook is who the
server is and Maitre D' it sounds like
we got mater dragon over here okay it
sounds like Chris trout a valve a thanks
sous chef yeah yeah have a baby a year
and you'll have to you'll have to solve
your own problems
trust me you'll you'll deal with your
honor plenty more you could wait do you
want to wait tables yes I'll take a nap
no no but it's got that I mean yeah he
can run some of them and I'll run the
rest of them I don't see how that works
out but yeah I can wait I'm I'm what
you're not gonna wait yeah and I'm okay
easy to ignore and friends okay so that
leasts yeah waiter is good throws I I
where can I put the lizard king on the
outside of my cloak to make it look like
instead of a jaunty little the lizard
king yeah where is he has stopped
laughing and stopped being observational
what I forgot to feed him
Dwight so I he's on me and I think about
a car well maybe he'll like to see
you've been showing him things things
that he might find interesting in his
adventure in the greater world and you
know your presumption was that the last
few just in land yeah but now I I take
its pulse that's mine so I looked a
little bit further just it's just you're
not sure how you would take the pulse of
a conscious skeleton it's just any piece
it's a piece of information I say you'd
like to know I'm sorry old friend
I don't change anything that I might
continue to wear living
and they continue to wear and then also
but entertain yeah why not yeah I liked
it too
why would I stop exactly so you were
telling me that the COO is cooking right
so it makes sense because Rosie's
learned the recipe however since we do
get to use our skills in assassins role
talk to me about them right yeah you've
got some like survival you got some
nature or that you're gonna be like if
we need extra ingredients you got your
forest because your horse you know I
just I looking at I could I could
happily float and I could happily cook I
mean let's think
keep Rosie okay okay yeah she's got four
hit points anyways yeah super safe
mm-hmm okay so Rosie's Cantor 17 good
berries to put the good Barry well not
in the cornerstone whoa no I was gonna
say a motherfucker is gonna roll through
if you like listen I'm not getting
cornerstone anyplace else I had a
cornerstone there it's like a million
goddamn dollars yeah great idea we
should do that how many can you became
addicted and then raise the price yeah
you want to feel good again okay fifty
bucks
[Music]
gold yeah
you gotta wait till next year I got what
you need right guys this could be great
that's okay I have an idea let's put
poison in them and then give me an adult
one I hope ur / yeah yeah great so
what's our turn order exactly how'd you
guys well the turn order is gonna go and
clear Rosie okay wait done order have to
be taken first
I'm not deliveries I think they're all
ordering the same thing yeah thrist yeah
they're here for a specific treat out
and then we have Dragonborn narcissist
and our blitz in that's number two on
the boil he's he's doing the maitre d
and it sounds like the server is gonna
be Chris trout yep yeah and velvety
mmm and the velvetine if he needs to be
there
and the Gotti uh-huh yeah a little
and hey boy let him go run to my where
like a tie yes all the daggers just like
right there in the middle oh right here
Dingle at harsh yeah okay is he good he
could say pound and then he looks at his
own sort of like the middle of his own
body goes you seen this before it's
nesting that we exactly yeah exactly
yeah yeah so we got Rosie kicking things
off yeah wrist backing it up okay and
then we got a situation
that only been our bulletin can handle
okay yeah charismatic beloved by the
town and then floater has her own
problems slaughter has her own welcome
floater yeah guys she's not Owen Hart
okay I don't have any more shit style oh
can we use our own shadow council given
advantages the shadow council provides
those advantages so that you can succeed
in your task okay because what I'm gonna
do I'm gonna kick this off do did you
get off the right way the right way so
here's here's what I'm going to suggest
to you yes yes so you're gonna talk to
me about your your skill upfront correct
right now I have a plus three decks
bonus and my other like secondary skills
my proficiencies may or may not come in
handy acrobatics seems like it might
like the flipping of the cakes and the
tossing of things onto plate this is a
cocktail guys soon yes yeah like a
mixologist type thing like I get in my
groove and I start doing some some sweet
flips who knows like short I'm and I'm
alone and that's what happens what's the
other outcome you can't if you can grant
me that then I get plus five to my roles
and I without it please me greatly
well I would like to see that so you can
use advantage
yes for this is what
yeah okay when use advantage and I'm
doing difficult check so that I may
confer advantage in the Indies on to
your friends net
so tell me a little bit about so how is
the staff gang involved currently the
staff is just us yeah um yeah this is
the staff weight it was used that the
knitting needle contraption was used to
flip the cake exactly I just sort of
yeah so right amount so I believe that
what Rosie will do is actually disinfect
and wash the bottom of the staff but it
comes down to a point at the very bottom
so that the staff of the master will
also be used to flip these cakes up oh
oh maybe so maybe Rosie it's like on a
stool or something yes she's got him
cooking and she's just right yep exactly
she's got she's got her leverage just
going through it yeah all right let's
see it and it's so perfectly balanced
for her no you do this no no no no no
it's an artifact yeah okay so I'm going
to take my advantage
yes I have robbed in fact they just gave
you another keep them coming baby more
everything that was a bad really dead
one what's more quiz five that one is go
Levin was 516 does not give me my
difficult to know that it's right right
Oh what else I've done done I could
better well you know this is a funny
thing is that is that Mike would let you
tell a story about how since you were
just one away mice not running this game
back it also have I wouldn't Monell
track with over the in listen when you
tell the story but then give me maybe
give you the point always tell story
with litter cart you let us get away
with some stuff there so talking about I
don't support the type of shit so you're
a year back there you're flipping them
around yeah and you that you're thinking
that you've got two pans yeah for the
price of one right you're flippin
one after the other right and then this
one over here actually gets flipped like
straight off yeah everything everything
looks
this is like the part of the montage
that is life-affirming right and makes
people feel great about themselves makes
me feel great about their skills the
second pan goes straight off the edge
okay and so everyone else you can hear
this like the place just sort of like
it's like cast-iron looks like ya know
it sounds like a dwarven mine it's it is
loud but you're able you're able to
deliver a decent supply but it wasn't we
were going for and now you're kind of
behind okay sorry all right so these
products have been delivered unto you
okay exactly products in powdered it's
okay
that can i granular you we're not going
for so these are your essence of their
powdered they're jellied there aren't
quite as many as are needed to push
through this first wave but we'll we'll
catch them on the we'll catch them on
the back now I need you to tell me how
you're delivering these treats these
legendary treats
let's see what's at my disposal here I
don't you tell me I don't know is it a
Dungeons &amp; Dragons
I don't know that Locati has the yes he
has the strength to lift this plate oh
by the way a little flavor for the knife
and for this delivery mechanism I see
him not as slithering with the knife
held detail but doing that that
Sidewinder move where he's made a
leaders of himself yeah and is walking
upon them like that so like oh I mean
weird yeah that's how he does it though
it's better how's he doing
it's like this it's what I needed okay
so if you can do that how does that help
you take cornerstones out to people oh
because then he then he can he can lift
he's now on the loops yeah I'm trying to
make sure that he can do this task and
he's up to it these are not heavy
objects they're baked goods they are
baked and and I have velvet as well
mm-hmm so these I think like those
Lakhani I'd have to be concerned about
if there was like a you might wanna get
with an open wound
it's been a problem before but well
that's good to go very loyal mm-hmm and
then as for me it as the function of the
server
I just want to deliver the goods and
then and then vanish as though they had
always been yeah exactly as though they
were like condensing out of the air like
naturally occurring right insane
charisma well the thing is always fit
for the charisma we'll see but that's
the swell wait a minute my lad use the
city you tell me whatever these are
saving saving versus pastry and you tell
me what types of cool skills oh and how
you want to interact
he doesn't have to roll no no you can't
the role the skill is gonna be the plus
on his yeah right there's gonna be
rolling believe it right okay
my the highest modifiers that I have our
investigation religion performance
persuasion or generously performance but
I'm hanging performance it's just not a
thing Chris likes all the world's a
stage kiss yeah you want tips what I was
gonna yeah I do like that I do like that
that's man I was gonna try and sell you
on the fact that religion was what does
it well like I could use you you sell it
to means let me see if you can
appreciate this yeah I understand that
every every recipe is its own series of
glyphs and that thing that is coming out
of the oven fully formed is not a baked
good it is like a baked goes it is a
collage like unto thank you big it is a
fully finished like conveyance of
information and I understand the the
form of worship that these people will
be applying to this beloved mouth
worship being yeah right students know
that baked good is an anagram for Oh
baked God
I didn't know that deep within so you're
saying that you've created in your mind
a kind of mystical grammar right that is
equally adept at describing
ecclesiastical revelation
I have partitioned a part of my own
beliefs into a subset which may be like
matrix transformed onto the food service
industry this has got to be I have never
in my life had a player work so hard I
can roll in there's a big smile listen
no no listen no no listen I like by the
way everyone his performance and his
religious bonus are the same he's just
doing this that's doing no no listen we
can do it but I want to put tell I want
you to have one customer interaction
with me after we do the roles where you
can synthesize the scenario you have
described for me Oh like I was like a
math I want to see that I want I want to
see this philosophy tested in the real
world okay thank you Merck can't leave
exactly now oh he won't pick up that
evil dice all right here it is in your
hands now no hold on we have the otha we
have the 12 check right easy check which
is easy check and we also have the 17
check you know historically I'm not the
best roller I almost feel like a 12
isn't even a lock remotely and we
thought we have four strikes among us
yes yes for character yeah yikes already
had one yep all right manager oh yeah
sure I do have an advantage but I might
take advantage on the easy check who's
that who's after me who's coming next
it may be denied what's in all right
that's exactly how to play it why does
he wind up
with a nanny was nothing my advantage
sorry and you get +4
oh that's correct right guys here we go
I don't need your advantage
nice no no further no further roles
required so you go for the easy one I do
go for the easy ones you go for the easy
one and change it now check now yeah you
have emerged as though from a mix route
at first have yeah one of one of your
evil ghosts is moving is moving product
to the far side of this realm this
revolting serpent the kids like it yeah
really the reality is that most people
can't actually seal Agati under there no
they think they think of it as being
much like velvet yeah there is just a
mystically animated tray he just he just
kind of throws that loop over that and
it lands on the table yeah stretches out
stretches out tall yeah
exactly now the challenge I have found
you know the the the most in tribulation
of this flock the angriest customer the
one whose faith this in the process of
being lost
oh he's shaken this is this is a long
time drawn in quarter mm-hmm customer
and he's upset he's looking around it's
never taken this long before I have the
cloak up over my over my head I I float
to him and I say my son trials have be
rewarded
rejoice place it oh and I'm in a little
rotation yeah okay look it'll look like
seven degrees yes could have just been a
balloon animal the sign of the
cornerstone overhead
tip square in the jambs and in the
sacrament yes yeah yeah he withdraws his
fork cracks right down the middle the
jam pools in the way that it has in the
past this was the test was there ever
any doubt this was the test he merely
cuts off and you can see you can tell
that he has some kind of ritual like
that that goes into the consumption of
these things he starts at a specific
corner you don't know if that like
corner is like Cardinal in some way was
he born in that direction how do you
know you watch him like a like a master
butcher dismantle this thing according
to some inner wisdom about its structure
moving on over here you did not confer
no any extra dice over to your man's
over here and the morale checks for you
are a little bit different okay the base
when you're you're high check is is 18
but that confers and it's it's it's very
important that you maintain the morale
of the overall endeavor because that'll
soften the blows of the other strikes
okay
and what's my base still 12 yeah base is
still 12 carrying this team dude okay
again as usual like I do welcome to
Bob's Big Boy
welcome to Daddy dinars
yum yum Hut
big time on the breastplate yeah
well so I've got really high persuasion
but I was inspired by cthis so I'm gonna
go animal handling know me let me see if
I can talk you into this one so I'm
really good I can hold my bat breath for
three minutes so let me see if I get
Sonny was giving me a bit yes I turned
blue I will do advantage and I will go
for the okay as I'm out there everybody
okay okay I am for this kid
Dragonman heel swings right through his
stool just right through the bottom of
the stool just crumbles it's like it's
like it's like that submarine and the
deep was like the clothes so won't let
you hear clatter in the kitchen and then
destruction out front and what's my job
but I don't even know now you have to do
your job
this place has gone to hell okay we're
talking before we are talking about it
it's on brand we are talking about
plates we're talking about one of the
cornerstone pans literally on the ground
for now in the kitchen we're talking
about Denard Blitzen serrated tail
shredding you didn't have a tail yeah
this would be great times
I know it's got anemia nothing but a
terrible curse your obvious or blizzard
yeah
it's alive did tonight I talked to it
walnut on grass what you have a chance
to get one of these strikes back if you
get it wrong we get two strings oh shit
and then we're teddy really we all does
it okay um so we need to reach a reason
place our reach into your bag a
motherfucking trip yeah so no I don't
need these right now I might I don't use
spells and I want to make sure you guys
know like your whole your whole
character sheet is available to you
turned into a bear nice okay there's a
bear in a drink
inside of me in um he's throwing weapon
I whip the Palais de no that would not
work with that because I can't roll I
think what happened and I want to use my
perceptive abilities to be following
along behind dinar and like for every
move that he makes I want to like all
night yes yes yes so like he tips over a
chair I grab it and then also and like
you know making sure everyone's okay
like hey how's your meal we have any
more tonight Wow love it I got the
chills you know sometimes you get the
chips yeah I got the chills off of that
okay and I would like it's really good
this is about perception so you're
you're you're trying to you're trying to
assess and analyze and you're basically
trying to be where you need to be before
you need to be there's the yes that's
exactly it
here's the problem I've been sitting
here while y'all were taking those big
rolls being like you stupid idiots why
just go for the easy one but now that
I'm like no indeed indeed it was
manufactured explicitly for this purpose
I'm gonna and it yeah I'm gonna do it I
want to do like a funeral okay you got
this perception yes please okay that's
at plus six
yeah plus sixteen seventeen yeah let's
just see what the other one
you should roll it okay at least you're
you new one but if somebody might get
some culinary hey that's a real shit
show and now we take you get five
strikes so you can see you can see like
just under just under the surface dinars
have you know glad-hand performance you
can see just the molding rock just
tension flowing underneath every
interaction and you are able to sort of
like just caboose this situation
wherever so whatever something is is
wrong you're standing there you're
between him and that you are the person
tell me how you solve this tell me how
you solve the the issue with the stool
om hittin the stool and it just
collapsing collapsing so you you you you
succeed in their role tell me tell me
how tell me how you fix it so yeah you
mean go through you go through your
spell's it's all yeah um so forest
friends and just like make it chair yeah
I'm not of animals and chair I turn into
a trainer and I say take from me my
business and I become the giving myself
know so that happens in the chair
explodes and then I use Giroud craft at
that exact same moment to create a small
illusory effect and I want to choose Oh
something P called something small yeah
oh I can make a gold I can make it I can
make a golden orb very well yeah
so I I missed a golden orb yeah while
that's there and then I try and do like
a little sleight of hand thing where I
grab another one
I feel like huh and it's their stool
yeah and it's a different stool yeah
yeah tada and then I go okay kids who
wants to sit in the glowy see it's just
a shyness kids love glowy seats kids
look glow stuff right so let's roll back
through yeah you are able to protect the
party from one of these strikes oh very
nice we have one strike and we go
through three rounds of this guy no no
we have we have one more round let's see
how you do it nice so we're back up to
cooking but how do you want to do it
Kohi mama I know it's me do it cooking
grandmama so I have retrieved my wayward
pan
yes so I've back to ate that exactly now
you can you can crank these if you
alright if you succeed well yeah I'd
like to crank them if you don't mind and
I have this for me yeah okay let's do it
I don't think I was just looking to see
if there's any cool grandma flavor that
I can throw in there well I mean listen
there is a lot there is a lot of you
know grandmother flavor in this entire
enterprise that you're constructing in
there also I don't want to mess with the
with the sauce or glass yeah
I don't I don't want to mess this
tradition yeah and I'm learning a lot as
I'm going plus I want to memorize this
recipe because I'm gonna bake it for my
granddaughter you all good
oh you only grandmother Li er oh yeah
all you need is okay okay then I will go
for the difficult check okay like I got
advantage on it
get your filth you know what just for
fun just for no reason I'm gonna spend a
key point
why yeah and I'm gonna do thank you
is it no it doesn't give me anything
except I'm gonna do step with the wind
just in case I need to bounce around
this kitchen faster that's it that's
just for flavor I don't even care best
okay that's not not that flavor come on
flavor that's a flavor
Oh do this this is the this is the best
all right so here throw it
give me some imagery here okay because
this is this is the first success on the
tub yeah
so the stove is not big enough to cook
both pans at the same time or is it you
kind of boys it's one of those
situations second those classic stoves
were you kind of like get to sit him
close by each other and like turn them
and okay yeah so I got all eight going I
hear the ruckus outside but I've got my
whole assembly line lined up like I've
got the the dough the batter I've got
the pans I've got the powdered sugar
I've got a lot of jams I found more jams
so I'm just like it's what all of them
have spoons they're ready to go and it
is a motion of me jumping I spit I spear
own it I spear a cornerstone I flip I
land in the powdered sugar with it I
push off I drop it on a plate grab a
spoon stick it in - stuff with a wind
back to zero do it all over again as a
breeze a warm breeze from the kitchen
that smells of delicious baked goods oh
wow that is that's pure magic
that is pure Graham I made see right
there but the bar you have two lined up
front you know exactly now Chris trout
emerging as though from a mist shroud
tell me how round - that is gonna go for
you here shatter
um question exactly inspired by what I
watched you do to not let dinar screw
everything up and just be there don't
wear how would you feel if I added some
more enjoyments to these children's day
and use fairy fire on the room to enable
everyone to see little bit better so
dark in here but it would also confer
advantage to do not deliver his next
please you I think it's interesting
let's worry about your own turn right
now okay you have advantage for me
exactly right okay yeah you got it you
got it because Rosie rocked it okay
forward yeah yeah right you can I just
paper I can just attempt to do it that
way right yeah and I do have an
advantage remaining so what you write
under that right out of the jelly Bowl
serve all meals at once every meal I
would love to see that I would to kanima
if I was is the same as the yes I
already did so he's got what I try try
it got two more strikes man I watch you
and on that stool as I saw all the
courses a bit bigger I might wow look in
the inside use like land if you look at
like wink amazing and I'm inspired by
this with shown what tentacles can do
for this restaurant you must hurry up
score is a downer up it's like when I
was in when I was in Provence during
this last stones day I minute I'm gonna
do something so much classier than what
happened in that kitchen there
there's like a beetle on the floor crush
it because I need a dead body to make
this head pop that little carapace up
there next to the into the car stones
now to tack Euler spectacular merge
bursts forth and sling those
cornerstones to the tables that still
need them that's what's gonna happen and
I feel great about I'm also going to
take advantage okay so the question is
Jarrett advantage you I knew the tough
check yeah doesn't go for yes alright
who do different go check yeah here we
go so one time he's not gonna roll
really like shit watch it I'll shit one
because we're not great I see kind of
things are like let's try to get hop it
off twice
now that's jack technically it's off the
edge it's just to commit I'm not allowed
to roll the same number twice
oh yeah that's a roll yeah statistically
you're not allowed yeah that's like
Lightning's 15 doesn't work yeah yeah
just a really rough yeah and then and
then it's just like you see you see the
The Beatles do you crush
sort of jumps back up on its legs and
then sort of skitters and then begins to
bite off its own land
and it flips over onto its back and
twelve jagged rope like tentacles if he
emerged can I can i pre flavor this a
little bit I was so ready for this
awesome moment that I said hey everybody
look at this
[Laughter]
so savage tentacles erupt casting
they're sort of violent lights around
that there you know within and without
the fairy lights nightmare is born
shattered from the corner it's like it's
like 12 long you know chainsaws like
hissing and burning in midair glowing
[Applause]
[Laughter]
are you I have to do like I did last
time just started writing everyone like
if anyone asks you had a great time
and I guess I roll I guess I got to go
for normal there's no reason to go for
the big one yeah and I'm just
threatening everyone not to tattle I
mean it gives our floater advantage if
you go to the big one it's no good so
you you you know band you know you
expand your silhouette yeah laughs
Brenda yeah in a threatening draconic
way with the acid trip yeah they can see
just put puffs of acrid smoke Oh God
there but then you just increased the
danger to equal around the
and that's fine exactly right now there
are two strikes and you have you have
gotten through that check now floater
all right it's use what you know
precious the precious floater you know
the situation that we have here you can
see this situation and I gotta I gotta
fix you have to try to fix it I have to
fix it no I produce flame it come it it
seems to me that we have 12 or so tiny
creatures that need to be taken care of
it um scenarios think I love Canaries
well so that's what I'm thinking is it's
like we saw I need to dispel the
tentacles is that Worthen you tell me
the situation you you tell me how you
want to manage because then are
succeeded in this check so you don't to
fix it for him and Rosie be stood it
everyone sounds good timed it yeah
exactly now could this a real fest yeah
I you know that moment in a magic show
though where you think everything's
fucked and then yeah yeah we need them
proceed you need to turn you need the
turn okay
okay I'm going to this is so dumb maybe
it maybe I maybe it'll happen
I want to they're coming from like
behind the bar is there yeah yeah yeah
they're at that still okay um so I want
to use forest friends okay and I want to
summon just like from the windows is a
nineteen yeah um
bunch of Canaries and have them just be
singing a little canary song doing like
the last stones day thing but as my
bonus action I would like to wild shape
into something that we that is
that that that could possibly get rid of
this so the Canaries are pure
distraction that's yeah let's take care
of that and then while that's going on I
want to wild shape into a oh this is
really good at this
um into a crocodile haha which I can do
precious channel not turn into a
crocodile reach up from behind the bar
grab all the tentacles at the origin
point which I would grapple yeah and
then I will do the crocodile barrel
world where they are rolled onto me
taking all that damage and then
sauntering like behind the bar back into
the kitchen so they can't see me awesome
art but I'm rapping technical gunfire
and bleeding well no I mean the reality
is it you hit zero points in your shape
you just turn back into walnut covered
in tentacles covering ten virgins
yes is enough covered yeah yeah and now
I'll roll my check you can to see if I
do it I'll just do whatever my modifier
is for this guy I did it yeah hey so you
reach up and you say no one of the pause
like just like pull yourself up on it
and like I just like snap into the thing
and so you is it's like imagine if you
went to a dark Italian restaurant
exactly the evil garden yeah there's no
yes you do grab that wreath that
basically that root clump and then just
pull it drag it off into the back and
you're you're over here like you're
trying to set up the next set of them
and I'm just trying to like jump around
her yeah it's like when you go through
and you roll up like when you
sufficiently stop giving a fuck about
Christmas and you just doing the lights
off like fuck fuck fuck
it's exactly what happens so you grab
that root clunk on your ma and then you
swallow a couple feet of it exactly and
then you start twisting yourself around
the corner into this into this mesh and
as you're able to pull that around the
Canaries are chirping their children
some of them are getting Canaries to put
in their empty cages the adults
I don't exactly a hundred percent know
what the scenario is right here it's a
morality play
it's our dinner canary yeah it got rid
of them the tentacles again the kind of
shave yes Canaries are here well it was
a dramatically earlier Cake Boss
yes yeah exactly and so as as walnut is
able to snatch this clump and wheel
around the edge and reduce the reduce
the insanity levels of this restaurant
substantially the bonus round is
revealed Wow
the front door opens and see you see a
man in brilliant royal purple garb large
floppy hat exhausted emaciated looking
scribed behind him trying to capture and
contain whatever this creature emits and
he says it is I mean song food critic of
1:30 I have heard that you have the best
corner stop oh my god food critic brews
bees near on space week
you sir are right okay that is our game
for day no no we burn through all the
time like we chewed through it like I we
were actually past time now that's shit
shadow council mayor Labor's please you
we are going to jump out for another
Mercer break we're gonna grab some sodas
at all we're gonna come back and we're
gonna do some table talk so don't go
anywhere
you