time is the enemy the pastor threatens
the fastest weapon you wouldn't make it
past a second and last a question
play it brash and reckless to choose a
cautious solution you saw it was prudent
in any sepulcher poker to don't become
the pew tree it's that welfare that
pursue in no mountain too steep for
dungeon too deep to send expendable
marks up to the top of the peak of
beneath they see you either come like
sharks to it while I swim in that money
burn like Carl Barks through it so send
your National Parks drew it I'll send
him home in a natural box with a close
tie but most of the parts included save
your breath for a cleric confessor death
is a lesson and life is a tenured
professor but if you're seeking my
official advice sign on the dotted line
and wish of the twice initial it twice
sorry late it's fine listen name it from
from Chris it's okay
hello oh that's great I'm Tycho Brahe
hey a penny arcade impacts I am also a
mini fest heroine drawn CEO of
acquisitions incorporated but today what
day is it further they always Thursday
when we do boy you know what you knew
what should have clued me in you know
what should have clued me in the
campaign to see team yeah yeah it's it's
always on Thursday anyway but today I'm
playing a game of Dungeons and Dragons
for my friends to my right best friend
Ragan born narcissist and I blitz in to
the right of my right repping the
natural world walnut dog grass where's
Brahma history yeah it's like you know
topical catchphrase not for internal use
yeah you know what I mean position now
addition to my left not your grandma's
grandma get ready not your grandma's
grandma except for those rare cases in
which she is your grandma's grandma
Rosie B stands
that's just like juicing to the left of
my left emerging is though from a mist
shroud Chris drought see ya now does
anybody remember where we left off last
gains memories no no no penetration
what's the last thing you remember
dinars we were cooking those square
cakes yeah a couple months ago when last
we saw our heroes Oh shadow Council the
party had recently found in the Third
Ward
of Scala a notoriously xenophobic
Dragonborn Enclave they had recently
found princess sources villa in the
Third Ward and having been led within
dinar Blitzen
was reunited with a hatched
Dragonborn girl named Crenn are so real
name the character has a real name now
there's a part of the Canon mm-hmm has
been established has a complex a
sophisticated relationship with her
mother they perhaps even more
sophisticated and complex relationship
with her father a fraught social
scenario that you were functionally
speaking plunged into the middle of
there were there were interactions of
various kinds Crenn eras a sprightly
child has made many Grimm attacks on the
artifacts and decor she's a grifter of
the villa
she's an iconoclast exactly
remove removed remove the sword strap
trying to pull toothbrush away into the
hedge it's it's a real mess it's a real
mess and then thrust into this already
robust scenario here comes Prince
shimmer scale perhaps invited in a sense
by the secret messages you picked up on
earlier that is the scenario we find
ourselves in kronar the scion of Scala
is on the tale that you have that other
Dragonborn do not and she is getting
some kind of ride from the tale
situation even as the the Prince turns
his heel his left arm profoundly scaled
with this violent punch weapon yeah this
Cistus like dinar is pretty excited I'm
gonna get that for sure scale just to
take that thing I'm gonna get his weapon
and his kid to feed his teeth to your
horse yeah is that is the classic you
know scenario now all my insults come
back exactly so just select out from the
menu
so Crenn are in this in this moment of
silence between this sort of hot
dangerous mystic triangle formed between
you the prince and the princess Akron R
is not does not have the psychological
tools to process that this is an
important mommy-daddy scenario and it is
it is precisely in this scenario that
she begins to climb from the
bail up the straps on the back of the
armor and with a quick poll
she has flopped capi off no and has is
now seated on your head and then she has
placed Kathy on top of her own hem and
it is completely covered we have we have
we have a brand new show it's like we
can't beat this yeah it'd be the same
pics but here buddy but here's here's
the situation I want to make sure that
Rosie be stinger walnut on grass and
Catherine know that the expression on
Cathy's face is not pleased
oh there is it's this is definitely not
exactly eyebrows have moved down in this
way and he's looking down at his own
sort of at his own Ridge spores any
really puffing out yeah he's it this
little dust rain it just looks like
glitter she's happenings like everything
that's happening and so this has been
we're talking about a full minute of
silence now kid Prince say anything or
you just show nothing they're just like
something something that is novel to
note so as I described sorsha is wearing
the traditional battle garb even in the
villa which constitutes armor plates but
also this wrap that is capable of
holding a child this is that this is a
pretty traditional gear for the mother
you'd be able to purchase this from the
app I mean it would be it would be a
featured product yeah Terry he is not
wearing one and that is that is a little
odd okay I know then in their picture
yeah you know that you know that that is
that there is some parents where
absolutely and he's not wearing yeah
yeah it is a ceremonial function I mean
it's it's also something for your
community to congratulate you on its
arraignment right yeah he's not gonna
say anything yeah I just be like so
here's something you got something gonna
pay me back money you stole me so his
his people had begun to filter out and
you can tell at some deep level that
there are sophistications to the the
social politics between these houses -
it's like it's like you you think there
would be some way to mathematically
represent yeah like how close each
individual person can be to any other
person you can see there start like
forming this social graph here in the
open space underneath these I told you
to go that's the source of the problem
[Music]
okay well so yeah she immediately as
soon as he tells her to do something she
she says no she looks at dinner and like
as the trying to give him that like I
got your back face yeah yeah for her
it's just yeah
I don't get it all like gonna be like
what different kind of friends yeah so
sherry scale crosses yeah this courtyard
not toward you not anywhere in your and
you're part of this diagram
and he switches to the draconic dialect
mm-hmm
when he speaks and they have it they
have a very it's in a can older form of
it it's like a very it's a very stuffy
version it's like a it's like an older
more proper yeah
version of it like you know in a typical
Dragonborn city like it skin the der
conic is gonna have some of the hard
it's gonna be like your conic but like
in a wind tunnel you know what I mean
like a lot of a weird is gonna be
pulled off of it like I mean so I'm
gonna be trying to take cues from
princess princess Georgia here karez
like that's Weiss don't want to look but
it's also like this family business
smile wearing this is none of our family
all right so I don't want to get and you
have what you want yeah I got the kid
Liam you're the one that wins and so
when he when he approaches princess
sorsha and just through through gritted
teeth
he says Indra conic so you don't know if
you don't know they're conic this is not
something that you perceive he says my
word is law this insolence and he points
over toward he points over toward dinar
he says it will be tested in virtues
forge and she and she responds instantly
to complete just completely flat no
emotion she says my word is law
he will have a second and he responds
just as quickly he says my word is law I
will choose the second and he points
over at rosy and says he will have this
useless old woman I do know anything but
I don't let on yeah
just no no no please he points at me
anyone but
but this martial master please don't
know like ogee more eager like not that
there's a there's a few there's a brief
pause and princess sorsha
nods you think you think that that's
that you think that that is the form of
combat that they generally get up to so
do I have a say in this
I say that do I have a say in this they
both they both just turn and look at you
with the same expression which is like
canard
is not cannot perceive yeah any of this
then if it's making sense she puts her
hand like like she looks down underneath
Kathy and like puts her hand down on my
head no no justjust like down for the
high-five oh she knew was coming but she
kneels down exactly you gotta let him
learn okay here give it to her
she gets down real flat on your head and
then sort of scuttles out and then Cappy
that's just him self back on the far
more substantial yeah brow Ridge of
dinar blitz and a place of comfort for
him he's enough toy my god underground
we've seen it so Rosie turns to you and
very um very very haughtily she's like
can someone please explain to me what's
going on and then I say please explain
to us what is going on he says he says
yes but I would be more than happy to
you are going to die tomorrow and you're
going to die tomorrow because your
friend is an idiot I do agree with you
on the second point which friend point
of clarification
[Laughter]
three that it couldn't be yeah
could be anybody really well I've lived
a long and happy life so if I die it's
more than I died tomorrow but I suppose
we'll have to find out he looks through
the gathered throng and he chooses that
the man who lets you in to the house
itself the the the sort of Dragonborn
monk the ascetic with the emblem of
Bahamut on a chain he indicates that
that will be his his second in the fight
I say you're not man enough to do it
yourself I I had a perfectly acceptable
honor battle established the rules were
modified by the princess and I'm down to
them so he's gonna pick a tiny old
happier man again so that's pretty cause
you don't know Bulford princely it's
kind then you can you can you can
recognize the trained like the the
training that this individual has like
these the like sort of servants in these
houses in these fine houses or not these
these rows aren't simple because they're
it's a class thing like these are monks
right these a monk in the sense that I'm
a monk in a sense that you are that you
are a monk like monk in the sense that
they are that they are given over to
marshal practice and they appear to have
they appear to be everywhere at this
tier of society
do I know anything about Mohammed other
than that it's a it's a the god of good
dragons that generally speaking is is
well revered among Dragonborn and many
other peoples okay
what is happening I look at Cathars my
girl I don't I truly hate cities and it
turns out truly I don't get pied I don't
know exactly what they're talking about
but this must have happened before it
seems like there there's some kind of an
impasse there's really is no other like
adjudicating body just resolve this they
don't get what they say well my girls
what is it judicata go back and she goes
sooner she's never mind uh maybe she
goes um I just think these people are
awful um and I would love for us to and
she is no she only heard shimmer scale
say that you were gonna die it's like
well it's like I think we could just
leave dinars right
it's not his it's not his kid we could
just just take off
Rosie's already stretching we have we
got to figure it out I could sneak out
the middle and we're now were conferring
amongst ourselves is that the cloud
leontiev around we just leave in the
middle of the night all this would sit
on a thousand years take it boy hey can
I get a perception check from you Rosie
beasting uh where is it in a 13 total
okay you you are all you can tell for
sure is that you are asked deep in some
super like level 10 social rules okay
you can you know that say you can you
know that things are happening and you
know that you don't understand something
important okay but you're just you're
just aware of how over your head you are
in this alien right zone I had a note
here
thus this social hierarchy that you
described in this room clearly is very
specific and has like mathematical law
governing in the kind of thing that we
would be observing absolutely again like
even the architecture seems to seems to
be moving towards some kind of ideal
right from the chaos of the base even
here in the Third Ward there's a
sophistication it is at this point that
two monks in similar garb to the the one
that led you in the one that was chosen
as the second they arrive from the door
and Prince Jairus scale indicates with
his head toward dinar and rosy and they
come over and attempt to lead you out
okay I think that I will not allow them
to touch me yeah no I'm gonna get away
from that with a quickness okay hmm do I
need a roll but well here yeah you go
ahead and roll okay would you give me a
chromatics just because this will set up
a cool scene 17 okay so the hand is
coming out for the elbow and describe
for me how you do not allow that so up
to this point rosie has actually been
trying to play dumb and once she
realized she was gonna be treated as a
dumb old lady she was like okay fine
that's what you want to believe we're
gonna lean into that but when this
person reaches out for her she's already
gotten into this mindset like okay
combat is gonna happen she started that
mental preparation and as soon as
someone comes near her it's it is like
she shifts just just slightly like it's
a graphical glitch oh yeah like I said
just a little like a little stunt yeah
yeah yeah like they reached out where
they thought her arm was gonna be yeah
exactly
it's like it's Swiper swipes through
right yeah and you register the
confusion
right on their face and in draconic you
hear princess sources say my word is law
My servants will lead them to the
chamber okay and she looks at you with
with authentic care okay so um before we
are taken anywhere I want to look at
princess sorcerer right in the face I do
speak to her in draconic go for it and
say your household staff belongs to
shimmer scale by the way and then I'll
let myself grama so what occurs is that
is that these these monks withdraw at
her statement and this dance continues
in this in this courtyard and then two
of her own retinue live been decked in
dragons scale and these her handmaidens
exactly exactly and they will they will
come out with much more ginger pressure
it starts with a bow and they they reach
a hand and they are directing you
instead of trying to make any kind of
physical contact but they're trying to
get us to so we're going to like stain
cell or something overnight like do we
have this am i familiar with this
practice well yeah that's just their
clan well yeah it could be it could be
similar it's not before a ritual before
a ritual combat it's not too strange for
there to be a period of meditation and
okay all right and care taken we have
still have no idea what's going on yeah
yeah and so I see them leading you away
and walnut is like what are we supposed
are we supposed to come with you I'm
gonna we're under arrest I mean it's
just like okay when I when I when I see
that look for him
rosio just quiet I don't like it then
they go oh yeah yeah yeah do I get them
we can I mean if you ya know
really though do we really come with you
do we though but do we really what do we
do um I think you guys need to leave
this place as soon as you can
and we'll be in touch cuz we need folks
on the outside we have to satisfy we're
in trial by combat start the beginning
yeah for the custody of Crenn are maybe
some sort of there was an honor bound
insult here Dragonborn don't we insult
it so we just kill him then we just go
after him yeah kill right now do me a
huge favor
oh she won't miss him she wasn't super
hot on this kill now I don't understand
it but I do really don't understand
Dragonborn but yeah we'll totally get
out of here and then I look at could
throw signs go oh no I can't wink it has
to be st both eyes and the mouth it's
like Rihanna I'm still I still have my
um my disguise self as a kind of a short
platinum boy I'm still at this point you
know spice caraway sauce no I reapplied
it for this understand canonically we
have decided we have decided that the
entire costume just slows off into a
physical right yes skin that's cool
right yeah but no I'm so I but I'm still
wearing it and I and I don't know how to
work that the armatures of the eyes sigh
I just got wink what yeah I can't tell
us how will work or not will tell you
guys where we're going yeah should be it
will be in touch won't figure out what's
in it totally well I guess I guess we'll
go find somewhere to sit for four hours
yeah get go research blessing spells and
spells to boost brain yeah yeah winning
spells any sort of ways to make people
luckier and then if you want to poison
the prince in all seriousness walnut
if you can figure out a way for us to
get out of the city the most effective
you you you know we've been riding on
top of the cart together for a long time
I feel like you've probably got some
some cartography skill in you so I trust
your sense of direction and if you can
you can help by figuring out where we go
I think that'll be really helpful well
it gives person knowing look and then
just says like okay well we can figure
that out over now so you're you're led
back into the intestines of this
building as I described before the
architecture and then even the inside of
the house establish sharped here as cool
yeah what is it is it is it is that cool
it is that in a way but just like the
just like this layer of town in general
it seems to be designed with siege in
mind so it's difficult to it's difficult
to conceive of directly by the people
who the people who are leading you
through know quite well and virtually
before you know it you are led through a
wall that they have opened and you think
that you are you think that you are
continuing to go north okay your sense
is that you are going north in a passage
that exists below the home okay and then
elevation begins to rise and you are
traveling up cool not cool like rad but
cool like doogal no bat achill obey
chess yeah you know you are you are
going up confusing meshes of stairs
climbing higher and higher until
ultimately you are deposited in a very
strange sort of room to anyone else
but this room is not confusing to you
Rosie because it echoes
the types of architecture that you would
have seen at the monastery Oh
so as you are led through and the door
behind you is closed and the you hear
click inside the mechanism of the door
you are actually looking out over what
must be the hata next higher level of
scala okay so the fourth ward right past
this area is all form so even high up in
this mountain ridge you can see small
monastery buildings and it's just this
massive tract of lush farmland that you
can see at half of this broom is
actually open out its open-air like
basically that wall doesn't exist you
have a you know and not not small like
the room you have is not small imagine a
like a circular floor here their bed
rolls cots other other niceties
but then out there there is no wall at
all you can actually walk out on a kind
of Dyess and look out over that next
level but that led that level seems
entirely populated by this ascetic class
that you keep seeing represented at
different points in this exactly at
different points in this town okay so
like we're being escorted by that the
handmaidens up this way grab princess
with us no no no way you have yours no
kronar okay
there is only you two of her handmaidens
and rosie be stinger okay uh can I see
how far the drop is outside of this
Dyess oh do you think that you would not
survive it okay
it's it is high high high up on a wall
okay
you're basically sort of like almost up
in Akron elation and it's just a flat
wall below that to say nothing of the
fact that this the floor extends a bit
beyond it so that it actually goes out a
bit you'd be dropping into raw space and
then being crushed on the rocks it's not
my first choice well it's I mean listen
I this is onions and dragons like that's
one of the options I need a dragon
that's that's one of the options you
have does it take selections like well
there's no getting out of here
supercells yeah I don't thinks I'm dying
tomorrow I die now as you're looking
around you can see that tract you can
see then another wall beyond that and
then up beyond up beyond that near the
near the actual peak like up basically
I'd like the neck Ridge of this massive
carved dragon you can see what must be
the ultimate expression of whatever
mathematics you see represented on this
third floor so we're moving into curves
and things like that up there it's it's
all solid simple eternal shapes at the
very highest peak 'you can't see anyone
milling around like you don't have that
type of access to it but you can see the
you can see there's strange architecture
sort of poking out above the ridge of
the wall does it seem like that's like
the temple of bahamut's like that it
doesn't it's it's iconography does not
look like that of Bahamut it doesn't
look like a temple either it looks like
a dwelling awesome yeah it is it is
definitely what passes for their highest
form of architecture here if the prince
and princess don't live in there yeah
who does ask them he names who lives
there said bahamut's house they're not
here Hey
you're fired
yuck no it's white so this is what's
interesting about this room to you
rosie is that it just it doesn't have it
makes it assumes that anyone here in
here is a Dragonborn hmm but there's
nothing me sighs no there is some doors
and they exactly like it has a bunch of
it has a bunch of like basically self
care items items that you recognize
instinctively but our our intimate tools
scale scrapers yeah it basically stuff
that people with flesh don't need mm-hmm
in the same way that you know it's like
a Dragonborn probably doesn't need a
razor in the classic sense you can see
just a bunt basically what it is clearly
a standardized set of tiny files and you
can see one of them is a small version
of what denars sword looks like oh it
goes up on a flat flat surface with a
handle at the bottom and then it has
like a tooth
because a little sawtooth design that is
disobey cyclists for tooth care that's
what this is right this is it Percival I
tried to fresh me to you for that that's
for the paronella ms sensitive yeah they
have all that they have all the plastic
but but this is like from a ritual
perspective these are all the things
that you would have for
like culturally it's the same preparing
for a honor battle like this as the same
as preparing for a funeral
yeah just there's just a wedding no
there's just a pragmatism at a very deep
level yeah about like we can save a step
here if we yeah if we manage all this
stuff the problem is that you can't you
can't do any of this yourself
the cleaning and the prepping it's not
something that you can do yeah
it won't work well we probably have to I
guess in the in there are we the the
fights tomorrow yes so we have to spend
the whole night in this room yes I have
to spend the whole night cleaning the
perineum we gotta you gotta get him
looking or splendor yeah you do me I'll
do you perfect okay I start scrubbing
your perineum start braiding your hair
rosy like everyone so now she'll be like
okay what's this one it has to be this
it has to be like this this one's for
the next drill yeah and so I climb up
and I'm like so Scala huh
is this your first time here it's your
first time this far in yeah I haven't
ever been more than passing by here
dragon board are pretty weird it's I
mean maybe just these you seem fine
Thanks is this a normal thing that's all
like ritual I don't even know why we're
a hundred percent why we're fighting for
the minute really okay cuz I don't fight
her yeah should be said something
[Music]
20/20 hindsight okay I feel like we
didn't really have a say I'm not sure
they would have explained it to us yeah
I'd seem like the type to deign to
respond to questions from the likes of
us
okay turn yeah
it's like look like a cat yeah he's just
like yeah it's just you know one don't
worry I won't tell anybody it's way way
down yeah I'm sort of it's a multi-stage
process mm-hmm
got a lot of fold the scaling yeah
obviously the scaling is going
splendidly but there is a bond there is
a pot it looks almost like a tea pot
that is set by the tools that has a kind
of almost like a it's fragrant it has a
good grip paste and it is basically four
scales shining it's just a part of the
fast doesn't say it's a neti pot it's
how you clean your breath sacks and
you're like treat yeah this is great
get some I get some with my hands mmm
shining all the scales down yeah I'm
like doing all the highlight and contour
so you look really good yeah what do we
do when we win well I guess you get to
keep the kid so how this is gonna work
is that about what you want no I don't
wanna kill someone's dad dad I'm gonna
build a monk that's fine
all right yeah they've got lots of those
and the dead isn't it - one - mmm oh did
I interpret that crazy I thought a
second was just like he was picking his
second I did the same thing at first it
was just the two monks having a fight
against him and and him in a dude TV -
no I mean you can always spare his life
hey I think we could we have a lot of
options I know but I'm not gonna I'm
gonna take his his glove and I'm gonna
take it he's gonna take his glove and a
couple of the Rings off his face sure so
he looks younger than you thought but
you don't know how long it's been
since he's actually a bath yeah was
insistence he's actually been taken care
of at all okay
I like gleaming oh sorry this is a rude
question how old are you like looking at
you from details like well things the
whole shadow realm makes things fuzzy 19
at one point wait
nineteen years old seriously yeah yeah
it's just there's there's just this
accumulation and you can dis as a boy
it's a sweet boy and you sending the
stud in the Shadow Realm 19 in
Dragonborn is like it's 22 in human yeah
all that grime really aged you up I
didn't know
so are you even old enough to have an
egg yeah yeah you sure no not really
this is all new to me Wood is Crenn are
your only family like where are your
parents
uh my clan is near here okay we don't
get along with Scotland yeah I picked
that one up uh they don't get along with
you either wait so your clan is near
here jealous the Scotland's obviously
we're better coppers a very good color
if you ask me um do you like if you if
you're here if you're there near York
can we escape and like go to your clan
and keep preneur safe mmm that's not no
I don't think they would be excited
Rosie's not gonna pry about that yeah
they wouldn't be excited about that
okay okay I'll let that one go no I'm
I'm like polishing your eyelids cuz
they're really skate like surprisingly
scary
you found a new type of scale yeah in
there so this is this is exactly how
it's supposed to go
thanks again you can't it's not
something that you can't do it for
yourself yeah and have it be correct and
I wouldn't say that what I'm doing is
necessarily correct but it's the darn
best thank you oh yeah yeah you're
you're putting it in I thought a lot of
things in my life but I've never
polished a Dragonborn before tonight
no you know one off the bucket list yep
now happy tomorrow okay the second the
second part of the preparation is
there's basically almost like a there's
like a family crest almost like a family
words that is supposed to be recited but
it needs to be recited over you you know
them but Rosie does not know them
so so it's a it's a it's a ritual that
is said to be a shield yes when recited
or over me over you
I would I would hold this I would return
the favor I'm not kidding I would like
try to after being cleaned like try to
wash your hands and feet for you and
braid your hair and put some of the
shine yeah off on me doesn't look right
as weird irritating like diatomaceous
earth it's like you bleed touching it's
rough friends I appreciate it anyway so
you say you've like you you've like
pulled the hair like the hairs out of
the blade like so big you have sisters
but don't really deal with hair they're
Dragonborn yeah
yeah but I've seen it
give it a good a shot it's like a knot
like a nut I Pat it I'm like I think
we're going in war we're in this
together we're going to war together
that's right yeah and then I would say
the Klan speech is this the that's
called yeah it doesn't need to be that
doesn't need to recite it okay the body
is a tomb we carry with us what
sweetness then to leave it behind
okay so I have to say this yes okay yes
so I stand on your shoulders
yeah so I say that over you and you have
to say it over me okay
so I say like a lay flat yeah yeah don't
stand on your tummy just yell it Wow you
have to cough it into my mouth the body
is a tomb what sweetness then to leave
it behind
I'm sorry let me do okay so I will I'll
be I'll be normal
it's like you know you're all clean so I
don't let you lay on the floor I'm like
no no I'm not doing this again make you
lay down and I say the body is a tomb we
carry with us what sweetness then to
leave it behind and I'm gonna I touch
you on the heart and on the head which
is not part of your ritual but it's it's
something that that I've done too many
many sad babies in my life to calm them
down so it's this like soothing thing
and I don't have any magic necessarily
to imbue to you but whatever whatever
grandmotherly blessings that I am able
to do alright now the last part of the
preparation is that you need to practice
you me waiting you need to practice
combat should have done it first we're
gonna get all sweaty dirty right now you
guys adds to it you got tomorrow buddy
I mean you have you know the sweat
dragon
this is give this is clearly something
that he wants to get to quickly mmm on
the morrow
so after this after the the litany is is
recited you hear the door open again and
you see two of sources handmaidens they
enter with a tray of food then they they
back out still looking down and they
close the door
yeah and so the Sun is the Sun is
setting outside this there's a breeze
starting to come in off at the top of
the mountain yeah and you can see the
monks outside preparing for the end of
the day you can see you can see them
carrying bells around through the
through the fields on that higher level
I like I like the sound of this because
it brings me back to the parts of my
time at the monastery that were my
favorite yeah which is the evening well
the ritual right everybody knows what to
do right that's nice yep I love that so
I'd go out before we start our practice
fighting and go out on the dais and I'm
watched these these monks and it sounds
like they serve Bahamut which is a good
God and that it would be something that
I've impressed with right like this this
whole venture is is crazy oh yeah yeah
absolutely organization of the sides
right it is and what's more is that it's
very high up I mean it's higher even
than some of the noble housing that this
that life and that approach to life is
is considered right in there you know
like I say in the way that they are
describing what they think is real and
what is important that's very near the
top the religion
the religious caste oh yeah yeah when we
look out the windows can we see the
sword mountains can I see yeah yeah out
along the sides but this what's
interesting about this this room is it
actually will not let you look towards
where I'm no you can't you can't see you
can't see down that road but also you
can't see the lower levels that you have
been in you can't see that first second
or third levels like this is a place
that is meant to orient the soul toward
ya the summit so we're both looking out
this big open air faint listen to these
bells and rosy turns to dinar and says
what do you think happens when you die
okay we're not that time oh geez
ya know what they can't figure it out
see you're the dragon sink
in Dungeons and Dragons
yeah what a flow man oh you're the
dungeon yeah is he by the the thing that
you just uttered huh yeah yeah yeah no
he does like so you saw the name of that
thing was the scale scales of VARs
maelys the scales of VARs MELAS is the
name of the little poem and he recited
yeah so that's his Clanton's god that's
his Bahamut oh god I got it okay so I
guess he would believe like in death
they would serve a pledge I know I'm
trying to think I woulda thought about
what he would like their how they viewed
the afterlife
I don't know how no normal I'm asking
table talking a little bit here no other
ones you the average afterlife cuz they
all pledged in service to a god right so
what did a normal paladin think exactly
when they die the the systems like the
meta systems that describe that have to
do with you know it's not dissimilar
from what many people in that regular
world believe that there are upper
regions
yeah of our universe and people dwell
there
if they've led good line yeah and they
have various versions of that some of
them would prefer to go to a lower place
you know but basically the idea is that
you'll spend eternity in this service in
reward yeah I mean and so what we what
you have to think about for dinar is
think about VARs maelys you think about
what it would mean to serve and then
think about you know try to help us
understand what it would mean to him
because there's a there's a back stop
here in dinars psychology well it's also
just a weird thought experiment to be
like there you're already in service to
a God that you see right like so it's
like what's to live in existential
service if you're already in service in
real life you can meet the the God in
person shake their hands when I'm still
alive so death is just more the same so
it's like what would be the mode of
being beyond life factor I feel like
this is a wonderful thing for dinar to
stay in character
yes exactly no I mean like like let's
just go whole hi I think it's - what he
says live forever
right just doing that education born
legs like just like dangling over the
edge of this thing yeah looking out at
these monks who spend all day thinking
about this they've got good answers for
this I guarantee it yeah yeah no I think
that's what he would say like he would
hadn't really thought about it like I
don't know a life is service to a God
already so maybe more in the same
what's your God like he's great
tell me more he's very handsome handsome
got very nice cool like that I never met
him really but he's supposed to be great
our paladin's they traditionally
paladins we their God right
is that true I don't know what made you
want to become a paladin it's it's not a
thing you get to choose in my clan
really at my station yeah all all the
royal family is paladin's or
called it oh okay royal family no I'm
royal yeah yeah yeah pretty well yes
yeah
royal adjacent I see so your family is
from a place near here and they're all
paladins
and they are royalty are they royalty
the way that sorcerer and skimmer set
skimmers gale shimmer scale all right no
I don't know what's going on here
nothing like my clan okay and they're
pretty straightforward setup I see I
know there's competing houses there's a
I read this book called Game of Thrones
getting that vibe here should read it
it's good but I'm getting this weird
rosy weird competing rosy nods and then
she puts the fourth wall back up yeah
dragons is called game of regular old
chairs yeah they're just plain old chair
game so you don't seem nervous about
tomorrow at all hi guys seems pushover I
could have taken them in the bar I'm not
too worried about it we should talk
about tactics sure what are you do you
want to me we could fastball special you
gotta talk about team up moves yeah yeah
talk about combos should we just
like should we just um say like Rosie
and Denard talk about combos so that we
don't we could come let's hopefully
we'll get a break before the fight Rosie
and dinner I talk about combos yeah you
come up with some really good combos
pretzels filled with cheese please talk
late into the night and Rosie
occasionally sprinkles in a question
about denars past that he avoids dinner
sprinkles and questions about Rosie
grandmother well you're gonna have to be
more specific than that
what what brought you to this place this
place in particular yeah what brings you
to Scotland come here often and Rosie
Rosie just chuckles and she looks out
again
at these monks and the Setting Sun and
she looks the monastery for a long time
and and she says there are things that
you don't want to remember I think that
you probably have some of those too yeah
Shadow Realm stuff I'm really sorry I've
never really apologized to you both that
I did not understand what that was going
on tail how many can't we ever seena run
in a lot of your kids how many kids do
you have
ah well biologically um I have a fair a
fair shake a lot of kids out there but
it's the it's the kids that aren't
related to me that really take up them
the vast majority of the be singer clan
I've I've been in Rosie pauses here and
she thinks about it she do it she she
wants to tell you but but not revealed
too much I've been in situations some of
which I've caused and some of which I
haven't where there were orphans left
behind and so I take it upon myself to
use my resources to keep them safe and
as a result they join my family and so
because of that there are a lot of bee
stingers out there and they're not
they're not all my blood but they're my
family and she looks at you specifically
when she says that and she's like not
all family is blood related just
something something I want you to know
and then deny things of Crenn are
when you say that break the tension
sneaky that you use I mean sparring is
one of the things you have to do you do
want to lead into this far into this
part was like in the middle of the
tender yeah let's try yeah good luck
yeah I imagined she would flip out of
the way take me out of the window well
we have a very easy way of determining
whether or not you can hit a person go
ahead alright sure you know what yeah in
the middle of our tender
character-building moment right at the
end yeah how dinar is that tomorrow's
you can get it and then assuming I fall
asleep mid attack is the only way to
make it more dinner all right
no like anything for it's a sneak attack
three I'm not really good see it's just
it is the most like right in the middle
of this tender thing like it is them
yellow sneak attack - yeah I yell at
first what three seconds before I do it
goes across the valley exactly and then
just this like salami just like a
slow-motion like 120 frames per second
salami just like moves into your
awareness and I grab it and I put it
around you you're able to transform it
into a hug that's other things the
grandmother skill yeah exactly it's the
best that's true alchemy yeah right
that's grandma Nancy for real they're in
so practice the Sun is setting outside
there's room to sleep in here the food
has been provided there as soon as
interactions with this food probably
yeah I was trying swallow
it's like I feel like I feel a curiosity
about what walnut and customers are up
to
oh no that's happening okay don't worry
Stax I'm wrapping up your sing yeah
yeah yeah we I think we eat Rosa tries
to keep it light don't want to overfill
yeah yeah all kinds of stuff you got
Martin nuts man the Dragonborn so am I
just doing what I'm describing the taint
brushes I'm also describing the food as
well exactly so I'm gonna get a hold of
our merchandise manager paintbrush and I
mean we've already we're already looking
into a documentary seal let's just keep
it moving you know you know documents
are sea lions but away you go
good documents a sea lion you invest now
I'm happy about it so yeah yeah weird if
we're talking about let's go down the
list
it's something like a like a gecko
wrapped in like a phyllo dough so it's
flaky its crisp delicious gecko inside
this is oh yeah this is kept locked
it's like a whole gecko with like legs
oh yeah no no it looks like a gecko that
is wearing clothing made out of a
snowsuit shadow exactly okay the arm is
tail head and then it's just yeah I'm
hungry though is this like normal
Dragonborn food is this you you think
you think jalapeno poppers or Jess this
is regional yeah really you just need
the lizard this yeah this is a different
take on it but yeah do you eat the head
yeah usually it's yeah it has to be a
three bites alright three bites
tiny this is giant you know it's like a
baby yeah it's like half food half test
you know you gotta get it down in three
bites you would Rosie gets it done in
three bites
no and then it just like and but then
like the job closes with a squeak like a
stove door uh-huh yeah so you guys are
you guys are prepped back at the villa
of Princess sorsha as after your friends
are led away there's a confused Crenn
are there's basically sort of standing
like on the edge just like begin the
Nimbus of her mother not keeping a
certain distance away from Prince
shimmer scale but but you can but you
can tell if I can get perception checks
from my people yeah no no no yes he has
Locati is it really 28 i don't
everything and all i have plus then
because I did my background my class
everything to have high perception yeah
but that's this is exactly I get this is
great this all the time so it worked out
great I now what if I had done all that
so you can like table talk yeah yeah
look at a blood pool and you're like I
could see the DNA so you can see you
hear them referring to Jess and
continually as they when their attention
is directed toward the monk that shimmer
scale is chosen as his second and you
can see the sheer scale is sort of
speaking under his breath to Jess and
adjacent is at his full height just
nodding every five or six seconds just
taking it in but you can see you can see
is so sheer scale is like so like
speaking out of the side of his mouth
like looking up and like he has his head
down in a sort of conspiratorial way and
then you see you see Jason lock eyes
with sorsha and it is the most subtle
like molecular level nod of
Understanding between the two of them
like it is it is you would need like a
you would need like it's like a spectrum
analysis like a 28 yeah yeah you would
have to do it it's the sort of thing
where you would have to build your
entire character around Scala it was a
CSI Scala type technology so so you you
are able so in the in this like
sophisticated social tapestry like you
just detect this I can see it but I
don't understand this no you yeah you
it's like you just know that it's there
and you know where all the pieces are
and you can see them moving and it's
hard for you to score each of the
individual pieces but you're aware of
the entire motion of the system but
didn't just like like like a like a drop
of lemon juice like there's just this
sense that cuts through all of that and
you just see this connection between the
two of them so I just kind of eyeball
okay there's and give them a nudge and
then went to my head here yeah they're
talking all the time oh no I'm saying
that's what this guy's feeling talking
wait there probably is going over what
they're gonna do tomorrow wheezes out
loud just quietly why did you say
like I'm blind I was trying to be subtle
she's anyway um I'll talk about that a
table talk um she goes something's going
on with shimmer scales second and
Princess sorsha she goes I'll be damned
if I know what it is and I don't but
they something is going on with them I'm
wearing a lover's spat well not
immediately goes well I didn't think
it's gonna be that and she goes look at
them do you think that that's what it is
I don't think so I'm just tossing it out
there it's not that many interactions
between two people I might be one of
them yeah well no it's just weird that
coming from him she's just like oh I
didn't think he did that what I heard it
somewhere right I read about it in a
book and when I go I was thinking that
maybe they're gonna try and fix the
fight yeah yeah that doesn't surprise me
that much I'm looking over at I want to
see what's between us and shimmer scale
and the aesthetic because I what I'd
love to be able to do is tell the guy T
to to creep up and give me a little it
so I can listen in there he send his
Saito and senses over there does look I
have years like it's nice yeah yeah it
can be it can be the snake knows here
that we all know about this whole body
is resonant I think that's fine resonate
evil I'm not saying it's like and
because yeah it's painful you know it's
worth taking a second yeah yeah anything
you need to like apply to him so that
I'm not like but he hears all and sees
all it's like nah
the senses of a snake so he could hear
then and you'd pick up that vibration
yeah I threw that wood Parsa yeah yeah I
just think he's a weird little guy yeah
so what you're gonna do is like
basically like I say yes your ear you
exist within the wheels of this massive
social clock right that's winding in
here and so you let so you let Locati go
right and then under underneath here
underneath your wrap the two pinned the
two pinpricks of light right but show
through and so you seal Agati that's
just observing I'd cover it up yeah yeah
poor boy yeah ligarius is slinking along
the ground
and then in your senses Livadia is this
is over there looking like looking up
getting ready to pick up this vital
information yeah um and then lagari is
immediately seized whoa and you can see
Lagasse looking at Crenn are I'm seeing
yeah I'm seeing this as I am looking at
him look I gotta has been pounced on oh
no
Byron are like Hercules my serpent again
hey you little goyim what you doing what
are you working on when I speak through
the gaudy that is the voice it's like
one of those microphones
Oh what are you making her think of this
snake yeah okay it's not creepy yeah I
was just fortunate looking for a mouse
or something you might blame me back
[Laughter]
Hey she she she babbles back it's a it's
it's like the sound is like what a
person would say like the tone and
everything like the feel of it is right
mmm but it's not any language mm-hmm
it's just like she thinks that she's
having a real conversation with this so
she puts she takes Locati and puts the
Gatti up on her shoulders mm-hmm
and then just toddles off into the brush
it's like you toddle toddle toddle then
it's like you see like your face is like
and then like you can't feel it
exactly but you can feel like the sense
of leaves and like crunching leaves and
seeing and hearing it is like a very
strong like VR like I am she is here in
this you know she has retreated to these
realms many times and you can see that
she keeps things here mm-hmm
she is just like a fairy isn't it neat
she's what we're gonna start she's gonna
do she's got 20 yeah so I'm gonna look
at her so no girl like you know what you
gotta mind me because I actually can't
hear you well my sister yeah so I guess
you know what I'm gonna go get this one
right I like dropping over towards the
bush but it's like so unceremonious when
she starts being like just like digging
through the bushes where Crenn are was
and she's like just kind of slows it
down a little more it was like this and
then like almost like she's like hunting
something oh oh yeah it's like she
starts to like the breath pattern is
like that of the wolf like yes yeah
lagari starts saying like well wouldn't
you got in here wouldn't you keep it
over here whoa
I actually like she locks onto it and
she's very very slowly like parts the
bush looking for there's all kinds of
stuff oh boy in here what I see um
there's a few skaaland coins various
tails eyes no there's a like a couple
gold coins three silver like just the
minting 's have the gold coins actually
have variably princess sorsha or prince
shimmer scale like on the coins
themselves in the pressing there's also
there's something else that you see
Percival first of all for real Percival
is here in the bush but there is also
something that it's like again that's
all this city money and you just like
yep yep okay city money great and then
it looks like there is another coin okay
but you don't think it's currency
because it is actually attached to a
chain on the coin it is basically around
the bottom it's just this is the massive
it's a dark pressed coin and there is a
massive body with five heads what the
hell
erupting from it all along the top oh
okay um well I'm gonna take that they're
just pocket water back pocket what that
is I look at it and I go seems like
something could throw us with life it's
like when you're shopping I say you got
something for dinner
was what is Craig one know nothing of
the keyring variety catering no keys you
don't see any keys okay
too easy I tried but no no she she know
she's sharing oh oh so I have to give
her something no no she's like she's
like sitting down in here like this is
her oh yeah place in she where she has
this new she has this new friend sort of
like a she's wearing like this necklace
and then there's like a new new friend
is like he has like crawled into her
please
it's like um it's parallel play she's
playing yeah
well it's like it's like it's just a
there's just an exchange what do you get
[Music]
for a snake yes oh you know what she has
she has something that she posted she
pulls something out and it is a small
very crudely crafted wouldn't flute um
and she oh yeah this is she has a parent
let me tell you she looks at Crenn art
and then she really very obviously blows
into it and she makes a trill and it
sounds like it sounds like a bird it
overdone yeah soon as you're holding
like this she starts to hold her hands
like against against the nothing yeah
right so she takes it she's gonna hold
it the way that you give it to her she
has to turn it around and then she just
starts to like just tweet away inside
this well inside this bush pretty much
yeah I checked me away okay anyway so at
this point well not knows enough yeah
you got some info should we it's true
she's got an empire is gonna say she
knows enough about children to know that
you don't just like take away a thing
that's like a toy she's playing with
right now like Lou gaw t while she's
playing that walnuts gonna just try and
like lead her back over two good thrusts
to get the think so
just gonna see if she can lead her out
of the bushes mm-hmm like okay we're
going this right now sure it's it's
slow-going yeah there's a lot of
resistance up front by the interest in
the interest in the flute let me try to
speed the process I will MIT person
calls and she may be like whoa no friend
I'll leave yet but as she's making the
sound like I'm like coiling fancifully
like it's making me dance a little bit
in the grass hopefully I would delight
her rather than like all my things leave
that's good that's great
yeah so legardie legaia is drawing these
incredible shapes yeah thank you exactly
and kronar is tweeting away on the flute
and then legardie flies through the air
at the end of a boot oh oh no I was
throw up because a vision is suddenly
like Princess Prince shimmer skill of
course snaps his fingers and then you
see this process of extrication between
the two groups oh and he leaves out the
way that he came having satisfied
himself presumably with his strategy
session with his second well that makes
a rude gesture as he leaves
what is the gesture yeah I seen it I was
doing okay can I come on back to my
ticket there's his body she pieces yeah
he's he's he's draped in the manner of
it like this versus one part of this
topiary that looks like it's it's
festooned for some dark festival because
it has this sort of like crystal serpent
yeah sort of stand-alone like Garland
CIN and he's he's chirping angrily after
after prince chamber skill and I are
throwing golf clubs shoes you could call
the you have to call it our different to
call the skull and Fire Department they
set the tree on fire where the breath
weapon is so how do you want to how do
you want to manage this thing as
Princess sorsha says that it's just you
are of course welcome to stay in my home
in safety okay
well or you can or you can go where you
came and I'll and I can invite you back
up to the two virtues Forge tomorrow I
have I have a private box you can use to
observe sure that sounds great
um why don't we uh well we'll get out of
your hair yeah I returned my senses back
because I can actually hear at the
distance and what she said for most of
it yeah and you just hear your hair it
is it is lovely is what I say assuming
that's what was a good look well I guess
we'll we'll be at we'll be out of your
hair um well I guess can I be so bold as
to ask you one question
you can ask as many as you like I'll
answer those I deem fit and she goes she
goes why why is shimmer scale fighting
Denar it's to me it seems it shouldn't
be a question that's that's his daughter
what I don't understand where our dinar
enters into this
I'd like to say that prints shimmer
scale is a sophisticated complicated man
I can't he he has not made the
connection that he perceives as his
right with Crenn R which I call a
blessing well just says something
reassuring not really reassuring to her
in her mind and she says she says well
at least she has her mother she's just
kind of stares at the ground she goes
okay well guess it will be a just
heading on heading on down the road
thanks for all the information so your
door at the closet no but she's gonna
commit she would stay there all night
yeah yeah transom in here into your
weasel form door shuts for half an hour
let's do it Kali no first time weasel
longtime listener now let's go so you
you are led out to the front of the
Zillah I apologize you're like at that
moment I say your highness I apologize
for messaging you directly I didn't know
we were I didn't realized that it wasn't
your intent to block us from coming but
shimmer skills
you're trying people pologize but like
there's some nicety like there's some
part of the tumbler it's like you didn't
like turn it right a couple times before
yeah I didn't lock the fullness of it
exactly she doesn't respond she just
sort of tilts her head and then you're
bowing as you leave already
exactly exactly for her to confirm
there's no there's no way to extricate
yourself from this thing your card is
gone my cart is gone my cart is gone my
horse you're grown as well
what same card yeah wait is our horse
guy yes
is anything left from the cart no this
is where we left
spice boy sit there at the fret board
for ffedith lord I would like I want to
go up to that of Fe tid I'm banging on
the door already sick brain seriously
good I want to bang on the door bang on
the door that's where it was boarded it
was boarded at that place yeah let's go
I'm Rob game just you're gonna leave
this second Ward oh yeah you're gonna
leave the Third Ward back down through
the gate
she said she'd let us back in well back
back to your back to her house oh I
thought she was saying I thought the
princess was saying she would return us
so I'm assuming we're going to watch
this combat yes absolutely
because I thought that we had walked out
of the word already and that we were at
no no you're not yes your cart is gone
from the front of the place okay well
then I'm gonna leave a weird cart in the
front of this place
they might probably hear it wouldn't fit
in this place it's so fancy look I made
it here too so I like it less and less
thought about who likes it the least
okay we can both dislike we do
absolutely we do and she goes okay well
I guess I gotta find this cart the door
in front of the the villa opens and you
see Jessen the Dragonborn that lets you
in originally he says
will you be needing a place to stay well
my goes well I had a perfectly good
place to stay in my cart so it seems yes
I'll make the preparations great thank
you
I mean thanks he seems nice yeah see he
he stands he stands further back he
speaks to a few people softly inside and
people come out and then draw you in to
the maze like structure and it seems
like you're going exactly the same way
that you did before but this time you
end up in a pair of well-appointed rooms
instead of an outdoor plaza well like
this this is nice uh and she goes um no
separate rooms I was with a crane yes
she goes she goes no separate rooms
one's fine they just put your arm around
cuz oh yeah oh jeez oh my goodness
are we scary yes but it is so rigid it's
like the ultimate hover hand we are
lovers I have known the carnal touch
apart from her show canceled merrily
rafflesia this is our break consider
seven subs to help us perform these
feats it is October 4 you're a treatment
yes it's summer there's a real thing
subs are red thank you so much don't go
anywhere we'll be right back hello when
last we saw our heroes they had recently
found an incredible place to sleep with
great rates at the Villa of Princess
sorsha
any rate that's 50% of the party the
other half of the party is in a very
different type of accommodation
overlooking a tract of mystically
beautiful farmland after an evening of
marshal practice and intimate ritual hmm
designed to prepare the scion of the
Blitzen clan for combat in the faraway
Dragonborn enclave of scala now where do
we want to go first what do you what do
you like what ause go back
nobody those guys we did not do anything
we were supposed to do
here's wonder get out of here we'll do
it this way we'll do it this way so when
you wake in the morning
obviously you have your choice of pastry
wrapped lizard bites
there's there's there is no shortage and
it's like when I was when I went to
Germany once no matter what I ordered on
the menu it was always sausages and
sauerkraut like it I don't know this is
not a problem for me like for me this is
a huge plus like this is what I want
we are worse oh but it was actually
that's the thing and so what happened
business is like that it's like no
matter what it is like even if you think
you've found something that isn't a
lizard in dough it's a dough lizard it
still is like the deep level there's
still some dough but it's been out under
the heat lamps for a while so it's like
cold alone well no this is the worst
it's like really like the limbs are
super hot imagine that imagine like a
crushed velvet dress full of beef juice
that you have to wring out and that's
George RR Martin's prose goes well have
a couple if you want to um or take some
with you
you are you're brought in the morning
you do not see like ladies sorsha
oh your cart or Crenn are but a mixture
of her handmaidens and these monks of
bahtman bring you out and you know the
cart had driven by this area before this
was the area that had a sign on it the
said virtuous Forge
so imagine if you will a like a city
square bustling built into the very
walls are the shop stalls executed to a
very high degree it's all that's a very
artisanal it's just in here Jason Jason
is not with this this group one presumes
he is preparing himself for today's
rigors indeed indeed
but this virtuous Forge has been given
over to this other purpose and as you
were you are led out to virtuous forage
and then you walk up a set of stairs
it's almost like a top of the atop these
shops that are built into the walls
there are stairs that go up and around
and these stairs go up into like a
honeycomb structure of rooms that Sun
rooms and things like that that they
must serve a recreational purpose the
rest of the time but when virtues forage
is being leveraged for its true purpose
they have this as well something that
you have noticed you sort of clinging to
the edges clinging to the eaves of
things are these tiny like imps like
these tiny silver shiny platinum amps
yeah absolutely
that was a warrant are um are you a
sling no that's so this is the opposite
of a womp-womp-womp this is yeah this is
a win/win
if you really want
to add your bonus no actually I don't so
it's a 1 so I look at that and I go
what's up with all the Dragonborn yeah
yeah it's a lot of them somewhere small
this is a cities let me try and look
it's not much better but before the ten
can I look at any do I notice them yeah
yeah you think that signal Agati is like
yeah oh yeah he's he's chirping at them
and they are just they're just looking
at him dispassionately almost like
little gargoyles or imps really well
they live well you know there's like an
ozone smell in the air around them and
so it's like as you're being as you're
being led up these stairs to a private
box they're like yeah yeah big and
they're hanging on to the edges of
things and they're just looking around
they're always keeping their eyes on
their surroundings they seem to be
observing everything sewing so they are
alive quite I thought there are like
statues no no they look they look like a
living weird little statue and they
smell it goes them they do and stone
exactly so inside the oh you think about
the tactical scenario here yes so inside
the box itself is a dish like a massive
pool of clear still water okay there's a
massive pool of crisps or water right
near us no no it's it's inside inside
inside the box itself you can easily
look out and see anything that's
occurring out in our virtuous gorgeous
so but the box also includes this pool
as well and then there's a walkway
behind the like behind the box itself in
that in the doorway that goes out to a
few other hallways that lead to other
boxes in this sort of mesh no do I see
other boxes have poles or definitely
they when you look in the Front's of
these some people are some people are
looking into their pools some people
have brought their children up there
they're like splashing in them the
Dragonborn
bottle service yeah sorry I just look at
the fool
I see anything it's just a fool whatever
II now and then you do see something you
see what looks to be like a perspective
like high up perched on the edges and
then as things as things are moving um
the pool is sort of switching between
these different perspectives everyone
camera one camera camera camera D yeah
exactly
okay methods so okay so you were led up
there there are there are decanters of
spirits and wine I know he's gone for
exactly this this there's no shortage
early so you are brought down through
you know walking down through this this
maze like corridors that dead now you
can there very very clearly you know
inside the physical structure of the
walls that separate each of these
districts these passages must go on for
miles so you are you are led quite a
long ways so long that they offer you
water at a point during the middle of it
and you are brought out into what looks
like a almost like a dead end alley not
in virtues forge proper but in an
enclosed corner space in the city and
your handlers tell you that you will
recognize wait here until you hear the
signal okay all right so we get a moment
to breathe the area yeah okay
shall we yeah I definitely want to I'm
gonna do it prepare yourself this is the
time well so I said this during the
break it was this against the rules I
would I have any knowledge that it's
against the rules to do a fine steed and
right in on that on my steed I have yet
to use yet yes whatever feels feels
right time to pose right yeah very
familiar fine Steve yeah I'm familiar
with fine steed I'm gonna find my my my
steed familiar he's pretty strong would
you I like you I like you so much
alright grace us with that what if that
card says about fine steed oh yeah yeah
it's just like just like it says on the
tin find your inner speed yeah he
summons a spirit that assumes the form
of an unusually intelligent strong and
loyal steed creating a long lasting bond
with it appearing and unoccupied space
within range the steed takes on a form
that you choose such as a warhorse pony
camel elk or Mastiff I'm choosing a
where reindeer now what is a where
reindeer tiring dear maybe okay a diary
near doctor big-ass reindeer reindeer
okay because we're reindeers like
reindeer it's a person but except the
home oh yeah that's true no here's that
here's the vital part you have to choose
its form a celestial Fey or fiend that's
that's something that's something that
you have to determine about the creature
cuz it's not a normal creature it's yeah
it's just here at shade looks like one
yeah it's a Patronus right so yeah I
don't want to fiend what's a fake fake
fairy yes exactly so this would be this
would be the sort of so untamed like
like natural yeah yeah exactly at a
range this for a second yes because
paladin's can hurt
like especially evil things so fiend out
the door you I ride that around but not
like what's where's Celeste you'll fall
on that so I saw steel in these in this
context yeah so let's deal is what
you're talking about
okay we're talking about upper planar
you know angelic it's that so if you
want that elk that like
emerges from that cops twinklin you know
they may want an okay oh yeah cool yeah
yeah yeah this is what I'm talking about
like a celestial is on brand for you
thinking like that one episode of
Inuyasha yeah what they had the one but
they'll never see the Alpha one with the
big reindeer fur stuff it's a reindeer
yeah first of all all right yeah so I
want to make him okay
I don't know the stats on his attack I
know they do get an attack it's not in
the book I will negotiate it for you
okay cool cool we describe to me what I
see when you summon this this steed oh
yeah exactly so understand this is a
ritual it takes you to do this so I want
you to I want you to tell me about this
I go full alchemist summoning circle
full metal alchemist together hit the
ground make a circle a slow circle that
goes around me chant in tongues and what
I make is a dire reindeer a big majestic
meaty sharp antlers strong razor sharp
beak a beak wings fire laser ball eyes
and then his name is Clark more Clark
more the reindeer and he is the Patronus
like in appearance okay kind of like
whiskey if see stars in him sort of
thing because he's celestial it doesn't
just look like a reindeer you look like
an awesome reindeer this would cost 25
bucks in your craft you
storage you would get from historic for
sure so while you are doing your ritual
by the way rosie has removed her shawl
whoa and she has nice I know and she's
jacked um but she's she is fastening it
into like a circular shape she's she is
tied it into a shade a loop a loop yep
and it's tied securely and as soon as
Clark more appears roses like whoa well
didn't know you had that in you were you
to keep in that guy it was after we made
the cakes I just fell to me geez way to
bury the lead how I never had been
married 10 min is the intention I know
are usually like battle gets sprung on
us
exactly exactly right please we're gonna
keep going yeah and so I go up to you
dinar and I ask you to bend down I put
the loop around your neck like a sash
and you look pretty resplendent even
more so than before is just like this
this it actually has kind of a cool
effect and I say don't mess this up I
hop in and say yes so so I get on the
stage and you're wearing you in a
manufactured BabyBjorn yeah so she's
placed the loop on you but there is a
moment obviously this is for her purpose
yeah but this is a father's garb like
this this loop is how a father would
ride into battle as they're doing this
you can see all of this I go in the in
the screen pool you can see you you can
see you can see your friends and then
there's like a huge deer like a elk said
it's a diary anger but it's a reindeer
yeah exactly and then you see Rosie
fashion this bjorn and then give it to
him and then now she's gonna ride with
him
I'm in this thing very hot
yeah I'm considering that I don't know
them as well as I don't think genuinely
like I like the person I go are you
seeing this and then I grab like a D
[Laughter]
I think mimics what's going on here yeah
no idea what nobody but it's switching
but it's switches from that perspective
to shimmer scale and Jessen have a
question about that
yeah how'd you how well can I see them
quite well um you do some stream sniping
for us I want yeah your stream snipe oh
nice oh I'm sorry go ahead
no no I was gonna say related question
it's a place I can see can I misty step
to it ah the distance might not work I
don't think the distance is right and
also I feel like that would be really
dangerous just speaking as your dungeon
master it sure Justin wearing the same
clothes as yesterday no he's not
is he wearing his medallion it is a
different medallion in fact you can see
the chain but the symbol itself is
tucked into the shirt yeah got it yeah
okay yeah cool um so I think that's it
for us you can but you can see the two
of them so they're starting out they've
taken their ten minutes to prepare and
they're moving out they're moving out as
well something you can notice as I said
before when you were riding through this
this the Third Ward is essentially a
kind of art that you can live in there's
the reliefs on the walls of great
dragons Taconic shapes motifs wings
statuary but no but this is you can see
as they walk through they are moving
through this place and this place has a
purpose so you can see that that shimmer
scale takes a step and you can see this
is a hesitation on his part momentarily
and you can see that you know on the on
the wall is a great dragon locked in
battle
and as he steps you can see the claw on
the wall swipe back what through the
alleyway and he just a just misses him
he ducks underneath it what does he how
does he look
does he look like no problem or is he
frustrated Oh interesting
I keep watching subscribe exactly so so
you you see you see much as I just
described you are now you have entered a
arena a city that has been transformed
into a a crucible to test people against
one another you can see these tiny
creatures just observing you with
glowing eyes they seem to be positioned
in many high places
looking down sort of impassively and
they're there their heads just they
track you perfectly like they're not
flitting about they are completely
locked onto individuals
so are as this this is not a big open
arena this is how no existen you are you
are like in you are in a sitting or like
in a little mock like the fake city town
square
yeah yeah the Town Square is over here
you are in an alley near there okay I
never thought it was like an alley
before we got no big arena okay
yeah virtuous Forge is that statue that
was outside the princess's villa with
the two figures shaking hands yeah
gotcha
uh-huh well I have ones in these
buildings left and right some item left
in Somalia yeah so so Yuri read about
Clark more any one of your friend is in
the rap baby you aren't facing out ready
to punch kick mm-hmm
I got toothbrush dragging it the little
the little teeth down so I'm like
carving this giant sentry yes arc Morse
massive yeah Dyer hooves
are just clacking against the cobbles
there's also this this scrape dragging
through but it's like it's communicating
in some some code as it like drags and
then like pings off of stones it's like
a four kind of place musicals think like
echoing through the intimidation tactic
yeah Rosie likes it yeah she's you I
don't think she's talking to you when
but she realizes like as it's going
through she's like she's kind of scared
of it she's like it's pretty good hey I
need I need the perception checks from
us for my sweet sweet players oh wait oh
no not you guys oh sweet flight recipe
you have opportunities 11 - all right
no three sorry I'm even on perception
okay okay so you you have absolutely
I mean you you've got it everything
ready to go here you got the montage
yeah
that's occurred the training montage has
happened you've got this great dear kind
of all our intro yeah oh yeah you bar
intro no it's like a towel with my horn
no no it's like it's like it's kick-ass
in that way like like in quotes like
like that youtuber intro yeah like it's
kept like the ak-47 it's going Katrina
here oh this is the the faze clan
right yeah you're executing everything
exactly right and then underneath you
can you can feel Clark Morris right hoof
descend a little bit farther than it
should what is it boy
and you can see immediately that the art
on the walls to your right springs to
life you see you see dragons in the in
the heat of battle and then one of the
claws that is currently locked around
you know a mortal foe swipes through hmm
understand three swipes through the DM
screen destroying the dungeon master
screen no ifs swipes it swipes bad
basically directly like mid-level right
through the alley mmm so we're looking
for those those acrobatics who keeps
paintings alley checks freaks is it I
might even though yeah yeah you have to
okay
lots of twenty really only one that's
gonna die well and this is Clark more
have acrobatics I got it hey 10-1 that's
perfectly okay for some looks like womp
womp womp Bom what daddy just rolled
womp-womp-womp you liar shadow council
mayor lyrics please you your servant
Jared cave organs has delivered you a
boon now if you are a subscriber you get
this cool box from Elderwood Academy and
we'll all sign it during Table Talk if
not you get a gift certificate also very
cool
although which one is cooler I will
leave it up to you to decide
Clark more fresh from the celestial
realm a creature of shaped spirit stuff
just like you just sidles to the side
and is able to just escape this dragon's
claw the dragon's claw swings around
this way and now this that's the other
part of this dragon isn't a lot is
engaged in combat with another dragon on
the other side
so anyway anywhere where the claw goes
it has an artistic purpose inside the
construct that's cool million bucks yeah
so this this alleyway curves out that's
sort of a shadowed it's a little bit
darker back here underneath some awnings
and you can see it curving out into a
brighter lit area
are there other paintings that you are
in you're basically inside of an
open-air museum I mean between us and
the exit there are counties are there
yes I know
is there a clever way to get through
that or just uh roll our way through I
don't know I could remember never forget
yes they were playing Dungeons &amp; Dragons
that's true yeah if you have if you can
and as has been the case many many times
Rosie beasting earth you have created
clever scenarios and they have they have
generated real drama at my table and I
appreciate it we could pass that trace
which would allow us to +10 to stealth
checks if you want to try to stall
through here
I think that's valuable here right yeah
just to make sure we can get into this
confrontation yeah okay fresh yeah I'll
do that a veil of shadows in silence
radiates from me this this is the peso
tracing mm-hm and then for duration
which is up to an hour each creature
eats use within 30 feet of you which is
you and Clark Clark you only have to
choose me everything that targets me
target car moreover free yeah well what
if you won a contest like what if you
won like a toy spree yeah yeah we get to
yes you have to give Clark more that's
pretty it's okay
so yeah so we can't be tracked except by
magical means Indy and then we leave no
tracks or traces so we both get costs
tend to stealth so we can just try to
try to trick these stupid paintings like
this the night off stuff yeah exactly
right here let's hear it okay let's see
some of these dopey health checks these
stealth ass checks oh my god that's a 35
yeah you're wearing a lot of heavy armor
don't scare him uh it's so what's your
stealth that Oh -1 so 13 it's by yeah
yeah I was 20 plus 10 but I need you to
roll another die because you're you got
a whole lot of armor okay so one was 124
the other was okay
they're kinky okay
for this one this one it should be okay
uh Clark Morris really learn when we
have to think about I guess cuz his
actually his feet that are on the ground
yeah so you are moving through this
alleyway and it is growing wider as the
light begins to filter down and you can
start to see at the end of the at the
end of this corridor you saw a reconyx
tachi looking down the alley proper but
the farther you get out you can see that
it is just one in a group of statues
that stretch out and then you think just
past these statues you can see the true
Ark of virtues forage itself okay let's
do this giddy up just keep going yeah
yes just go fast yeah go fast right
walnut and kethry strobe you hear a
commotion in the hallway behind as you
are looking down and you've just seen
this great arm swipe out that your
friends in the alley and around the
corner coming into the box is a
flustered looking spice caraway he comes
into our box he says yeah I'm sorry I I
look at him and I go is it I found it
then I go spice caraway walnut on grass
because and she goes why did I tell you
my last name don't then she goes I knew
you were a crafty Sophie she goes
where's my cart today can i interject
yeah okay it's spice caraway walnut
unrest good there's drought
Oh God exactly
where's my cart your cart is someplace
Prince trimmer scale can't break it
apart so you did take me with this
that's oh absolutely 100% yes if you had
two carts I would just stolen the other
one I don't people my thing I don't like
people touching your things either so I
had to touch it first how'd we get this
cart this is very friendly this is a
friendly thing I did
whoa I dunno I do a lot of friendly
things for you guys why and I get a lot
of trouble for it she goes fine all
right don't ever do it again your inner
your head kid what makes you say that
how high the water is
and how high you seem to think it is
yeah now I'm familiar with the same
probably a good tall we are he's gonna
get in yes to get old like probably a
tall we are too it's related for a
system such it's all connected
listen yes I a spice comes up and he's
like we're watching oh hey yeah right
this is this here's the situation my
parents went away from I think you left
the keys to the brand new Porsche know
what they might truly what happened yeah
ah here's a situation our friends are
fighting to the death over custody of a
kid that's not anybody's except for the
rightful parents but that's beside the
point
we've been tasked with finding a way out
of the city in a hurry and you are the
only person that knows where the cart is
yes so unfortunately I have need of your
services and those services are exactly
this finding the cart figuring a fast
way out of the city no more no less
deal okay I know how to do all that
stuff what do you want relax in return
maybe we'll do nicely
he'll give you whatever this is if this
is bothering you I ask for the same
thing I need you to use it yeah
now it's Arthur can I get a procession
check sure 17 that's very good
so much perception flashes like blah
atomic brain yeah it's very good um so
you there's been a lot of cologne but
there's a lot of but there's a lot of
sweat - yeah there's a lot of sweat and
a lot of Cologne you would say it's like
there's so much sweat that it's almost
like intentional at a certain level it's
like it's a part of it's a part of the
the scent assault that he's trying to
create
he smells like salt mm-hmm um it's a
sensation well not a scent of salt yeah
I look at him and I just go I gotta tell
you something
um because apparently we're friends now
you smell real stink about you yeah just
a lot there's just a lot to smell is it
too much yeah I would say that I would
emphatically say that it's too much we
have a pool of water that you know we're
looking at the fight through but you
could avail yourself okay well my goes
yeah if we're gonna be in a cart
together you might want to just consider
taking a dunk real quick and she goes
believe me I get it I don't like to
bathe either but as you can tell
yeah somehow well you wait long enough
and it just sort of fades in the back
yeah this is used to it you know spices
huh and pokes the water a couple times
and the ripples go out and there is a
moment where you all see instead of what
you're supposed to see you saw you see
all of your reflections in the water
looking up and from the fretboard past
the keys you can see that there is a
blade extended on the loot all right so
we're back in - we're back in - virtues
forge no we're not
nothing's happening
so we're back into virtuous Forge
these all these statues seem pissed off
they all seem like they're mad for
whatever reason you are still ensconced
in the daddy rap you bet yeah like when
we just got to keep fighting
museum-quality we're still stuffed works
of art yeah that's true I know what is
it dude I don't for to start screaming
but work yeah I reach up and cover your
mouth you guys are invisible and your
voice show yourself
[Laughter]
so so you are you have you have emerged
now out into the light and you can see
it isn't like a it's just the the must
be the full way here you know that there
are people watching hmm but it is
completely silent this is not like um
this isn't like a gladiatorial arena
like it's a it's a it's a ritual of
state and its accorded the same sort of
its accorded the same sort of respect as
a court proceeding hmm
I need perception roles for my special
friends 54:15 right behind so you are
viewer passing each of each of these
angry statues
I'm each one more agitated than the last
and you can see the mailed boot of a man
a dragon individual just passed sort of
like the stone Dyess
part you can see that you can see that
someone is waiting just past it
okay past the last statue you exactly
alright I got me like do I do you want
to make an appearance or should we
stealth past him in surprise I feel like
in a fight of Honor for this is so if
this is such a this is an honor duel
yeah this is has the gravity of a court
proceeding if you shouldn't sneak it
attack I agree with you but if you have
to put a numerical value on the amount
of Honor that numerous Kara has true
this conversation like she's in the bin
the thing that you aren't just looking
up yeah I'm just like you're making good
points
you're making a lot of sense that's fine
you know I value winning above all else
and sneak we shall okay absolutely
now let's give me some initiative roles
21 it's a yeah I think technically
disease - well yeah you don't go let me
never go cuz you get you'd know so Rosie
so you were gonna take that you were to
take advantage of this sneaky scenario
yeah yeah especially since dinar is
taking a power nap so yeah you can you
can live pause we're invisible can't be
seen and then we can start me and you
back-to-back right sure yeah um I would
definitely hold action until until
dinars ready if it's his fight and I'm
just a bjorn so yeah I'm not gonna do
too much swimming in it
come over here I got you yeah so dinars
Rosie's gonna pull that whole action
until we get the chance to do our cool
combo okay and we are still solved okay
so as you you are nearing this this foot
mmm
the hated foot oh yeah of your foe the
dread so you can you can see you can you
can see that there is that at the end of
this this is waiting for you behind a
statue to your left
arcs out a whip is your your AC 18 it is
18 so you are seized by this whip I need
you to make a strength athletics check
for feet that's what the big strong boy
is about o+ 315 not bad
so he there is an attempt to pull you
bodily off of Clarke more and down onto
the cobble and you were able to you were
able to retain your position up on your
found speed so I pull them out from no
no from no you're simply you're simply
not laid prone which was a positive
experience for you for me - yeah and I
can see where it is
so yeah this it's connected directly to
a rope and that is his second yeah Jason
so no me namine in a grey robe with
black edges and I says a silvered
necklace whose token is hid inside the
cloak so so the whip though you're as
you're just as you're managing
but this interruption
bare-minimum the boot and its wielder
emerge from around the front of this
Dyess and he emerges at a high wall ship
okay okay sure that comes along well
show counsel may our Labor's please you
I may be a situation to annihilate your
servant in our blitz in our invisible
past that race does not make you
invisible it makes you difficult to
track sure so don't want to be that guy
so he is he has emerged from around this
corner and he has run up and jumped and
has brought this male violet that have
bit him
you know he's brought it this scale
gauntlet directly down on you with a
natural 20 yeah completely couldn't use
it last game or last session yes all
right no I will be honest I on to d12 I
rolled it to 100 Thank You Tamura yeah
yeah exactly so nine points no it's
nothing to DEET well and it just it
connects just with your with the your
pauldron on your on your right shoulder
just like just but the force is
tremendous it's like a battering ram
that comes down on your on your body
dinar blitz in this your turn so it says
your steed serves as a mount both in
combat and out and you have which rhymed
fun and you have an instinctive bond
with it that allows you to fight as a
seamless unit so it is that a status
like being on a mount like a do I might
get like like extra value want an attack
or is it just like no it's a malleable
reverses foot soldiers yeah
I'm just but I don't know yeah I think I
can handle the back parts and I can also
make sure that he is using those hooves
and look like a professional all right
that's what I want yeah yeah I'll make
sure that he's swinging with a hoof so
um I just let's just let's just get
right to it let's get right to know it's
in where is it uh here's what I want to
do I want to get down and dirty with
with Prince trimmer scale mm-hmm and
we're in this Buuren because combat
effectiveness middle of the road but
it's also you know it's how its cultural
it's like you know this is this is
family yeah sort of thing
so when I say that to him and then I
want a compelled duel so I attempt to
compel a creature into a duel one
creature that you can see within range
must make a wisdom saving throw on a
failed save he's drawn you compelled by
your divine demand for duration he has
disadvantage on the tack role against
creatures other than you and must make
it wasn't saving through each time it
attempts to move through a space more
than 30 feet away from you so he
basically has to keep coming at me yeah
and then I just want to draw him into
this you know choice now once he gets
ground up in that the spell will end
because once he is like takes damage
from someone other than me saving
through snaps out of it but yeah yeah
but at least we can draw him in so yeah
yeah hypnotically and then just grind
him up with me right yeah kill the young
girl's dad yeah he punched me no I
he was meaner he was mean he was meaning
me twice he kicked click daddy
and he kicked ligado garbage look based
on all the normal plot points this guy's
a dick we're totally in the right no one
there won't be a trial that's person who
even sorsha seem to like him no ever his
kid calls me dead we doing her a favor
dual wears I'm saving throw okay I'm
shipping surgeon Walnut yes
that's my ship sailing 14 spell DC yeah
exactly but I came away with a 19 on
that oh
so I was able luckily for you and
luckily for you I mean he comes re in my
face compelled you into this entire
thing yeah this whole thing is this
compelled yo but I wanted to just know
so you're a traitor he couldn't double
back or anything I agree that it was
awesome I agree that it was awesome and
I want to support you in whatever day an
awesome yeah I agree that was it would
have been awesome yeah crazy beast here
yeah
um is he close enough for me to wail on
it yeah I mean he is he is basically
right in your face you can get out of
the Bjorn you can stay in the Bjorn
alright here it is
so um once I realized that we had been
spotted with the whip crack yeah I hid
like tucked my name's in the Bjorn yeah
and then as soon as he comes down and
punches you all the limbs pop out that
spider yeah and they're just start
whaling arms so um my I get two attacks
per action and I'm gonna have spend a
key point to do flurry of blows so it's
gonna be four unarmed attack so did he
phonetically he punches me in the head
on the side and then I just turned my
chest okay so I'm about to do four
unarmed attack one with each limb I love
it oh that's not great okay so the first
one is definitely not gonna hit which
was an 8 mm hmm that one's a 15 yeah
that one is a 24 and that one is an 18
yes they hit smoke okay so three hits um
it's just my left hand that doesn't hit
because it was it fell asleep yeah yeah
yeah you're like like odd geez I'll get
that one next time okay so then I'm
gonna do three unearned damage attack
hits on him and I can see it he's well
armoured so I'm going for the juicy bits
like the neck and the eyeballs yeah
so that's gonna be 6 &amp; 8 &amp; a 5 6 19 mm
very nice nice yeah he he absorbs this
with a what you would describe as a
psychotic level of non engagement with
the physical hats
oh it just doesn't blink and just takes
it all in the face and just like why are
we
shutters a little bit yeah all right
Wi-Fi was good talk it out I guess
[Music]
diplomacy yeah I like that you you try
to compel duel you turn him I fight him
doesn't affect him you're like you guys
we've rushed into this you know what is
this is this even a plan in this
glittering giant steed you want to Bjorn
and I'm just like you know maybe do it
about this the wrong way
Schumer scale I said some things
I'm sorry Stefan
we started off wrong all right we're
we're gonna wear your head right back
into the top yeah we're going back with
excited with Jason who is going to get
Leah Rosie held her action from the end
she's actually at the front well I mean
we can keep her here I mean I know that
now that we're going in sequence oh I
just met in case you wanted to go again
sure wouldn't you technically Thanks
well yeah I guess that's true no no
that's that's correct
she would have she would have gone there
but typically speaking you take if you'd
taken your action in this round that was
the previous round its previous in cuz
she held action she was originally first
maybe I mom well no no I liked it
I basically a son of her is coming in
here in flood oh oh she was gonna
permanently be there for my bad side is
it it's you know what the scene we're
doing with the same thing we are talking
about the same thing yeah
so again I have to go again I have a
rope around my arm you should cut the
rope so he can't you know it goes off do
you have her all the width yeah I
grabbed it but I don't know on a history
continuing keep track yeah yeah yeah
sure I don't have any cutting mechanisms
with my teeth I have I have a knife end
up pickaxe that I never use but I've got
both of them like on my belt okay so I
could I could potentially like lift one
off of you yeah you can grab them for
the night from just yank it and okay cut
the rope
yeah I'll do that is that my whole
action to cut this whip off love Denar
it wouldn't hurt
maybe do things I'm doing okay alright
uh sure I'll do that okay just so you
can't tell us yeah yeah I don't have to
roll again against it okay okay
evenly exactly it's taut but the the
whip is taut he's keen he's still trying
to pull him off and just snaps and
springs back and then Jason takes this
opportunity to leap up and attack
Clark more what I'm the gorram dick know
what his health is it's a lot of
standard so well you're like yeah I was
trying to find his American see I had
yeah I think some of the nice sheep you
I've got on like these than you think
Jonathan for familiars and stuff I got
two so okay didn't get you one yeah you
can get you some of these some of these
good roles you've seen you've seen
maneuvers like this from Rosie be
stinger just a torrent just a torrent of
open and closed hand blows against the
massive battleship
like side of Clark more right in the
Hodge
yeah reading his most tender haunch
that's the hot chief don't want anyone
hit no no that's a that's your private
hunch right touching private reserve you
know as I say reserve punch this is a 98
select grapefruit fresh gardener knows
coriander so he is he has decided to go
hard at work on that but he has Prince
your skill his face just oddly out of
sync with the situation is Jesus Christ
is a specific yeah as is those as the
Lord of the fight he is able to deliver
another nine points to me yeah to you
and he also so and after he punches you
he Tate he takes a step back and sort of
sets his back foot into the Kabul and
much like your nuke you can tell that he
is adopting a breath weapon position but
when he opens his mouth
there's no it is it's not fire or acid
or anything like that it's just a sonic
[Applause]
[Laughter]
Clark word Clark more stumbles badly
under the
Effects of that he hardly knew you you
take 15 points of damage rosy everybody
and you grab another six jakers
that was this kid or not who did that
okay that's just yeah no no shimmer
scales breath weapon is this 9 fo 4 is
this sonic pulse he can punch you and
breed on you know Hodge amber you you
got you got a bonus it's called the P
and B yeah I do I get two attacks right
then Odin are boats in tell me how tell
me first of all tell me how you
condemned how you contend with this new
information the new information that
he's got a sonic sonic weapon and just
what is your HP I've got I mean he's
burned that spell sauce he's a nice
slide yeah he's just like me he's gonna
have to take a short rest if he wants to
do it again so I'm not too worried about
it
my health slow yeah yeah so yeah so do
you produce how are you gonna contend
with this no so where does he think so
his easy dinner everything that's right
yeah he's it knock back oh yeah
absolutely like this these are these are
big hits
but Clark more under the effects of that
that sonic pulse his knees have begin to
wobble
yeah well he's no longer us 100% safe
platform so well we're of one mind me
and the Feinstein's we might as well do
like dual attack sort of thing yeah you
know you know chill one way send Clark
more another way try to flank him with
Clark more and so will jump down off
Clark mourner um or Russian mmm-hmm I
would grab him up I want to grab him
grab him good mm-hm
one gram good mean uh that would be one
attack right there grapple yeah yes or
not one of it well I'm thinking like do
I want to attack first then grapple well
yeah I think I think that you want to
well I can't say
I can say as much as I want to I get to
attacks like I don't want I want you to
win not this monster we're not doing
Table Talk today right we're gonna last
to release we're gonna do Table Talk in
a moment keep going all right
yeah so tell me how you look how you
contend with it I'm gonna jump down I
wanted you to get is this enough of
movement to jump down and get over to
him oh yeah easily easily and then I
want to I want to hit him with the sword
and get one good great weapon swinging
and then assuming that goes fine
second attack I want to grab him I want
to grab him like a like a boy toy like a
headlock Piniella's head towards my
chest sort of thing the game so well
first I'll do the great weapon swing so
I'm gonna do great weapon I'm going to
take advantage no no as you as you
remove tooth brush from your 30 head to
this version but interesting as as you
produce it as you brandish it the light
of the Sun just plays all along right
place all along your scales like you
feel you feel like you feel like a new
you feel like a new person
you get +2 attack Oh what oh sweet just
for being clean you should clean myself
more often for undergoing the the proper
ritual with justice and necessary
reverence so where's a great weapon
master so you do an advantage yeah okay
on your turn when you score a critical
hit all right I get plus ten attack to
this well I stab it that was a 313 much
better 13 + + - all right so yeah plus a
bunch plus your strengthened oh no I'm
no I said +10 no I take a sorry I take a
minus 5 penalty so I'm rolling even and
I do plus 10 damage
fifteen is correct okay so so if I hit
him then then I'm doing yeah so let's
see the damage doing 10 plus 2d six plus
three four five six nineteen seventy
nine nineteen and that's attack one and
then attack two would be in cripple
month so grip him up sixteen mm-hmm so
you
so you've you just describes the
toothbrush assault
it's that is gonna lead into this grip
I would love to flourish this as
possible so right but yeah toothbrush
for joining before when I jump down it's
still in hand I want to bring it down
mm-hmm crack them with it good flourish
it resheath it and you put it away and
grab a bowl and one in one fluid like
smack across the face and then grabbing
it I want to throw them on the ground
according to the rules but this is
pretty sweet super anime you could only
impossible so he said so you agree you
grip him up rock solid and then I want
to like I said boy tie exactly both your
hands behind a lower part of your head
not his neck so you don't go the neck
you go there right here no what do you
say this is vital uh what do I say oh
it's my my cool actually I know I do
this yeah I know your kid doesn't like
you she likes me more okay I pull his
head right into Rosie alright hey now
shadow council mayor Larry's place you
that is our game for this week yeah we
will pick up this vigorous combat
scenario next sir
at around the same time for now we're
going to go attempt the red trailer
facility see if they work for us I never
reduce um table talk so don't go
anywhere
you