time is the enemy of the past and
threatens the fastest weapon you
wouldn't make it past a second and last
a question play a brash and reckless to
choose a card solution you saw it was
prudent in any soccer poker to don't
become the putrid it's that well-fed I
pursue in no mountain too steep for
dungeon too deep to send expendable
marks up to the top of the peak of
beneath they see Yugi they come like
sharks to it while I swim in that money
build like Carl Barks drew it so send
your national parks drew it I'll send
him home in a natural box with a close
tie the most of the parts included save
your breath for a cleric confessor death
is a lesson that life is attending
professor but if you're seeking my
official advice sign on the dotted line
English of the choice hello
I'm trying to do the introduction to the
show thank you hello hi I'm Tycho Brahe
he negated pacts I am also a mini fost
Hereward drawn CEO of acquisitions
incorporated but today Jerry Hawkins and
I'm here to run a game of Dungeons &amp;
Dragons for my friends like to my right
Dragonborn narcissist dinar blitz in its
attenuation yeah right Doppler indeed
indeed to the right Doppler blitz in to
the right of my right emerging is though
one I know which one is it
it's like how are you Oh No next is
repping the natural world
let's yourself walnuts on grass not cha
you don't twist I lose best at the end I
have a tree that's right now
it's too involved to to my left not your
grandma's grandma except in those rare
cases where she is your grandma's
grandma Rossy bee stingers getting wild
on this hint now but to the left of my
left emerging as though from a mist
shroud it's just first route it's guest
route now grind it up oh that
so when does a couple there's a couple
items that we need to establish firmly
really important things so everybody pay
close attention good now let's start
wonderful no no nope so Alyssa the
producer for the C team she used to say
spectacles testicles wallet watch but we
have a brand new one that we do now
that is really really great and so as I
want to I want to just I want to just
you know part the curtain a little bit
but she inside the show this is the real
now she says celestials tentacles
walnut and ramp ramp so Amy for your
home games you know obviously leverage
this this technology you know any way
that you can see fit we also have a
special guest with us today here in the
studio
it's Ryan Hartman no no no mom nut mom
mom nut is here but her but her presence
is here with us and we know because we
can feel it 100% you your table talk if
you hear anyone
yelling foul things name me off-camera
that is for mother yeah exactly so
speaking of moms
exactly exactly neon blast exactly know
my perception isn't 10 if nine will go
into it later okay
table talk obviously we have a lot we
have a lot to cover now when last we saw
our heroes one of them was being beaten
to a pulp by what I think is a
legitimately unpleasant Dragonborn
Prince by the name of sheer scale now
obviously as the arbiter as the arbiter
of this universe I'm not supposed to
take sides you know what I mean like I'm
supposed to exactly I'm supposed to you
know just just operate the atoms
in this universe like the God karissa
seeks exactly exactly gonna be like
that's what I try to represent but he is
authentically unpleasant person he due
to a series of edicts made in rapid-fire
precision between princess sorsha
and prince dimmer scale dinar Blitzen
was allowed to have a second someone to
assist him in this battle to the death
maybe inside virtues for Chen I
mentioned that I mentioned that to the
death
yeah it wasn't gonna be to the death
it's about with something we'll figure
out but he is joined by a useless old
woman chosen by Prince shimmer scale one
rosy bee stinger exactly we can go back
through the whole thing now during this
time
princess sorsha has offered one of her
boxes in a virtues forge for the
observation of this bout standing around
a dish of crystal clear water in this
box currently our cthe risint route
emerging as though from a mist shroud
walnut dog wrasse who as we described
before wraps the natural world but they
are also joined by one spice caraway who
made his way to their to their
observation zone and has joined them in
peering into this dish
now there it should be it should be
established well established that in the
reflection of this water briefly before
I began to fill with images of their
friends being murdered because there was
a there was a blade an arrant blade that
was still out from the loot that spice
caraway carries on his back regularly no
but this is good thrist drab and walnut
and spice caraway are not the only ones
who are currently peering deep into
pools indeed so around there are other
you can hear whose and ahhs from the
adjacent boxes that are sort of stacked
around virtues forage itself but there
are a number of other there are a number
of other people looking at it
observing it in their own ways there are
taverns even in the lowest part in the
first rung of Scala where barrels have
been brought in from outside rain
barrels people are gathered around them
with drinks wagering over outcomes you
can see there is a dragon born woman at
home far away from virtues Forge looking
into her glass of wine and on the
surface of the wineglass she can see
whatever is being transmitted yeah
exactly she'll drain a glass and then
refill it again so is not to miss even a
moment
of the of the challenges oops now here
won't now your main stars this is great
this is good stuff now we are going to
get initiative from everybody again join
ich causa hey it's my favorite number
for you for as well I did I took it to
for is a six from you know six o classic
you know classic initiative mmm classic
hey or put more enemies in front because
that would just I don't need to know
they're all represented by this one dad
it smells just know that it's more
that's different wonderful yeah imagine
that this is a stack of them I'm
infinitely deep and wide so a well it's
a set that contains itself so there's a
couple questions that I wanted to
establish so Clark more is not in not in
good shape he's in right now that the
dire reindeer grace man get it yeah be
sure to look right into the camera when
you deliver information of that no it's
just right there know you've doing it
that's you couldn't have done it more
wrong so we'll fix it in post
no we won't known its its life it's all
life so Clark more not in you've only
recently made this beasts acquaintance
if this is the sort of thing that Clark
work and expect with regularity it may
be a complex relationship we know have a
bond a bond beyond bonds he knows yeah
no I did have a question I'm trying to
figure out if Rosie is still in some
kind of battle Bjorn so or
are you free no where we ended it
yeah where we ended it was we hopped off
Clark more he was going to flank and
then grappled Shimer scale and I pulled
him in and basically and Rosie is down
here yeah so that I can hold him while
Rosie yeah I like it okay now I
understand I just had in my mind I
wanted to make sure that I had pictured
that and also to provide that I mean if
I confirm ation for the oh the whole
series that wearing the bjorn something
he is not wearing it's all reinforcing
like the familial ties insulting him
because he's not there's a dig there and
then the whole time I'm holding him I'm
just like talking on him and
telling him like this was this is family
looks like you're nothing just gave me
work in the solar plexus and I'm like
hype Manning everything you say so like
anytime you see I say the last word
again just like family father of none
right that's for drink oh oh treasures
yeah got it okay where did they come
Clark Clark Morris clopped between two
dragon statues attempting to secure an
avenue of attack
jason has engaged this this dire
reindeer and one of the most ridiculous
visible feats of martial arts
yes scene I'm trying to figure out
obviously I'm doing everything I can to
create a dramatic scenario yeah at the
same time how he could not how they
could have missed a gigantic deer
reindeer I mean I I don't know tell me
where like Clark Morris origin like as a
spirit being like how is he so good at
evading martial mastery well he's made
of stars
yeah he's star stuff like we all are
yeah
you know what let's talk about got a lot
of dexterity from sleigh pulling I'll
say mm-hmm you think it would be a
strength thing baby it's really about
not remember it's a job yeah it's about
leverage moving your body and being able
to pivot no is simple machines advances
between the snowflakes I think that's
right so he is now Prince shimmer scale
having been fully seized massive paws
around the back of the neck he is going
to attempt to throw you off the front he
does not that's terrible
that is that is not so he is he is he is
trying to get his gauntlet in here to
press the press the two of you off and
it does not succeed and that takes us to
rosy bee stingers okay so he is pulled
down
oh he is he is you are you are right
here and whatever the draconic
equivalent of chest hair is okay just
musk and reek okay gross yes more scales
dude yeah all the way down okay so I
guess I will go for the solar plexus
area with again just you know just
unchain BRR yeah just just Huk Huk a
bunch of fights Adam and I also want to
say something pithy mm-hmm which is like
guess nobody cleaned your scales today
okay so I'm still just gonna do four
unarmed attacks I also wanted to ask a
clarifying question does an unarmed
attack count as a melee weapon attack
because they are I am a deadly weapon
with all four if you were thrown you and
took your fists off it yeah okay so
that's what is it 20
Jimmy I'll read up on that and then 23
she's 20 another 20 calm scales
yeah David Schwimmer's again addition up
905 mm-hmm 14 12 and 9 she that's all I
got is the inside out yet is he taking
anything extra from being like gripped
up like this yeah do I get like an extra
attack my head can I hit him I hold and
someone else is punching I bite him bite
him you can do a bite I do not why do it
shadow council mayor leavers please your
servant rosy bee stinger has delivered
unto you a boon now if you are a
subscriber of course you get this cool
box from hell Rick had me there we're
going to sign later if not you get a
2000 or gifts give it to our store I
leave it up to you to decide which one
of those is cooler now it's a box so I
do a bite it's the bus yeah my ticket
here well yeah but sorry but tell me
about this tell me about this 20 okay
you've you bought yourself some you
bought yourselves the spotlight here
alright um so this comes after all of
the hits oh yeah yeah you just load a
military how many points oh my gosh I
love 9 9 6 yeah it's a lot yeah
36 who could say there's no science
agenda
um and Rosie maybe enjoys that little
too much and so loses a bit of her
composure mmm which i think is like her
monastic tradition is that of you're not
you don't fight because you enjoy it but
something about all of those punches
Rosie's adrenaline overcomes that fat
training and she just growls and opens
her tiny little mouth and just snaps
right in front of shimmer scale even if
she doesn't make contact
yes
it's not about that no it's not about
that right I think this is an
intimidation because he's covered in
scales was she really gonna do she's not
gonna take a chunk out because scale
right yeah like you rip one of his lip
rings out with her Jimmy she does that
oh no no and she Pierce's herself just
like a bite yeah you do a bite I just
yank one of these rings out of the
plates in it yeah they didn't purchase
for just write down walnut dumb grass
where our air of an incredible tradition
largely passed into legend The Enclave
taxonomy all seriousness so I see in the
water that spice is in fact deceiving us
masquerading as a regular Bard
and here has a concealed weapon and I
very well look at him and I'll go um I
go when were you gonna tell me you were
armed he reaches up feels the blade puts
his hand down and says I was busy with
the assassins in the hall the assassins
in the hall oh my god I'm sorry did you
want to mention that there were
assassins and I say who's assassins
they're dead now yeah but who sent them
they probably have more assassin didn't
have any cards as year there were
assassins and they're just guys hanging
on the hall hey you're next
okay and then for real for my action for
real is stab know I'd kill I'm gonna
grab takeout for mother and I'm gonna
point it at him and I'm gonna say I'm
gonna say spice you've been really weird
since I've known you
which is better very
and you're not on my best side I'm gonna
give you about 10 seconds to start
talking so when you take for mother out
and leverage it directly a spice caraway
face it's like shining a light in a dark
place so as you bring up the blade do
you see another person in front of you
in any place where this point the point
of this sword exists spice caraway does
not exist and Brahma Lu da exists
instead you did it discord yeah okay
well then why don't we leave it with
walnut is just seeing her face and just
does not move
I mean she she's frozen just stunned
good therus cuz wrist rope what are you
gonna do hyoseong why or just exactly
what did you do
okay so now we've revealed that you
don't know anything about walnut and
Brahma though really yeah what does good
person you know then I did a security
detail for her and that's it well and he
also he knows that Brahma is a member of
Team Bellerophon right yeah we all know
you're crushing at least a little bit
okay I think I'm really I was gonna say
I don't think it's that secret I feel
like you haven't done that well yeah but
it's also good thrist yeah you would
miss all of those cues yeah that's it
yeah your lover is here
well how the respond that the line is
still great yeah okay me which one it's
really great line no no just the idea
it's like how do you do there's a key
he's asking the wrong questions and
they're probably estimate ly wrong tires
discomfort between the two of them Chris
Wood oh it's a what was this instant so
it's like bTW what are you doing here
we've been do I just could there's no
that we've been we did she went missing
yeah cuz we
The Merry Widow okay that's right this
yeah I remember they established it yeah
it was just say um dr. Nancy buddies
obviously why are you hiding out in this
dragon town so Walnut doesn't get
herself killed
is that a good enough reason for you you
can go check the bodies out there I
don't know what kinds of experiences
you've had with tiamat cultists
generally speaking you know they they
don't get five stars well yeah they do
man one for each head I knew it you
didn't know about it the whole time what
are they doing here why would they why
are they trying to infiltrate this city
I think that this city has been very
abstract to the old houses for a very
long time because just like a wild card
license it's a good thing we got to get
one of those how much work she says I'm
not here as a part of acquisitions
incorporated hmm it's like pro bono you
try it's very sweet you tried you tried
there's no boners involved is it then
you're working for free he says it like
that
why are you do I don't understand what
this is so he said well not what is this
so he's still like this that's what I'm
getting
yes he's right here
okay you can ask him to his face I am
like this our secret yeah sort of blind
knock his eyes a little different yeah
it's addition by subtraction take away
the eyes
what's in here yeah what's in
do as much as you can before I mean my
butt fun fact when I hear myself it
heals Clark more fun that is fun see
this is a lot of fun when I think about
having fun it is fun yeah we're having a
good time so I'm gonna use all my all
but dump them in oh yeah cuz I'm at 20
right now yeah so I'm gonna drop oh oh
I'm at 18 save a couple yeah well I'll
save a couple so I could go to 25 so
I'll drop only on myself I keep five
more okay Clark Clark he'll say mom yeah
how many hit points with Clark more have
there is it Jerry knows Jerry well I
have it over here but he gets healed for
the same amount yeah 420 mm-hmm cuz I
wanna make sure he he's good too it
feels good yeah yeah he's our third
combat yeah that's a super one a value
there we totally it's just it's too good
you gotta pin then you can lose this guy
you guys get rid of me
okay he's already worth so much more
exactly No so that's your that's your
action do you have any other pity well
join ders I get to a tax return I get to
smartass catchphrases I don't get per
turn yeah yeah I think that was your
whole action right yeah yeah you can say
something I couldn't move Irene got him
three good hook that yeah yeah guess I
couldn't shake him yeah
you try to throw them on the ground sure
yeah making president but does that
count as like an attack cuz yeah alright
well I've already used my action right
yeah okay I wouldn't count as a minute
so you see it within to the ground just
lay down
yeah yeah
it's therapeutic yeah what you got
shimmer skills right now God Jason is
doing much much better now
against Clark more you can you can hear
the you can hear the hooves clanging
against the the statues they're fighting
somewhere but behind these this forest
of statues here so Clark more gets an
attack oh yeah do I get to like dictate
what he does he is your friend but he's
not like you know it says we operate in
like perfect harmony like we have a
mental bond yeah oh yeah you can you can
you're welcome to communicate with seeks
bargain work I want him to try to I want
him to try to to to at least take this
fight and charge it this guy and get him
farther away from us oh yes well we've
got two on one I want the name farther
away yes in a way
yes okay either lure them away or Gore
him and drag them away
preferably the quarry yeah probably
gorings but however however we can
divide these two up exactly Allah I will
you'll see that directive reflected next
time Clark more acts in the meantime
schumer skills so now bleeding from the
from the lip Ridge on the left just
going it's just straight down starting
to flow freely down the left side of his
face yes it happened what happened to
your trinket yeah it's he gets two
attacks so it's it's not as bad as it
could be but I need him to deliver I was
Jack Jack alright oh nice
boys check no it was off the edge so he
is he is trying to connect with your
your bread basket nanny bread that
exactly and he is still up on bread
buddy go ahead of time I'll be the
alluring bread yeah you can be the
bottomless possible so you oh this is
marvelous but you see like off to the
left you here like this that the hooting
screeching cry from Clark more and you
see Jason like take to the air um he's
not flying I want to make sure you
understand that is this is something he
chose to do yeah he flies through the
air and lands hard on the cobble rosie
be stinger yeah okay we're still in the
situation shimmer scale it strange yeah
you get a powerful grip he's going for
denars obliques
he's trying yeah he is doing his best
take me damage he's on the ground like
his feet are touching the ground right
okay I'm like just kind of hold them
embracing here okay I'm going to use all
Mukherjee yeah that's that's an
incredible type of Turkey thank you yeah
you manifest you manifest a minor wonder
of sign of supernatural power within
range you create one of the following
magical effects within range in this
lasts for a minute I am going to create
harmless tremors in the ground
underneath shimmer scales feet and I'm
going to lean close to him and little
whisper aligning yourself against
Muhammad was a bad choice yeah coming at
it actually yeah it feels good it just
feels good but he's like the ground is
shaking beneath his feet it's all
but I know Bahamut is not what
he's after you can get to you month
garbage do you want to stay in the
burner do you want to jump out I'm
feeling like the Bjorn's pretty good and
I have an idea for how to jump out so
I'll do it on my next okay very cozy
yeah
no no a lot of dammit it's a hug yeah
it's a it's a war hug yeah yeah yeah
yeah seeing it were hugs what effect
does this does this intimidation move
have one I'm pretty sure we're scale
disadvantage no he's fine she gets it
man but it was really good
vomits my father he did nothing time I
mean my mean face no I could do an
intimidation role you could Minh you
could uh one grass it was good and I
liked it
okay so um pun seeing Brahma she starts
to lower for mother and I'm assuming
that then Brahmas face turns back into
spice yeah so that all that points it
back up and then she's just kind of
staring at her like waiting to see if
she'll just turn into Brahma and I guess
she's not it's just continuously in this
this other person
she hasn't she hasn't dropped it right
right now I mean there's definitely you
you're not sure what it would require
okay um instead then want to draw for
mother again and shares an spice and
then she walks up to her and she goes um
she says I'm so crushed that you left me
I know she says that she's gonna kiss
spice right on the mouth and it looks
like for one second she's like and then
she's like no no no no everyone she gets
close enough so I cough thank God oh
yeah yeah the closer you get no it's
like you can it's it's underneath it
right you've you you you know that like
you have found her in this like in every
one of the disguises like it's like the
uncanny valley it's like ah stinks all
smells real bad
uh oh no there's a stronger
it's in there if excellent as your as
your lips touch the the black hair the
unkempt greasy black hair starts to
unravel and fall the lips kiss exactly
the the authentically vile potpourri of
yeah it's it's paling away but she is
underneath all of that and then what's
gonna apply for a second and like kind
of you know whatever like make make
sense of herself again and Rama and then
like now all of a sudden she's like
we've filled with like new purpose and
she goes um she goes we have to get out
of here and unfortunately we have to get
all of my friends out of here she's like
this is why I hid the cart look well
like us in retrospect I get it now and
also I'm very sorry you were crossed
with me no I I understand that it I
understand why yeah I understand why no
it was like yeah um she's like just
really sure like why she goes um you'll
notice I said no to him though but she
doesn't like really quietly like the
first cannot hear that she hears yeah
she says it's it's to your credit spice
caraway doesn't get a lot of nose what
is no very keen about that and then she
goes okay what do we what's the plan I
hope you have one I do not
she goes I'm at the mercy of the
Dragonborn right now and it is quite
vexing she says it's me yeah so
at that it's it's a me no no that's not
a part of it so she says I can't I can't
guarantee it's gonna be a straight shot
quite literally never is so she turns
she fiddles with her her loot exposing
more danger hiding some danger exposing
more in another place feel relief coming
over me yeah yeah just like seeing all
the night after the knives come out a
couple times she her brown knits for a
second and she Tunes the e string and
then gives it a nod and then she leads
you out into the hall and to the left
wait I would just want to say real quick
that when she's doing it I look at
caparison ago no I was gonna say that
Chris is worried that an aspect of
disguise self is that a kiss will remove
the disguise I did not know that you
think about the whole spell so he's more
careful
no one kiss me oh we got your mask on
many faces now you're like hey everybody
do not kiss me the veil right it's very
important veil so anyway yeah I have
cold sores here's are all inside it's
just all source can't see them but you
will get them it's a bloodbath don't my
fault like where they murdered I need to
know this does it look like was were
they like butchered or is it just like
they were skillfully killed wanna tell
me why this is important cuz I don't
know if she's like it's like a
psychopath actually you know what
they're both good answers and you don't
actually no no no I was gonna say food
for your for your edification
no I I totally understand why this is
important which one's the red flag and
it's okay exactly
no no what no it's just they're just all
flags yeah degrees I can tell you I
actually know why but I didn't think I'd
have to explain it I know how I know how
it happened how did it happen what you
see is strange one of them has a wound
tasteful surgical in the throat okay
it's great wound the other the other two
yeah a pair to have killed each other
Oh delightful I knew you'd like it
delightful they're there they're locking
they're locked in a kind of embrace yeah
that that culminated in there you know
yeah in a final kiss was just so
enamored with this display of dead
people she's like wow and then she sees
they I'm assuming they have medallions
they absolutely do and they're worn
they're worn naked yeah
Oh like just flaking just straight-out
just right on the outside of the clothes
I'm sure catharsis already put it
together well it's like it's the same
medallion I got last night from Kern are
yes yes so um with this mini you know
attacking I'm not trying to disguise
anymore
this town is gonna be lousy with them
and you're making a move yeah you have
you have arrived in scala at something
of a moment
it would appear mm-hmm who do we trust
we need to we need to find the the
element in this city that still serves
vomit gym or something and stop this
nonsense that's happening in that in the
arena it's all mental yeah whole town's
this and this toe tip that's nothing
it's all okay so this level they need on
a geological time scale I believe yeah
all of us can go out care yeah for now
so so you have emerged with brahma and
walnut out you can see this sort of
grizzly diorama here in the hallway and
then as you go down the stairs at the
base of these stairs you can see two
figures TMI medallions just naked
exposed for all to see no no even though
it no attempt to hide it anymore what's
in there what's in beyond the hallway
right down here you were at the end of
this hallway you were looking down a set
of stairs that you would use to emerge
from this place brahma has led you here
she's got some kind of a plan but now
you are at the top of a set of stairs
they are at the landing at the bottom of
these set of stairs but how would you
like to contend depends on what shape
does Brahma look like she's in looks she
could probably do this much faster than
I could good she looks like she's doing
quite well she has the the glow of a
person who's just left the gym she
always looks like that that she's
dressed to the nines you didn't wait
till your turn no you know what I mean
that was a gift for me so I hold well
but I say that Brahma will you show us
how you did that that's awesome
yeah that's horrible but that's that's
so cthe wrists Jesus Christ look all
right
Denard Blitzen of the house Blitzen of
Janardan all right you were an
foundation I am all healed up and away
from shore Mikael not looking too good
I got his head pulled down while Rosie's
working on him yeah
so his head is down like this and he's
kind of flailing like this he's trying
to swing won't do as much damage would
be cool eh yeah I'm gonna he's like kind
of push his head up right yeah I'll let
him push his head up I'm still gonna
hold it and I'm just gonna be like you
brought this on yourself my money back
yeah kiss on the cheek yes I know it's
like being right in his face kiss for
good luck and back in his mouth no I
just
he has to do a dex he does he's c15 he
does but this may be very difficult
well we're always gonna dodge - yeah
exactly
let's see some damage yeah that's big
money all that for - ds2dio classic hey
that's pretty good
all right so just basically just like
eyes mouth it's just this it's just this
this just waterfall imagine if you will
a dark fondue pot wonderful for our
first thing don't chase it
second the fondue pot well note it
stated that's pretty good Gary so it's
just like right down it's just like it's
cominging with the blood out of this
torn limb young yeah you see this finery
just this finery just withering and
melting under this under this flow
that's denial it's in now it's his turn
Yelp's from exactly that's incredible
taking place to damage I'm not a
reindeer you know well that's not this
is not Jason Jason and Kirk nor have
their own problems what does humor scale
to that they're managing although we're
gonna get there he he just that acid
washes down 18 points and then just
underneath it like a person would react
to this you know what I mean mm-hmm like
a real person would have some response
to this on their face somewhere he's
just its Britta his he brings this this
male gauntlet attack and then it just it
connects with your side you can feel and
hear and you can hear it as well you can
hear something go wrong inside dinar as
a ribcage this strong this this a
powerful punch and then he brings his
knee up into rosey
seventeen
[Music]
you CAC oh yeah that's okay that only
seven for you eleven lucky number rosy
be stinger where where are you at if I
may be so bold um I'm in the Bjorn I'm
weirding if you're in the Bjorn but HP
wise 11 okay
where are you at dinner 22 okay okay I
think is it time
oh my good time there might be time I
got so many I know it's so many are you
gonna have to figure out whether can you
do a double ELISA I don't have my laptop
all right yeah so Rosie here is that
crunching sound of what is surely denars
rib cage and she winces my whimpers
right next to me too so I hear it I hear
it like Dolby Atmos and it's very and so
she's like all right you know what
Annapolis we're gonna called out called
the big guns
and she looks up at you she's like look
look out below and then she's going to
miss grandma the-- and call assume we're
in broad daylight call shadows from as
far a radius around her as she can but
they're mostly they're gonna go after
this what's the word for this gloves
justice
that's this yeah so her her main goal is
to use the the shadows on the ground to
trap that arm in particular but she'll
take whatever she can get and she's
going after this whole Plaza so if if we
can get Justin in there great if not
it's fine but it's to disable the
attackers that are around her you know
nothing too crazy that's awesome so that
you are just you're looking to every
shadow yeah - yeah aid you yep and
finding that finding that intention
right in each one yep
and it's just like it's like a family
reunion
it's like how every time the family gets
together you have to you have to speak
to every individual person a little
differently
you have your own okay that's right and
so just instinctually effortlessly you
start seizing this shadow army and so
the most ready most willing shadows in
this cadre are the shadows of the
statues right and so they they stretch
and descend and then you can see like a
shadowy mouth just clamp down on the arm
itself and then just pull it down to the
ground so his left arm it's just like
back at an angle like this because he's
still gripped up up here and he is
currently fighting with the this force
in the earth walnut dank grass first off
the K is silent don't ever call me that
um second of all I'm gonna what are we
looking at also writing right now you
Brahma Lu da and kethry Straub are at
the top of a staircase down this stair
at the landing there are two Tiamat
cultists oh yeah yeah yeah so I'm gonna
hold ya ya gonna let it happen yeah I'm
gonna our next move I'll get the next
guys okay she she steps to the top of
the landing and tells you to cover your
ears which I do know what oh my god
don't
does he cover his ears I'm so curious
things looking will be enough so um she
is she seems to be yeah
she seems to be choosing she takes a
moment like too long and they begin to
come up the stairs at her and just as
they are about to swipe at the loot she
just gives a little nod no and plucks a
single cord and their legs just stop
working correctly so there they
basically just turn into noodles at the
top of this thing and they fall right on
their faces like hard and then they are
scrambling over each other and in an
attempt to scale this this mount to try
to get ad there fo and there is just
like Brahmas neck that just the posture
there's a kind of feline cruelty in it
oh that would make sense that she's a
cat person
okay I had to write a note okay so
they're they're just getting this
they're just useless
yeah but they can't they're not able to
do what they want to do it's like
delighted yeah I just just walk right
right past them maybe like step on
somebody's hand for good measure on the
way down but just like yeah yeah they're
like okay please as they have no they
have there's nothing that they can
they're not they're no longer effectual
as assassins or indeed any other type of
organism I look back at Brahma and you
can hear like their voices just bubbling
in their throats whatever it is that has
affected their their control is
absolutely
Ami's starting to feel this is weird but
one that is loving this but yes a walnut
looks back in a trauma and like you know
her face is always like the emoji where
it's just the two dots in the straight
line it's like just like a very slight
little like
like yes good so joining plan now three
times so when I get to over the bottom
of the landing - I see anything that
means my there are you see two more
cultists amazing they're not alive
whatever need to go to work guys and I
receive if they have anything for
something they have fun they have simple
like simple martial weapons like but
they're there well no they're not of a
make you've seen before they're made of
a kind of black metal it'll be like like
like traditional martial weapons like
the kind that were that had an origin in
farm implements mmm oh really
yeah yeah absolutely so so there may
have a black metal exactly something
that would have been something that
would have been used for planting seeds
or yeah simple staves things like that
but have been converted in the mastered
as as weapons Oh interesting
well you see you see a kind of punch
dagger that has five short blades I love
that around it yo Inc I'll take the
small stuff yeah well that's what's the
small stuff ain't anything big you got
the punch dagger just like holding on to
it or she's like she's big on that you
can't take it with you kind of thing yes
it's like they're not gonna miss it and
she's like this is nice I'm gonna put
this in catharsis bag yeah yeah you know
it's something tasteful yeah yeah
momentum yeah well also just doesn't
know I don't know things might get
really hairy we might need some extra
also somebody doesn't have their magic
and just remember that and that is
probably why she and we don't know that
either right yeah yeah yeah yeah only
well yeah all kinds of stuff so I guess
that's that we can do mmm
I don't do anything my turn okay let's
see so that's one I don't grass head at
that point once once you're down to the
bottom Brahma has broken into a flat run
oh I guess were following her mm-hmm mr.
Stroud I guess I'm following yes no what
I was gonna do but now that she's
running I'm not going to I really badly
wanted to use awakened mind on some of
the on the two incapacitated ones just
to listen just to see what's going on in
there oh you can still say you did that
yeah yeah yeah you can you can do this
okay you can think about it sure do I
have time to do it you're on the run
right yeah I can do it I had a little
space here yeah before I yeah before I
drop into a run as well I'm just gonna
this challenge just you Inc one hello
anybody here it's all prayers Taconic
prayers save your life I think yeah
there there's only way hey there these
face prayers are in draconic do you have
I do not have that yeah yeah yeah so
they are as long as it knows a language
you can communicate mm-hmm you know I
see yeah that's that's that's cool yeah
yeah but it wouldn't let me well yeah
but it's like a radio so you're
communicating with them yeah yes yeah so
you so what's your auntie oh wait
exactly maybe you and even though you
wouldn't even know if the channel was
open to someone didn't talk to you right
can I tell that it their prayers even
though I can't understand
oh yeah they have a rhythmic they have a
they start and stop in a in a rhythmic
way steam that boy or girl team is
generally considered to be the the
mother figure so I say she helping you
out in the market is she working for you
he's here preach the good word good work
hmm they think so it speeds the recycle
in the rate increases
best of luck putting mean exactly but it
can you imagine how that camera shot
looks
where it's like the three of you were
running out and then then audio drops
out and you're having this moment it's
totally shake your head scary now yeah
he is
I'm very curious about some of these
techniques no dinar Blitzen
all right well so are we worried the
fact that he's not responding the stuff
I'm just gonna keep hammering on this
guy he's got this locked down to the
ground
yep so he's off balance I can kind of I
would kind of let him go okay to take
credit check credit work him yeah well
I'm going I'm just gonna go no nonsense
I'm gonna go yeah start hacking while
he's falling back this way just kind of
go sword straight down especially nose
fancy move because I got Rosie on there
the front okay so to do okay and I'll
great weapon master is to where's my
grace I need to look at my great weapon
master - five penalty and +2 10 damage I
should notify man all right I'm gonna
take advantage I think right so I forgot
I'm blessed to so take me here of course
so yeah
hashtag blessed left hash thanks what so
we - five but that ends up being a plus
three with the boss okay you seem nice
it's pretty good 21 yeah it's pretty
good oh nine oh nine it's 21 I see my
head yeah you did yay we did it - d6 + 3
5 6 7 8 + 10 18 damn + smite good
thunderous smite to d6 Thunder damage
additionally if the target is a creature
it must succeed his strengths and you
throw or pushed pushed away in prone I'm
trying to go down so I want to push me
out of the game I want to push them
straight down did you have to knock your
pro me has to do a strength to strength
check in so to d6 thunder damage whoo 10
Wow so it's a 28 total now yeah yeah 28
so now hunters money saver strength
check your what's your DCA 13 your yeah
well that's what it was for the breath
yeah yeah kissing yeah history takes you
guys straight chick is this good oh so
he doesn't go down he doesn't go down
but he is anchored okay still
well that was attack one yeah all right
[Music]
had one advantage it's true I'll just
have you the nineteen nineties Kenny
he's controlling you better because I
have my laptop yeah just affect the
other when you're get nineteen count
okay sure I don't know I think maybe not
like this no no no five you picked it up
[Laughter]
should believe in yourself I know I
should've well I don't think I don't
like calling advantage I'm like believe
in the heart of the cards I know I
should have yeah exactly
huh you missed completely no smite well
yeah you talk of smite on if you connect
I think yeah I was know a lot of day I
mean that's it I don't we been applied
yeah exactly 0 but damage thanks but
this is but he is a cagey canny
individual and when you bring the sword
down in a Miss he punishes you for that
extension know if he misses yes take 5
points so he swings out with his right
hand right so now we are back to the top
you you hear a cry a cry of pain from
Clark more hmm
and since that he has left the field
okay i can re-summon whatever no he's
fine good feeling this it's hard for him
does he remember next time I'll make
sure he remembers witty with me how else
is he gonna learn any that really sucked
daddy let me die oh yeah
tell me he was three I need a DC 14
charisma saving throw from Rosie and
from dinar but since he's not my most
charismatic Amos plus oh oh yeah plus
three
Sony very good okay this is 20 points of
damage you take half oh oh oh I found
negative nine let's does it feel great
that's sub how negative do I go before
I'm dead well yeah you're on the
ground okay so limp in my yeah no I took
tickle on that yeah so wait so here it
says it's like this now at the time so
he is oh yes he has punched with when
you Ben you missed he was able to punish
you for that yeah you can see the acid
yes now with the hand that's tight now
Mike no no so the acid has continued to
eat away at the at his finery his robes
it is actually chewed through the part
of the chest and when the naked emblem
of tea amat is exposed in the center
even the sight of it is just it emits a
kind of keening wail in your mind
well whose turn is it
right now it's rosie be Stingers trans
yeah save what you have yeah I do you
only working you want to work the
advantage yeah it's probably good idea
and reminder your death saves 10 or more
yeah or a lot more it's teri more what
is it's like a coin flip that's okay
successes right yep stayed so is there
anything I can do healed yeah absolutely
yeah you can heal okay call y'all your
it's still D&amp;D alright
like always got his arm tied down right
make a little space right and kind of
retreat back a little bit yeah and then
just get away from him all day yeah here
so back over to ya this is what I want
this is what I want to see you now so
walnut on grass cath wrists Rao and
Brahma Louie a as you get down through
here you have left the this section of
the boxes of the define part of virtues
forge and you can see over it well it
looks like a like a bazaar you can see
tent poles coverings things like that
she reaches over and grabs one of the
rods of a of a stall yeah and as she
pulls it over yeah the cart is
underneath it yeah yeah so I just did
like it's like tissue basically tears
away the real thing that you're looking
at like a kind of tissue and then pulls
it off and then part of its kind of
caught on the edge yep and then she has
to tug it off and throw it on the ground
still okay she Pat's corriander on the
nose a couple times palms a coin into
coriander's mouth oh man she oh yes she
does watch every move we make
yeah every breath we take yes
um and she gets up in the seat amazing
I'll I just in jump next door like okay
like this is I guess this is how this
works
I like it Thurston I'm like alright
let's go get in I guess yeah I'm gonna
get uh I'm not gonna get up on the roof
at this time oh just to change it up
different seats no mmm I like it just to
see we need the utility positions not
this is not like a water faucet how do
you Sint well how do I sit when I'm up
there let me think about it let's see
how do you sit when you're up there she
lays down you lay down always laying
down usually on the stomach but like
imagine like a lizard basking in the Sun
right that's very much her thing hmm
and that's how really your questions
right it seems so small yeah yeah but
it'sit's but it wouldn't have real-world
cosmesis we'll know a lot we'll know a
lot about kethry strobe cuz even if he
could even want to stand up but it's not
stable but that doesn't mean he wouldn't
try he would try for sure but his cell
for going down on one knee it's
basically that that Marvel superhero
Gary going yeah yeah
so here hold you're holding on to the
front edge yawns your friends are in the
are on the bench in front of you the
cloak of stars spills out over the top
of the cart and she she she says a
couple words to coriander such as and
then pulls it out coriander has
incredible vigor inspired Wow perhaps by
her and will handling prowess and
exactly right and she she she folded she
pulls the cart around in a circle she
turns it around in a kind of cul-de-sac
and then starts moving it starts moving
at high speeds all aboard
all right dinar blitz in so here's
unwinnable they're like yeah you are you
are seeing shadowy shadowy faces
beginning to bloom out of this this
emblem on his chest go for the emblem or
I can save your life and then we'll both
die together at the same time well yeah
that's nice and action of his I'm scared
if you don't hit him
yeah but also Rosie's dying yeah and in
a tough position
I know some accolade yeah I'm a few
death saves away from a total death so
won't you do thing well they only have
seven hit points two and then I'm right
there with you yeah I'm just thinking
like if I if I put Gibbs face and bring
you back then what's good what's dinars
like in his mind what's his play is he
doing this because this is all that's
going on cuz you're not aware that we
are coming to know help you know and
also yeah like well body going limp on
his chest would freak him out look then
change everything uh new meth I think he
would defer to helping Rosie rather than
getting some sort of revenge and going
for that the medallion so yeah I will
disengage retreat as far back as
possible and then cure wounds
paladin's hell dude Wow yeah if I can't
be crew up right try to get behind a
statue or something whatever uh a very
noticeable lack of shit-talking
he said because he's bound up he's not
in the type of position that he'd like
to be in to take a swing so yeah and I
got one d8 + spell-casting
modifier which is that one da plus 31 da
plus three what's the number
Hey so 99 points that brings me back to
zero unless I'm healing from zero yeah
you go from zero so you may get more
help than me now she comes to a little
restaurant so you you have you have
pulled back on those spells you've tried
you tried to you've set up shop behind
one of the statues in this in this sort
of garden of sculpture here you can see
as you as you pull back and look out you
can see Jessen come around the other
side of these statues toward his fellow
is he hurt essence yeah yes yeah he's
got some pretty messed up in his face
looks messed up yeah significant gore
whoo yeah yeah he gets him before
starburns activity right here yeah it's
just dust yeah everywhere so you can see
him he is he's coming up alongside his
Lord here and you can see that these
these shadowy heads that have begun to
sort of sprout and stretch from the
medallion have are doing battle with
Rosie's shadows and they are more adept
they are more powerful than the shadows
you have rested this is an older more
refined
stuff okay so they're so they're just
reaching out shredding the shadows and
then he like with is still with great
effort picks up his hand off of the
ground and flexes his hand inside the
cestus a couple times and he begins to
move toward you and Rosie
it is now Rosie be Stingers turn okay do
we know we're being filmed
I'm just carry it was yes I mean why
because it's it's a strange thing if
this isn't a common magic yeah that's um
like and I like when we were going in we
do you can guess and you haven't
typically speaking you know when people
this sort of thing occurs in public for
a reason but there's it's very sparse
but I mean people people are watching it
and they're aware of it but I'm saying
that they aren't watching you you can't
see them yeah I know but it's like would
it be and understood to expectation on
our part since it's so uncommon you know
what's so weird it's a weird cultural
thing was it you want to do I'm just
curious cuz this guy has just played his
hand he's in a town built around a good
dragon and he was like I'm worshiping an
evil one
I mom on TV so I'm just sure how would
that a I'm just our expectations like
cuz this daughter duels too long yeah
it'll be Broadway right that's well put
the the Assassin's being to you might
sound like this is like some kind of
coup this is happening at the same yeah
okay so what do you got rid of Godfather
oh what a perfect distraction well I
just put it together right right yeah I
like this one I know scale sucks
so Schumer scale sucks so um this whole
time Rosie's been to Bjorn and dinar has
her staff across his back and so I love
it all months a whole and so does it
home so it's entirely possible indeed
canonical that there is an image of
dinar standing with toothbrush and the
staff of the master yeah yeah nice I
need to talk to Lydia about this dallisa
get that merchandise wagon rolling
please contain an action figure with a
little like rosy you can insert special
when there's the special maybe like the
Scala Scala battle
she's a she's going to UM crawl like
pull herself out of the viewer and kind
of shake off she did just almost died so
she's gotta work some kinks out
maybe and then she's gonna grab that
staff and push off with her other hand
in her foot and leap out toward shimmer
scale because she doesn't know when to
stop at this point and so that's going
to be her move action is using dinner
art to push off and fly directly in the
front of shimmer scale and then what I'd
like to do is one thing I've never done
before with my Lightfoot halfling is she
has the ability to hide behind a
creature that's one size bigger than her
so what I'd like to do if yeah if it
pleases the council is go straight for
his face with my staff and take out take
a whack at him and then actually attempt
to hide behind him again before he can
figure out what I'm doing and then take
it I heared that possible great well
yeah by you I think that you can do that
but you can't hide from a creature who's
attacking me well no no you you can't
use that creature both as the cover and
the target of an attack
okay alright that's that's awesome that
is an awesome idea
I thought use the other guy yeah I think
I'll do Dan is um split my move and
bounce between the two of them yeah you
can flip out on them on your
square goes sure scale first and I will
attack him and then bounce to Justin and
attack him and then try one special
thing that'll be a surprise like the
idea that it was like I read by to hit
you I'm just like oh my gosh bring back
to life
so what are we gonna do and you're just
like and I'm like man we really
shouldn't you're just like what
[Laughter]
the place slope he's trying to hold on
to her alright okay so that Louie xx so
that's my first weapon attack on
shimmers a sheer scale okay
tell her I'm sayin yeah and then so you
know actually before I bounce over to
Jason I'm gonna try a stunning strike on
him which means after I hit him with a
melee weapon I can spend a key point to
some judgment on no unsure scale and he
has a sexy icon state would be stunned
into the end of my next journey it's
being a giant doing right now um then
after I will attempt that stunning
strike I'll bounce over to Jason and do
a regular melee attack which is gonna be
at 11 it's probably not gonna do it no
okay and then I will I will use may be
my last key point to know I have to dive
through my thank you I'm going to use
another key points because I have not
yet done is are my moves bonus actions
or can I do another bonus section one
bonus section or is a move of bonus
section no no no okay then um I will use
my my fourth key point which I think I'm
keeping track of this to take the dodge
action with patient defense and I've
never done that before so you're gonna
have to adjudicate that for me I don't
exactly know how that works here we go
like I can't do it as a reaction so I
don't know how it works yeah yeah we
used to but we used to have it we used
to have it in there when you write it
down yeah yeah dogs means to get it
passed
yeah that's what I remember but I want
to make sure that I want to make sure
that I'm doing this right for you talk
amongst yourselves class see how it all
ends up yours does invincible bad dragon
now I mean I think this is like big
finish time right yeah oh yeah oh for
sure like it do you I maybe don't want
more stuff I was gonna
try to do a combo but the problem is
we're split like our teams are split so
combo and yeah unless you hell - there's
a way for him that's you that's or you
can also we could just yeah that's true
you guys about to run in well I'd love
to know yeah where we are relative to
the class if we're one water annoying
yeah I don't know
I don't want metagame on that
necessarily but yeah sure thank you - I
have thought about combo but I mean I
just like one that's true that's when I
was like my last option
oh yeah absolutely
taking the dodge action was the patient
defense you focus entirely on avoiding
attacks toaster your next turning attack
roll made against you has disadvantage
if you can see the attacker and you make
a dexterity saving throw and you make
straight saving throws with a bench oh
great okay so feel better
okay so then it is one successful attack
against shimmer scale which will be a
six six points very good one
unsuccessful win against Jason and then
he has to succeed succeed on a con save
in order to avoid my stunning strike and
that's against shimmer scale he does
quite well then that's just me being
dodgy somewhere near Jason that's gonna
be very handy handy all right
Rosie based here so Walnut dong grass
here and cthe wrist row very concerned
about our friends yeah you guys are
pulling out coming around this the
southern part of virtues Forge yeah you
you recognized it briefly because you
had driven by it before on your way to
the princess as a state this cart is
going you know on the left you can see a
series of statues that you recall from
the dish and she is driving this cart
directly for
shimmer scale oh wow okay
like coriander is pointed directly at
them like a missile okay at at does that
the heart of this fight and you can see
that Rosie is there okay but not next to
shimmer skills fix it David they are
close together they're very close okay
good note good note no they're all in
them yes
did you triangle some no no she she
threw herself right into the mix and you
can see dinar Blitzen hiding behind a
statue i leaning against the statue all
right
attack the Tri I would like to see
shimmer scale do a wisdom saving throw
Oh so what I know what happens I can see
him within range which is 60 feet and
now he is paralyzed for one action at
the end of its turn it can make another
wisdom saving thermite on success the
smell and so he has to pass a whiz check
to be able to move to do at all he
is hell oh he's held actually in at
higher levels which I can do now
if I want to completely blow this I can
I'd which I do let's I mean Justin will
probably succeed but what isn't Justin
try one too okay
yeah that's a one yeah so they are
frozen let's get him does anything weird
happen are they held but they are they
are held anything in a place you want to
know if anything I want to know if I
mean before it happens you are too far
away to know look didn't I think of the
consequences okay
classic walnut yeah exactly that nut hey
Chris drought yes
how are you how will you increase joy so
I want to know how close are
the two if there was any Sam feet of
each other oh that's that's lovely
it's so perfect I like that butter Rosie
is right next to Cheston is that right
it's true although if you do anything
that's gonna be a deck save you she's
looking great a lot of decks save that
ain't gonna be wedding I'm asking you to
do a mass by that's not a small a G
shower yzma yeah I need your dad I can
take advantage let's not do it that way
we can do yeah I want you gramma manse
yourself a protective cocoon of traffic
Oakland cuz it doesn't negate Thunder
damage what does darkness it does hmm
sorry yeah which one is ending balance
sounds just kidding
yeah okay you could drop silence and
sitting there edge of it that's a very
real thing you could do that's true what
are you thinking here cuz wrist you're
out well while they're stunned so
they're just stock still there just
standing right there so ready yeah I
mean like like the like the rest of the
statues in this place they've just if
it's peer pressure I guess what is this
you're playing a game like you can move
first
okay instead of doing that I see that
from this distance I can see that
shimmer scale is the one who's the most
beat up I'm going to let's hex him okay
and how bad does he look pretty bad what
do you mean that yeah that's kind of a
qualitative thing I have to assess how
much acid is he covered in 2d6 for it
Wow I think he's hemming off for a
little bit longer so here we go hey I
can help you are you trying to create a
scenario where you ham and ha for
another few seconds so that you can
think about your action during the break
shadow council mayor labor squeezing
that's a tough one you guys your
servants have prepared a feast for your
enjoyment hope you're enjoying it as
much as we are we are going to try the
facilities but we will return after a
short break
don't go nowhere oh I'm Geoffrey K whore
Kim's I was I was surprised by how fast
the camera came back it's great
everybody's having a great time it's
awesome
now when last we saw her heroes Chris
trout was looking feverishly through his
cards and spells doing what he could
well no no no to to hatch an eldritch
plot to create maximum negative impacts
for their foes oh yeah so what did you
what did you arrive at I'm you know so I
promise I won't I want to get the both
of them in shatter but you're too close
so instead she would be shredded who'd
be destroyed her life
I did once this little sweeter hexamer
skills I have that don't let him relax
with that we just even it see I don't
think it makes that big of a difference
in combat the target has disadvantaged
disability but it's also innocent
Plus t6 of damage that's why I would do
it yeah yeah exactly what that hex is
saving tars that items it seems less
ability its ability checks yeah people
generally say that it that's not yeah
people generally what happens is that it
seems like it's really cool but then if
you ever try to do anything cool with it
people get mad that's the survivalist
and then I'm gonna pivot Jeremy pivot a
punk rock to Jason are you the turret
he's up here that's exactly what our
duty is me and I'm gonna do a dissonant
whispers on Jesse
it's good he's gonna enjoy that one uh I
love that yeah I love that way um so I
try and think of what I say to him
it's a wisdom saving throw ah God
it's just all about its ulti in line
it's just a it's just a snake with five
minutes it's a deforms me it's not even
a good saying it's a dumb snake it's a
jungle less is more you know what I mean
yeah most dissonant you've ever lame
I just think sucks you're gonna enjoy it
so can he pass that wisdom let's see I
got stone there's a fifteen no good
because I'm enjoy it when he goes to his
new position is he still held yeah
that's right because he won't he won't
try to run away from this this
revelation it what he's so no he's
intended paralyzed snake yeah yeah so
we're like him for a turn yeah so I've
got when we looking at here we're
looking at fate plus o 13 no don't roll
it x-ray cuz hex
I know another house but I'm casting
this a third-level nice you so I'm
getting oh oh sorry I'm reading the
wrong one yeah it's the one okay
so anymore these very excited o+ 619 hey
plus 423 you you see you see just in
this eyes widen and you aren't entirely
sure why then yeah yeah check me out
next Eldon our blitz in so they're both
still paralyzed alive with their
paralyzed yeah so they're not gonna do
be able to do anything their turn so you
have a turn to recover do you if you run
in there
but their love yeah if they recognizes
that they're paralyzed or oh by the way
before that in my turn I want it I'm
going to shatter them don't go near them
please Bert I'm just trying to go a
little bit so don't go in there and yeah
I know
they got a stupid just don't go well you
got to arrange the tax then oh yeah yeah
all right I'll come and add a level to
at the both of them yeah what does that
do I can say one word and make him do it
they must have succeed a wisdom saving
throw um and at second level you can do
it on both of do it on both of them I
don't know what I was gonna command them
to attack each other
so what I'll do is well I want to know
what's going on get some info pumping
from a focus so you already mid-flight
interrogation
your word is confessed where it is a
confessor monologue monologue monologue
good paralyzed cannot move or speak
oh they can't speak man that crap I'm
sorry I was helping really classic okay
yeah like once a few if you did it they
awaken minds on the party trip
curse you okay pass this part yeah we'll
just skip I'm not gonna sweat the
shatter I'm just gonna run in there and
get mine so you real mad so me all right
yeah yeah I know now that I see an
attack of opportunity when they're all
weak attack of opportunity now I'm like
out of the best come from cowering
behind a statue or CDO
screaming with my sword so they're so
they're doing saves this next turn to
try to fix their okay at the end of
their turn right sure okay you can see
there may still remain just the
paralyzed the spell that you used ah
oh I'm sorry did you want this one stone
oh yeah okay the end gentle sure scale
yes okay go for it guided by our last
targets highest you got it I'm gonna
come at it attacks against the creature
within 5 feet are critical so it's it
means you rolled out the damage died
twice okay all right well I'm gonna take
advantage - I need to I'm here I don't
get no no no paralyzed creatures you
have advantage to the instant - okay
it's like the site they're not paralyzed
this guy so much
yeah I just walk over to him well he's
just sitting there not moving and I'm
just like it's just sweeping up I call
my shot God okay well I'm not gonna do
great weapon master you get advantage
then yeah huh yeah I'm just yeah what
the master is he only open so 18 I'll do
I'll do okay well master my second one
okay
18 - d6 + 3 I remember it's it's
critical so roll your d6 is twice okay
okay this will be interested in 818
let's say plus 3 okay so 21 first plus
wrathful smite hell yes 1 d6 psychic
damage if the target is a creature it
must make a wizard savings always
frightened frozen frightens and business
is doubled or just the smite does this
might double - no okay so then it's
another - - and a wisdom yeah it's like
why not so that was a tackling one yeah
still alive yeah yeah he's still alive
somehow so these this of these they are
closing around you
as you have walked up to these serpents
business shadow surface they are okay
hmm well in for a penny in for a pound
dinar house word by everyone just line
them up I say what's sweet is then to
leave it behind
I'll take advantage all right no I'm
doing great webmaster on this one no
that's the no no no it's blah wah
wah wah wah what I'm already doubling
with a great wailing quarter oh no that
means it's a crit but but you basically
get those for free from the paralyzed
now shadow council merely respuesta good
servant dinar placentas offered you a
boon yeah
if your subscriber cool box not a
subscriber coupon coupon cool bun will
give you a coupon this is this is crazy
okay I got it
I'm very surprised okay and then this is
my last I can do so I will make it good
so come on to d6 + 46 plus 3 plus 10 oh
my god so five - and then another five
and then 10 so 5 10 20 a right to meet
you thank you sure when I tell ya we had
two plus three is five first one was a
five that's 10 plus another 10 20 just
20 that's fine just 20 plus searing
smite which is next melee weapon 1 p6
fire and ignites start the turn on saver
26 fire and you're so done with this guy
I know 3 I'm fired another 3 + yeah I
don't have the card on here must have Oh
what is that long waist
searing spine but I got my little blurb
here neck 1 d6 fire end ignites start a
turn con save or another 1 d6 fire on
pass ends + 1 d6 Wow I think he just
stays on fire unless
they keep doing one of these six and
let's see that's great no this is frozen
and burning this is yeah yeah Maggie the
night do you feel like dragon tonight
we're gonna wrap it phyllo dough his
whole body and just deep-fry that hold
you like it cheat day so this is so if
you so you've just gone up and put him
to work
yeah just hack after hack it just is you
know here's I it's just cold each of
each age swing happens and then as the
less as the as the last blow hits and
that last smite strikes him with holy
fire his body goes limp but it is hung
in the air
mmm by these heads and this shadow
there's a marionette each one of the
heads is like no the heads are coming
down around you and just appraising you
you can tell that like a like a predator
just assessing this new meal and they're
having a speaker chronic so you know
what they're saying they're having a
conversation amongst themselves about
whether this would be a good champion
show my little holy similar
I already got one I got one you flash it
oh yeah you flash it far as male it's
not a large male is some pool no there's
there's hissing hmm and where the light
glints you can see it sort of shine
through the shadow but two of these
heads good try to get a little piece of
dinar blitz in 1608 1600 18 okay the
first the first hit misses right that's
good that's a 20 not a natural 20 but
it's really no
team by a love bite
you know he's it's a real chomp right
ten dead are you doing yeah so the so
whether you see you see one of these one
of these heads didn't if this is begin
to whisper to each other and you can you
can you can recognize it too right
this is a very very old accent in
draconic very prim almost precise and
they're they're talking about their two
father yeah they're talking to that and
you can see them just assessing him and
then as he as he shows his holy symbol
what they they retract when it snaps out
at him and the other one just grabs him
on the shoulder like this just right
over the top right through the armor you
can see the teeth crush it and then it
whips him in the air back and forth and
hit thrust when he's flying yeah yeah
and just flings him on the ground okay
my turn
it is rosy bee stinger oh do I see
evidence of any of these folks come in
oh yeah yeah you can see view you can
see them you can see your cart okay it's
fast approaching behind you okay it's
someone else is driving your horse
well address that later okay then I want
to yell just at the top of my lungs I
want to yell walnut and point at dinar
and then I want to use another gram I'm
antsy to fix some problems yeah
so what I've seen these two mots
snakeheads already defeat my shadows so
I know that they're no match for him but
I think that they could I'd like to be a
distraction
right so I will summon as many little
fingers of shadow as I
and from the limbs that the the shadows
of the limbs of of Jason and shimmer
scale and crawl up and try to engage
these these snakes hopefully
outnumbering just like a derma brush
approach because I know I can't take
them in strength so yeah I'm gonna do
that to try and give them off my boy yes
absolutely
kind of Nancy of course a boon offered
by the shadow council so you you
summoned them and shapes halfling shapes
begin to emerge and step up out of these
shadow cracks into massing themselves
into a kind of army they are armed with
shadow weapons and they have donned
shadow armor and they are basically
trying to box in this these figures
Chesson and whatever shimmery skill has
becomes I'm impressed yes oh there yeah
yeah it is not it is not that first it
is not the first time you've led a force
so they are they are they have they have
this situation basically lockdown like
its long shadow spears all just sort of
surrounding this entity and sort of
closing it in Walnut dong grass your
cart yeah is right here you can give you
can give Brahma a request as to what
should happen
Oh be plowing through yes stop and just
want to say that I see Jenner go down
and I go to speak my healing word to
heal him and I stop because I'm scared
of what my magic might do to him
and so I stop myself and I go to take
the reins from Brahma and I look at her
and then I went to dinner and I go um I
go help him yep
she smiles she smiles and kisses the top
of your head and she jumps off the side
of the of the carts rolls expertly was a
distracted driver right now cars destroy
one second just like yes no go describe
more what this what'd you what'd she do
absolutely so is so you're gonna
basically you want you want to sort of
like rain the cart in to gear your
allies back in yeah so you see so the
closer you get up you see this shadow
army and you have every reason to be
scared of it if it didn't seem like
rosie was in concert with it they are
doing battle with a creature that you
can see the closer you get resembles the
creature from the medallions rising up
out of the body of Prince trimmer scale
and keeping him suspended in the air and
so it's lashing out at this shadow army
that rosie has summoned you can see that
Jason is to the left paralyzed
cool I would like to mow him down with
the card yes I would like to do that how
do you want to do it this is happening
okay so you basically you draw this and
this was Brahmas plan anyway so yeah so
you draw corriander over and you know
you're trying to figure out it so you
know how do you phrase this how do you
Cory under just raises up oh and then
when these hoes come down there is no
more Jason oh oh it's Jeffy just like
you hear it's like the lowest it's like
the lowest notes of a marimba like it's
just coming on
[Applause]
I'm here for those references what could
she possibly be talking about it was you
it looks like Jason might have had a
coin purse because coriander is eating
nosing around in this just whisper she
goes another day my turn it was good
yeah yeah and I liked it so you can see
Brahma has as gingerly as as possible
brought dinar back into the side oh and
she strong of the cart and then you can
feel the cart like like obviously
plainly go back to the level you've a
you expect from this cart and then you
hear the door on the side close okay
well I like it
I'd say okay yes doesn't I just look at
it I just got grandmother and start
pulling it around like we're gonna like
we're gonna get go mmm
absolutely um Brahma Brahma says this
way or that way yep so you go that way
and you enter you pass around the front
of Princess source as a state and then
you move into an alley and then pull
behind the estate okay and inside as the
door opens you can see a magnificently
armed princess sorsha
promises your highness and the cart
pulls in and they close this big wagon
style there's this big like barn style
door oh yeah back in and then bar it Oh
we got you right yeah related corriander
Sasha Sasha says to bhrama she says was
justin able to help his own special way
to the very end he did yeah Rosie says
um in what way exactly was he supposed
to help and bros it's like breathing
super hard she's all up looking
and she's not into this idea that Justin
was supposed to be helpful yeah if it
ever came to it if it ever came to the
end Jason was going to help you escape
oh yeah did he not his loyalty was is
above reproach I'm just a gun inside
that's it nice nice was beyond mystic it
was exactly
Saoirse is is constantly turning back to
the exit of this hall and talking to
magnificently armed individuals who then
leave on her order white robed monks
enter she issues other orders someone
gonna help yo my friend I'm dead yes I'm
like we like slap him in this is my dead
body
yes limp and like your harness our
friend here your champion
yeah I'm like a big X's on that
Rosie by the way is not gonna leave
dinar side notice like no icing yeah
she's she's fussing for sure and she's
whispering and like carrying the body so
yes you need a roll there's no one
healing me yeah well Cody healing
anymore good okay you want a yeah you
went 10 or so essentially at when dinar
is brought out and laid on the marble
floor of this you can see Crenn are peek
out from inside the wrap pika-pika from
inside the wrap and then immediately
hide in wait in sources right yeah oh no
too late greedy Utley walk in front of
dinar just like stand just like very
awkwardly like looking like oh please
look at me do not look at the giant
thing way bigger than me like we're just
buddies right right yeah you guys have a
relationship
yeah exactly can I do like medicine on
dinar if nobody's gonna go get them a
potion or something
Saoirse it doesn't seem that worried
yeah yeah yeah you can take care of 9
it's not ok I'm trying I'm trying
tight like strips of cloth the things
that I did look at card is worried she's
good well yeah that's usually true you
usually your magics not rosy I don't I
don't understand I don't yet know that
you're mad let's go yeah so I'd be like
can do that the the word do you remember
oh how many times can use it um healing
word I can that's right dude I don't
know if it's working or not that's right
yeah I think it's fine yeah yeah we're
all screaming good bearings my house um
yes so yeah so uh
the the what word it was a I can't run
with the exact word but you use it once
Anna it it made it made someone who was
ill feel better they were they were hurt
and so at this point I'm gonna pull
Rosie aside because I actually trust her
and I'm gonna be like I'll be like yeah
okay let's look at dinar over here and
just kind of pull her away for a second
then um I'm gonna go grandmother um my
magic isn't right right now and I don't
think that I should I'm sure it's fine
do you no no not like that it's really
not right something's wrong something's
really wrong with it but this is not
about me right now and I just need you
to just don't break just don't pressure
me I I can't do it I'm sorry oh we're
fine we're fine there again Rosie's not
really one surprise though if you know
your magic busted its busted so we'll
figure out a different way can I get
another roll from Hugh de Narbo 1014 I
am matching up which means to blow off
I'm making a poultice out of good
berries right now yeah and just starting
to smear them on some wounds and I'm
demanding things from any monk that I
can see like you what white robe you've
got to have something good around here
give me some booze whatever you got I'm
disinfecting whatever's going on here
bring me anything
are you serious you princess figure this
out
she she she looks down her snout I got
you now back at her and then she looks
back to the warm map she has laid out on
the table I've got two passes yeah
Brahma Brahma comes over into the the
healing circle Rama's probably got some
songs good yeah she says she's just what
level is your cartographer to to baby
she says she should get started now oh
oh okay I don't know what that means but
you know what that means yes okay oh god
a trauma and start and so you so you you
have you have the sheet yeah and
basically you need to load everything
into the cart okay everything that you
want to make the trip okay you have to
load into the cart okay dinar yep what
we need to do we need to get then our
yield right are we drunk okay so you're
you're applying a poultice of mystic
fruit yeah so for when did you cast
those good berries I cast them every day
I blow a spell and it's just assumed
that I have is every single day free
assholes yeah so when you is when you're
mashing these good berries into the
poultice huh
you can but I just like everything else
is finally looking for you you can see
in the in the base of the bowl huh you
can see what looked like tiny worms
health worms oh okay I Oh
I'd scrape anything off that I that I if
I got anything on him at all and I am
just like tossing it in the nearest
basin yeah even the good berries in the
nearest basin I'm just like nope we have
any health potions your money I have one
health potion oh that we retrieved from
you hey can I get another check nice no
exactly so he so his breath starts to
even out on the velvet inside exactly
like what do I hear Tufts but you can
see that his his armor the plates on the
plates on his right shoulder are crushed
but they need to be they need to be
removed they need to be repaired the
ritual now that everyone is inside the
ritual requires that you tell the story
of how you escaped of how you get home I
see as long as you tell the story and
tell it correctly and with reverence and
with precision time out exactly who's in
the cart with us all of us suppose Rama
Rama Rama is not in there you see you
see Brahma Brahma mentioned this to you
about the ritual and then she is with
princess sorsha
moving pieces around on this pap cool
then I would not be in the car though
okay I'm stabilized short rest
yeah I'm fine how does that work I mean
you can do your thing but not be in the
curve yeah boo and start start the
preparations yeah yeah I thought we had
a sit in it for 45 sorry you know I'll
let you know what it's good yes okay Oh
Snoopy's sorry okay and I'm telling this
story to coriander yeah I think I think
that's I think that's how I should work
think I think that's how it works since
she's had so much practice doing that
anyway I'm telling all the stories the
coriander so yeah so tell the first part
of the story tell how you escaped scala
okay
but first a quick commercial break so
Kate can script this out in her head
we're here you script it out okay and
remember you're telling it to coriander
so it's got to be right okay now well
you see her preparing her thoughts up on
the thing she has her reins and she sort
of folded them over her lap thoughtfully
and you see you see Brahmas back against
the table yes so we're gonna walk up to
bromo be like be like okay we're getting
ready to leave you know are you coming
I will when but I can't come now what
are you doing why did you leave I have
so many questions ask them why did you
leave which time on the ship and then
she reaches into her pocket and she
pulls out the ring and she goes she says
get rid of that this why do you still
have that because this is yours I've
been holding on to it this whole time
she says you need to find the farthest
place from you that you can put that and
put it there oh why why'd you have it if
you don't like it and actually why does
oak have the same one she that takes her
back hmm wanna notice is this and she's
like fearful for the answer but she's
like so wants to hear that it's not what
she thinks it is there was a time when
oak and I saw the world in the same way
we saw many things the same way
we saw each other the same way that's
that's not the case now you have to get
rid of that he can find either of us
with that ring mm-hmm okay ah chick she
goes mm-hmm that's fine um are there
windows in this place no no it's it's
it's like a part up yeah yeah it's a out
door and she goes okay she does often
appropriate time to take care of this
and just puts it in her pocket for later
uh she's like it's fine if he finds me
right now she's clearly deeply
uncomfortable and has never had to deal
with anything in a situation like that
before because she is emotionally very
immature surprised um so wanna goes fine
so you're not coming with me now
not right now well it's just this okay
fine she's like shutting down over here
and then she looks just right a sore
chef I'm just like from Ramallah Saoirse
and she goes um she goes what are we
doing you know all right it is your kid
gonna stay here during this upheaval
what's happening she says I'm going to
leave this city
sure very shortly once I have put the
once I have put the anchor of resistance
in place yes this is no longer safe for
me or my house great well it's great I
guess we're all leaving leaving this
place and we'll make it was just like
angry and just kind of stops over
towards the cart is just like a great
story
all right so Rosie is murmuring to
coriander I think in a voice but no one
but coriander is meant to hear this it's
this coriander is this coriander's voice
yeah okay coriander I'm required to tell
you the story of how we get out of this
place so that you can bring us back to
red larch so that we can get our friends
back in shape and figure out what our
next moves are we came to this place
with our friend in our blood son who was
in very very rough shape after fighting
so bravely and luckily he stabilized but
the prince didn't know he what he
couldn't have known he sought to not go
down so in our in our haste and in our
lack of immediate resources we decided
that the best way to get our friend and
our out was to fake his death completely
so we had the monks and the dragon board
princess Sasha's household drape our
cart in finery befitting the death of
Prince or or other royalty and they
escorted us out as we as we all behaved
as mournfully as we could on this cart
with the monks chanting
their their funerary rites alongside us
and by doing so we escaped the city of
Scala in plain sight so between you and
Brahma you can see that almost like a
soap bubble finest orb a sphere has
begun to sort of form around the cart
and in this shimmer you can see events
happening events that never happened you
can look out it looks as though you are
driving through streets it looks as
though the cart itself has a funeral
crowd around it you can look up and see
ghostly versions of your friends in
different places on the cart but even
through that you can see Brahma and she
is no longer paying any attention at all
to the table and you can see that source
that you can see sort of looking back
and talking to her and like she has her
hand on her and then she's trying to
turn her back to her at the table and
you see Brahma just brush it off so this
is all happening and I'm like there's
this is like a place beyond words
for all that I guess because like this
ritual is happening so she's just like a
Brahma and every every second the bubble
picture is sickening so while I was just
reach up and she puts that like it sorry
my microphone it's a closed hand over
her heart and looks at Rama and just is
conveying like all of these like words
aren't good enough for what she's trying
to convey to her and then she'll just
watch her fade away I'm assuming story
ender also we have to either the color
story ended this is a great name for it
so picking up you have left Scala you
have escaped via the mountainous route
but now you are driving through the
central square of Westbridge do you stop
and do you stop and talk to her van der
dragon do you of simply pass through
okay look what happens check now uh yeah
I know this is a big fan of his of his
art collection so I thought this could
be a good place for us to stop in and
get a drink and take a breath and look
at some butts sure you know yes that's a
nice spot yeah it's always appreciated
yeah what is art remind me aware our
current relationship status is it
urban he's recently
yeah it seems like they finally worked
their stuff out happy marriage yeah so
we'll stop in his in and see if he has
anything that can raise our friends hit
points this is understand this is this
is a lot of time yeah like this time is
spent and the other thing about the
ritual that's strange is that it takes
the same amount of time hmm
it takes the same amount of time to
travel it takes you 45 minutes to plan
and do it you don't experience the time
I think but that time passes
oh okay so everybody got like a good
what are the long rest
why not a long list exactly and I'm just
like so you missed the whole is it you
basically the bubble pops and you are
back in your stable at the drawing
courtier in the carriage house nice okay
uh you're up I'm tired I get up I'm
physically tired my dear friends you
saved my life this first person I see uh
did we beat him do it laughs your hand I
want you friends oh poor walnut you got
a fantasy cold it's late for we left
while you were unconscious I sent a
message to Crenn arm and if I can change
it yeah yeah I'm our daddy she doesn't
know me know I would I say your daddy is
resting
nope tinge it is even possible to say
something pleasant we're going to make
him better and then we're gonna bring
him back to you I don't know if I get
anything back yeah it's moot because she
definitely smuggled her way on the back
yeah yeah yeah yeah that's possible so
yeah so you're I mean you are you are
back home the first few when you open
the door that hair is crisp
we're red larches moving into winter now
and there is a cold breeze that comes in
coriander of course has not bothered by
that in any way coriander folds up and
locks down as trained to do in the in
the carriage house but the drawn
courtier of course warm light spills out
from the window you see the the sign and
of course the sub sign of the
acquisitions incorporated franchise that
has an exclusive domain here in the
destron Valley and this is their
headquarters yeah we've been here before
okay I could use a drink yeah it's it's
jumping okay oh it's jumping in there
it's jumping doing here music oh there's
no music oh there's no music but this
place is this place is pop in
its taking a favorable yelp review oh
yeah yeah I mean visit this is the thing
there's definitely out-of-towners and
you can tell by the hats like these are
hats you know what I mean like nobody in
red larch it's like their largest a sort
of place that would have an ordinance
against these types of hats
but absolutely I mean you and you can
smell like profit is still making like a
month two months after last stones day
cornerstones are still popping put it
back there and you can tell you you can
see her back there
you can hear that you can hear the the
pan bang out a couple times and it's
getting dusted oh yeah
it's it's amazing you can did she's got
she has a barrel of red larch regular
set out by the door she's got another
one up there she's pulling mugs off of
it it's just you it's hard to believe
that she only has two arms so she is she
is bringing those cornerstones out
laying them out she has two jams you
don't know when that started
what yeah it's it's a little it's a
little city yeah a try
it's a little things it's a little city
but she has a shelter there's a big pot
back on the stove but the fire isn't on
underneath it it's steaming but there's
no there's no heat
oh underneath it then you can see a
couple tiny hands reach up to the top of
the pot and then peek out and you can
see Crenn arse face up there she's
looking out and then she goes back in
like one killing her like one hand at a
time
yeah what a scam um your sustenance
friend
Arceus with Crenn are in the pot do we
all see it yeah I just right over here
you're looking in the back scholar or
anyone else you saw Jefferson or sources
you see Saoirse but she does not look as
you remember her she has a kind of
traveling
armored oh it's it's for its for lighter
use yeah it's for it's BAE it's
basically designed for travel it isn't
like the it isn't like how she was
representing herself in Scala proper
okay I want to show but she see it over
by the fire yeah I I want to go over to
her and show her whatever form of
respect that her staff did her her like
household staff oh yeah video you you
try and she's like I have to ask that
you it could be a matter of survival
some day for now we will be as equals oh
I see
Rosie's way more comfortable with that
hmm this she like sits down at the table
and goes you can see so there's like a
half-eaten cornerstone with the jelly
that she sort of like tried to plate it
you can tell that she's tried to
recreate it and then she also has a full
mug of red ale that she is eyeing sort
of strategically yeah yeah it's like she
she knows that she should be drinking it
like to fit in you see you see here you
see here reach over and put her hand
thumb on top and then fingers laced
through ah and then she takes her hand
off and then looks back over and then
tries to lean back with your natural
energy and zest for life she tries to
lean back in the chair yeah um you know
that red ale is not the houses best
offering I can get you something a
little stronger yes you got it
I'll pop up and hit everyone uh uh okay
I'm sorry dad I was gonna ask if I could
do something before this is Dungeons &amp;
Dragons
um so when we were getting out of the
cart yes Craner was shutting down I want
to go to quarry in there and I want to
put my hand up to her mouth and I want
to feed her the ring oh god it's the
best I have that I have I have the best
player so absolutely so as you hold your
hand out the rest of the rest of
coriander is very compact but she
extends the neck those plates open and
this head comes down and then her sort
of cold rubbery tongue sort of plays
over your palm and snatches up the ring
and then you hear a couple pings and
snaps and then she swallows and then
gives you a little nuzzle oh she's ice
cold I bet her so so good and I say I
said good good I do not like I haven't
really given her any affection I
recognize her as a good animal yeah it's
no fun it's no problem but yeah she is
she is definitely trying to do a new
your ear in the back cuz you know where
the good stuff is because you've been
hanging out with profit and sorsha
is the Saoirse has brought it up to the
mouth and then has put it back down and
then I sort of push it away and then
she's like turned the handle away Oh
does she need a different drinking
vessels no no it isn't it isn't the mug
it's just she can't do it I think it's a
little quotidian little work a day to
find that oh I see do you want to have
oh yeah so like I mean there are missed
it the whole and and maybe confused
and yeah also lamb
hungry no resolution yeah right cuz it's
just like what happened I'd and woke up
right never much with death to right
that's going on I'm catching I'm
catching you up yeah yeah yeah as been
like is now besieged by these TMR yeah
and I guess like he would be in a
humdrum kind of place but then once they
get in and then he see it's good times
Crenn arm yeah absolutely gonna run over
and see crab corner yeah it's just right
out of there just I mean dripping wet
yeah dripping Wagner around no yeah
exactly
slippery spirits slippery you know what
I mean maybe we'll drive first there dad
but you know what I mean but yeah it's
it's big tosses and then the the ceiling
the ceiling in the front room is much
higher than the ceiling back in the
kitchen mmm-hmm bring her out into the
into the wide rooms also there's also
over by the stage and the fireplace
yeah and Dragonborn kids are tough so
he's just oh yeah I don't wonder with
zero regard plan a stuffed dragon and
all the children basically have dr yeah
like they have dr v bare minimum and
then having had a couple of those tongue
her around right yes period exactly as
you as you mean to toss her around you
see a very changed sorsha trying her
best to be of the people yeah and
failing as you would you know exactly
the same like this is this is this is
not this is not that but it's like every
time that every time the baby goes up
she's just like yeah i mean eventually
he would just like catch her yeah just
be like yeah this or what Saoirse can
relax
what are we what's our next move here
what are we yeah
[Laughter]
you you were gonna you're gonna talk to
a dinar about the yeah so you'd heared
you're telling him about this while he's
throwing this yeah well I was telling
him about it prior to that I'm curious
about well what was it like under there
cuz I never feel anything when I'm dead
yeah and this was different than last
time
how so more shadowy there was something
in those in those bytes I didn't like
this mmm
it wasn't good the byte tinged it yeah
said felt like was a tainted bite it was
a bite tainted it yeah do you remember
what the shadows were saying because I
do
oh right before they bit what are they
were asking if yeah I was a suitable
champion and that's when I instigated
them by showing the holy symbol yeah
yeah yeah yeah I think that death
probably would not have been been the
end for you either way yeah I was gonna
say like what he see
marah's mail is probably not no no it's
just nothing there's nothing after you
died you know man that's just it really
weird
well say it's like I want to ask the
princess yeah like how how long do you
think you have before they come here you
have reason to think that they followed
you already I won't be here as I said I
assume she are you can beezie and are
else I won't be here but I'll be back
what about corn or a car will come with
me she needs her daddy for a time they
were gonna work out a joint custody
you were not her father but she does
need you for whatever reason yeah you
can you can tell that it's forced yeah
like that like so much else that's
happened like taking up the weight of
that
of that station you can tell that it's
just this the bite isn't there like the
sting isn't there and she's been on the
road a while and this is the opposite
luckily as a skaaland princess as a
dragon born princess she's trained for
virtually any outcome yeah
but the performance is weighing on her
she can barely get all the way out so
what would what is that how does it work
right now did they hammer in weight yeah
they didn't hammer it right now oh I
don't know I don't know what are the
what are the requirements where she says
she says I can commit to visits roughly
once a season I will contact you via
coded methodology you will receive the
code you will you will know that it is a
code hmm fun puzzles you won't you won't
be surprised that sounds good that
sounds fair
that's probably should be better well
yes we'll be here for a season yeah if
I'm not mistaken it's a particular
season yeah there's an important one
season exhuming loose ends to tie up
oh yeah I'm not too sure season to give
it commerce absolutely I think yeah then
I would agree to that yeah yeah yeah you
have you you have you have you have
Crenn are closed mm-hmm and then she she
stands up and then here in front of the
hearth and get in front of a picture of
the drawn family this new family is here
and she is stroking Crenn are as well
shadow council their labors please you
that is our game for this Thursday we're
gonna be back at it obviously next week
don't forget a couple other things it
just announced we know wood
get to it in tabletop there's all kinds
of tabletop chick well we'll we'll
handle that like I say if you don't stay
for tabletop generally speaking you
might want to consider it this time
we'll be back as soon as you come back
in fact as soon as you're there and
we're there you'll see us it'll be fine
we'll see you later
you