time is the enemy of the past and
threatens the fastest weapon you
wouldn't make it past a second and last
question
play it brash and will become the putrid
it's that well-fed I pursue in no
mountain too steep for dungeon too deep
to send expended their marks up to the
top of the peak of beneath they see you
leave they come like sharks to it why I
hope everyone electing everybody every
horse home in a natural box with a close
tie the most of the parts included save
your breath for a cleric confessor death
is a lesson and life is attending
professor but if you're seeking my
official advice sign on the dotted line
and wish of the twice I miss London
leave the past I've heard about this
fact we already started yes
no listen no listen up so there's there
is something that you may not know is
that in the secret reaches a fool to
Penny Arcade sometimes cthe risk drought
and rosy bee sting or do the theme song
and they didn't do the theme song this
time and I'm a very superstitious person
so as you're a dungeon master this is
gonna be our first good show dungeon
master I have to insist that one or both
of you does this song let's do a real
time you want to do it like dog show you
got no content today's ever have okay no
I can't come to this zone but it's like
at the same time like the ritual must be
reached okay it's gotta be you okay all
right
really well just come in when you feel
like oh yeah your leisure yeah time is
the enemy the past it threatens to pass
this weapon you were to make it past a
second and that's the question play a
brash and reckless in she's a cautious
solution thought was prudent in any
Sepulchre platoon you become the putrid
except well said I'm pursuing no
mountain too steep or dungeon too deep
to say expendable marks up to the top of
the heater beneath and that's a Mary
they see bleed that come like sharks to
it well I swimming I might even like her
- it sits in your national parks - it
I'll send them all in a natural box with
a closed top most of the parts included
think it's best for a clear confessor it
has a lesson in life is a tenured
professor but if you're seeking my
official advice sign on the dotted line
initially twice yeah Wow
all right well I'm done thank you very
much I am Tycho Brahe hey of Penny
Arcade pax yes yes all will be revealed
I also AM in if his hair would grow and
CEO of acquisitions incorporated but
today I'm Jerry Hawkins and I am playing
a game of Dungeons &amp; Dragons
with my friends the friends I was
referring to surrounding the table to my
right
Dragonborn narcissist dinar Blitzen no
to the right of my right repping the
natural world walnut on grass Wow in
credit in credit to my left not your
grandma's grandma except for rare cases
in which she is your grandma's grandma
recipes dear yes to the left of my left
emerging is so for a mist shroud because
first job walnut is anyone emotionally
exhausted from the the effects the
lingering effects of last week's game
causality maybe preferably damaged gods
and goddesses may be fighting beyond our
knowledge mummy and other mummy in this
case are fighting mommy said you NEC
skin show single show nothing dad yeah
I'm not a fan of it up dad NBC yeah are
you keeping my dad yeah and then that
mouth guy is like my yucky
that's that's Brad we just telling what
we're talking about though no this is
convo yeah yeah yeah so we're gonna go
back oh well we'll retreat momentarily
when last we saw her heroes yes they had
emerged from a very sophisticated
emotional scenario that involved their
new friends in team diet which operate
on the Merry Widow out of the court at
Neverwinter a lot of stuff happened this
was the culmination of an event that it
occurred
long long ago at least in terms of our
campaign where Rosie be stinger in her
hunger for gambling decided to go one
more round against the skeleton his own
ghost and the furniture inside of a
gelatinous cube she secured and locket
and inside the locket gazed forth a
young woman in the groups of Terror able
to finally seek her out it turned out
that this was the bizarre lure of a
strange creature affiliated or accreted
around the same material perhaps as the
wandering crypt which is this season's
Bugaboo but certainly affiliated with
what people are calling if a People
magazine is calling m and M oh yeah meat
and mouth's thrust 100% assured that
there is an actual name the entire
purpose of this campaign is just to
reward you with the name that I have
made for this creature I think it's very
clever and I bet a bit Chris will like
it I don't think he cares it okay I'm on
my way
no they'll both like it's amazing
again else another come on Johnny mouth
alongside this the B plot if you will
Cupid dinar blitz in emerge from her own
mister have shadowy mist shroud the air
of an ancient prophecy that involved her
stealing the head from your vest mmm and
also whipping a tentacle with a languid
bone in what must and what must be
considered the hottest episode of the
c-team yet I said come on ass for sure
it was horny anticipate our tentacle
with a happy bone X it's like they're
dead I don't like diem daddy and then I
don't also the word horny makes me
uncomfortable
we're risky and I want to put I just
want to put like guardrails around some
of this spiciest episode yet in fuel
language diem father engorged I don't
know it's all weird I think that it's
all weird on urgent in it Helios any
case Cupid boarded a vessel heading
Southland coast not to return to that
self same shadow portal that our own
party had communicated themselves
through our own party here and let's
take a moment to appreciate friends that
this is the first time that it's just
been the family the core I mean since
Paxton congratulations
good night it's valid yeah like it
really is well it's been good it no II
did even before packs right because we
had Rothfuss on though oh yeah I mean
it's vignette it's been a it's been a
slab there yeah it's been a sniper
though the space on our side
i sat down I was like there's no table
like between my knees yeah well notice
he no I was gonna say you kissed me the
one challenge I would say with having
Cupid here was obviously the last 100%
delightful but there was like a thousand
percent more footy I'm sorry no no I
wouldn't apologize no there was it was
the horniest there was a contact any way
it's like this creepy so as we had
suggested previously the party had
returned to their cart coriander in
shutdown mode getting some looks from
the occasional horse that's right a
horse dating simulator is this episode
absolutely yeah yeah end to end we're
just gonna create brush and care for
incredible horses how there's a horse
total boyfriend minigame like this
finally you like that no you can see
that drivas be stinger is sort of
kicking he's just kicking stones he
doesn't quite know exactly what he's
supposed to do yeah next he sees
everybody's sort of getting in the cart
he suspects that maybe there's a place
in the cart for him but it's he seems he
seems troubled he's looking back out
across that expanse of the ocean I walk
up to him and I I stand there for a
moment and I hear him like grunting
absolutely obviously inviting me to ask
him what's wrong
you know that kind of person finally
heavy signs like yeah like I don't know
so finally I bite and I say rebus what
are you gonna do now
he says mom sometimes you do love a girl
and she's a piece of demon fruit yeah
that's what they say
I mean I heard that but I never I never
thought it could be true
it happens to the best of us what now
that you know that she was of many
pieces of diamond fruit in fact do you
have a plan I think I think Paladins not
for me mom okay
all right I think I can't maintain it
I've missed five rituals today yeah well
I could I think I might have mind powers
what I think that I might have I think
that I can I think I can do things with
my mind mom not not like math like I
think I can move math is not your strong
suit like thoughts but you guys I'd lift
and move things just with just with my
big noodle really yeah
can I do it give me a little
demonstration tired right now I would
but I don't think I could do it right
now I just I need a big breakfast dinner
sure sure okay well why don't you take
where you take a rest we're gonna be
past them back through here so maybe
when I come back you might be able to
show me something
yeah I'll work on it maybe I'll go back
to the staggers and Jags yeah you'll
catch a fish or two do you still owe
them a debt probably fish debt okay a
little bit well yeah why don't you work
on that um and we'll I'll come check on
you after a bit okay he he just sort of
collapses down on you just like like an
old Wizards Tower
yeah he just sort of collapses down on
your part you're offering in the hug
zone yeah I can make I can make my hands
reach about to like either side of his
belly and that's as far as it goes and
they give him like the awkward but I'm
used to this at this yeah
it's hasn't yeah yeah it gives you a
kiss a firm kiss to right on the top of
the bun and then trudges off packs back
to the staggers and Jags
yeah I gave I I until I I know that he's
out of
like sight I'm giving him like a dark
look it just in case he turns around to
look at me it's just to energize him
yeah and then as soon as I'm sure he's
not gonna turn around there's like this
big smile mmm this soon as I know
nobody's watching can you see that that
butcher sticker like on the back of your
cart yeah yeah student yeah my
dishonours baby oh
now there are a couple horses now check
and Cory is sniffing around coriander
all right so they're these they're
looking at each other yeah sort of like
sizing each other up coriander is
completely shut down coriander is
functionally speaking a kind of statue
right now I think there's there's zero
interest she it's like got sexy statue
no no not hot okay not no I don't know
it's like listen I'm gonna I'm gonna
establish some cannon here yeah okay
Quran is a book statute were so where
are we position our we're all ready to
get into the cart or like absolutely up
yeah I wanna I want to use the Gotti to
just take a gander at the underside of
some of these these suitors what we're
talking about what we're talking about
down there well I said there's I'm ready
to go there's some yo-yo some USDA
choice beef hmm under there what is the
deal why is this new
so you question just real quick so
you're looking at EULA Gotti yes and he
has like hyper version yeah it's just
like more saturated yeah exactly
Oh God look honey is able to Livadia is
able to see in the dark in a way that
people don't yeah I didn't know if you
could see like the horses or right
horses intent yeah it's just insight all
the time you know is coriander attached
to the front of our cart right now
absolutely so in Neverwinter they're
just horses roaming around looking for
girlfriends over here and over here in
the docs I think it maybe it's cumin
coriander is I guess there's a thing
or any of them like threatening to mount
like do we need to shoe these horses
away so we get on our business it might
be a good idea
rolled watch horses bang can we see that
doesn't require a role tonight in the
okay how do I say you're free just does
will not have any family out like can we
just like calculate sources let's get
more verses yeah let's get these let's
get these bad boys released so they
wander away okay so do some like some
some of that work yeah some that stable
work wait are you I mean if we want an
extra horse we can get so I'm like
leaning every gets asserted that Kirk's
it's just like it's been a big day yeah
it's true goal day uh and I was like
which one do you like grandmother just
show me tell me what about the horses
got well we've got two horses they're
brown these are Mena thoroughbred Oh
Appaloosa dapple listen you need to stir
there's zero feathered horses now ties
that's a version in this era you've got
here's our suitors
alright okay let's call them gray
cheddar great great cheddar that's not
the name is it breed yeah what's this
horse made out of cheddar Bay exactly I
regret a great biscuits mm-hmm yeah
great cheddar and red lobster large meal
large meal before we gotta go for
cheddar right yeah is there is there a
way to UM do do I know how to activate
coriander at this point yeah absolutely
yeah if you if you go near her
yeah and just as it just as it was done
at the barge right in yeah should she
purse right up okay
machine but but it's it's like um it's
like those things that you put on your
steering wheel yeah okay well I'm gonna
go Pat her and wake her
yeah I envisioned this like Tim Burton
Batman when it goes into security mode
yeah yeah yeah exactly so yeah instantly
the plates fold out and push out like
her her size increases by about 30 or 40
percent okay and as soon as these clangs
occur and as soon as her vine curtain
dot you densely knotted vine
substructure is exposed the interest
level from these horses is minimized it
it goes very very low in fact it goes
below zero to the extent that they start
to kick up and start running in
different directions away from the cart
that's fine Rosie laughs they can't they
can't handle me if they can't handle
coriander or worse at her active mode
they don't deserve her password I pad
coriander and I tell her like they
weren't good enough for you anyway the
Raiders have sex of a statue of horse
but now that it's like a statue like a
like a sphinx II like yeah thank you
good for sure we meet them again there's
a sharp inhalations of breath from
coriander and you can feel you can feel
the jaw grind hmm
underneath your underneath your palms
you want a medallion yeah yeah that's uh
we only got one laughs it's it's number
one
it's wallet your new attack and she cuz
that seems to like not matter as much
about anything where she had in her
document sirs bag and she just like
she'd been holding on to it like maybe
there was a fake like a really horrible
false one in the at the drone record
here and she just gives it two denarii
she's like here you go you you don't see
there you love feeding there's so much I
know you looking yeah yeah eat it you
stupid horse eat the metal eat it
tomorrow yeah it's like a each bite it's
just like a Klondike bar you say it
every time that's so good and then it's
slurps it's just like a thick just a
thick bite straight through powerful and
then just slurps up the necklace just
straight down doesn't got like a like a
like a fettuccine like a with a
delicious great cheddar sauce I wish we
had seen that but he left them all or
get them to leave by jerking them off so
I enter the car way too hard just reform
takes a lot longer yeah we didn't get
any clarity as far as like mechanically
what my like cuz my eyes were gouged out
but I didn't yeah I didn't denote any
damage that's taken well we have we have
the presumption is that we've been able
to rest pretty well right way back okay
true proper rest okay so I'm so sorry
exactly exactly now obviously magical
healing would help you with your problem
sure but right now you can see right now
you can you basically are just using
ligarius eyes yeah to look around pretty
much permanently swapped with him yeah
yeah yeah and you can tell he's it's you
know this is how he does it of course
but there's definitely attempts on the
Gottis part to make good Oh buddy like
like how like I'm making my way into the
cart I'm stepping up and it's a little
bit more difficult just not as trivial
you you sort of like exactly you're
looking up from here you can see it's
like it's like um playing Resident Evil
you control yourself from the
third-person isometric angle yeah you're
stumbling through but it's like you
you're holding over here and then you're
pushing here and then he slithers up and
just sort of like tilts up and like
tries to help your foot up into the oh I
see it like don't use the head to do it
that's yeah I can see no exactly it gets
dark it gets very dark trying to push
you see that nobody that's no I don't
want so then he comes in he you move in
you have you're quite familiar with the
inside of the car by now you and dinars
have spent well Dawei many afternoons
right I'll help you I'm in which I just
I just flop down enriching one another
flop down on that couch and I've and
I've I've removed that fence badly but
yeah and and I have not I mean we may
have rested yeah for our whatever it is
yeah not but I did not bother to wash
what crust a lot of dried blood
mm-hm it's just run down I'll deal with
it when we get to a place by the time
it'll have flaked off I'm like a coop
resolved I guess that's but but he's
yeah he's continuing to attempt to
repair this relationship and all in the
ways that that he thinks one would do
that would bring me mice no you know
it's just just up on the shoulder he's
just keeps like giving your little nips
oh no I was like I really got a parakeet
yes exactly yeah it's a little I tell
him I know you didn't mean it and also
when you do that I see myself biting my
own ear
yeah weird you don't have to do it right
just hang out right here it's closest to
my actual eyes as you get maybe in front
would be ideal you coil around and then
just just right there and then I just
have to adjust for this distance you
know it's like driving a new car
yeah so the longer than mile so I'm in
the back with you yeah - all right so
he's having this conversation with this
glass this glass snake and I'd be like
well I saw I don't know what happened he
just came back blind I've been a oh yeah
just look front of your scarred eyes
like yeah I say like oh I can I can see
you through ligardi but I think this is
how's this looking oh not great man
that's what I figured yeah cause if I
switch sight back to my own sight I'm I
don't see a damn thing
yeah and like I figured that this would
happen at some point what happened oh oh
you know the the intercessor got of
mouths you know took over ligadinho
he can't bit my eyes most of their huh
well and it he didn't mean it
yeah well the God did but I've I've had
I've been cited for about three hundred
and eighty years and I think I've seen
enough like if you said oh you gotta
check out this tree like I know what it
looks like probably you just described
it I'm more interested in big stuff that
I haven't seen before well let me try
this out 90% of the accidents happen in
the home yeah it's true I wasn't I
wouldn't care
I do me like heal this I didn't lay I
could touch your eyes and fix them I try
this on for a while
oh I'll be okay all right okay gross
Isaac
yeah you're really sure and blinking and
you can see into the orbits yeah
destroyed a milky bush yeah red it's
alright for now we'll work at some now
like we've the Guardian I've got I want
to put on airs like don't trouble
yourself with me I'm fine being blind
it's fine that's oh my god I get a fresh
bandage for you at least okay no Rosie
bee stinger you have taken up your
historical position up on the bench
hysterical position hope and you are you
are with your best friend yes up there
your granddaughter obviously up on top
of the roof yep well what's next I mean
I think I've heard it I've heard that
very specific labels but right now you
are in charge of the c-team okay well we
have a missive that is not a well-paying
quest that's going to take us to the
region of Scala we do have to return the
one gold coin the thing I suppose it's
not paying but it should pay fairly well
in there's an arbitration JC's but let's
head that way shall we
so here's my question does he you do you
want to have even wanting to go to Scala
are you telling him we're going home no
tricking you ya know cuz I cuz could the
race brought up the Aggie aspect suppose
I kept in check out check on Aggie
bounce yep well avoid you're gonna want
to I mean we'll get Ben but we'll stay
dipped yeah you know that's what I see
were you into high school that's a rival
time yeah this is yeah these are the
Cougars now cats
listen this is how much I know about
your friggin backstory I thought you
were from Scala so no hizo Z is ignorant
ascator
your Gennari yes right that's via yeah
yes in our is a different town this is
all in character right yeah I've been
doing like what's the deal
so I'm sorry are you are you what's
wrong about story you pulling out to the
yeah yeah main road so you're you're
driving back through you can still you
can see that there's still
reconstruction occurring from full
reconstruction occurring on this city
you're able to pull out of the main gate
and head north you know that there's an
elbow at a town called Luskin these are
all places that you know of from maps
okay yeah
from cherished Maps what but this is
this is pretty far north okay and I'm
just increasingly agitated you can see
Jessica and this is nice let's stop here
guys it's probably a quest here it's
left Caen
let's stop it Lusk Ridge Ridge Ridge but
essentially you you've got this you've
got this this piece slid and open yeah
and you're usually you thought that he
was from janar yeah and it says like
this from Scala yeah do it
yeah do it okay so I've got the reins on
corriander but it's just one road so she
doesn't really need my help so I'm kind
of half paying attention and I open the
window I'm like so gala huh at the hell
of a hometown for you
no I that's not where I'm from we met
her already
it's not I don't like him you don't like
them I don't like them so that the
princess that we met at the inn was
someone that you don't know from a
different town yes and she was stealing
your child that's a macho our child
sorry her child eggy right your egg she
joints it's not my egg an egg probably
her sure okay
so why why was she so rude to you I know
right yeah so you guys know I've been
dealing with you can hear this like
laying down yeah playing on them so you
can hear it you can sort of feel denars
voice just resonating the roof of that
exactly you just hear this conversation
right over the top right now yeah I'm a
nice guy I give and I give
save children yeah that's true
right now Rosie's legitimately not
arguing with you yeah she's like yeah
you are you're a nice guy let's just go
home too late for that we're basically
there why what does janar have against
scala if you had to put yourself in
their shoes which are ridiculous and and
too harsh you're probably jealous yeah
of what I mean I got a lot is this it's
like banging the walls like was everyone
from janar as resplendent as you uh yeah
okay okay so we get this straight Scala
is full of Dragonborn who are not as
resplendent and they're envious of the
resplendence II of the Gennari
Dragonborn yeah
and so they come showing up dressed
really really nicely in cool armor
and steal your egg hey she knew me I
didn't know her oh well that doesn't go
along you know okay okay interesting
interesting
well uh thanks
well it's been it's like we can just
stop right here talking about me no
nobody exactly but Scala is basically
Scala must be considered the Canada that
was the Forgotten Realms I mean it's
it's up north of the wall you can have
obviously bad words one can have a
girlfriend
exactly exactly sidequest should we try
to find her okay
we'll never find her no exactly I'm like
listen I wanted to make that happen for
you please he'll play Trevor's
girlfriend that's the premium girlfriend
experience well got a fraction of the
price also know one quick side yeah
we've gotten three resplendence in two
games really I've got a resplendent
tracker because every time someone says
resplendent I'm like that's a good word
no it's good it's good
so you're able to you head north along
the main road just sort of like bisected
by Neverwinter yeah you are able to camp
without incident okay you arrive at
Luskin that the wrong time to to stay
it's it's a big probably a better
investment of your time just keep
traveling okay yeah um I'll let these
bad boys they are out yes it takes a
little bit too long oh my god what
happens when I get crossed out my stuff
what clutch it just happens oh wow I'm
like that smells bad dude you got to fix
that I've know what the inside of its
supposed to smell like pack it with
potpourri or something Oh burying your
eye socket well we got we got that
smells good started rummaging through
the car yeah
my balls tickling well I mean I would
love to investigate that later feel like
that takes a little more effort than yes
you're from the top being like you pack
your eyes full of good bearings make a
poultice yeah yeah wait I mean oh at
least help the scent it might be love
though what if they just smell like yeah
what do they smell like what a gimmick
what are those wait trees that's not
like absolute piss
yeah the ornamental pears they smell
like dead gingko trees right I get any
voice I understand I wanna be I wanna
lean over I have this fantasy that
walnut like leans over and so that's
like very much like her talking to the
boys but it's like the whole hair is
around him back yeah like she's holding
herself just up by her boots and she's
like leaning over this thing um like
she's talking over a bunk bed um she
wants to give him a good Barry but um
she just wants to see here we go um she
gets she wants to give him the the that
could very good good good there yeah and
she mushes it up and she's just kind of
like like she's gonna like put it on him
and like see if that's gonna help
anything but then she wants to try to
just do like a like a healing word and
see if that does anything how does it
how's that feel um it feels good I think
that these things are I honestly have
never considered doesn't even let me see
the card for that does it actually
generally speaking even positive effects
have to have a willing target yeah
you're right you know consent
you can't decipher with the good berries
though it also has no effect on the
undead and he's been dead for years
yeah eyes are dead you can't smear so
she smears berries on it but then she
also has like other various herbs as
she's been that's true oh the function
of our like she's like it's basically
here's what you're really what's happens
she has mud Swiss mud on your face and
then she puts a bunch of like leaves in
it and I should put one big
we're gonna need the guy to note like
bloody nose and then she goes um yeah
and you just let that sit and you'll be
right as rain in the morning I remember
this one from whatever it doesn't matter
but anyway I like the smelliest team
ever trying to yeah but it's like an
amalgamation of what she remembers a
grandmother doing yeah mother she
doesn't know know what the materials
were she just knows that they did that
yeah exactly I was literally rubbing
dirt on it yeah as long as it seals that
weep you know I mean like any of those
any of those it flensed surfaces in
there if it's gonna close him up that's
good news for me as she's doing she's
like she's sick she goes I feel a little
responsible
she's like you um you you help me with
me life but you know I saw I saw your
symbol in there too anyway thanks you're
going out like I grabbed you I'll grab
your wrist or whatever so available is
just here hold on a second no like I I
don't know what I what happened if you
weren't there I would have died and as
far as the ER the crack was in maelys
jail I thought it made the most sense to
start there I say oh go ahead she goes
so you want to go back like just matter
of fact not right now I have to go back
oh you want to go back just like okay so
so we have to go back you know I don't
think I don't know that that's the right
move I was ready I would have been ready
to die in there the earth spoke to me in
there it directly began to tell me how I
could free it but that even that would
have been enough you know I only learned
about it and got these powers you know
and it was very passive this is the
first time it directly tried to convey
me
formation I open the window like hey
what are y'all talking about like
sitting here like why I turn a little
bit too fast and some of the mud
uh yeah well I should goes I know what
it's like when your God our God has
talks to you it can be very meaningful
she was you were there for me when that
happens do you know oh yeah she's like
also what did the earth tell you know
this ayat know this Chris isn't clear
about because in that in that vision
with my eyes torn out
it was conveying to me you were saying
like data as how to get it out of there
ya know practice for splintering that
sort of amalgamation and it created mmm
what kind of amalgamate oh yeah the this
amalgamated like a meta God mm-hm
scenario it was basically trying to
describe like fractures and fissures in
its supernatural corpus right that could
be exploited yeah so I I convey this to
you now how we get to do that I don't
know yeah and that might be a job that's
just mine since since your gods are or
you know they're good back in business
right Wow I mean look we left them there
assume that's how it's done I assume
they escaped but we have to help them
yeah you know what if we should help
them right now guys let's just give me
one thing but it's just the time yeah
this is the time let's go now I only
worry because may not looked like a you
know person's dreamed and I felt very
dreamed there
did you feel like that the bottle yeah
physically certainly no I mean like like
something inside that's not physical Oh
like your blood I've lost a lot of that
anyway maybe opens the window she goes
was it love the whole time
Cheers hmm close the window now and then
I hearing that walnut seems to be very
distracted by something and then decide
okay all right well let me know she it
looks like a Thurston really quietly
goes I know you won
and then just links back so what's up
there's like no movement it's just a
recoiling no possible physical
musculature she's closing she has closed
this portal and you're when you consider
it when you consider the ER and what it
represents that is what you have that is
what you have sought yeah and the
overwhelming sensation of it when you
were being communed with without any
there was no ego of any kind there was
just information of the purest form and
the overriding sensation wasn't what
doesn't mean like confidence or security
it was just certainty right and that
there is a substrate that there is of a
foundation that can be understood yeah
and thus manipulated right and that's
where I like this is what I want I'm not
even looking for those aspects of
justice ration note just this this
fraction of its communication right
with enough time mm-hmm if I if I were
able to live long enough this would be
you know unavoidable that it could be
freed exactly right yeah
not now exactly well huh like I hear all
this and it's just like getting
increasingly agitated as we get close to
Scotland be like I would never suggest
to be like this sounds important I oh I
think I would help you do this let's go
look for this right now friend
you hate the Crypt I hate all this magic
stuff and I'm like no we give up in
Scala I got your back
you're blind back let's go do it right
now let's jump out of the moving cart
these wars are our my eternal we will
keep leave let's take care of Scala this
is a much more important hey don't you
uh don't you need your eight ah who can
sleep at a time like this hearts broken
look at this poor Fred we've got a
hospital I know for a fact they're nuns
in Scala let's stop in in Brinks burg
one Road like five minutes turn left
it's a shortcut what surprised me into
it it's gonna be a big day for you yeah
you get your eighth I'll spend the rest
of my time meditating on the ER and
considering all those things but let's
yeah let's definitely we got a hit Scala
I say we go early you've had many
opportunities now to experience the
improvements granted by your franchise
yes buff yes it's it's it's a
substantial improvement I mean you've
seen multiple tears now from coriander
you know the original coriander Prime
the original coriander described as
barely a horse mm-hmm a horse style pull
creature up to an including the
coriander with the buff yes now this
coriander and now we're talking about a
situation that can only be called
coriander plus this is the elite this is
the pull creature the stars demand
yeah I mean yeah - lines of society of
course okay which ends of course we also
have our cart upgrade from our base
building exercise
yeah it's bits bumpin okay it's bumping
100% they were in Scala just thinking
about that yeah it's here no you cross
the bridge that you've noted that you
you expected it and then part of you is
a little relieved to see the wheels of
your cart going over this bridge because
it means that you're on the right on the
right track okay this is the bridge that
is over the Black Raven River okay it is
fashioned of black stone hauled down
chunks of obsidian it's a it's a
beautiful bridge that you swear looks as
though it has feathers sort of carved
into the sides it looks like it's a
beautiful wing here in this mountain
pass there is another river that you'd
know of and before that river turns and
not every map has this before that River
that is where you will turn to the left
and it's only a couple hours time before
you see that River and then the path
that leads up to Scala
okay and the sign to Scala is not
written in any kind of common language
it's just sort of assumed that if you're
gonna go there you know how Scala would
be written of course it's just like like
the first letters you learned is it your
chronic it is draconic well guess who
speaks that absolutely but it's not it
isn't like it isn't welcoming okay if
you wanted somebody to come to your town
keeping so does it say just Scala just
says it's just Scala
okay oh I have a general question
actually I assume that through legate
that eyes are the rune keeper would
still function at least as it has in the
past
not for that is a credulous not called
live Gatti's eyes of the room oh it's
not mind of the room but it depends on
whether or not I'm receiving like any
glyphs you know what let's talk for the
next 40 minutes about the nature of
perception okay okay and what is the eye
this is this is this is the greatest
campaign of all time no this is this
it's in what was the name of the other
River Way past is designed the Black
Raven River that's the that's still the
black very interesting okay we we're
actually turning before the next River
what and the next River was called Kobol
I just want complete your the best
scholar yeah
s Kol LA all right for your memo I'm not
mad I just I know that you want it to be
correct
ska ala not correct Scala yeah okay copy
written so crazy I'm exactly a legend
boy see now you want to go there don't
you know I actually seen the sign I say
that that says a Bloomsburg it's the one
after this one okay I turned I turn
around completely like all the way I
just look at dinar and I turn all the
way back right now I think he's
definitely pulling to the left and then
before there's the second river is the
Haggard River hmm like I say known every
man so you you pull left and you
immediately the road continues fairly
well you know curated road experience
moving fairly rapidly up into a kind of
terrain that you would not want to go
coriander's full speed on okay mountains
yeah you're moving you're moving into
you're moving into mountain roads of
hewn stone that clearly see a lot of use
of
lot of trade a lot of carts obviously
make use of these but it is not it is
not the type of you don't want to be
hauling ass alright I shift her down
exactly weight would have this on the
tail presumably yeah absolutely so you
were traveling on this high stone road
for perhaps 45 minutes when your dungeon
master asks you to make a perception
check anybody who is outside the curtain
perception check I'm gonna take it back
I mean I'm freaking out and staying off
the windows look yeah definitely oh yeah
I'm doing this well you're both good
three I got six all right I will do one
Oh bigger why use lucky I think you have
seventeen thirteen thirteen it's pretty
good in the distance up the road it's
you can barely make it out it looks like
it almost looks like there is a rope of
some kind going from the road itself up
at an angle maybe a slightly off ninety
degree type angle and it goes up so high
that it is ultimately enveloped by
clouds Wow okay
rope a road let's go up let's go over to
the side look at Rosie and I go you see
that yeah should we avoid it or should
we go closer to it
let's uh let's check out oh yeah let's
check it out gotta look s we should
check it out decision is let's check it
out
do you want me to that makes Rosie know
whatever it will delay is getting there
like yeah this camp there guys no Chico
okay second out real fast cuz what if
it's like an elevator or something again
yeah what are the shortcuts yeah um well
um we've had enough arrests now she's
better
look she's everybody is she boy
and she'll real quick sister apex wild
shape into oh it's nice hmm why a spider
so that she can screaming get her up the
side of the she's always thinking always
think about this is our woman that trick
rope um give me that rope and she'd look
saying she got she looks at the rope
even her spider form when she thinks
alone it's not as good as my
grandmother's rope and then uh yeah she
can just spider climb climb so so
basically up along the the side of the
of the rock wall yeah even including
upside down without any ability check so
you just deal with that no she can
that's totally my fool exact from time
to from time to time this mountain road
goes through sort of carved out holes in
the in the rock wall itself there's some
brief tunnels exactly try get to that
room know exactly but add the closer you
get to it the more ropes you see so in
the distance there are additional ropes
coming down at these slightly off angles
until they're starting to form
themselves into denser and denser
lattices
are they always up against the rock wall
off the road yeah exactly exactly and
then they emerge from a point above the
cloud layer do they look like look at
climb the earth we're not spiders uh if
you don't know okay you have no idea
what this is it does climb it does are
you engaging in this I think maybe I've
heard I've overheard yeah I stopped
meditating yeah yeah yes
some rope stuff here something my rope
yep
I love rope you think this just say this
reminds you of the tendril that enables
flight Wow are they so do they yeah are
we anywhere near one that we can observe
yeah you are you are nearing one now and
as I say that close guys close as you've
gotten to this one hundreds more mmm are
starting to launch down and then sort of
launch down pierce the ground and then
tug a little bit Todd oh oh I see so
it's like it's like like I'm making like
that like a guy watch exactly so the
couldn't and the closer you get you can
see you can hear like a stretching hum
almost like a imagine a cello string
being tuned okay oh but these are not
like knitted like braided rope no not
yet
it seems not yet that's that won't
happen for several turns um first makes
note of that she thought she was gonna
climb out there and then seeing more of
them um
immediately just shifts out of it and
goes um she goes uh oh do we think we
want to maybe get out of here hmm do you
think it's dangerous well I think that
there's a certainly more of these
whatever's at the end of these lines in
there are of us well that's true we're
scholar relative to us do we have to
pass through these yes exactly this is
on the road this is the road that goes
north are they avoiding the road or just
anywhere they are they're just they are
coming down it's like a like an AoE
imagine that it's coming down in a
region and whatever they're shooting the
ends of the ropes that are embedding in
the earth I assume are very sharp
harpoons yeah just you and you can you
can see that they that hits and then you
hear this like stretching metallic sound
you consider spinning as it does so okay
stretchy hey what do we know mud scala
can I do a survival check to see if I'm
the worst ooh seen something like this
before
Jennifer are you like don't you know
this is gonna this this isn't a normal
first Kyle no no this is not this is
this has got nothing to do with
obviously this is Scala guys we're here
we're here looks like they're doing the
thing this is yeah they do this every
year this is the festival we don't
interrupt it they put scallop there and
I know I don't ask me I start like doing
that like pacing like when you take a
dog to the vet and they have this like
open mouth like
yeah Arcana check and see if I
understand the nature of this weird rope
if that's okay that's a 24 so you think
that you think that their purpose either
this sound is not a a you think that
this sound is not for how best to put
this oh sorry
mm-hmm - me - entire universe good risk
I'm not so this is just waiting for the
result you know behind the idea is we
don't think that that sound is
incidental you think that that sound may
be the purpose of these oh it's not
about like anchoring some object it's
about producing at me no no it's
building an ATAR yeah exactly needs that
- well there is a sonic component to
this that you think may have a seismic
outcome does it all remind me of the of
the tones that were it absolutely does
there is they have some shredding some
some capability some power over solid
matter hmm
the tons of Ria's what Oh in they when
we were in the oh he ain't got a mouse
yeah although I don't even know that I
was aware that I was speaking in that
yeah sure so I would recognize this yeah
yeah hmm all the more reason um and I
would I think I tap on the the thing we
never decide and say um this sounds a
lot like through the gate this sounds a
lot like the noises I heard while we
were there this sounds like we need to
not I don't like it yeah sounds I don't
like that either
is it rope do I know that it's rope oh
yeah it's it's it's like a it's like a
string its nature is like that of a of a
tightly woven nylon string it's not a
live thing no oh the cars
or in violence room well I don't know um
I think I could fly up there in ten
minutes this one we'd find out you could
I could kind of enforce and the blind
guy up thing yeah one let me let me go
up instead of down the last time I
worked out well for me so let me just
pop up no Dewey I offered to do so at
this point at this point it is very
careful work to navigate this card okay
through these yeah and you after a half
an hour or so of this as you have you're
just bringing all this information in
you can see a cart on the edge of the on
the edge of the road after you've come
around a corner that is basically
sheared at a diagonal angle oh and it's
laying flat along the side and you feel
confident that if you were to look down
the edge you would see the rest of this
cart yeah got anything good in there I
was just gonna say this is a problem
with you guys give you a quest designed
to show your virtue no we never see any
its sheared from the front to the back
to it
oh no it's flopped down like this you
see the outside of the cart okay go for
it I'm gonna jump down and be like I'm
just looking for any proof in the
pudding here where I can be like we need
to go out are we from scholars it
probably if we can get there in the next
two minutes okay but that's another hour
this I'm saying do we need this cart
that's all I want you you that's what I
would like you folks to think about
while I'm gonna go check out just now
and uh goes and like is there like a
window I can peek in yet exactly yeah
you see you see half of a person which
half
okay the left half nice just right down
the side ah I know I'm gonna say this
they don't know this yeah wine casks
sheared any brandy on those Wonka
yeah um does the person have anything on
them let's have good naked I could not
love you more we never loot bodies
though yeah yeah but no one's out there
a good time with words talking about
it's like I need to see their wallet to
know they're not it can't take it with
you I don't know that's my mom's
there's a satchel yes take this satchel
with that you see you snatch it inside
the snatch it said this is that photo
inside this natural listen I'm going to
talk to Lydia our merchandise manager
yes and I'm gonna see if we can get an
officially-licensed see team's natural
[Music]
snatch positions incorporated alright
just listening into it yeah all too
deeply into this yeah thanks I got my
full fist when I get there is a necklace
and a ring and necklace in a ring is
worth 26 gold pieces total Wow you can
log that I guess cuz I don't know by
well not yet um what do you what are you
doing over there and Robin years
everyone oh it's always just the first
person I talked to oh and then I got
bring people in um and then was someone
here met with an unfortunate and I was
just seeing if there was anything we
could get to recoup the costs that we're
not getting paid for this good idea and
then she comes back and she has uh some
jewelry and she's like this free friend
but
oh boy so you said 26 ago yeah yeah she
she she'll slide in next up next to
Rosie not going on top this time
um I know that she'll be like just sit
there for a minute and then realized I
shouldn't update that when she goes oh
they're dead
very good yeah um does it seem like
these things that are coming from the
sky are they aiming for us and we're
dodging them or no no seem to be aiming
for they they seem to be their intention
seems to be to blanket this mountain
pass okay with themselves and to create
this so this this resonance is only
increasing between the different strings
okay and you're starting to feel it like
up into the cart are they metal they're
strings themselves they might as well be
they communicate this sound mm-hmm but
are they actually metal they're made out
of the stuff that the flying thing is we
have like the black tendril that comes
to fly yeah it's a strange material it
would be difficult to classify well we
could see if it our way through sure our
thinking also I don't know how much you
can fly but can you pick up the cart
with your fly it's the so it's but I
think that's bound by like my the carry
weight of the person flying so we would
have to give it to the strongest boy
enhance the ability of the strongest boy
in flew could he be a superhero and fly
the cart into Scala yes well I feel like
we're doing it's too heavy I feel like
we're dealing with the vertical these
ropes so like we would still have to do
this even if we're flying so so you're
still easing this easing corriander
through the thing coriander is managing
the task expertly you have rounded a
corner again around this this high road
yeah and in the distance you can see a
what looks like a massive grey dragon
okay
Wow great dragons y'all it's gonna
happen eventually
not great cheddar giant hard you know I
can't wait yeah
so where is the dragon is used to
basically out you know through this this
tangled whining mass of cables mm-hmm
you can see in the distance you can see
a great gray dragon hmm it's back to the
road and indeed the Forgotten Realms in
general hmm
yeah well I'm invested now we gotta go
see that dragon how's it look like is it
looked like it's oh yeah do I or is he
like does it resonate with me and in its
capacity massive and its massive in the
distance just a big ol dragon yeah is it
moving
no it's not not at all maybe a statue
hmm yeah you see woozi's like hey listen
listen I get crazy
need some mechanism you can see through
this mesh you can see that there are
several carts waiting to find their way
through this okay oh okay
there's tangle there they're not dead
there's no no no they they stopped their
cart this is like getting on a ferry
that's like yep the long line
what say you did you reserve a spot yes
that's what they say you gotta go on
line first
yeah is there anything that any of us
can do to try to cut these ropes can
command them could corriander fight them
chop I'll shake any metal yeah no it's
not metal but we can try it it might as
well be said the DM okay so
coriander's boy I would like to ask
coriander to do a bite just to do a bite
yeah bite a rope hey despite it I'm on
board with that hey that's interesting
yak so you so you so you lead you lead
her up yeah and just she's right in
front of one of these these uh like
bizarrely angled cables they're not
gonna make her do it well no she's in
front of it she's just looking at it
she's missed it a couple times and she
looks over you
she goes over sir tilts her head opens
up her or jaw box and this starts to go
nuts on it just like the key thinks the
teeth come out a little bit farther than
you think is like appropriate for like
you don't think this is like a hundred
percent horse what's happening here
she's never really been 100 persons
gonna say it's like it's like it's like
each bite it's getting slightly worse
and then in that last bite it snaps
clean through and the whiplash of it
knocks coriander over huh whoa but but
it it does indeed cling straight into
space okay
coriander it hits the ground and shuts
oh okay well we gotta fix that well they
can be okay good night dinar can you
come help me pick up this giant metal
horse
hey horse
you know without a horse we probably
can't get in muscala yeah say is a
writer here that would say bring the
horse tsk oh yeah they say we really
can't drink he gets up on two of the
hose yes yeah okay sorry
and there's a few fateful seconds before
coriander unfolds again she's just
sniffing around for that purse oh sure
this is this is like the horsey out in
front of Kmart you know what I mean yeah
but it isn't one thing it gots to get
paid you know we got it we got some Oh
give her that give her the jewelry I
just found yeah how much does she want
well how much can eat how hungry are you
that she wants with 76 gold she
specifically want gold or can it just be
anything valuable yeah sure
yeah so you're trying to hand over some
stuff yeah I'm I mean I have a lot of
gold necklace as well yeah so I was like
yeah exactly just reach the teeth down
get a hold of it
choose thought for a little while she
spits the ruby off the side of the
mountain road
should know that was gonna happen I want
to apologize for using it obviously it's
tired you know what I mean
okay yeah so I give her its coin pure
gold straight through so we can avoid
that issue in the future okay after you
have fed three coins okay
she gets her her Verve she gets her get
up and go I I can't tell you how pleased
I am
every time this horse eats your money
like I you know I smile at night just in
my room good come to my smile and then I
just I pull the blankets over and I
sleep I sleep well okay so we can cut
these ropes but corriander might not be
the right person for it gotta pay three
dollars crazy like any order the guy's a
knife is not super big staggered e-mini
- you like a serrated sighing yeah I do
want to see the dragon right yeah you
got to wear that dragon I got to come
away to the dry tellin I would like to
cook that dragon did art you wait to
that dragon you got Carl those ropes go
and I smack you so you obviously you've
been put in better coach yes
you saw what happened with corriander
you suspect that this is gonna require
precision execution or style slicing uh
I'm gonna oh when I did I give you dance
ability
oh and I give you full strength which
will give you advantage on strength
tricks oh nice
good luck and it just stands really far
back but when she does she pulls them
good thirst back with her like you
is going well I'll get myself
shield of faith you just the boost money
see a little bit yeah that's how I get
myself shield face so let's let's let's
see some attack rolls but Cody buddy I
got a roll attack I want to aim high too
so when I snap this and it's whipping
around at least yes rich for the seconds
to duck down yes of course yeah
wah they of course yeah I thought that
was very clever I support you whatever
Center how many got the wrong 18 oh
that's where do you want
that's very good go all day well it's
way we're gonna need two more okay that
so you you connect with the blade and
then just edit at a perfect angle and
then just slice straight through in one
motion and the tendril snaps out and you
dude you're able to duck just under this
jagged edge yeah as it whips around and
it flies up there ah me out as I
say you can you can start to roll
coriander a little bit closer he's going
through trying to carve you a place
through this thing what's happening
around us while I'm doing so so you so
you're you feel you feel confident that
if you had hair it would be it would be
standing on end as it stands walking
through this strange garden this this
vibration is like getting under your
scales you can just there's like a sound
wall exactly it's like a like imagine
like a dentist's drill mmm just except
it's your flesh in general terms not do
they know you're coming
do they
much there's a lot of effort I know I
said I said advantage you do for me yeah
oh yeah enjoy it 13 am i doing Plus
drink that's what you are D that's 16
yeah that's very good so you you feel
pretty confident that you have mastered
this process no I'm just saying I'm the
best great at this yeah thank you
everything else what's your response
damn it
20 whoa for real seven fights I gave
myself to Sheila for faith oh so it's
sweeps over and you're able to dodge it
and you're continuing to hum you're on
the best song yeah and then does it go
the lure and the best
and so the with the bottom half swipes
around and catches the back of your calf
whoa my razor scooter yeah exactly no I
need I need I need one more and that
should that will constitute you having
provided a premium variance I gotta rub
some goober math I got I got more where
this came from so you're able to you're
able to get that so now look you're you
kind of got it in mind you guys the
upper one and then you got the lower one
and you feel like you got it you feel
like you have a good message for how
this is for house is gonna have to keep
seeing but you're cautious about it so
basically it sweeps over you duck that
you sidestep the bumper goes runs this
it swings around again as you step up
and catches you in the shoulder dang it
like I dodged the tool and I turn around
I got six plates Wow
so where does that put you by the way
well we healed in there
I'm back to normal yes and I'm at 31 oh
this is gonna be my soap in any case so
what I'm gonna need from you is that
animal handling me yeah yeah she's not
an animal so she was a vehicle if
anything animal is her UI it's a history
okay why obviously the shadow council
has seen fit to grant you know advantage
[Laughter]
have a grimy
what's it I almost there I have a more
robust version of this you have an
updated version oh that's a nice yes I
wonder if you want it well yeah thanks
Chris Perkins I'd love it oh boy
oh seven oh I know that's wrong
obviously the way it was wrong I
apologize so glad you're finally getting
have some funds Jerry so this this
strange primarily open air cavern that
your cart is passing through
you're just out on the edge and you can
see these other carts you know heavy
laden with goods from Scala sort of
waiting and looking on this strange
contraption pulling up the road through
this place that they are not interested
in going and then you're feeling pretty
good you just read the end of as you're
pulling out you sort of you give a quick
wave and then you hear that
here's that scrape that tuning scrape
and the catapult is sheared completely
off no I forgot we had it definitely you
know left side I got launched out of it
once yeah those were good times it gets
cut off is just like a montage
like three frames of Rosie yeah getting
catapulted out of it over and over
Wow I repeat yeah it's clean this is not
you don't think this is fixable in the
classic sense
okay that's fine like it's it's straight
it's such a clean cut
I'm impressed without cut how clean the
cut is yeah exactly oh yeah you're like
goddamn yeah that's couldn't have that's
a nice clean ten pounds of a five-pound
bag and so as you merge from this they
are curiously they can give you can hear
them talking amongst their party about
how they're gonna manage this bizarre
new weather and they're going the other
way
yeah they're they're they're they're
attempting to get their incredible
wealth and bring it back out of Scala Oh
interesting so their carts are laden
with wealth what we found ourselves in
very upstanding from today's it
therefore Scala so they are not
Dragonborn I don't care what happens to
them exceedingly very various in the
classic sense but they definitely have
made the extra effort monetarily to
ensure that they've got rough characters
mmm with them on their cars they're
armed them thoroughly
hmm - a piece okay wherever they don't
have more I write ooh give you a
disapproving look but like there's it's
all in the eyes and there's nothing
there and you look like it just looks
like this look do you need to change
well that's not gonna you know she if
she gets it she's like she's a little
more in tune with her she's just like
she's like oh I'm not gonna do anything
I mean I'd love to know I'm not sure and
then she looks at them that she looks
back at the road that they have in front
of them and she's like good luck
buttercup okay so this massive dragon
that you see
as the blue sky is moving into sunset
you can see that the closer you get to
it that many things about it that become
apparent so from the road it might as
well be a massive statue of a grey
dragon it isn't until you get closer and
you you've you've heard of it but you
haven't seen it that you can see that
it's actually several discrete layers
coming out almost going up like a tiered
garden and so the closer you get to it
as you come around the side you can see
it's sort of split like your perspective
shows it in its different layers and so
around the base layer you can see smoke
and city fires rising up just beyond
that you can see taller finer homes that
exist on that threshold just beyond that
you see the traditional like small
castles traditional stonework buildings
up beyond that you can see what looks
like a traditional garden but understand
that we're talking about layers of a
massive city each one of these sort of
rings stacked up on top of each other
and then when viewed from the road it
conveys the idea of this single
structure it's awesome
I say that to dinar this place is
awesome you should see tonight it's like
this times 10 so much better 10 of this
on top of each one more glorious this
garbage hovel let's go home onward
that's all I want to heal myself ah nice
downtime by the way like while you're
complaining
this place is laying on hand
yeah well yeah I want to lay on hands
and I do want to say like I can give you
some of this buddy give you a little
taste of this and like rubbing my leg
you know what I'm making myself better
yeah
oh my god I go here you want some of
this yeah zeliha proposition in front of
his eyes
yeah oh no his eyes only know you've
touched your calf with it
oh yeah it's like the most disgusting
like I'm like I feel better you know
like lay on hands by any of you again
they had a bin for this purpose see they
run that here yeah it's well funded it's
great I'm looking forward so clear path
absolutely and so there are more carts
pulling out so this this is when people
going to leave the town at night this is
when they're doing it when they're
finally going in when carts are finally
going in to rest right now there are
multiple lines of carts that you can see
at each of three gates going inside
going inside so there are three gates
built into the lowest sort of layer of
this thing how long are the lines there
they're not short Rosie doesn't wait in
lines okay why would you wait in line to
get into it yeah royalty with us so
let's Jerry that confers them yes stuck
my head and rosie drives the cart
between the lines what is great to the
game Oh mystery gates whichever one yeah
looks looks at the best could we do a
minor evolution on him so that it looks
platinum oh well I'm not you're not
gonna do that
be okay with that I feel like between
intimidation and your entitlement
we could probably Bluff our way through
this gate what do you think yeah how do
you say it louder and we'll be fine I
could be eating egg you right now I
don't know what I do here probably
eating eggs this will be all right now
I laid eggs I was gonna send all right
guys like peek freaked out this is like
dog right when you get to the vet just
like okay no I'm talking like not at the
start of the drive the end of the drive
yeah that's like drooling a little bit
racing plan right so eating the cart I'm
like I'm like very confident about it
like I'm definitely it's gonna be fine
I'm gonna get I'm gonna use intimidation
these fools don't know what's coming
dinner is gonna be all about it I turn I
look at you and you're you're like
actually slaw plates starting everywhere
like okay can you pull this can you pull
your together or you guys okay all
right shadow council their livers please
you ha we are going to have our course
break subs are cool we like them thank
you so much and and there's another
reason sub 2 because if we roll it 20
instead of getting a gift certificate if
you were a subscriber then Elderwood
boxes gave us these really sweet dice
boxes and so you'll get this super
killer dice box instead something to
consider don't go anywhere we'll be
right back
shadow council mayor laborious pays you
when last we saw our heroes they had
just approached the gate of scala the
notoriously xenophobic northern city of
platinum dragon board now it's only
there was a plot Hatchin you were trying
to put something together your associate
dinar blitz in getting in creating a lot
of saliva mm-hmm increasing agitation
ackles risen yep
who can say why
okay uh all right I would like to try to
put something together really quick I'm
going I'm I'm approaching the gates as
fast as poss are you rolling the cart
yeah okay as your cart is passing the
other carts they are starting to Pelt
your cart with stones crusts of bread
yeah the occasional vegetable or fruit I
mean they're geese I'm a big hunks are
they all Dragonborn or they're going
into the garden so the the the cart that
carts themselves yeah are multicolored
okay are broad but but but in terms of
the people Manning these gates you're
not gonna find a nun drag all Dragonborn
up there but these are okay since it's
multicultural I'm I'm gonna make rude
signals in every culture that I go
through a way to say it yeah yeah just
like every just to make sure I can
offend as many of these as
possible and then as we get closer are
you suggesting next to me right okay so
I would like to I I whisper to you like
okay
and I cast minor illusion on myself
you're transformed into a minor now I'm
a minor actually a minor
it was just a with the light I cast my
illusion on myself and I am what I'm
attempting to produce is the look of
feeling calm the feel of cotton fabric
of our lives
I'm sorry a driver a cart driver who
would be driving a cart with a fancy
dragon board in the back like the kind
of like a a chauffeur a dragon board
chauffeur hopeful at who looks very
wealthy who looks like someone who a
royal member you are yourself Dragonborn
yeah I would I would look dragon board
yes but it's just the look i subbed my
voice and
I want to try to approach and do some
some Bluff check you I love it you
shouldn't lean on dinar to another
that's why first of all he's crazy right
now secondly it's like yeah they're all
xenophobic and all the Dragon Warrior
claims up here hate each other sure they
see him they'll hate him could be a
different color yeah
oh wow raised us up yeah okay one knot
and you're in the back and yeah
presumably rolling around yeah yeah yeah
I think it was you gave with the just
yeah just think all whites no pupils
phone yeah yeah Rosie saw that you were
her plan and now she is on Plan B okay
so I roll up to the gates and right
alongside the rest of these carts yeah
yeah right alongside and I get you just
a look of a looked at would cause damage
right okay um do I know anything about
Scala myself very very few people
outside Scala know much about Skagen I'm
you the only thing that you know for
certain is that like janar and like
other Dragonborn enclaves yeah
they typically have a separate city for
people who are not of their clan in
their house okay so that that's this
outer ring constitutes their contact
with the outside world got it
so I the the illusion then that rosie is
cast and herself is one that looks like
the same race as the guards exactly as
you're pulling up you're pulling it in
yeah yeah and I whispered to dinar stay
down and then roll up to these guards
and I look extreme I'm sure I look
extremely impatient and wave one down
okay you're you you pull up this cart
the cart in front of you is going in the
next person is coming in and you're
sorta like trying to yeah yeah you're
trying to like a lot well yeah exactly
I don't even need to cut them off I'm
waving down a guard just to pay special
attention to me excuse me I'm speaking
and you're crying yeah yeah excuse me
nice yeah
yeah you know it you were made for them
going to do it yeah you boy
yeah that's that's probably more like it
it's like you you can feed me live you
have the boy bring my clothes what I I
do try to I'm gonna channel my inner
dinars exactly just please diaphragm
play yeah you over here now yeah the
helmet turns yeah you I have I need to I
need to get to the furnace line
immediately I need to be through the
gates I have a pregnant cousin of the
princess and she is about to lay some
eggs back here and if she does not lay
eggs in the town of Scala you aren't
going to have a world-class scandal on
your hands and I panic moment for the
back like like uh vibrates a little bit
yeah exactly hey so I'm looking for
looking for that let's see my suspicion
is a limitation right yep and I don't
suppose the shadow council is given me
nothing better have not they have not
but dude but do you need it uh maybe
we'll see we'll see that is a nine can I
give to you one of my he says he says
what is that accent Wow I am a
dishwasher hahaha
friggin our excuse me a dishwasher Oh
cuz I am channeling Dena right I my
sister you have what in there you've
been outside the city for too long your
f nope so so he's he is now approaching
the cart okay uh do not come any closer
I've now shifted my accident to be more
like this
perhaps you misheard me looks like I
have one sentence you're trying to pull
all the exactly
perhaps you misheard me this is the
princess's cousin hole affari and she is
having two eggs at the same time like
you hear in your mind they say in in
common I say tell me how to say the eggs
are coming they're arming okay I say I
turn erotic Oh
are the eggs coming no that you can get
it no give me the freaking the tongue
will come back actually yeah so I can
say all right okay great to get
performance role yeah so and my
performance forgot before I do it I got
some babies yeah thank God advantages
that's gonna be 23 performance so so he
is he is getting to the glass yeah he is
reaching out for the door and he hears
this uh he does not want to see that no
he does not want to see I'm saying that
panicked oh so she wants no part of that
and also you know that he would probably
be jailed for evencio yeah yeah um so
he's he immediately steps back starts
barking and the other at the other carts
yeah yeah basically makes that second
car to sort of like pull off in this
up angle yeah so your card is
able to roll through you just kept your
job today yeah yeah females I don't pay
any more attention he just did he just
his helmet which had gotten incredibly
wobbly so you can see you can see that
the flow of carts into the outer city
here this merchant district this is it's
not
squalor but it's not amazing it doesn't
reflect what you saw from the road of
the upper tiers in any way the the zone
just passed this is more like a bustling
you know middle-class trades town this
is their this is where they get their
dirty work done basically so you can see
these these carts coming in as they do
as they're being allowed in and it you
can you can tell that they're all sort
of navigating these streets with with
knowledge you are not 100% sure how to
manage this new environment but you are
more than capable you have incredible
ability you've been doing a lot of urban
spaces you think that you can probably
try to put something together okay so
brand new town yeah trying to get
somewhere you've never been yep
let's see it okay hell yeah these rules
have not been good today come on baby
lucky lucky lucky
two ones today I know that
look really bad oh boy it's a 10 it's a
10 so in the in the darkening city
streets you're able to start assessing
the like out here in this merchant
district this the streets the street
signs themselves are in common and Oh
draconic Thanks okay and so you can see
that it just says gates and then there's
an arrow that goes left deeper into the
city okay
gates gate sounds good let's go let's
turn left okay I'm trying to figure out
um I wrote it down but I can't find it
who or what was the name on our missive
to go to it only says the princess of
Scala princess Colin oh we have that
missive right so we could probably wash
that it'll you have it you have a
documents okay absolutely
did you forget little new yeah the whole
tube okay so I head to the gates and I
turn a walnut and say do you have the
document the the missive the quest miss
it on your markers I'm so glad that you
asked then she pulls out her beautiful
leather-bound ledger with its foil and I
say it's that level too much yes very
gently is just like everything it's like
a pornographic amount of like no it's
like those like 120 frames per second
slow mo videos oh yeah it's aunt
it's a Samara - Rosie - she's like oh my
god oh that's a rough line and then she
takes out has been so carefully kept and
then she goes yes are on paying jobs
alright hang on to that we might need it
she goes yeah sure okay
we head to the gates exactly so after
you've taken this left moved through
this bustle you basically come to like a
t-intersection
up against this wall and you can see
that there are two gates inside here so
there's three gates in the outer wall
and there's two gates that go into this
into the finer merchant district but
they're both going into the sandy
district okay indeed the line of the
left one is slightly shorter than the
right okay I charged to the front of
that one but I think I think we'll try
with the document we'll just say the way
we have a an urgent missive from the
princess in the correctly accented
draconic this time um very uh should I
should I should I should I hold on to it
yes yeah
you're I don't you touch these things I
am above it that's sure yeah I have
right I have my my wood elven handmaiden
to show you my document well it's
standard herself and she says she is 27
episodes of filthy one wash oh never
she's like yeah this makes sense that's
not ever yeah
he's been water nope she tried not to be
helped
yeah oh that's that's not true we went
through the water to visit that's that's
true but I think that the rich oils that
had accumulated provided a sort of his
little work omega-3 oh yeah yeah yeah
very yeah so I say all that yeah he
doesn't actually look he doesn't
actually look at you
excuse me neither of them look hello so
there's no passage into the city for non
Dragonborn at this time of night did you
she looks like a dragon board I do
usually you'll be going alone here you
won't be bringing your retinue I I have
to this is this is the princesses
cousins retinue we have a missive from
the princess herself do you not see this
it's in her own hand this is not the
this is not a royal house paper this is
this is some contrivance these are
coming he takes he reaches over and
reaches over interesting grab the
document this is official he said yeah
he says I don't know what an
acquisitions incorporated is doesn't
matter
first off I hate this signature and she
she looks she's like looks at Rosie like
to translate you just signature signed
signature signs princess right there
look
the initial signature twice it's it's on
every friggin statue ever okay it's
right there so you have beta paper this
is your forger hope this is not my
fighter one that looks at one looks at
Rosina's just cuz I don't have to go in
I can stay out here and the shooter is
is just winks okay fine you're having
your way my incredibly loyal
servant filthy as she is will stay out
and we will continue I saw you and
denied what sin I don't even know that
he's visible in the car yeah yeah yes
yeah somebody Chris is in there too I am
sure sure I'm laying low but sweet so
what so while I makes a big scene of
this yeah like a huge scene and she's
talking in elvish comment and she's like
oh I'm so insulted I'm supposed to be
here to send the missives I guess I'll
have to go somewhere in this horrible
say I don't get to go in the great place
with all the dragons in the second the
second of the two skaaland guards goes
oh yeah like I didn't think you were the
same I don't like this but I'm like
would rouse and elves suck walnut does a
thing to him and she goes what you know
is something extremely I mean she storms
off big show here's what I would love to
try and do storms off cos hmm soon she's
out of eyeshot she transforms into her
weasel because it's getting dark correct
yes oh yes quite she goes ahead and just
squeeze these on up to the car and she
Swezey sign up inside the undercarriage
with the with the ground effects yeah we
did then we turn it on there's just a
little weasel shadow it's like this
would be a this is the first meme in the
Forgotten Realms yeah it's just this
shadow of this weasel against these
bright lights sneaked in again
that's what that means yes I'm yeah it's
like on a carriage there's this and then
there's these wheels right but then
there's the little what is it yeah a
little weasel holder yeah anyway in
siddhis crambles scrambles up there and
then uh in her in her head because she
can't speak at all she's thinking so
they think they come over to check the
cart one of them one of them is trying
to assess exactly what sort of creature
coriander is is not able to so they go
back and open up the they go back and
open up the the cart itself and inside
they can see a salivating hot dinar
coppered rolling around on the ground
yeah this is hyperventilating I assume
like Inuyasha yeah yeah but it's dark so
that can I see his colour oh yeah
absolutely
if this is there's also other markings
don't forget Gennari dragon board have
tails as well sure and so he but he also
sees kethry Strout yeah and I've I have
I've got this up or my head but it's
very clear that I'm not the build of a
dragon board or anything like that yeah
yeah and he he's looking in there he
surpasses his pikestaff with him he says
who now and you're coming why we are
here at the behest of the princess do we
know why no but you know what we respect
the royalty of scala enough to come
without any questions that she hasn't
even paid us to be here but we respect
your royalty so much that that is why we
are here hmm you're the persuade okay
and usually use did you oh man
for not I'm not gonna be good it's gonna
be an eight oh yeah - on it no wait yeah
you rolled it's ten yes sorry Ted
yeah yeah yeah don't you know I rolled a
ten yeah 12 sorry yeah I I took - it's
an Ironman - um he's just like he's in
his mind you can see that he is sort of
calculating all the different futures
that result from this decision made at
this point in the middle of the night
let me the goddamn mouth let me let me
put it to you this way you can let us
stay here wait it out go in the morning
yes but I'm going to tell the princess
exactly who you are where you are and
she will find you and it's just a matter
of time you can let us in now let us do
our job or the princess can fire you
tomorrow when we do get in fix it give
me your badge number yeah yeah
what are you you're like ro seven foot
two you got you got these little frills
she's gonna find you no problem okay so
he he feels at this point that it would
be worse for him but the outcome is so
negative on the other side of this that
he is going to allow this to occur but
he does offer a warning hmm he says
regardless of what the requests might
have said any attempts to try to see the
princess tonight is not a good idea is
not a good strategy even with this
document why I would see the princess
tomorrow we're seeing it on that from
under the card okay there's something
about the way he's telling me this that
doesn't sound like he's just being a
dick to me he's just he's like oh no
yeah yeah I mean you're welcome to
assess it okay check what do
you want here
perception inside its right
it's four I guess I can't speak you said
some words sure thing yeah yeah but you
don't you don't get any
you're not sensing any kind of ill-will
or malice yeah it's just one of these
things where you feel like it would take
a very long time to explain it it's just
like friendly advice
yeah okay all right well let us in I
have understood your words and we will
take them into account but we do need to
get inside right he says right
please commend her kind gaze upon gate
one eight one
you bet I read gate one gate once sir
but gate one actually the gay
ones cool you look up at the gate it's a
clearly Gate 2 1 1 is 1 so you you roll
from the filthier more decrepit outer
husk of scala into a something that is a
little bit like I say more middle to
upper class the construction is superior
the levels of toxic smoke you feel like
are lower
nice you feel like that's something that
they prize yeah up here but you do need
a place to stay the night here okay how
long is your minor illusion last I
dropped it okay okay I dropped it
secretly without telling anyone yes
mid-sentence the guy in the middle of it
I turn into a halfling you don't know
anything you're useless right so right
if I were to ask you okay you got your
friends here you yes you do you just
drill at me yeah legally or allowed to
stay in our cart
squatter's rights it's county-by-county
but okay well I'm happy to pull us up
somewhere quiet
we could still just try to go see the
princess yeah maybe she's afraid of you
coming
[Music]
I'm with Weezy on this - a hard weasel
yeah it's a cold we don't play let's go
for it and if we got a camp let's camp
like right up against the final gate
yeah like I don't want to like we'll be
polite over here no it's ridiculous
yeah don't teach em we got business can
uh yeah can we send a message to the
palace that we're here I can you've seen
the princess before I have met her
that's right that's right
why'd he do that to start with yeah
what's the range on that maybe anywhere
Oh ultra I can old place playing all
right you know I think it's a twice
plane essentially - or love it takes
Thursday like a 5% chance that doesn't
come literally 5% yeah yeah someone so
you have to love it
someone thought about it all right yeah
% sounds right your plane it just feels
good what it's taken 10 like it's yeah
go ahead all right so um let's see
uh yeah but yeah I don't even know her
name
oh yeah it doesn't matter um what was
then it was the actual text print so
just as you come over I know yes but
it's like but it's like there was some
like a polite like here's a dollar
right here's old and we had to return it
upon our return to scholar we don't yeah
we don't get unless you get do not have
her name yeah okay doesn't it doesn't
take her name though okay
and then I say write down all our quest
givers exactly yeah no it's acquisitions
incorporated read large we have your
coin it's just like this fun little
comment card yeah yeah
we found your coin pardon our dust we're
here now
well like we're and and ready to they
have audience I guess yeah all right
let's do that yeah it after a couple
moments you receive a message in return
says this is princess sources sorcerer
adjunct to contacting the princess in
this way isn't it front and Beyond
illegal oh you will find lodgings in the
city until such time as we can meet you
tomorrow can I get him back because he's
a new person that I've just been
acquaintance to it exactly it's like new
contact added ok so we got to find
lodgings now yeah we're there they're
taking their sweet time getting a
getting anything out of you yeah see I
don't want you either
you're right ears we're just sleeping a
card stirred your cuddle puddle with the
prospect of not seeing her tonight
snap out of it are you caught dust
myself off get it together and I'll be
like yeah good timing
welcome back yeah no I wasn't myself I'm
going through like the stages now it's
like bargaining and like I'll give you
each fifty gold if we leave today you
have my personal golden like 50 gold
apiece can you roll up reception check
please their latest please
your servant dinar of the noble house
split Senate junior and I give he gives
any gifts no that's just little indeed
indeed now if you are viewing you get a
$20 gift certificate but if you are a
subscriber you get one of these awesome
Elderwood academy thingamajigs will sign
this for you at tabletop and then we'll
send it to you it's gonna be pretty
sweet now you hear
outside the cart you are in the middle
of what must seem like a negotiation for
your life with terrorists you hear the
unmistakable sound of dice on a table he
does either this is he rolled it 20 I
bet I have my little gold bag or I'm
offering anyone you say I'm like we'll
stay the night
fifty gold pieces each to leave in the
morning first light will just leave you
got it buddy we all got paid you guys
all got paid absolutely sounds great
let's do that take a little snooze I
could leave with some total of our
entire enterprise whenever I want fifty
gold is imatinib right okay think I
could rob everyone right now this is
personal this isn't assessment from my
personal bank account this is personal
huh yeah this time yeah this time it's
personal
yeah so the one day from retirement but
precious cart and coriander the friendly
metallic horse happens to be parked near
and in on a corner of this street and
this Inn is called the day's end really
start to loosen you think that you smell
even from inside the cart you think that
you might use my smell smoke on the wind
gambling siren yeah yeah exactly not not
not they're really delicious kind like
the real like the smell of a place
burning can I perhaps to the ground hmm
can I do it sure you do a bite I can do
it but I also know are you still busy
boy vampire maybe a good perception
checks that have to do is smell in fact
I get natural advantage being yeah I am
because I'm but can you see it like on
the step block it's like Weezy ma'am
like games advantage um yes so easy Ruth
on on on on wisdom so yeah I want to do
a check to see if I can discern where it
is potentially come from just a little
absolutely look like a bloodhound but
that's an eight but hang on wait there's
more
and then I'd your perception onus
another eight wow that's an eight so
that's that humanity yeah it's very very
good even at that it's like AIT's just
dude do you camera do you want to pop
hop down the road and find this yeah I
wanna yeah absolutely
so you you you go to you you travel the
you travel what is known as the weasel
Road I just want to do a very small bark
at my companions like you know you give
him that premium yet you and we
following
cthe risk goes like in the wrong way
feeding trough gotta wake up let's do
cat room yeah so you you know jump on a
barrel you know skitter up the side
assassins we have the dream yeah exactly
and you can see two blocks over
first of all something else oh you'd
notice as we see although they don't
notice you is that is that armed
incredibly tough looking guards moving
in in groups of three is not a comp is
not an uncommon sight it's like it was
already a rough spot in the in the outer
city but there isn't even anything for
them to accomplish but they're
everywhere so you look you look over
from this from this lip of the building
and you see a you see an inn called the
well pinworm hmm and you can see like
great fires inside the inn mm-hmm and
you can see people being led out like on
a chain
multiple people let out and you can see
a group of guards like the one I
described they have actually cut the
sign you you you you have time to read
it just before they cut the sign down
and throw it through the window oh this
is the torching situation I love this
great um how how how far gone is the
burning it's I mean it's it's most of
what is happening is inside it would be
hard made without without having a lot
of knowledge about the weapon world
gonna be hard to say but it seems like
it's going well and they've added some
additional fuel right um okay so I'm
like up on a building right now yeah
you're sure to pop all other green okay
um and clean burn what clean burn yeah
it's a clean where I got a lower that
carbon put on I'm disgusted to zero I
wonder I want to just bring us back for
some real context real quick so for some
magic hate cities
hate cities in the best sense then for
people to be like ostracizing of each
other for being like no I'm the best
shitty city dweller like this is like
like yeah like squabbling among fiends
sir yeah yeah what are the people look
like that are being led out like in
Chains do they look like they're
Dragonborn er now but some are some are
some are right okay um so she's going to
turn back into herself and she's up five
away people yeah she just she's just
basically sit she's just that she's
seated up on these to do a bite come
fight the fire she turns back into
walnut and then she does a fight fire no
she is gonna use my same thing that we
used to clean out the and she's gonna
create her rain cloud shake justice go
yes which is she wants it she's gonna
like do this thing with that hurt motion
as she does where she would conjure up a
cloud and the cloud would rain just that
we didn't we cleaned out there
absolutely yeah okay so yes she's gonna
be
everything sir just just describe for me
the process how do you how do you how do
you coax sorry you beseech the natural
world to Walmart in these cases where
she's doing anything that's natural it's
like she has those feelings all natural
in she has those feelings inside her
we're in the way that she stumped
someone set that cloud it's like you
know it's from some kind of tumultuous
Ness deep inside and she she does this
and that's just her motion that she does
like swirl it's like a swirly one I
don't know I know the Shiva and then as
she normally imagines um it would be
like oh she's I was writing it yeah as
if she's like manifesting it
she's like stirring it into existence
mmm actually absolutely nothing happens
she mmm laughs for a second yes okay and
thinking like okay I did not concentrate
enough maybe I'm distracted yeah yeah
okay and then she like stirs the pot
again
what am i giving nothing I go are you
okay all right we're with you what are
you doing bullies daddy already having a
stroke yeah so um at this point well not
whole like snap she'll do some of the
other gestures that she does get she's
like doing anything to try and like
conjured up like concentrating really
hard
nothing you are able to bring about the
magical effect that you craved but it is
said about half of its ability Wow it's
just it's just consumed by the it's
consumed by this flame just burned away
you here's some hiss I feel marked by
the hissing as if it is mocking me okay
that's unfortunate
you have a solo dreads yeah it happens
to a lot of druids
um okay the fire needs magic um yeah
just the fire ain't magic no so I guess
that that that's like the really about
the only thing that she would um know
she wants to do something real quick
so her tried-and-true spelling the
spells that she can do would be um like
druid crafts where she could like make
make it make something make something
really quickly happen so real quick she
sees like what a window box with like
some plants in it typically she could
make something bloom and like this is
like should be bread and butter right
yeah yeah this is a three year old druid
this is druid 101 this is like I hope
you're in the right class you know yeah
like I'm not like she sneezes and stuff
can bloom and she looks at me sick
looking plant I'm just yeah
it immediately fills with life that it
was flopping down it's growing rigid
that's from the center of the bulb
three crystalline tendrils burrow up
from the middle and then split out from
the top of the plant
she and seek prey yes yeah she takes out
four more there very quickly and grabs
it and cuts it and then doesn't look at
what's in her hand it could still be
wriggling you tell me but puts a four
mother away and it's just like
horrifyingly crying to get into her fist
as she makes her way from perfect for
folks to get back to them and then right
before she gets them she'll open her
hand is it crushed is it done yes just
bent wriggling um she tries to we'll see
do a produce flame to just burn it away
in her own hand to get any flames going
well then she just tosses it behind her
someone else just got bigger fish to fry
her slicker but that is I mean she is
spit she got nerfed
yeah yeah you got spell impotent um but
she will join the rest of the group
exactly so so back at the things are
jumping back at the day's end and yeah
we relied on Freya not in and you can
see that this place is not on fire which
is a competitive advantage in this
marketplace but it is on fire
metaphorically
oh yeah it's late if it's what you mean
ed you I'm I want to put that out yeah
thank you exactly you think that this in
for the environ that it's in it seems
like it might have a rough clientele it
might be a tougher place to turn over
maybe they may have some built-in
defenses against the watch inside here
you can see many bay the many of the
clientele have thick cloaks like wide
profiles underneath them you can see in
the back left corner you can see a vault
table
Merilee clicking away you can see you
can see people standing up and kicking
table legs and moving away as you enter
there is the unmistakable scent of a
strawberry field in summer so we'll get
back to that I guess but it's probably
not important yeah it's who cares it's
you know whatever but flavor exactly so
but as you so as as your as your group
rolls in here
it's it's not hard to find a table but
as you sit down
more people are definitely trying to
come in and they look like they are
dressed for a night out like they're
trying to find a place to go pushing
through this crowd you see a young man
black hair gentil green pointed cap loot
at his side to push through but like in
such a way that the loot is always never
touched by any other entity that
fretboard is a the keys bent back it
doesn't seem like a the lutes that
you've seen or not thus normal lutes
like that your experience with bleeds so
that they are very sharp this is weird
it's a huge problem cause that's like a
clubbing yeah exactly it's like come in
here with that type of yeah it's
rewarding tranny he walks in you guys
have taken this table by that by the
window and as he's able to push through
the rest of the largely Dragonborn
audience he looks over at the table and
says there is an inn that is not on fire
and is not being cracked out here it is
it's time to celebrate so he moves up he
moves up to a small stage near the front
and begins to like significantly
substantially profoundly flatter
Dragonborn nah I love this song with the
tracks there's a lot of there's a lot of
songs about sort of unrequited love
between Dragonborn and like polymorphs
dragons this is a theme that happens a
lot
oh yeah the origin of the Dragonborn
race there's a song about how each of
the each of the Dragonborn clans are in
bed Oh
what do they say I want a Gennari all
grow turgid audience what did they say
about the dream yeah what are we
learning about the nori from the dog oh
the basically says that a degenerate man
have two dicks Wow yeah I'm growing out
the side of the other perpendicular you
and you belong in jail oh we're all
having fun but now tiller is down
planning rest when they say yeah what he
says to do excitement like Rosie looks
at I'll never tell you know what's bad
enough no we get to God so you can see
where this where this bard has set up
his shop you can see like fresh pies
being brought out from the back dessert
pies are being brought to each dessert
pies are being brought to each table for
for your slicing use excellent
strawberry rhubarb her she'd been almost
about to search no and then as soon as
she sees the pies she's immediately no
no it's like a memory pie like it's it's
it's a gruesome it is a perfect
manifestation of that am i impressed
with the craftsmanship the line this is
this is definitely gonna say it's not
your grandma's pie but grandmas are very
good at pies yeah no this is this is
your grandmother's your honor this is my
grandmother's pie oh you know exactly so
you have and then between songs the bard
is saying you know I got this bleep at
fretted boards in the higher merchant
district afraid boards for vetted Lords
bedded Lords and then he goes back into
his his piece and commercially she check
I should check that out competition I
didn't want to buy a lute until now
subscribers don't see that
so dinar Blitzen yeah not this place
this is a this looks like a good vault
stable yeah I mean I got a there is hot
there is hot action I gotta get that
siren song that table whoo oh I believe
I can
I believe it so did you do take a seat
oh yeah I run over there if anyone wants
to join and ripped cheer me on
nope I might get interesting cuz I'll be
nice to gamble she well she she you've
got on her so yeah it seems mentally I
think that kind of a that's true she
doesn't know that um but she's got like
30 gold pieces but she's been saving up
for the last 50 years or so hmm Oh her
done make it interesting she's on a
fixed income bad influence she's on a
fixed income I gotta play this oh don't
worry I can show you then trust me this
this individual this individual once I
got him yeah this this individual wants
very much for you to play and they are
willing to instruct you in this ways
although being Dragonborn it's their
presumption most likely that they won't
have to yeah I mean you've played faults
before yeah exactly exactly yeah you're
Sam no walnut my dog eyes have mine too
I had very good success with your dice
last time huh and then I had to take
them home and salt them so no one's the
ones that are sharp I know I got these
this contrast this contrast should be
very good nice try
okay taint my dice guys changing yeah I
got mine ooo DICE Chandru yeah okay I'm
upset whoa wow this is just a toe I want
to lean over ten years - I just see with
it you know you keep it a nice little
bed
that's actually the the Barbies
background you know I want to ask them
what is that what's this crackdown about
what's going on what did he mention
something right oh it's just who you're
talking to
just somebody at an adjacent table or
just like excuse me man you're Hollow
yeah I play leeteuk Dave Nick away they
don't want to talk to you okay figures
I'm used to it yeah it's just no I mean
they're eating like a couple different
yeah owns like hey no all right but
they're dry there is someone who has
spoken to the party all right now
dinerral attend yeah do you recall the
process well do did you say you're gonna
bet yeah here ah she isn't that much but
she'll throw down shows weird in here
yeah you'll be able to place your bets
for it yeah sure now so as soon as as
soon as there is a figure in the corner
that has his feet up on a table and his
arms folded under his cloak and as soon
as he sees that two people are betting
on the same player he comes over and
physically grabs the dealer like by the
back of their neck like by the back of
their shirt and just pulls them off like
just like this like a napkin just a
useless amount of weight just over here
we win we win no no that's that's not
what this indicates so hero remember
you're trying to beat my d8 yes on your
2d6 that remember if you roll do you
throw yeah they're right there yeah
we're here so if you mind exactly so if
you go if you roll passive you're old 9
10 11 or 12 yeah you lose yeah if I roll
one you lose yeah
I gotta hit the middle
twelve oh boy but it was doubles he
laughs hey do you own this place
chum the manner of speaking oh yeah keep
it
sorry many places seven snorts yeah
that's right yeah
Oh another place by the time this nights
over talk so much try you know I know
two two pushes yeah take that seven ten
senators damn it you platinum cheaters
yes he reaches as he reaches out to
scoop the chips back you can see that he
has a series of bites around his around
the knuckles and fingers of it yeah
right hand he's a dragon born right
absolutely okay then I shouldn't plan
him flesh his own hands
yeah what's wrong he's like what's wrong
with your hands yeah go yourself
they look all messed up and you're
stupid
fine you but you but you in actually
yeah I win on ties or anything you're
gonna tell me about your stupid knuckles
now sure I beat you on this one tell me
what's wrong with your dumb hand
Rosie is studying the is watching
I'm losing a lot of money yeah I lost
all my money about 30 seconds of this
all the money I was gonna give you leave
right now look are their drinks are
there as they will not serve this table
[Laughter]
you're always beating it by one oh my
god daddy now come on till I have a
question for yes this is Rosie and
Carrick yes Rosie um the guards at the
gate told us that we shouldn't try to
see the princess tonight what's that
about in Europe haffley
right yeah yeah so there's a lot of
reasons he looks back to the table what
are the reasons
give me like I say top three yeah she's
a princess and you're not well she
summoned us so to the over to the table
I'm a prince over to the table maybe a
platinum Dragonborn approaches and sort
of pushes everybody out of the way
what sort of hassle messing with me out
there hey was this crackdown about
they're gonna let me in here they're
burn another bar down
I'll try don't try and get drunk all the
time I'm a platinum Dragonborn what's
the what you wasn't in common
oh yeah so this one can understand yeah
he he whistles and one of the massive
creatures in cloaks comes over and just
picks you up and then let just look live
like this like a just like a barrel is
he able to because I'm using masks of
many faces oh absolutely okay do I still
have the same weight yeah yeah he is
incredibly strong
oh he just picks you up and then takes
you over to the door and then puts you
down and then goes back to what he was
doing
that's nice yeah
you two cover better than me she did
cover better than me
it's terrible don't with my one alright
that's it you're out
Madeline how Oh No that what are you
gonna feed that horse I don't know give
me a perception killed my horse
I'm gonna cut pieces out horse often use
a gamble it away 21 womp womp womp
that's two from the dark shadow council
mayor labor space it reserves a minute
ago okay servant dinar blatant and has
once again delivered unto you a book Oh
understood understood now so here's
here's it when you see the dice yeah
he rolls it and you see it hit like this
but for extra split standard yeah
exactly
pretty extra split second and then fun
no say what's cheating hey how can you
prove it I saw it I saw you cheat you're
cheating you're a platinum cheater
you're disgusting kind all cheat cheater
cheater that's rich I sold his hood back
and you see platinum scales rings in
between each plate he says you would
talk to me of cheating you who would
steal a man's daughter shadow counsels
merely was pleasing we will of course be
back for Table Talk momentarily thank
you so much don't go away
you