time is the enemy of the past it
threatens the fastest wedding you
wouldn't make it past a second and ask
the question
play it brash and reckless to choose a
cautious solution you saw it was prudent
in any Sepulcher poker to don't become
the putrid it's that well-fed I pursue
in no mountain too steep for dungeon too
deep to send expanded that marks up to
the top of the peak of beneath they see
Yugi they come like sharks to it while I
swim in that line even like Carl Barks
through it so send your National Parks
drew it I'll send him home in a natural
box with a close tie but most of the
parts included save your breath for a
cleric confessor death is a lesson that
life is a tenured professor but if
you're seeking my official advice sign
on the dotted line and wish in the
choice hello fuck I know how to do this
aye aye
ELISA did you adjust this in any way get
it wrong obviously this is very
emotional for me it's a very emotional
game obviously we you know two players
two in died last week I hope it's not a
spoiler for you but if you hadn't seen
last week's episode I'm sure was very
surprising to see that they were not
here but I will reference their spectres
out of respect respect er I'll pay my
respects just good stuff Lee we think
they were they were holding them they
were like their rug that held the room
together
hello I am Tycho Brahe hey of Penny
Arcade in packs
I am also a manifest Hereward run CEO of
acquisitions incorporated but today I'm
Jerry Hogan's I'm going to be running a
game of Dungeons and Dragons for my
friends half of which are dead
to my right historically would have been
Dragonborn narcissist dinar blitz and
but he's dead and then obviously to the
right of my right emerging as though
from a mister out or later he would if
he had not been annihilated to my left
not your grandma's grandma
except for those rare cases where she is
your grandma's grandma Rosie bee stinger
what are you kidding you've never seen
it so close
yeah scrappy exactly um to the left of
my left repping the natural world walnut
dawn grass it's in my tree land in your
tree it lives there so this is these are
this is like the power combos you know
some classic Marvel comic exactly
already we're having a great time how is
this side of Jerry's hit oh that's
different
um I haven't really seen you from this
angle before I think the other ones your
good side I'm into I'm intimidated by
this but yeah I mean it's it's sad
obviously we did lose a couple players
so well yeah they died a hardship here
yeah exactly
what other scenario is possible now when
last we saw our heroes as I did make
some intimations as to some of the
events that did occur insofar as Chris
drab discovered his father's secret
laboratory the work of which was almost
certainly what had him murdered for
heresy in the very very firm strictures
of drought society where you know really
really understanding that their gods
besides loathe is like had no no bad
thing to do but it was within a small
dagger that his father had hidden this
secret laboratory and at long last
hundreds of years hence his son did
enter that place perfectly pristine
absolutely maintained in perfect
readiness for research and he discovered
things inside their strange things one
of which was a jar that included a kind
of writhing worm that when looked at
from different angles appeared to extend
to infinity the other thing was a seed
that had been kept inside a sort of bell
jar container and then fixed in
something like a jewel setting that
almost immediately began to sort of gnaw
at Kathuria album talks yet well talk
all kinds of shit about his dad all
kinds of stuff and this seed took the
opportunity to escape from this and then
unfold itself on the ground into into
the shape of a magnificently clad elven
warrior one presumes of the enclave that
walnut serves as well but it would be a
very very you would you would need some
very very old books to determine the the
serial numbers on some of this equipment
I don't like to assume that all wood
elves are from the same Grove well it's
not it's not even about that it's it's
more about listen it's how that's how
the campaign goes anyway you and I can
just play this game you know what I mean
no okay understood understood well
listen I can run that game also that is
the scenario that we find ourselves in
now two Swift flashes of her emerald
green blade have left cthe wrist drab
and dinar Blitzen of course in there you
know Christmas job as himself and then
dinar in the guise of Chris drab much as
you yourselves are in this place but
there was two quick flashes of this
blade and then and now this this woman
is trying to absorb as much information
as she can but job one was apparently to
interact in a lethal way with your
companions so I think Rosie's initial
reaction to this would be immediately
shield walnut with her tiny little body
she's in front with her staff out like
you won't get her to you back off you
crazy son of a bitch
walnut kneels and says I'll be hot
behind the grandmother who is yes
walnut kneels and says she says does she
know she doesn't know that this is part
of her order or not I mean though she
can take a good guess but this is
someone that's probably involved with
her but whatever the only piece of
information we have is that it takes her
less than a second to kill half the
party and for whatever reason she has
chosen not to yeah in this case it's the
woman meals oh and I mean there's like a
lot of emotions right like everyone who
went down but this person isn't in front
of us and seems like a high ranking elf
I've lived a long life I'm very happy
she goes she points her sword which is
something like for mother right
obviously like every like every plant
there is something unique about its
manufacturer but this is this is clearly
a weapon that this was not plucked from
a tree a few months ago this is this is
a instrument of war and then she she as
I said she extends the blade toward
basically your sternum and then with a
couple quick tilts of the blade sort of
gestures you to get up
like that okay I stand up back I'm like
at attention yet she says how is it that
you knew to bow but you have not
instructed your handmaiden in the proper
obeisance top woman says she is old and
her back is awful not wrong but hurtful
so I so I I bow in her stead that seems
to satisfy her seems to satisfy her for
the time and she says there are other
questions how came you to travel with
this drow and his mutant this drow was
at one time an emissary of the goddess
and when that was made known to me I
gladly traveled with him which got us
justjust haughty yeah she who portrays
it's good fucking so good I'm sorry I
got I got super please - let me let me
let me get back in and she says child
you must be very hungry are very thirsty
we haven't heard no one has heard no
sage no scholar has heard from her
indeed we act against her if this man
and you are suggesting that this man
somehow was an envoy of Mela
then what I did was absolutely correct
and a woman immediately it is like oh oh
no oh oh so much there's a couple hard
blinks yeah like as as there is an
attempt to incorporate new information
yeah um it's at this point yeah woman's
been wearing that like wooden medallion
of nails and she's just like making sure
the bit like covering up and she says uh
she says Maliki granted me a vision and
in that vision I was her and in that
vision he was mainly and I saw we saw
Mela be captured and imprisoned and
that's why she stopped responding to
prayers what force this is just beggars
belief what force could cease bailiffs
without her wanting it to occur it was
hungry and amethyst and crystalline and
I I don't play I understand the brow
froze there you may recall that long
long ago there was a period of time
where the early EPA had to manage a
crystalline entity then as well there's
a few breadcrumbs of information here
that are slowly being amalgamated into
something edible mm-hmm and then she
uses the tip of her boot to turn dinar
over onto his back Oh Rosie's not happy
about that Rosie's instantly has shifted
no and is protecting the corpse of dinar
don't touch him
did not touch my boys they says he says
this is a I don't know what to call this
creature I don't know what mad sorcerer
made this chimera well you know drow she
is beginning to pace around this room as
I recall we are down on the main floor
at this point
the party having aggregated themselves
after getting various things from place
to place and trying to put things trying
to harvest as much as you could from
this from this venue she as she is
walking closer to one of the ledges
where people must have been greeted at
another time of this place you can see
that the shield actually drops out of
her right hand and that she steadies
herself to keep herself from collapsing
onto the floor I I go up to her and I
don't touch her
but and making that very worried like oh
can I help
expression your clothes yeah yeah yeah
she she looks over you and there's no
there's no pain and this this is not the
same face that you saw before I don't
mean the same physicality right it's
obviously the same person I'm not sure I
met that sounds like me but that's not
but that's not what I'm trying to do
this time the look it's an expression of
deep maybe even intimate familiarity and
as she as she looks over and as you
kneel but with the correct amount of
help like the sort of help where it's
like Oh
help you would offer a proud person yeah
you just want to make sure they saw you
trying to help but you know if you think
you think that if you actually committed
to any of it it would probably be bad
for some other reason
and then she just says vervain no then
she she looks over at Rosie and says
we must make ready and you know this
because you are a clever old woman and
you have performed this task more than
one time but you can see something like
the soap bubble shimmer that you see
when you're utilizing your ability to
tell a story and travel and you can see
that there is sort of in the area effect
of this of this floor of the house you
can see that there is a sort of
thickening of the air just outside of
the group a sphere that can readily
contain everyone who is here and present
and having been down in the Underdark
for days upon days now the light the the
said the rich texture of sunlight on
grass and plants and a sweet breeze it
is just it's all manifesting itself
around you you can feel a cool welcomed
breeze in addition to this place is now
flooded with bright light unwelcome here
certainly very unnerved by this right no
indeed indeed it's probably worth taking
a moment to say that outside the ruin of
what was once housed Ruth Li it now
looks something like a mystic Lantern
where every window of this place is just
firing beams of hot sunlight directly
from the wreckage out into
out into the gloom of the Underdark
there's a there's there's a dry der
rifling through a ribcage that looks up
and hisses briefly we'll keep them away
but your your selves are changed also
along with this template that she seems
to be applying to this fixed area you
have you're just you're aware of
yourself in this place it's like it's
like you're seeing yourself the way
someone else would see you right you're
conscious you're conscious that someone
else's expectations are being just your
best frosted with them you're contained
inside someone else's fantasy
functionally speaking and so for example
the staff of the master has retained
most of its overall shape and you can
handle it with ease just as you always
could but it has a fixed blades at each
end blades of ridiculously sharp green
glass for mother for good or ill looks
almost exactly like for mother almost
exactly like for mother the difference
is that the two of you are now clad in
armor similar to that which you saw on
this strange woman who has grown herself
from a seed no no in fact you can see
you can you know that this is walnut you
know that this is your friend walnut but
she is much taller and indeed you
yourself are tall as well like yeah
it is it is a
that's the closest thing that it draws
you to mind is there were two air sort
of air pipes to like blow holes on the
wandering crypt mm-hmm one of which you
were you're able to get down into and
the other contained EPA druids of both
in a bit but they have two modes of garb
this week I'm a leaky guard my Alika
garb and a male ahthe garb that had that
clearly had some kind of function you
don't know if it was for if it had a
ritual function if it was for intramural
sports like there's a there's no way to
know really but this is these are the
proportions and the style and the that
is that was evoke by that roomful of
these stone these petrified priestesses
it was I did not mean to alliterate this
is very serious business obviously
grandmother well do are we able to talk
can we can tell our bob solutely yeah
you can move quite freely explore the
space okay it has an open concept
excellent um does walnut look like
walnut but taller yeah in a lot of ways
yes okay are there any other significant
differences to her appearance the main
thing you would say is that she is the
decked in armor that is similar to the
woman that you saw before but is lighter
and allows for more allows for a more
reasonable movement the the garb of the
the garb of the woman that emerged from
the seed is impenetrable okay and the
bodies of our friends what's up with
them come on if you had friend bodies
they are not visible here but you in
fact as you as you look you you look
down to see them
what you do see are hundreds looking out
from just from your feet and out you can
see hundreds upon hundreds of Enclave
warrior druids massing around you and
the woman from the seed okay so the
house is now filled with with elves you
cannot there's what house oh yeah okay I
see so we're on a platform we can see
this army forming mm-hmm and the
platform itself is built around the base
of a tree whose genus is known to you
it reaches high high up into the sky and
you can tell that there is a light in
the core of this that will allow you to
with a moment's intention travel down
where their roots are to smite your foes
so Rosie looked down at you and then
down back to where our friends were and
they're gone and there's a we've we've
been utterly transported and I think
losses are shit immediately yeah we have
to get back they weren't dead they were
not dead we have to get back we have to
get to that grandmother grandmother
clearly we've been wrapped up in
something but I have to see what is
happening here I have to see this I have
to know
okay ah okay just let's let's hurry this
up
let's make it quick let's find let's
find what we need to find but we have to
get back I also want to get back to them
okay oh we look good you look great
okay oh you do I turned to the woman
that we came here with and I you know
immediately like this the template that
comes along with these shifts you can
feel your own face soften as you see her
you know that this is Nilayam know a
grove keeper which for all practical
purposes anyone else would think of as a
like a groundskeeper mm-hmm but you know
that the grove they're talking about is
the entire world right there is one
growth and it reaches from the top to
the bottom of the planet and it's a
grove keepers job to ensure that that
remains the case so this is a type of
ultra general in the in the culture of
the Enclave and I I'm giving like
somebody else's knowledge so I look at
her and I say no way and what what what
do you we have no words are surprising
coming in right mouth - it just rolls on
right out yeah they're automatic and and
I say what will you have us do what she
good she steps close mm-hm and kisses
you and this feels like totally normal
it feels however you want it to feel
because yours you are still walnut yeah
you you know that you you know that you
would you know that this would be a
normal thing but how you feel about it
right now is up to you um their romantic
type kiss or some kind of like
no it's a tube on each cheek yeah okay
no it's just that it comes along with
it's a very authoritative it it is like
work yes yeah I don't
a woman doesn't pull away or anything
but she is extremely conflicted yeah
it's just his feelings
yeah right and then she when she pulls
away she looks out over this gathered I
mean army a battalion of Enclave warrior
druids and without looking without
looking back at you she says there will
be two after I say oh very well after
after what she laughs because you
couldn't possibly not know she's
calendar she holds her she holds her
sword up in the air and then you can see
all the bright faces of these warriors
just with maximal adoration trust and
respect and then she says blade words
and you see everyone raised their weapon
from the ground in front of them they're
all sort of they're all sort of like
like kneeling mm-hmm and you can see
them all raised their sword or their
staff or their daggers like to their
lips and you can just hear like this
whisper throughout the whole thing it's
you were literally the only two people
not doing it just oh I do it
it's weird I immediately start to look
at Rosie like
it's like when you take a blade of grass
and you go yeah the ring follows after
the after the whispering is done
obviously you know blade words typically
are only for your spouse and your blade
but if you would like to tell us what
they are purely for the use of the of
the shadow Council to be in their
service only for your spouse in your
weapon oh yeah okay so while it holds up
and she goes she says mother mother I am
just I am but your daughter mother's
mother is a plus so you know you have
your own challenge I mean basically this
is the darksouls of blade words because
you've got like a blade on each side
yeah I don't give me the Pythons I don't
know how also they could be the key like
like gun show I don't know
Rosie is not so sacrilegious as to
partake in the ceremony so she she
wouldn't whisper anything you know like
she she would watch and and like make
breathy gestures just so that no one
arrested her but to that like there's no
there's no God she wants to summon
there's no spiritual connection she's
looking for okay well so I could not
love you more it is a plus so you can
see so after after you've spoken to for
mother and held it out you can see you
know how but you remember how in school
like you got to look at the plant
like underneath the thing and you could
see that this whole plant was actually
made of all these tiny adjacent little
gems in there you can see those forming
and then filling with some kind of
liquid in and around the blade I know I
know it's true now you said the blade
words are tried to these do it you can
read them but don't read
loud you'll need them later these are
your miracles
excuse yes what these are your miracles
understand that understand that you know
would your childhood in the EPA your
childhood in the EPA was functionally
you know anyone else outside of the crib
garden forest would have said that it
was like a weird witch cult we don't
like that word we don't like that I know
that we don't like the word witch cult
or the W word the W slur oh no it's just
called the C word right and this you
don't know about this Wow like this
these are the stories that you would
hear with no context and the presumption
imagine if imagine if like the stories
your grandfather told you about the size
of the fish were actually true like this
is your year was an army this big yeah
there was an army there was an army this
big and so you can see the sun shining
off of this blade and growth deeper in
the land is the first into the NEMA's
here
Oh on the way down okay down into the
Underdark I'm I look at Rosie and I grab
your hand and then I go in I'm with you
yeah so you I'm dragging him yeah yeah
so you can travel you can travel
directly in to it it's almost like from
from outside it looks as though it's
just a trunk it just has this sort of
the natural grooves and whirls of the
wood but as you get close it's it's it's
as irrelevant as a curtain you can just
part it and it allows that and
encourages it and as soon as you enter
in
to this as soon as you enter into the
trunk of it it is basically like a an
elevator that it's a combination
elevator roller coaster where Ella
coaster yeah yeah where you're basically
shot down you don't you don't have a
hundred percent sense of the amount of
time it takes but you're next awareness
is of being flung through the air out
over a massive drow city that looks as
though it is just as gala death looks it
looks like it's made from the candle wax
it's just around the basis of these
stalactites everything everything is
just sort of wet
it's a glistening in the in the cool air
of this cavern but you can you can see
you think that the center of this town
it looks like the town beyond the wall
as you approached the house where holy
you think that you think that this may
be the same city at a very very
different point oh wow
in its evolution are we able to see
whether that redistricting has already
happened oh no no is this there's
nothing of that there's nothing of that
kind
it extends it extends much much farther
out indeed out to the road that you came
in with immoral okay like the city
itself is massive Wow
there's no but there's been no
reclamation of any kind and you and your
sister Warriors are now flown directly
through space it's something like the
feather fall spell if you've ever had an
experience with that except you have the
choice of motion and you also have the
choice of speed it's something about
the area where the base of the name is
air holds sway so if you could look back
behind yourself you can see this you can
see the boring just like monstrous core
of this much like you saw coming up
through NEMA's ear except now this is
coming down out of what is there sky
directly into the town does it look like
it just landed our people scattering
yeah people are definitely scattering
from the the base wherever this wherever
this massive drill like fanged
protrusions coming down and then a basic
sort of splits imagine that that comes
down in the center and then it's drills
into the town and then the rest of it is
sort of peeled up in a way you can see
little roots just sort of seeking in the
air for who knows what
but you and then what you get what you
guess now is a hundred and then more
every second that Warriors flying out of
this do we see an obvious target or is
it the city are we just messing around
the city do you think it's that you
think it's the city itself okay this is
the this is a point in a campaign mm-hmm
do the other sisters look like they're
attacking the drought they are
absolutely doing so okay yikes
well here Rosie obviously having a very
conflicted time about this we're smart
enough to figure out that we're like
living through some fat past vision
right yeah so being a bit of a fatalist
it seems like well we'll just see where
this goes when in the Underdark with
[Laughter]
okay exactly
you deceide assess the odds here at
about five to one in our favor
no oh no the other way but this this
instrument definitely seems to have an
effect on enemy we're out okay
are these all Warriors ornate Commodores
this is a city
oh boy okay so there's kids this is the
full meal deal okay this is this is this
is what it looks like okay can we help
no you you are now playing Dungeons and
Dragons oh I'm not gonna read the whole
thing okay
I haven't written down I literally have
the two names written down and then a
list and then I have a couple puns that
Eric and I made up when we were drunk on
Saturday oh don't worry
that's not optional okay
Jesus okay so we hit this town square I
guess and they're scattering and
screaming and biting everywhere and do
we have the the memories of being able
to execute on these miracles absolutely
we have this in ourselves you know
exactly what to do okay you you know how
they are you think that they are like
you think that they must be like in a
traditional military you think they must
be like the stripes that an officer
might wear okay
the knowledge of these miracles is the
station okay do I have any other
memories that aren't mine you have to
dig around okay explore the space I'll
talk to me about them I don't know if
Rosie wants to wants to share yeah well
she's mine she doesn't want to split
no she doesn't wanna have a roommate all
right I will
I guess I'll look at you and say like
you know how to do new things yes me too
yeah let's help horrible thing yeah
we're gonna carry some
poof do I feel do I feel that would she
save her vein yeah do I do I have an
overwhelming sense of vervain yet
or am I still very much myself well you
know you it's like you know what she
would want
mm-hmm and you know what she would do
okay but it's almost like she she is not
gonna push it
gotcha right she wants you to know what
she would have done but she is not here
to orchestrate it was like a respect at
some level okay so yeah I look at Rosie
and I said let's make it quick
yeah I'm with I'm just gonna be with you
like I would follow your lead
I take my staff and I tell you I'm with
you okay okay so I look around yep so so
so right now now that you basically
you've emerged from the from the root
and you basically like just hit the
ground like bolts of lightning
heroically oh absolutely 100% it's like
[Music]
but you were surrounded it's like it
would be cooler if it didn't happen like
a hundred times like in one second right
right you feel like you feel like it you
they could have given you a second like
to have the moment have that entrance
but as soon as as soon as they hit I
mean they know exactly where they're
here they're there aren't two versions
of them right trying to have a
discussion with themselves and you can
see off far in the in the front distance
you can see no way and doing what looks
like the work of an army okay
just like the weapon that she has in her
hand seems to change with each attack
okay it's whatever she wants it to be in
that moment and so she's cutting carts
in half
she's flipped if she's flipping someone
in the air and then jumping after them
as a bird who like it is a horrifying
like there is she is working something
out on these people
um so four out and the city square I
want to do I'm gonna just get get to
work I'm gonna get to work yeah and I
want to start I have this overwhelming
feeling that vervain would do a sunburst
here yeah that's probably true and I'm
gonna start with that sure I read out
loud please an orb of terrible burning
light fashioned from the stuff of the
quasi elemental plane of radiance is
pulled through a pinhole in the prime
material plane it's light is hateful to
those of the Underdark
and they cannot long abide it the orbit
self is fixed in space and allies are
bolstered by it while enemies are seared
okay I'm bolstered as hell dude yeah you
were bolstered AF yeah right now yeah
like that would be your that would be
your status and so when you introduce
the Sun to this place yeah you know you
know what you're you know what you're
doing mm-hmm and it is not I mean this
is this is war and it mean in an instant
it is they it is exactly as it says on
the tin like it's not like bright if you
are from this town and from this place
you are blind and your sisters are just
traveling through the streets basically
catching up with no layin as they do so
so you can see them rushing through just
cutting down a battalion of soldiers as
they are trying to do so and then from a
side street you see a what looks like a
shadow at first and then as it emerges
you can see a tail sort of flick up
behind its back and it stretches its
wings
out and it is as though the the tail and
the wicked black barb at the end is like
another creature that this thing can
barely control it is immediately down
just sweeping this tail through groups
1020 soldiers at a time that it is it is
coming out basically to break the The
Enclave assault up into the center of
the city so I'm yeah and you also all
your regular stuff all your regular
attacks spells I still know how to do
that you can do all of your regular so
you exactly so you get to use your you
get to use this new version of your
staff okay all that stuff is all your
D&amp;D is still here you just have extra
goose okay from your station okay and
this this scorpion beast thing yeah
clear a threat oh my yeah it's it's it
is it is single-handedly it's acting as
a combination roadblock murderer
okay so rosy sees this and the knowledge
of another of these miracles wells
inside her and this this other person
all right this other consciousness menu
and you know her name in an instant it's
just as soon as you try to tap into the
station the power of this station you
know that you are in addition to Rosie
at least for a time
you are also someone named wardens Sofia
I think it's cool whereas he's horrified
um but yeah so warden Sofia tells me she
whispers in this way that I can
understand exactly what I'm supposed to
what she would do in this situation well
I know it's like it's like a devil angel
thing yeah yeah she is always trying she
is always has an idea and she about what
you're gonna do she suggests this to me
and it's so horrible that Rosie's like
oh my god no but then the desire to to
help and that is
to defend the sisters uh actually
overwhelms it and frankly Rosie would
like she does want to help so it's not a
hard-fought battle but when she as she's
about to do this she looks at walnut and
she goes she says she she and and then
it escapes her and she cast oblivion oh
no you're jumping right in huh yeah
a stitch in sand she's casting this
wherever this this scorpion creature is
to create this this rip a stitch in
space is ripped and the place beyond it
watch what we termed the quasi elemental
plane of vacuum is a place of terrible
hunger those nearest the rend are sucked
through immediately to a place where
there is no sucker for living things and
that's that's what she does and and
please and Rosie was horrified by this
is it that she knows innocent bystanders
what elves drow are all gonna get sucked
into this thing but it's to warden
Sathya it's worth it like that sacrifice
is worth but you also you get as you use
it you get just like like an echo or
like a texture of another like another
thing another feeling and that is that
you think that this is the sort of thing
this type of quick action in the face of
these odds that might make vervain
reconsider oh okay so this is this is
exactly what has happened it's almost
like it's the there's a couple quick
pops in the air over this creature and
as soon as as soon as air like a great
rushing wind of air starts to flow into
this place it doesn't seem to have any
end like how much it can consume is
profound and so the creature who you
know just
instinctively to be a wyvern that they
have somehow twisted to their purpose it
it starts with the tail so it's a first
instinct is to try to protect itself
with the tail but all that's done is
expose something extraneous to this
portal and so it immediately catches
that and then pulls the entire creature
through and the creature is massive it
pulls the entire creature through an
aperture about the size of a shield and
then as that happens there are a few a
few drow soldiers and there are a few a
few Enclave warrior druids are pulled
through this strike up through this
aperture and you think that you may be
in a position you can feel this evil tug
and presence yeah pulling like with with
each new thing that goes in its mouth
gets a little wider and I needed
dexterity checks oh yeah can I take
advantage
you can't I shall look that's jack oh I
got a 13 13 is not good all right oh yay
15 15 so you you have done it and just
in this wash of alien emotions coming
from this other person you lose your
footing on this street and our dragged
along the street itself along with many
of your sisters in battle you have found
a way how do you what do you do to
stabilize yourself against this
Paul this incredible hunger oh I kneel
down and I slam for mother into the into
the ground and just put my forehead on
her and I'm just like hunker yeah so as
you as you put it down flowers which
have never known the Underdark and their
firm roots hold you tight in place so
you know so you are pulled along this
row there's wagon wheels and carts and
everything is just being stuffed into
this this go it hmm and you are pulled
and you're sort of sliding face-first
and then you catch the edge of the
cobble wrong and then sort of flip over
and so your feet are the first thing
through
so you enter a place of hunger really
are jumping right into it okay oh yeah
I'm playing a vacuum so it is it's it's
every everything about it is detests
life it detests existence itself and you
know that this is a this is a place that
loathes disturbance at any time it's
introduced like it's a it's a it's a
heavy it's a heavy burden to use it so
you are pulled through and there is and
you're surrounded by almost like a path
of just like a constellation of ruin
there's individually tarah body it's
like terrified bodies frozen in place
parts of parts of the city
infrastructure you think that you don't
you think that you do not have long in
this place ok the only the only light
that is coming in is that which come is
coming into this sort of flapping
aperture that is kicking it out into the
street
okay am i able to brace myself against
anything to try to get back through that
aperture yeah you think that right now
you think that it has taken in a lot
yeah and you think that you think that
you have an opportunity now maybe to use
the things that are in here or use
another miracle or a spell okay to get
your way back out your shiner stuff yeah
oh sure yeah that's even cooler
yeah can I pull from the plane of shadow
since this thing hates life I try to
work the job and it did tests life the
shadow the stuff of shadow that I work
with is not life and potentially could
like choke up the works somehow or at
least distract it long enough to let it
let let me go so I'm here for this as
the young say they do you say that let
me do a light to your grammar man see
and what what happens if if if you will
if my Labor's please you yeah yeah is
that the shadow actually is gonna come
through this aperture from the Material
Plane - almost like fingers grabbing on
either side go see style
oh no yeah and pulling pulling this
aperture and and more MORE these snakes
slither through as the aperture widens
and I am I have my my staff is also
plunged into the earth of whatever plane
this is and I'm I'm trying very hard to
it has no earth of any kind oh it's
terrifying about okay so I'm just
suspended it's just yeah I mean its
orientation doesn't even exist in this
place okay but you have leveraged the
power of grandma Mansi to widen the
aperture and hopefully then also send
tendrils of various kinds in yeah to if
they can they can reach me then perhaps
one of them can can grab me and pull me
through well here what I would like to
get from you is a charisma check okay
nope that's the one
no no that's not a real roll that was a
sheep aren't you were naive like you say
like you're not even partner to that
that's the 17 absolutely no 17 is very
good okay all that has to do with is
because you can do what you want to with
grammar man see ya
check surfer when you want to do crazy
stuff and utilize your staff right but
this is for something else
oh so the shadow tendrils that reach
through they reach out and then the
staff reaches out to them oh look in a
mesh is itself with those tendrils and
it's pulling you in and you can see
other tendrils of shadow reaching in and
bringing out still struggling battle
sisters back into the planet yeah they
are cold and terrified but these are
it's entirely possible that these are
some of the most sophisticated martial
warriors torille has ever seen so they
get back to work okay Wow
after seeing that giant scorpion
wouldn't we like found this little
initiative order even though I haven't
um after seeing that giant scorpion go
down I want to use giant insect yeah
well and I want to make our own giant
creatures so being under dark there's a
lot of good crawlies hell yeah there are
all kinds of grass and I can do up to
three spiders and I know that that's the
thing that they hold dear so great
yes so I want to make three giant
spiders which obey my verbal commands
and they act on my turn each round but
you can do what you want with them when
I get zero hit points then it's done he
so what I want to
I want to command them to I guess it's
like a psyche psionic link hmm
to shoot their use their web attacks on
as many of the foes as possible
just to slow them down and make them
easier for the sisters to get to exactly
so they're basically going through just
full-on co-op yeah there's gonna go
along with sisters they they risk you
you know that they understand what you
mean but it'd be hard to get be hard to
characterize the mode of communication
you just know that they fear you um and
in accordance with the ancient pacts
they will do as you've asked so some
really cool shit yeah good yeah the
dopest so you start to hear a sound like
a a sound of just great weight it sounds
like like balls of glass like balls of
heavy blown glass falling and cracking
against something hard and even when you
look back to the
NEMA's ear you can see that it's a drill
portion of it has actually drilled into
something not the city itself not the
town but into a material of some kind
okay like an ochre like a yellow fluid
that appears to be traveling up through
the trunk of the nemah 0 itself and you
can see the battle sisters like now that
it is sort of taken it and begun to be
sort of like whipped up into the
structure you can see that sisters are
coming through
and they are materializing in midair and
falling to their deaths oh no I'm sorry
that's that's what's happening that's
terrible so it's not yeah I mean it's
it's you know you can manage it any way
you want you can what's what spirals are
there you can go back and do it you can
handle it any way you want what's the
level at which they're getting ejected
from the Nova Zero how high they eject
high just as you did because the NEMA's
or grants them some ability to move
through okay to move through space but
it's something as being interfered with
with this material this substance I see
um maybe I don't know I don't think that
helped I was thinking maybe this might
hold off whatever's getting whipped up
the tree oh yeah try it yeah sure yeah I
want to try to dry it out with a
sunburst if it's coming from the
Underdark there's a chance that it hates
the Sun so a warden Sathya will turn
toward the tree and and cast this
terrible orb of brightness in the hopes
of slowing it down does the warden
Sophie I think that's a good idea she
into that oh that Jack she's not she is
not turning you down okay when it comes
when it comes to the when it comes to
utilizing yeah these and divine powers
allies are bolstered by it perhaps it
will help these these warriors give them
more damage resistance when they hit the
grounds they don'ts flat yeah yeah yeah
so you're able to you're able to
manifest it very near and and you can
see that even the even the lower
portions of the of the NEMA's here are
encouraged by this bright light and it's
and it's healing energy but you can see
that whatever this material is at the
base of this is not just a liquid like
now
here in the in the pure radiant light
you can see that as it sort of travels
around and tries to find areas of
purchase you can see that eyes are
routinely like bubbling to the surface
and looking around and then falling back
in yeah and you can see around the edge
you can see tendrils reaching out from
the fluid itself you know a grasping way
nasty grasps you don't like it they
don't mean a thing I'm gonna do
something without a bean let's just blow
it let's just cast Moonbeam at a
[Music]
constitution saving throw it'll still
still do have the details
these are you moaning yeah so the the
thing with the liquid with the eyes yeah
when I see the eyes come out of it it's
Dunham I realize you know what it is and
she my ray of Moonbeam in it and just
maintain that beam read there around the
root yeah exactly and it does its
constitution thing mm-hmm forget it does
its constitution thing and what did it
did you better than 15 uh no no I did a
seven oh it was shitty
wonderful help me do basic math what was
that five and three okay so is it it's
nothing I'm sorry
yes eleven okay so there's this 1919
moon very healthy sorry I wish this no
I know I'm just like what am i rolling
how do I do this if I kill that's no
problem so this so it is bizarre it's
basically like a it's like a tour of
everything people from this city have
never seen before
it's all happening at one place you're
not even you know even charging for a
ticket like everyone can see it this the
silver moonlight is just focused on a
massive portion of this creature that
has spread itself out around through the
base and it is basically scabbing up in
real time and as it continues to arrive
just massive flakes and plates of it are
falling off of the NEMA's ear root yep
go I don't like it okay um how big is
this is this Nemus your planet's
annerose ear root itself is gigantic
okay like when it when it comes down its
purpose as to its purpose is to drill
out the basis of a of a city okay um I
think I will try this yeah go for it so
around the base then in an expression of
frustration if we can't scare it off if
we can't slow it to growth of it we can
just stop it entirely so I cast knew
this miracle called Earth glass in the
hopes of binding the bottom of the root
off from further like being climbed by
this nastiness to just cut it just
cauterize it yeah exactly yeah yeah read
it there yeah well molten stone issues
from a place of our choosing just as the
ancient Accords ensure the issuance from
these flows freely like a river pulling
wide but hardens to obsidian when it
finds a foe to our efforts this too is
defined by our arrangement with the
deepest places mm-hmm well that sounds
good to me
so you
Manifest at a point even below this
structure and then rising up around the
edge of the nemah zero obviously this is
the this is basically the mouth of this
thing it's a calculation it seems like
on your part if we can if we can manage
this and fix this yeah then maybe it'll
fix this other part up here even if we
don't get to bore out at the bottom of
this particular place necessarily and so
you can see for a time this creature and
the lava are commingled as it is boiling
up around the edge of the root and then
there is a time at the end where you no
longer see it rising to the surface and
then in a moment just like a like a snap
all of the magma becomes black glass
around the base of the nose your roof
does the growth of this scabbing you
can't you don't see you don't see it
moving anywhere you don't see it
traversing anything over there at all
okay and as it is at that time where
like I said just out of midair sisters
are materializing and then just like
falling hard around and then like as
that is happening as you manage this
issue at the base fresh troops come
through and with the power that has
granted them in that area they can move
very swiftly even in midair
oh good god to cease to cease friends
and bring them to the ground safely okay
all right it's very stressful it is very
stressful
do I see is there anything else that's
it's fucked up that's big like anything
that's really causing a lot of AoE well
you can look around even now you see you
can just sort of see who where where
Nolan must be mm-hmm
just because that's where the greatest
concentration of the enemy is okay but
that but that fight just keeps moving
around like wherever that is they are
always trying to contend and
occasionally a massive creature will
come in swoop down and try to interact
and it has an experience in that crush
that causes it to leave very quickly
okay do we want to try and get to the
lion and yeah all right I want to try
and start making my way over what what
photos do I have to contend with Oh
actually so many foes let me try this I
want to cut through the foes I want to
make a path for Rosie and I I love it I
think I could do Legion to do that okay
tell me more oh yeah okay I don't even
know what that ability means Legion is
you have the power within you to marshal
a force of up to 500 sisters as a single
weapon with a single purpose your
awareness includes everything that is
heard or felt by this Legion
unfortunately and enables the caster to
conceive of the information received
you must have protection during this
time as your concentration must be
absolute yes yeah so I look to Rosie who
I know to be wardens warden sathya i had
forsythia in my head yeah oh no I did
all this stuff to make it sound like
plants okay I worked very hard on this
this is very good warden Sonia and I say
there's a when you look on her there's a
moment of wistful pain you don't know it
sorry
[Music]
and I I say I say shield me and I I you
know summing up this force how do I have
I linked with these sisters so that I
can you tell me them know your you mean
your first sword vervain I mean you're
right you're the one who knows so I
raise my sword high and I let out this
like call and when I do I want to
imagine it's like it's not my voice and
it's it's like both of our voices
intermingling and it is it's too loud
for what for one person to make somehow
and it brings these 500 sisters together
in like a single and and I motion with
the sword forward and they they become
like a protective Chevron to move
through that those yeah yeah it's it's a
chevron that has several oh it's a shame
it's a goat-cheese that knows it knows
exactly but but also it has access to
all the information of any individual
soldier in any part the issue is that it
is too much mere protection is not going
to be enough it's too much to maintain
okay you need to have someone physically
carry you or you need to be brought with
on something you need to come up with a
way and obviously you have control of
them so you can do it but the
concentration required to do this is the
miracle allows you to do it but it is
complete concentration but at what cost
exactly okay great so I will have I'll
say yeah I'll have some of the the ones
off the back here come and what is it
called the palanquin palanquin I was
like Palantir
a palanquin of of these sisters to like
ferry me in the middle and then you know
if anything happens to them then another
one would replace them exactly look at
reverse phalanx type thing can I ask for
one thing yeah of course
can you remove our charges that we use
for this thank you well of course I
think I'm I'm down like for well I I've
been in cash okay sorry it's just the
screen hi guys I really need everything
to work out yeah yeah no I got you okay
even cash Neiman so this is exactly it
is like a cowcatcher
but like it's the butts like the battle
mode yeah for the cowcatcher character
that's it so foes foes will foes are
coming from any side and like the person
to the left or right of them will
actually do the parry and then the
person who they tried to attack does the
killing blow hmm like it's like it it's
less it's less a force and more like a
octopus or something it's like a single
a single creature that has a purpose and
that purpose is to seek out and assist
growth keeper Nolan and you don't have
to wait long
warden city of by the waying is bringing
up the rear as a mode of protection
however because the this Chevron this
blade of Warriors that you have
certainly has the front covered yeah so
she's she's behind and there's something
in Sofia when she sees vervain first for
sword preserving for sword vervain
there's a twinge of like that that regal
status no riding on this palanquin and
and commanding this this powerful troop
warden Sofia like dies a little
she's like no my god yeah that's
incredible just like just like the story
school is also roses here though is like
oh my that's that's there's something
about walnuts position in this battle
roses like that's where she belongs
right she can see it
thing writer was she's like oh this is
this is right you know but so as you are
pulling up through this like you can you
can see that no held where she is
walnut / ver vanes head is like
constantly looking in different places
like she has it she has it dialed in but
the labor just the intellectual and
emotional labor of maintaining this much
capacity is clearly pretty profound but
this this thing is is just slicing
through the city moving it as it does so
and you are starting to get into you're
starting to push into a different area
of town now so there's clearly class
markers and class distinctions okay that
you're starting to see you're starting
to see a number of banners that if they
remind you of anything remind you of the
banners in the in the crate okay but
they don't see but those looked a
certain way they said I mean you you
were able to discern from the documents
that those red house really mm-hmm
but these say circle really okay so for
whatever reason but there are many of
them and they tend to they drape mage
towers and what looks to be other
scholarly places places of learning
thanks then you can see been in even
from these towers you know out here
billowing and the heat driven off
because now these hot winds from these
Sun bursts are changing the atmosphere
in this town and you can see that there
are figures looking down on this
conflict from high places with looks of
concern
and there are discussions taking place
between various robed figures almost in
a clinical hmm just a clinical
assessment like in it like in the
abstract like they were controlling it
with a mouse or something I see do do
our split selves have any kind of
reaction to this circle erroneously well
you know that one of the reasons that
this was chosen to be the place of the
battle was that circle ruth was supposed
to be in another city at that time but
they're clearly not but they are clearly
here and in great force okay interesting
and you and I recognize the banners is
belonging tickets versus house mhm so in
some way right yeah and so I don't know
if you you're busy well I'm yeah I would
come being concentrated like fully on
this yeah
do you notice do the banners evoke
anything for you
I would feel a great walnut never being
walnut will feel yeah a great sense of
remorse oh yeah yeah because even though
like there's no way to quantify this
like abstract time travel it's like
either it is in relation to a friend or
it isn't in relation to a friend it is
so I would just imagine this is like
extremely difficult knowing that there
are like these ancestors like these you
know these bloodlines that are being
murdered yeah
and the concept of time travel is very
much like a real world thing right what
what is the difference for us except
that we're seeing we're experiencing
something very radically different from
where we were before so is it's just as
real right it's like it's like totally
real what's real
what x in there okay
so Rosie would immediately be extremely
worried and on the lookout because I
don't know if she's looking for anything
in particular but there is some perverse
part of her it's like if we see if we
seeketh ris or any part of his family
I'm just gonna shit myself so that's
that's suddenly she's extremely aware
absolutely
so from these from these different
towers you can see that you're very very
close now to tuna lion and the throng
that has gathered around but you can you
can see her moving with the same mastery
right in the middle not not missing a
step
perfect just perfect cut glue moving
into another perfect cut and she's been
doing this since you got here so you can
see that figures from each of these
towers they've begun to take their
conversation into a tower and they're
communicating with a series of symbols
atop each tower there's a here's a
symbol and then here's a symbol and then
it's responded to over here like
bat-signal yeah basically yeah exactly
right over the top just gluing CID
jewels if you will delicious sigils and
you can in the center if you think that
you see a priestess step off of the
veranda into the open air and below her
a circle is is inscribed just standing
in the just in the open space and she
begins to shed she holds her hand in
different positions you can see smoke
the colored smoke beginning to issue
forth and then at a deep place
below the tower you can see like a
massive hand rise in fire from the earth
itself oh no the creature is truly
spectacular a spectacular specimen in
absolutely every regard huge in size not
just absolutely unnatural in every in
every possible way every aspect of its
of its shape seems to be a mockery of
the living of living creatures
everywhere it has a massive two sharp
horns that emit that just jut outs just
straight like nobody even fucking care
at all right it randomized on the
character just straight out you wouldn't
pick it this way this is just another
way it's haunting the living but the the
most profound aspects have to do with
massive dark wings that unfold from its
back and it's I mean it's it's of a
piece with the rest of the towers like
it doesn't belong he doesn't belong here
at all there's no reason it should be
here this is the sort of thing that you
would this is why you have to fight a
war against them because as soon as
their backs are against the wall this is
what they turn to just summon up a demon
this is their first idea this is their
plan eight and assuming they could even
deal with it right yeah there's there's
nothing to say that it won't destroy the
town exactly after it destroys the
invaders this is it it speaks to a moral
issue what does this does this creature
seem beholden to them or is it resentful
of it somehow
it is
cursing and bellowing at the woman who
is now in this for now atop of this
circle right that allows her temporarily
to look down upon it in a haughty way
okay it's right hand the forearm itself
very Kratos very a lot of chains going
on guys but the hand itself holds a
massive flaming whip okay great the left
hand a gigantic sword that looks to be
made if not entirely but mostly of
lightning you would say wonderful yeah I
put these creatures in here for Alyssa I
know I was going to say this creature
this creature is greater than any of us
this this both is greater than any of us
we have to run which animal in D&amp;D is
called a baile or am i right am i right
about that I am right about they do what
serve God baby no more I guess baby was
rather no more yeah oh yeah well so then
you know the rest of that what's on this
cheetah I think I do is how do you feel
right I've believed that the Challenger
eating of a bailar is significantly
higher than what we can accomplish I
thought a bailar at a in another
campaign at level 14 yeah so how'd that
go it was really really hard so I'm just
thinking that right now some maybe some
oblivion so there was a there was a
theory for a time that Mela that gone to
serve and be served by the drow mmm-hmm
but looking at this you think that
couldn't possibly be the case that no
matter how far nor recalcitrant or petty
or angry whatever you had done to make
May let's leave she would never she
would never talk
this sort of action how recently was her
betrayal in our timeline in your
timeline Scythians - at this time it was
probably 200 years prior okay the anger
is still very new but shadow council my
hair leaders please you that is our
first break I say first break but
there's really only the one break I
guess there's a break between this and
Table Talk
either way it's not absolute pleasure to
serve you don't go anywhere
come back and I'll kill the rest of the
party thank you hello this is your 4q
Arkham's and this is to see teams any
rate it's half of the C team mm-hmm
because I killed though I killed one
half of them already
as you can see if you would you'd be so
kind as to take a look at our cthe wrist
drab and dinar blitzen recipes memorial
toys over here listen they did a good
job yeah I mean Aaron commute I should
be laughs they are dead by you can you
bring those in thanks guys yeah because
I mean it's it's pretty serious business
obviously like we really enjoyed playing
the game with them but rip they were bad
at D&amp;D so yeah you know I think we're
betting a lot of a gravity indie that's
their fault that's on them maybe they
should have maybe they should get good
nubs you know man I miss them kind of
yeah no I don't know I feel like we're
having a good time
hey speaking of which more fun the most
recent phenomenon the varied the top
tweet if you will well is that a
creature deeply unlike the sort of
creature that the EPA would leverage the
EPA would enter into it holy union with
a creature that was advantageous for all
for the protection of nature itself
what has happened here instead is that
they have pulled a demon from a place a
lien to the prime material plane and
indeed nature itself a creature inimical
to the natural world if you will now
that is the that is the newest thing so
it is continued to issue a stream of
curses at the woman who is standing up
there and you can you can see that she
is very plainly directing like doing her
best to direct this creature and you
don't know if it's just a communications
thing like you don't know if she needs
to take a webinar you know what I mean
you don't know she needs to learn how to
make friends and influence demons but it
doesn't seem to be functioning can I get
some I need a you won't be able to do it
because you were completely obsessed
with these fees five hundred people you
don't get to take a look at it okay I
want to look at it what do I roll please
just precision uh not great eight no no
she it looks like she's it looks like
she's performing no it looks like she's
performing some kind of interpretive
dance and he doesn't like it you don't
you don't think that's what's happening
but that's what it looks like her her
emotions have become increasingly
frenzied and you can see that the other
people from the towers have actually
retreated from the exterior parts of
their towers and doors have been shut so
I understand this is happening while you
are on yeah as your wedge has moved into
the finer imagined regions clearly some
kind of like the mystical ward of some
kind
okay there's there's temples wizardly
goods nice products
so we can do some shopping you're saying
well no it's not time to shop what I'm
saying and just I'm just telling you
that's the type of place you're in
that's just gonna be a girl's upset why
we've laid our trap for you the fallen
and I I like that the drow all
disappeared as if they're like odd geez
Sharon got the Baylor out again there we
go looks like days since Sharon has
ruined the mystic ward it's like zero
Jesus Sharon here lost Sharon okay
so remind me do Baylor the Baylor only
speak of Bissell tears are languages
yeah well that's what it suggests but
you don't know his history you know its
journey I don't know what kind of shit
he's been through all right so then
roses gonna she can sue there's some
tension going on between these two and
she's good yes now he's waving and
pointing the lightning sword okay yeah
okay so Rosie's gonna try commands it
doesn't have a level ending any kind of
restriction whatsoever except that if he
doesn't speak my language then it
doesn't doesn't do anything but the one
word that she would speak would would be
to point this giant staff right out of
and yell betray and then cast this
command spell which would the cars and
wisdom safe it's like yeah he he did
well on that but you do get a response
okay
no from Sharon no sure hey that's my
baler no you did I get that what you
what you get instead it just sort of
creeps just like a hot darkness just
like a breath
it's just filling the edges of your
perception and you just you hear a voice
like a very low whispery voice that just
cuts right through the middle of all the
sensations that accompany it and it says
when I have killed her I will kill you
Wow okay deal
let me help so you can so you were
moving here however we you want to like
choose your own adventure style
whichever aspect of this you want to
crank you want to crank the baler you
want to split your attention you can you
can help Nolan you can go baler a style
it's up to you you want a solo baler
yeah why not so last episode so yeah
you're right I think probably it seems
like this baler is kind of obsessed with
Sharon at the moment and so Sharon
problems a better name but so I think
Misha
yeah there you go yeah Sharon's Susie's
fantasy Sharon yeah
so I think that Rosie would kind of like
until that bail or stops paying
attention to its master focus on
something else like not draw its
attention okay
and I was gonna ask you reasonable call
if I can she's nothing if not reasonable
is it possible to juice the legion
concentration that vervain is
interesting don't tell me tell me what
you mean well you mentioned that it is
cherry it's sort of to share the load if
you will so they're all for Alice I -
you mentioned it's having an emotional
toll on her death so the idea would be
that if I were to somehow add in my
power to her Legion that she might be
able to divide her attention even a
little bit to split the cost
[Laughter]
casting Alissa just type share the load
on the screen where we could see it at
all caps to make it so that she can
actually do other shit
besides and like half concentrate well I
share the other half it's cool if not I
got another plan no I I like it cool
so well you get what you get will you
extend a few more of them to carry your
now he useless Bobbie somewhat yeah I
think so so the idea is that we are all
part of this weird hive mind yeah and
that I am joining into this hive mind
with what is concise warden city is
considerable druidic power yes indeed
help infuse that would be like I imagine
it would be an overflowing of power and
the way that that overflowing would
manifest is to regain some of your
consciousness so that you can kind of
discuss so you so basically your you're
gonna try to carry you're gonna jump in
in to come in and try to carry most of
it yeah yeah okay I like it just so that
you can kind of cuz it Rosie's here to
follow in Walnut here here so tell me
what it looks like when you when you
enter that wedge and then give yourself
over to it okay
so warden Cynthia has been running
behind this blade the Chevron of people
and although it's clear that vervain is
looking around it seems like almost like
a puppet like that angles yeah strange
angles and I can see from my vantage
point the heads and the arms moving in
accord with verve aims to so that there
I can see the sisters that she's
directly controlling it's very very
weird so I will go I will touch the
shoulder of one of these one of these
soldiers that's sort of in your thrall
and whisper walnut I want to help you
and then cast the flee j'en and the the
power of this this flow of energy out of
my hand will cause these these soldiers
these these wood elves around me to kind
of shudder
and that this this sort of
lassy look that they perhaps had before
they'll focus their attention on me and
a sort of crowd-surf me up to this
palanquin where you are and and I I'll
say at the moment until this this
distraction becomes mine that that
transition of power I'll say I need your
eyes Oh what are your elven I see how
many more can we go No so so you so you
were able so as soon as you're it's the
second your eyes closed
walnuts eyes open you're still being
carried through this like you basically
go limp and then you're immediately on
someone's shoulder which is you
recognize at that moment like your own
shoulder well and you just are just like
your consciousness telescopes out and
just knit all these people together but
now you know now up close you can see
that yet at a distance it might look
like a single group but there's a very
stylized version of a maliki headdress
oh but it's all made out of it's all
made out of metals and gems but there's
a portion maybe 20% of each of these
groups that actually that seem to revere
Maliki higher and that group it would
appear is responsible for they basically
operate the heels right okay so that's
it's like at a distance it looks like
it's a single unified thing but it's
actually a very sophisticated interplay
of people and so as you're doing this
the reach of Legion is snaring fresh
troops that are actually coming from the
last wave of people of a warrior druids
that were rescued and those would come
through down so this the group that you
now have marshaled together is
substantially is a substantial force
okay so I still want to get to know I
okay you but mean you are there Adam you
were there in a moment
great so then I say I say a million
we're we're with you I'm hoping that
maybe she I mean if we have to fight
this Baylor I'm figuring that she's
gonna she's gonna help yeah yeah she's
like she's a whole army on her own yeah
exactly and she says I I never doubted
it she's killing people while she says
they're just moving it's like it's like
they're being fed into a chipper
shredder right and I say maybe she
hasn't seen it I say they've summoned a
demon she's just Oh what I know its name
no okay probably call it something here
yeah here let's make some EPA Laurie
yeah yeah so what would we call this oh
right because again this distinction is
a pretty serious cultural distinction
this is not this is not how you get down
it'd be like uh not this like like doom
bringer like that kind of thing like
there's almost like there's no why would
the EPA have a word for this it would be
unspeakable oh yeah what if she just
says that yeah what if she just says
it's unspeakable yeah yes yes yes well
it's a whole category right then guys
they don't even want to know what these
things are
yeah right yeah so she just let certain
she says I know that it's one of those
unspeakable things it's yeah with a
caveat you
yeah yeah right in speakable have Dave
make this shirt yeah this is gonna be
good stuff yeah so basically with the
help of your legion force that you just
sort of like wash you basically bike
break over in the layin like a like an
ocean rock
and encapsulate the rest of the armies
that have been sent down to manage her
and there are some losses but they are
quickly brought back up there's
something about the radius of the
there's something about the radius of
the Nana's ear that puts things in your
favor as long as it's not being occupied
by a and a demon made out of goo that's
the only time it doesn't work if you
demons have their first I don't know I
don't know I think is different but it
is at this time as you've sort of washed
out the rest of this battle you look
back and you can see the Lightning sword
he actually pushes it up to the bottom
of this disk and then it begins to arc
and shock the Bale or as well like from
like off of this disc but he fights
through it and pushes through it and it
breaks like glass and when she falls she
falls down along the blade of this sword
and somewhere at the base of this tower
there are more than there's more than
one piece of Sharon love Sharon a
fantasy share yikes yeah I know
rest in peace taken too soon rest in
pieces thank you good night
Wow so that is the that is the situation
Thanks
okay you can and you can see that these
other towers orbs have begun to fill
with energy and were and they are trying
to they're trying to attack this
creature as best they can but he doesn't
he doesn't seem especially
he doesn't seem especially harmed by it
yeah he's definitely he is definitely a
bailar you think that that's you think
that's accurate okay uh so you have your
force yeah you have this Bale or did you
want to try something elemental yeah I
can try something elemental um what if I
ooh I got it what I'm just excited I'm
like oh yeah I got it I got it I got it
okay I want to I'm gonna cast this and
then maybe we could like suck him
through it
hell yeah I guess try that so I'm gonna
cast I always want to call it a water
wall it's horrible it's Wonderwall yeah
and after all you're my water wall it's
a way says wall of water which is oh
really high oh I can do a radius or a
height yeah you know what let's do the
20-foot radius nice so just goes up
around him cool yes and so then we will
try and do something really cool on Rose
Eastern okay that's the combo platter
do it yeah so how do you communicate to
me this is combo by the way oh I mean we
know each other like so just so good so
well I mean at this point it's like
there's you're sure we're sharing the
same brain I wonder at some level like
it's I bet that it's very strange and
like abstract almost but there's a place
where you can discuss all the things
that yeah all the people that are in
you're better in your care right now
yeah and the thing is opening the
Oblivion stitch to the the quasi
elemental plane of vacuum I think that
sorry Cynthia being connected to this
this legion of sisters I might not want
to suck any of them into it that's fair
but we're having this conversation in an
instant by the way but please let's just
okay it's the language of just pure
in tension yes well I'm thinking it's
like not like we're really having this
conversation it's like we're conveying
emotions to each other where it's like
yeah yeah yeah yeah um what if what you
were saying before was that you trying
yeah okay
so then the thing to do would be my
perfect understanding of wellness
intention I create I cast another
oblivion
rip rip a stitch in space right just
where uh right next to this water wall
in the hopes of sucking the water into
the baler is that kind of what you're
thinking yes like to create a suction
watch just we pass us through it
you want to suck all of the baler in
along with the water or just the water
good oh I see I see I just get him past
it I thought you had perfect awareness
exactly I do and this is exactly what
awareness the perfect awareness is
happening now
so I do that I create the stitch and my
concentration drops yeah because I can't
maintain concentration of over Legion
while I'm doing that exactly and so
there's there's a moment in here where
all for the weight of all of it because
new people have now been added to this
mm-hmm the weight of all of it just
descends on you right so you're carrying
it now but you could drop it too
I think we maybe we just drop it it's
everything asleep mister you cast you
cast what it's not so it was all on you
okay so I was carrying all of it and I
drop it mm-hmm and so all of these
sisters are still around us but they're
there themselves themselves yeah and
then which is not a bad thing I mean
their business yeah so then I will cast
a stitch and I'm what I'm gonna try to
do is having seen what happens if I
leave it open too long is to use a
charge of this miracle to open it and
then suck this baylor through the water
hopefully causing this elemental damage
to this fire creature and partially or
completely and close him into this plane
so
either and it's fine if it we splint him
and snip him that's that's totally fine
too but I what I want to avoid is
sucking any of my sisters into this hole
yes yeah that's recall try great thanks
I love it so you want to leverage the
Oblivion miracle right you want to
basically DOS yeah yeah exactly but you
want to douse him mm-hmm big time yes
with this water because as a creature of
of flames your hope is that this will be
a negative experience for him yeah he
won't like it bad review on Yelp yep I'm
looking for those 1 stars no no no if I
could give less than 1 star right ok who
visit this is a pretty sophisticated
play yeah it might not work yeah yeah so
you are so you activate it and
immediately begin small right just like
last time and then it hauls if like this
massive water construct straight over
and through him and you can see like
this is just this curtain cloud of steam
that is rising off of this flaming whip
and the you can see lightning from the
sword like playing through the steam
clouds and so after he just pulled all
that past him then you are going to try
to shut it on the other side yeah if we
can suck any part of the bail or into it
I think I would want to hold out for
that you can yeah right as it as it
stands right now one of the two wings
has been enveloped almost completely
okay before I close it I'll tell him
can I can I still communicate to him I
think that would be cool and so on I
want that to happen ok I'm going to
allow it yeah ok then I shout up at him
I say you you fight with us or you fight
never again and I and he knows he's
about to get and I'm pointing to this
stitch I'm like that this is my thing
I'm acting like I know exactly what I'm
doing but I have no idea what's gonna
happen
if this happens even even life such as
yours is aboard in the quasi elemental
plane of vacuum demons this is so great
he what he does is he he basically looks
through this massive group of to him
undifferentiated mortal insects and I
just locks eyes directly with you and I
don't like it
no he pulls up his lightning sword and
just cuts his own wing off and then
reaches over and basically like slams
the side of the tower mm-hmm
so that it is getting loose on its base
and he pulls the tower back so that now
this tower is in this process of being
consumed oh but it's by the stitch okay
good point now we need a nisshin's oh
that's good sixteen so close
it's a venti okay
20 20 then you go wet sixteen okay I got
good this upside down boy let's put the
baler right there he's great he's doing
quite well so he is going to just sweep
there was this massive group of foes
down in the middle of the road
mmm-hmm he is just gonna he is first
gonna he raises his whip and then like
cracks like flings and cracks it out and
it bursts back into flames
mm-hmm and then he just sweeps it across
the street
what's your AC mine yep a 16 your
conscious AC yeah dad honestly he did
not hit you so that's great okay but he
hits a lot of other people no yeah yeah
yeah yeah you want to feel what it's
like to died 20 times in one second
walnut it's actually Rosie's turn she
got 20 I got 6 oh no no no it's not your
turn
oh it's I'm gonna die never mind so this
sword is coming this sword is coming
down yeah directly on to as near as you
can tell like directly on 2 million and
I'm just gonna give you I'm just gonna
give you an opportunity oh shit as
someone of of intimacy with to react in
the way that would be that you think is
appropriate so she's also super tough
lady the correct correction might be too
you know she knew the risks
yeah so I feel like I'm overcome with
her veins feelings like they're so
strong like walnut takes a backseat and
somebody take the wheel yeah she does
think that no I knew the risks like they
all did going in but that doesn't make
it any less difficult to see it's right
in front of you and it's just to see it
happen and I think that she is overcome
with feelings of like she really let's
like the hatred in at this point who or
it's not sorrow because it's not it's
barely real so she is overcome with this
anguish
and it's gonna do something sick nasty
on her time okay so here we go ah he he
brings it directly down mm-hmm and right
as it is like three feet over it was
like as the thing is coming down it's
just like all this hair is on end and
like people people get out of the way
your battle sisters are moving to sort
of make a a gulf and as it comes down as
three feet up she raises her shield
herself and is able to deflect the blade
of this bale or what Wow
so yeah exactly
maybe maybe maybe maybe I can't see that
yeah exact you can't see it well not
done grass which is to say first sword
vervain sure I want to I have to use I
have to use magic for this there's no
way
magic is great that anything else is
well yeah you gotta love it just give it
one try your first spells free this is
like the only thing I have left that can
do damage just hate okay fine sure um he
likes lightning so much suck on this I'm
gonna do um call lightning hell yeah
yes lightning lightning hello which I
believe does a save will do half and
it's a deck save yeah so let's try do
that first and then uh-oh what's your
spell doing nothing my spell ding-dong
is 15 okay
and he gets advantage on saving throws
against spells another magical effects
kiss this is the sucks it's because it's
assisting yes and he does he does take
half okay so it's 3d 10 plus 1 D 10
damage oh my god healthy this is insane
[Music]
fucking beast right are you I feel this
clause so 9 points oh oh
6x plus 6 18 you're right you're right 9
yeah I forgot about the hats so excited
she just rolled six six six for her
dammit listen as you know as you know
Alyssa that's the number of the beast
number we still got the cool level of
shit but I have got this Elderwood nice
case we will sign this for you
precious remember it comes the generally
the demon demon dude it has a demon
within its on it it's haunted AF alright
man I know I just want to rest in that
in that perfect place right so you're so
you're calling lightning down and
multiple multiple Forks of hot lightning
are just there they're coming down and
they're being drawn into the blade but
one of them one of them catches him full
in the shoulder
and he yells Rosie B singer that is to
say more than Sofia wow they're kind of
heavy metal' all together aren't they
dude the epitome of know know that if
you're playing a dungeon the Dragons
game and it could be with very little
efforts airbrushed on to the side of a
van that's how you know you're doing it
correctly yeah that's true okay oh so he
didn't like that I didn't like that you
didn't like that I think then I'm gonna
do an earth glass mmm do it I'm gonna do
it
so molten stone shall issue from a place
of my choosing indeed which will be
under his feet and to my my goal would
be that this this would climb the the
lava would kind of like pool around his
hooves yeah cloven hooves and obsidian
him fully yes just rock hard
although absolutely yes yes that's
that's a very good choice I would say
from a damage and tactical perspective
yeah yeah he's he's taking some gruesome
hits here so the the magma rises and
then almost as though it barring some
kind of intellect is starting to creep
up creep up these legs and then it
hardens about halfway up his torso nice
those kind nice ripped yeah absolutely
it gives him more abs 666 yes that's why
that's the number exactly so it is at
this point that Grove keeper know layin
her walking in a very conscious way
wherever she goes
other people are not
if they were there they are immediately
moving out of the way and as though she
can't decide the weapon in her hand is
almost like trying to give her
suggestions mmm right she's just sort of
like moving the hilt but around this
hill this green glass is becoming
different instruments that in her
arsenal and as she moves up that the
baler reaches the whip back to cut being
fully ensconced in this as he turns you
can hear the Obsidian of the glass like
squeaking and shrieking in the torso and
she deftly avoids the whoo she
definitely avoids the the crack of the
whip she just is where it is not and
hacks deep into his left wrist which
proceeds to sort of almost hang dangling
Lee and it's it's it's he's maintaining
his grip on the sword but it is you're
not sure that's a long-term strategy
excellent yeah yeah indeed does he yell
again oh yeah he sweeps again through
the street and you see five battle
sisters just flung literally into
another district through the air he he
reaches up with his hand and then tries
to swing the sword down at Malayan and
connects okay that's not good
I had a plan for this occurrence I can
make this work all right
I'm the dungeon master here walnut dog
grass
yeah I should do something you can if
you want to he brought it down on okay
he is that's all he cares about is her I
want to you know I'm gonna do it I'm
gonna I want to cast oh yeah wait
you can do your my regular yeah maybe
she is awesome
yeah she did Graham it's okay who knows
how this fight actually happened so yeah
I'm wondering I mean actually I would
have I have that spell already anyway so
a version of it yeah
a version yes but here's my question for
you is what kind of force friends would
vervain have who would she not
could she be friends with something I
don't know her veins I mean I do but
but her veins forests friends would be
elk Oh Elks like I look like a running
elk herd well I know exactly what kind
of damage they do so let's go for that
yeah so I yeah I feel this connection to
the elk and walnut has a connection to
that to obviously because of her form
whatever yeah yeah so you feel that that
consonance yeah in those to me like I
and I just get this like this mental
image of this like proud and so um yeah
I like do my normal thing I look within
myself and I somehow in that same way
that like the spiders knew what I was
saying you know let out this call which
just seems impossible the shriek yeah
it's easy it seems impossible to call
for something in this place to call for
it to call it L for Alex down here
exactly
but the NEMA's ear answers right and
just sailing out from its mystic aura
battle ready determined forest friends
basically fire him exactly like their
merit there
there no no no it's just chunks of
chunks no they're fired
this group of them hits and then as they
as they descend they catch the road just
that they after exactly the right point
and they are up and you can hear them
coming around the around the same street
that your procession went through and
they run up what do you want to happen
with these friendly out I say
God forgive me I want them to do their
charge which I know they have oh
absolutely and I want them to charge at
the I want to try to get them to disarm
him
because he's already weakened no yet dis
hand yeah right dis hand I want it I
want it completely out of the picture I
love it
so they are they have that super odd run
yeah that weird the bound galumph e yeah
it's it's it's vector would actually be
very difficult to protect yourself
against which is probably its purpose
yeah
so they are they're running up the roads
and streets because this is a
multi-level as you've moved into the
place of scholarship and learning it's a
more ornamented architecture and they
are they are coming up they're running
into people's houses and going up the
stairs and coming out of second-story
balconies yes to jump out and they are
driving like into this deep wound that
it already has in the wrist
they are just driving their antlers just
gonna heap and until they have worried
it off at dangles for a moment the skin
stretches and then the blade falls in
the middle of the street you've gotta
hate that god I hate it
[Laughter]
Rosi be senior you are also playing
dungeons indirect I am this blade it's
Jackie
maybe very because it's it's it's a
sword designed for a huge creature it
would be difficult to pick it up if I
were one creature I connected with it do
it do it do it do it do it all right
Jerry let me do this I would like to
cast Legion no Necker let me do this no
this is too cool I'm gonna do it that is
the coolest yes in case any of you are
not coming along with me here I'd like
to do yeah exactly
I would like to cath lead gen and build
myself a baler made of wood elf warriors
who will you wield this weapon in one of
its giant multi exactly well basically
so they're all gonna be picking it up
back here from the haft me the blade
itself is coursing with deadly lightning
but securing elemental protection from a
member of your elite enclaves battle
force is not a selling proposition so
they basically make themselves into a
kind of ballista yeah that is designed
to drive this thing straight through
this bale or let me be very clear I'm
thinking like a kaiju oh no I know the
situation okay just check meters are
piling up on each other right I can't
give you that oh I can't give you cheer
squad wind on it but let me like
Bollywood
no no no it's listen there's another
game that we can do that in but in this
in this they have basically made
themselves an instrument capable of
hauling and lifting this blade to use
against their own master all right well
who do we want to do these attacks uh
I'll do ya I can roll die what so what
do you want you want me to do well no
just good let's go ahead and give me a
500 yeah yeah give me 500 each 20 no
what I would like you to do is give me
two rolls okay at +8 okay I'd like to
take advantage Oh
okay both rolls you can thank you for
the 18 charges from last time y'all
there's our plus eight so that's a 23
that's an 11 okay that's a 27 and and
there we go
all right so you are so they are able to
orient this blade and then like angle it
on another piece of architecture like a
veranda and then they get behind it and
then push it there slide it off the rest
of the way it squeaks straight through
the black glass of the obsidian directly
through its chest and then out in the
back they're all very near to it because
that is part of the process right of
driving it through and it's cruel face a
alien though it may be exalts in these
last moments
it has fallen forward on its own blade
and is sort of greedily almost like
imagine a child playing with marbles
it is greedily scooping everyone
together Oh No just like drawing them
into itself and he's even got Nilayam
huh and the two of you in the entire
fight he has pulled you together and you
can feel the heat it was already giving
off rising and it's increasing and you
can see even the inside of his mouth
like waves of heat are beginning to
spill out and delay on issues her order
which is to enter the aegis
it's a shield wall type position okay in
front of the general basically yes okay
as you do that
a moment later you are no longer
conscious of anything you know at this
point that the bail or again this alien
creature in the act of dying and Nile
eats everything that's close to it and
in the moment before this happened
billion had the presence of mind to
mercifully keep that from occur for the
two of you so she would rather that you
died by her hand then by the
ministrations of this creature and it is
at that moment that you are all in the
lowest level of how smoothly with the
corpses of your friends and growth
keeper Nolan who is less haughty even
more silent now I don't even know what
to say to her yeah what do you say she
says
how far does the Grove extend and I say
I say no farther than let's see if I'm
right I'm right if I'm right here no
farther than the sword mountains
and I've come back to a world where
my daughter's consort with the drow I
say there are none left but me
she says
strictly true
there are two of us and we will only got
our hopes up
we will comport ourselves with honor
though - we may be she says
do you have need of these - yes to what
end
and I say I say together there's no end
to what we can accomplish and
specifically the drought can take me
back to where me love is imprisoned and
you have suggested on your honour as a
daughter of the Enclave then male a--the
was captured and not cruel I look at her
dead in the eyes and I say on my
mother's honor she says
your world exhausts me and she walks out
the front of the house were loosely
notes some of the sigils scrunches her
face up and then she looks down at the
earth and stomps a couple times and
waits this sort of looks at the
impression of her great boot in the just
the spongy you know useless soil of this
ruined place and then she kneels down
and starts to like yell and curse at the
ground and she says it may be that you
have not heard it for a while but you
will do as I ask
you will hey the ancient Accords and in
that impression of the boot the spongy
soil boils and shifts itself until it
grants her to gems Wow and then she'd
scoops them up and then she goes back
into the house and she places she'd just
you know very work add a zero affection
way just grabs their dead mouths and
pulls them open like roughly hey gentle
important okay
I don't you could resurrect them do I
look like a cleric to you
she puts it puts a Jim and Carissa
Smouse she wrestles like even in death
daenerys recalcitrant she wrestles open
denars craw stuffs the gym in there
closes up both mouth puts her hands on
their faces and you think a little
roughly but almost like a almost like a
mother trying to just wake them up as if
they'd been just been asleep for a
little while
she shakes them back and forth and
quickly and they each of them spits out
a Jim that's about half the size that it
was mm-hmm and they cough for a while
but they come to oh my god
oh we did it shadow council Merrill
Labor's please it has been it has been
our great pleasure just spend this day
with you hey I'm gonna get something to
drink and then we're gonna come back and
have a table clock it's gonna be super
talk yeah table talk you off you heard
right hey don't go nowhere we read back
you