time is the enemy of the past it
threatens the fastest weapon you
wouldn't make it past a second and
answer the question play it brash and
reckless to choose a cautious solution
you saw was prudent in any sepulcher
poker to don't become the putrid it's
that well said I pursue in no mountain
too steep for dungeon too deep to send
expendable marks up to the top of the
peak of beneath they see Yugi they come
like sharks to it while I swim in that
money bill like Carl Barks through it so
send your National Parks drew it I'll
send him home in a natural box with a
close tie the most of the parts included
save your breath for a cleric confessor
death is a lesson that life is attending
professor but if you're seeking my
official advice sign on the dotted line
and this should the choice well I'm
Jericho Hawkins well no they didn't have
didn't finish their song here you do the
song we did it hello okay okay I
finished them here
I'm Ted Cobra hey if Penny Arcade
attacks I'm also a minute.this Hereward
run CEO of acquisitions incorporated but
today Jerry Hawkins and here to run a
game of Dungeons and Dragons for my hand
my friends specifically birthday and
best friend episode 2 season 2 of
acquisitions incorporated the c-team see
my right I am joined by Dragonborn
narcissist dinar blitz in yeah yes yes
the Doppler this is just self
high-fiving over and over again and it
is in it I never even thought about that
to the right of my right repping the
natural world walnut dog grass
[Music]
is that just for the is it just for
today's episode or is it I don't know
find out I was guys how did you do it
I got cranked up what it's gonna take a
game or two to find a rhythm it's the
watering-pot was very good I like that
oh hello to my left not your grandma's
grandma except for those rare cases
where she is your grandma's grandma
Rosie bee stinger fresh from the
acquisitions incorporated main stage all
night crazy on a rod like it's an
incredible new fitness regimen
I'm only available here at the ski team
to the left of my left emerging as
though from a mist shroud cthe wrist
route no no no what there is some nerd
that I have to get out of the way
first
before we jump in a whole hog or with
both feet or whoever you want to jump in
both hogs intentionally get inside that
hog get all your high bring it with you
jump they can jump too so just like just
like last time you may have recalled
that you were able to grant boons in
your role as members of the shadow
Council you were able to grant boons to
our players that they can leverage
either as advantages on rolls or special
abilities that are unique to each
character that's still true the values
are there you'll see them in the UI but
when you donate bits when you cheer in
there if you use hashtag and then the
character's name these will be
apportioned directly to them they can
choose to use them either as abilities
or as advantage but there's another
thing that happens which is all kinds of
crazy which is that I have a bar the
players cannot see it but I have a bar
hoho it's just mine it's a special bar
called the cauldron and I have a special
table I can roll on where sometimes good
and sometimes bad things happen to
players based on the aggregate
bits so it hits a certain value then I
get to do something cool cool being
defined by me for once you know finally
some cool not others yeah sorry
no no parents allowed don't that's my
cauldron early voting so last season
people could vote during the show which
was very fun right but we want to extend
the window a little bit
so now voting will be available starting
on Monday so if you're somebody who
watches the show over the weekend are
you catch it on YouTube or on podcast
you'll be able to put your votes in
because these votes have changed a lot
of really important things in the game a
lot of things if you're not familiar
with that part of the show a lot of
characters in the show are named by it
there's been a lot of interesting Forks
in the road that have drastically
changed the campaign and that is all due
to this works of the shadow council so
you'll be able to sign in to AK dash
ENCOM with your Twitter handle do your
voting right there if you change your
mind later you can vote and go just
overwrite it it's fine our engineer
rules so that's gonna be pretty sweet
and then but the natural twenty
giveaways two things two things for one
Gavin murdered
yeah these emotes they look so good they
look so good oh they're they're straight
murder but but here's here's the dealio
when in natural twenty-year-old
two things should occur one you should
use the womp-womp-womp
ste mode that's vital but also just like
last time we are gonna give you cool
now if you are not a sub we welcome
you into the shadow council even still
but you get a $20 gift certificate to
the penny arcade store whether it has
all kinds of acting stuff subs get a
signed elder would hex chests or
something cool from level up dice that
will debut next week
get trumps no they don't get no they get
the truck you got hug
Thank You nubs no these are the video
subscribe this branding is subpar I mean
I want I want to minimize that now so
here's what's going on
subs get rubs yeah so if you are new to
the c-team you should recognize that
this dynamic is a constant feature
I am favorite no we play our own version
of Dungeons &amp; Dragons pretty much like
everybody else does yeah we crank up the
romance we play a game it's a radically
charged no that's not true either well
no you know it is occasionally you're
out of the charger but it's like this
it's like this hopefully you have caught
up with the last episode that debuted at
PAX South this course up on the Penny
Arcade YouTube and on Twitter if you're
into that sort of thing but the main
thing that we need to know is in the
current incarnation it would appear that
Brahma Sigrid Lu da there is some
evidence that Brahma Sigrid Ludi eight
underwent some kind of a change as she
remained behind in Scala to resist an
incursion of Tiamat cultists now I
blamed her well no you shouldn't blame -
no you should blame the channel because
the channel action kept her there good
one I'm transferring my anger I blame
the audience and our fans thanks to
business didn't pull the drop down all
right fans um but that's that's we
learned that very very quickly before a
battle with cultists deep in the guts of
an abandoned sort of Sepulcher -
Lysander I said things about Lysander
that an oppressor Robinson did not
appreciate and I want to apologize for
that right now
sorry about that it is becoming a member
of the tribulus ender is not exactly a
hundred percent
joining Scientology I think that there's
some interplay right there are levels
yeah you know exactly all clear
well note exactly light but no but also
it's like it wait as soon as you go to
the with ender Celebrity Center who you
know I mean you're seeing some parallels
yeah oh and across the Robertson oh yeah
may we you name any big fan yeah but so
that is the situation obviously our
parents are wrapped in here somewhere so
when that game ended
you were left sort of in this evil
cistern yes at the base of this cylinder
what of the brother no you are fired
like that cauldrons full now what this
is what's going on you can see oak true
strike who said she went through all the
proper channels issued an authentic
acquisitions incorporated job order to
help him find Brahma
Ludi a half way through your journeys
inside this dungeon you received a
communique from the head office that
said that team Bellerophon had been
dissolved so that his part of the
organization his ability to do anything
he wants wherever he wants under the
company's auspices are also gone and
indeed there are specific 700 gold
rewards to bring in any member of Team B
so he is now standing before you he is
on the stairs that lead back up to level
two and then level one then obviously
out into the town of Westbridge that is
where we said our scene C team okay how
can I be of assistance which portion of
this world can I simulate for your
pleasure
I grow zis looking at you at walnut cuz
there's a there's a lot to unpack here
and Brahma has vanished right if she is
here you cannot find her okay and are
you in a wolf form still no you ever
know
was okay no I'll be back as a person now
okay Rosie please do the transformation
blue what's the opposite of helu Rosie's
like are you guys fighting what's going
on here
and then okay um yeah well not start
stammering exactly like I just did yeah
and then while she's doing that she's
looking at cthis hoping that maybe he
gets gets it I don't think she does
never gotten it so she says she goes
okay we have a situation and I'm just
gonna say it I'm just gonna say it
uh-hmm oak is no longer part of
acquisitions incorporated and we have to
bring him in then she just looks right
at oak uh Rosie looks right it out
sounds good to me so what are you
talking about you no longer have a wild
card license and you are to come with us
where uh you didn't you didn't get there
you can get to the next part of that I
don't need a next part I'm concerned
with this part yeah yeah
Rosie's prepping a stunning strike just
in case oak tries anything yeah well my
goes I'm gonna take you to our office
and I'm gonna do all the paperwork on it
and I want to kiss untangle let's see it
yeah you consider Thor whip sock the
better of it consider throwing whip
it's alright it's a little while whip
okay gravity and vine sprout from the
ground in a twenty foot square starting
from a point within range for the
duration these plants turn the ground
into difficult terrain
he must succeed a strength saving throw
or be restrained okay
I took the spell out exactly so the
whole area is is like that for everybody
yeah I got it 20-foot radius okay just I
just wanna make sure like you're gonna
entangle him and then you're gonna go
and try to give him and you will also be
slight
no I support Mali I support you one here
percent yeah I'm about it yeah so
strength strength check and away we go
okay he sidesteps the grasping roots and
then one especially tenacious P vine
begins to wrap up and around his boot
and he cuts it he grabs his who's got
claw like knife and slices it out and he
says I'll go you don't you don't have to
force me you're just gonna come with us
what kind of trick is this what's like
as convenient as it might be to die in a
mausoleum I'd rather not do it today if
we can get away with it mmm-hmm you can
always be put in a mausoleum later after
death you know we're not to do it here
it just is always inbound it's exactly
like his report I mean like to a tee
it's this is exactly the sort of thing
he would say he's been nothing but a
good guy this whole time see I don't buy
any of this he's like you can cast it
again
no it's fine it did exactly what I
wanted to do this time you just scare
you into submitting and I win and
everyone saw me win shut off that bow
he's like okay right why are you being
so agreeable you've been nothing but a
butthole to us every single time we've
seen you arguably I was mostly a
butthole to walnut you're about holding
you're like you're a butthole to all of
us even dinar I don't think that's how
it works I I think that I think maybe
I'll make a case I think I pretty much
know how it works I know a lot of things
work in five holes this one yeah my
goddamn little savant since I got there
my PhD I'm gonna go upstairs and as a
proof of my you know equanimity in these
matters he's so smart
that's a big word guys
you will find me waiting by the horse
equanimity I liked it no no you're not
going not letting him just walk up all
on his own no of course not
Alice Court listen to you you let me
tell you hold on both knives go back in
he says listen I just want you one time
I want you to make up the rules ahead of
time and then I can follow them because
what's happening now is you're making up
the rules every five minutes and I have
to relearn them let's just I'll do what
you want but I want you to decide what
that is now I want you to decide what
that is now what could she possibly see
in you all right that's exactly what I'm
talking about
that's the butthole rocket but always it
to us though yeah it wasn't it was tough
but fair honestly here's the rules I'm
gonna tie you up
my grandmother's rope I'm gonna take you
upstairs I'm gonna put you in our cart
and we're gonna take you to our office
to a really good office that we have
very good it's very official and then
I'm gonna contact head office Rosy's
growls for some reason she's like okay
he's like no kinky stuff just like
they're regular you know like don't make
it here uh-uh she'll do whatever kinky
stuff she wants yeah so she ropes up his
wrist and she looks at that and she's
like yeah good job
and then she and then she goes like this
and then she wraps that around him she's
good and then also maybe she's not
really good at not so it's just a puzzle
it's like your hand fasting him to
himself yeah yeah exactly she's kinda
like tucking it in itself and then tying
a bow I guess survival check maybe yeah
I love it
oh yeah no bad it's like a it's like
this sort of dress you might see on
today's runways yeah I mean it's just
well it's beautiful but it's loose and
drape you know what I mean rosie is
it'll mess around it looks like he's
wearing a doily it's called a trust not
sure Rosa says I'm decoy and
when walnuts not looking she does better
so ties it nice it's one of these things
case Brennan would be able to do this
yeah she like takes the loop and like
underneath here and then yep yep I'm
like this is a really good work and then
I got like a sixteen you know no good
knots because you're a sailor you do
like a bowline knot yeah like a see
that's some see stuff yeah yeah I know
but basically it's like a couple a
couple flips of this rope have you ever
seen these I talked about
this I think when we were in never win
here before these old on
the dock yeah we can take the rope and
go whoa and that boat is never gonna
move exactly it's like this it's like
it's like tuck tuck tuck and then all of
a sudden one big pull in the back and
it's a corset yeah it's just like fat
that's the clue
see that's good role playing pretending
you don't know about knots when you
really do that's the ultimate gamer
experience obviously that our viewers
yeah why's about nice rosy rosy jabs him
in the knot that she made like get
walking read the knots I'm not carrying
retinas screen is nuts thankful cycle
okay you're gonna carry her like a sack
of potatoes but really gently and then
when you go my shoulder I just go when
you're ready to betray them just so you
know I do a perception insight check or
something on that because I want to hear
that oh that's awesome yeah all
right I'm gonna do a they're both the
same oh no didn't hear anything I love
you dinar it's not the best your loyalty
that I treasure yeah you you hear him
you hear him utter something no very
close very in this very intimate context
you know that that hot breath was
exchanged I'm starting to ship it yeah
I'm like this cute together
alright yeah it works
yeah opposites attract no magnets work
plus plus so as you guys you get up to
the second floor yes
Gaylord Durer rolls up oh yeah
and then you hear he sees he sees who is
and he's like oh that's nuts tan no
right no we're right on out of here
going okay it's like I don't have 100%
control over these boys you got a you
got a skedaddle we're gonna look out for
your boys all right all right you seem
come and just don't be where they are
beat to the left or right it's fine but
you know talking about this guy's got it
all right I like it level two boom Rosie
makes friends everywhere this is short
well short all right do what you
discussion we keep going up yeah yeah up
and up so he's there's there's some
hopping it's not the optimal you know
comfort level for a person is it is
there's some inch were Marie yeah
especially when the staircase is sort of
go up and split it's a it's inconvenient
but he is trying to manage it there's
not a lot of complaints I thought he was
being carried by oh that's right yeah
that's right this is all lovingly yeah
that's right good potatoes romance yeah
exactly yeah cradle his head it's good
because his head is click behind you or
in front of you I shift a moment okay
okay so Rosie Rosie who's gonna whisper
everyone surrounds like kind of ropes
uncomfortable they a little too tight
it's made out of the worst most scratchy
material oh it's it's like savage like
hemp
yeah it's essentially barbed wire yeah
it's grandma's hemp rope it's good it's
great fingers of yeah no it's like
a it's like a chainsaw blade yeah
basically just sort of loose steel
thirteen pieces okay he's gone so he
wasn't feeling in your extremities yet
he smiles and gives you a week don't
want it I throw it back I reject it no
no three it's not gonna do it for you
got a fourth one no I'm good
these guys are winking to each other
round that's about what Rosie's gonna
betray us everyone get her
there's some mean things to me recently
that's true really sorry hurtful things
it's true
you don't even have daddy issues what
faucet that's right thank you okay say
it's a low can hear it oh yeah I was
gonna I have this wonderful thing is
like um I go up to oak and I'm just
talking I'm tormenting him yeah just
just just like needling him and I say
you know it's a shame you got yourself
captured you know maybe a real man had
been around might not happen oh nasty I
say it loud some walnut will hear me so
she'll be proud of me yeah
she likes it she like she smiles herself
a little bit yeah a real man like well
ver yeah oh you don't even know so your
speed uh something like that I like that
yeah yeah I could I could teach you a
finger too if I bothered I can find the
time I'm not sure you've ever met a real
man I gotta be honest with you like that
see this this what I'm talking about
you just said you're not a butthole to
anybody but her but you were justified
holding me what is that
I was profiting him I say this is how I
flirt if you're gonna get mad every time
I tell the truth I'm not sure we can
work together I don't I don't doubt it
this staircases turning me on yeah this
is like we're at the top of the seventh
started walking into the sky all right
where'd the carton all right yeah it's
just like all right cool well uh yeah I
mean I wherever you want to lay me it's
good sweetly like a little baby Jesus
well there's only major dinar and
there's like an evil staff just like
this like maternal clucking like yeah
yeah enjoy enjoy that his his neck is
twitching a little bit he's trying to
absorb it but it's like
jerk sit next to Rosie and open the
sliding door and just have face like
like stretch the litter yeah like and
angry - perfect
perfect I whispered a coriander Oaks had
some really mean things about you down
there just so you know I don't I don't
want anybody else to tell you I want to
hear coriander steps down hard
yeah and chips the cobble I know whoa I
know there's some fanfic about coriander
being the one that ends oak by the way
yeah it's gross okay where where are we
going is there anything in the missive
that says where we're supposed to take
him uh you you said you wanted to go
home well I mean we've never been to the
play we can't fast travel to the place
where head offices but we could go to
head office when we do that well gang
also I can message them I can send to
them and just say we got away on you
yeah that's true so why don't you do
that and then I'll train right on the
thing at the same time that we're a
location magician yeah oh yeah thank you
hmm well I mean I guess omens ago -
right sure one of the missiles was for
who's the least mad when I intruded upon
their mind not Jeff seems extreme didn't
like it yeah seems like they'd be
pleased to hear this news
so I compose a message which says we're
locked weak yeah Westbridge captured oak
how are you yeah like space yeah yeah
what um where would you like him
bring money yes yes I'm very hungry
have a great day await response awaiting
response when yours yeah
that's yours up to 25 yeah yeah yeah
yeah you receive a message back in omens
voice that says that you should return
him to the drawing courier and they will
be sending up a cart from Waterdeep to
bring him back okay
wait been doing in pick one I convinced
it's very terse - very terse very
businesslike and having a simple we're
not to set up the John and Cordy like a
gulag you can stay in my room
that's fine no no you can stay in denars
room I'll sleep on them he's got I got a
B honestly he's had eyes on the whole
time I've been watching him is there
going to be an incredible guard broke he
hasn't let's lift his eyes drift at all
maybe we should tell coriander a story
yeah and get back to you faster happy -
I want to hear it um so coriander so as
soon as as soon as you begin to whisper
- coriander yeah the soap bubble shimmer
starts to form nice it's spin and then
add some details okay we have to get
back quickly so at top speed under cover
of night we are on our way back to red
larch oak says some really insulting
things about copper Dragonborn and you
know it gets really angry at him and and
it's it's something that they can't
reconcile they they hate each other
really good real bad back there it's a
lot it's a lot and it's loud and a
walnut falls asleep with her head on my
shoulder for a little while
did we get back what do what do I do I
just take turns peeing into the cart
yeah I mean yeah
Curtis is is also upset about the mean
things that oak said about copper
driving board because he didn't or have
a special relationship
it was very defensive okay his friend
I'm gonna make the ship happen exactly
you're sitting very close to you when we
arrived yeah
when the bubble I wouldn't a bubble
around the cart pops you're only a few
feet from the carriage house and
coriander is just awaiting direction
okay to get it back in there
all right reach into my mic my coin
purse and she's expensive this season
interests yeah she's ten coins top her
off
yeah yeah yes first trade off yeah
exactly she did good job so yeah at the
ten coins um coriander backs the card in
herself do it it's like some kind of or
it's like oh yeah he's a good eye on the
orb how does you have an orb you could
you could install an orb right there and
that would be your that would be your
ear Revier mmm-hmm all right so this
thing is is slotted back in here back
into there exactly
put him in the fridge yeah exactly
I like that idea really think the
holding cell should be fridge no he's
been nothing but amenable so meaning so
he said yeah I go from like barring him
did not understand yet so do you is he
is it still well gently lay him on the
floor okay so good but you but I'm
saying you've carried him he's not
hopping in or anything like that so you
have him over your shoulder as you're
walking in and
okk says well know what you better
hope you find her before I do
and as he passes through the doorway of
the drowning courtier come on there is a
pop and a slight pressure on the inner
ear and as you cross the threshold he is
completely gone they're sending a cart
now somebody make it oak oh my god and
I'm looking around at the patrons and
I'm like who looks like him oh my god
but all we need is ashes and some teeth
and like that's all I need it's real
fast leave it to necromancer Catherine
yes
oh I just met his evidence what he was I
know it seems weird to me you have son
yeah you have some experience with this
with this process yeah with the what do
you want it was the way that Brahma left
right right that one time but she didn't
she disappeared through a portal yeah
she disappeared through a pole and we've
seen it happen with potions too that
people drink and disappear
they just solvents wither away we've
never seen someone bound and then
Houdini Styles finish while they're
being held they came across the
threshold Oh
so the b-team can't exist inside the dnc
somehow they're all dreams but they used
to be stationed at the DNC that's true
yeah that's true you remembered so much
I remember DeRozan he runs outside to
see if maybe he's just been like
vanished back outside the threshold is
he out there he's only out there he's
gone he's completely go he's not pushed
out can I do a locate object give me an
object I can look it hard I'll then
describe her name an object that is
familiar to you I can something on his
garb his knight what was he wearing
you know his codpiece he has confidence
baby do you count no that's not where
this is going this is admiration times
oak smarty want to remove the cut pieces
yeah just ditch no he's a step ahead he
put her on a cat chasing the Saturn you
have finite
like dragon like this sparks all right
yeah I'll uh yeah I'll thinking to
describe his knives his knives are his
telltale thing actually if you you are
not pulling up anything about his knives
on this plane hmm what wolf on this
plane um I do detect magic on the
threshold Oh what do you got for me oh
absolutely
then you have experience with this you
have experienced with this threshold
your silk I know that is that
enchantment and that enchantment has not
been altered or removed since you had
your own experiences there may be he's
always in the end now maybe he's still
back in there he's tiny everyone look at
their feet where's the what part is he I
would have located him then I would have
felt him yeah you're right okay
unless I was too tiny to feel between my
as you come in onyx emerges for
underneath a table and Rose her face on
your boot nice she has kind of a limp in
the right paw um I want to talk to her
speak with animals and I say um friend
what's wrong well hearing us yeah I got
a refresh refresh
I got refresh heard now um she's like oh
this and then she like raises a paw like
in what she must think is a brave oh and
she's like it's nothing nothing what to
do I'm not leaning into the paw I say I
I looked down at her and I go um and I
go what what why don't I why don't I fix
that for you how um cast healing word
you asking the cat
oh no I'm talking to you Oh totally yeah
yeah yeah yeah you try you to my dungeon
man you know exactly you know exactly
ask the cat
okay it's onyx that says how okay I know
I know you're in Truitt save eight um I
look at onyx and I go oh I have I have a
way my people have a way are you guys
meowing at each other right now by the
way yeah yeah you know just like right
in the middle of the foyer but it's the
weird Mouse like for this level of
sophistication it's like no it's like
that like some of the chitter well no
it's like it's like I'm gonna see a fly
in the windowsill yeah it's legit cat
talk it's like well I hate mondays
you nermal I'm just cracking up I
don't get that reference
Heathcliff Hobbes was a tiger yeah I go
I go
may may I touch her paw Oh cat scent no
she says for a moment I and while it
goes oh oh just just for a moment
she knows that onyx is a very proud
creature and then she gets to heal some
stuff cuz I say my healing word which is
Wow which is something sure wish I knew
what it was they never can know it's
good enough like Anna healthy ever been
yeah it's amazing
da to the cat ears it becomes like it's
like you know it's like it's like it got
a invincibility star it's just like all
rainbows that's a song no but it's just
like like imbue you so you you hold it
in your hand
hmm you hold the paw and then as you
whisper the word like you can feel like
you can feel three pretty substantial
pricks in the base of the paw and you
can sort of feel them you can feel them
and the
reassert themselves in proper healthy
configuration hey how did this happen
you know me well yes I do you know that
I am a proud creature yes you're right
so it must have been hunting there are
creatures who are full of boldness
mm-hmm
this time of year and think that a cat
is not their master it's just just brown
whiskers down that's a dangerous time so
since I have you here let me ask you a
question do you remember a man who used
to work here
[Music]
his name's Oak yeah that's how I feel
that's him yep that's the one no need to
tell me that can't wait I'm Nick yeah
you fat cat it's freaking out shut up
I'm doing something but just like the
back is arching and she says I am not
unfamiliar with this creature I say we
just tried to bring him here and he
disappeared has he ever done that before
well there was a period of time where he
dwelt here with us hmm
a time I do not enjoy recalling who
would but every one of the groups that
profit mothers in this place the first
time they enter as it was with you they
don't enter completely they enter one of
the other worlds right
as we know as is true how do I get to
that other you know how to get to the
other worlds
don't you for me there's one world
well then I'm perplexed but she crawls
up like yeah you ever have a cat to give
you a hug no no animals ever love me
jury
oh well it happens yes yeah the paws are
up and she says did you have anything
the first time you came that you never
had again yes I did an acorn a Gold
capped acorn not delicious not delicious
I agree with you hmm
kinda extra points yeah lousy problem
maybe no so at this point I'll say I'm
Leslie thank you I hope you're feeling
better
there's never anything else I can do
right up right upstairs good various
like take to it yeah I'm just gonna melt
back into the ground in the inner in the
meantime I'm talking to you and I'm
saying did you know he was gonna do that
did he did you help him do that cuz if
you didn't vanish
ya know was awesome though yeah I mean
because if you didn't then like we got a
terrible advice from the head office as
in terms of what to do with him don't
tell us to do that it's probably the
worst place we could have taken them
what's here that's known um I had to
know if that was what's gonna happen
that's true
can you talk to I'm gonna get her is
your size I had to take a break
yeah that cuz it's blown but because I
don't bother him right the Secretary on
yeah yeah go for it I'm gonna pull out
the ledger at this point little two
level to ledger document believe
should have it we should have it with us
here just while we do the show but it
was it would be okay what's on this way
back to my truck but it would be totally
okay if you wanted to have the documents
in seven years we just wear costumes
every week this will just be right to
the on the missed' that the that had
been said before yeah like we're turning
on it and say you know like went walnut
from obviously very official all of the
steps a yep and then upon entering
drownin courtier office okay sure strike
disappeared with a popping noise
threatened us was it butthole was like
that pothole is still at large
nobody the decoration me like if you're
like was a butthole was not a butthole
and it's like you see a check big check
big hole at large I like going back to
the idea that walnut right right so it's
like just an asterisk yeah yeah so um
even like halfway through your your
missive you start to hear scratching on
the next page okay I turn it so you you
flip it up and it says why did you not
search your prisoner - secretary and
then what you say is what were they
saying you know um they just want
confirmation of our location right now
and then walnut writes our decision
assuming like put that on me well
risking him for 24 hours
first of all wasn't my prisoner your
prisoner is my friend I don't brisk my
friend did dinar maybe notice
something that would have known his
person is that a role that can be made I
yeah an acorn some acorn in your pocket
yeah may not have been in his pocket
yeah a desperate man I don't just had
people cut I mean you were he was all up
on you
maybe yours own it's like the princess
in the teeth yeah yeah yeah trying to
make it so dinar could be helpful but
retro actively so yeah so I write our
decision to shortcomings and then while
I'm waiting for a reply is there a point
and snores remember the reply so you
flip it over write your note slip it
over and then after a pause it says that
most likely Oh true strike had a port
key to access the test market so I slam
it shut and I say here's what we know
remember those acorns that we had and we
first got here and how they took us to
the other versions of the end yeah it
seems that oak had one of those on his
person and he is now in a place that we
can't get to without these tokens well
is he gonna be stuck there cuz that's
fine yeah how did we get out is he gonna
show up in here yeah that's the thing
you've got two things we can do we can
either find one and go after him or wait
cuz he's gonna pop up in the end that's
what we did only got another test market
yeah that's a great idea dinar that's a
great idea
that's true I guess yeah you just chill
out but Oka's a sneaky bastard
so where did we pop out and then in our
West you know okay in the middle round
if we know exactly where then what we
could do is go to that room that was his
and just put like some blades where his
hamstrings are gonna show up I'm just
ladies last them oh my god I think
that's a really and I'm gonna go low
blood just to try just try and then
we'll have them an assault it's all good
yeah you gave some to I'll have it dark
up before dark everybody well look you
can be it's 700 gold
all right let's should go upstairs and
we should hang out okay all right I'm
wait for him which room was his well if
we go in the sniffing just check them
all out here in our beds oh I can still
talk to that Onix I like it yeah I look
at onyx if she if she's still here I go
front Oh friend uh what room was Oakes
room she walks over to the stairs and
then walks up to the top of the stairs
mm-hmm and I follow her it looks
delicious looks down Thao swish swish
okay I follow her really fast
ungracefully she takes you to denars
room where we in any other room the in
new I look at new um well like us thank
you friend you are so generous and then
she in Washington um so we're just gonna
chill in dinner sir yeah sleepover in
denars room nice this is not all right
[Laughter]
you know get your so I get in and get
immediately naked you guys do what you
want armor comes off the second I
welcome here Josie has zero reaction
perfectly fine clothes are off this is a
close on or off room I just wanna be
polite I think I'm surprised you even
yeah this is ours ruin ours rules
there's a placid smell of Mercy space
and she goes I'll go get I'm gonna wait
outside the door I'm Casey gets out
thank you yes she's standing outside
tonari story she is this like the same
Redis or Armour it's just like one color
yeah it like came up steam steam that's
the classic yep happy years absolutely
Rosie does go down and get some slumber
party snacks
cornerstones scones any kind of like
fruits that she could find
a big ol picture yeah yeah I mean you
know you know that cornerstones are
they're not best you know cold right
some people like him like that so you're
on the counter overnight yeah yeah I'm
I'm up but there aren't me there are if
there are a few that you can did you
guys get a profit down here too
she is okay I'd like to just fill her in
on the situation which parts make it up
stash their naked the boys are naked
we're having a slumber party
I'm looking Nicky you're invited we've
got Nicky boys it's gonna be fun but no
I tell her about the situation with
bromine oak and the the mausoleum of
Lysander and the statue and she looks
over at her door and she's just like
this dark magic boy never I never really
understood it
yeah he's kind of a it's kind of a
birdbrain yeah I was told that he had
removed it because something happened to
it once what
well people I was assured that they were
eventually rescued but people would go
in and then not return what kind of
people like a lot of people trainees oh
yeah yeah it's kind of have you been in
there Ohman told me that he went in
right away
oh and was able to get them back out I
see well okay have you have you been
through it yourself
have you ever tried it no no I I'm I am
told that I am never to cross the
threshold while having an acorn captain
gold and I felt like that was a
reasonable restriction because that's
not something I customarily have it's
oddly specific so we've been through it
that's like the trial they've to to
become a part of the enterprise and
there were some folks last how we were
there that had not come out but also
didn't seem like they wanted to they
seemed pretty chill good for them
yeah I mean they're living their best
life yeah they babe they made the best
of a bad situation yeah I'd like I'd
like to meet these easy
oh um the trial isn't fun
I wouldn't recommend voluntarily
entering it and you know it's a dark
it's it's a mess in there carnivores I
don't know how you feel about rodents a
lot of those they're in a better place
though you don't have to cross the
threshold but we could certainly get you
these nuts where do you have do you know
where they keep well yeah that's one of
the roasted nuts or one of the people
come here for that right well I don't
know if it's just any nut though well
you have gold and she sucky she's like
it's not it's done but let proffer help
you so all right she she goes over next
to the stove and she opens a bin it has
almost like a there's like a brass
handle on it and she pulls it down and
then looking with her into it it is
absolutely empty okay and then in the
base of it you can see a little daylight
peeking through inside the bin where the
outside is okay she looks in close and
she says damn it yeah that's damn it
she's like I needed ID he doesn't see
what happened on the outside oh oh so
she just lets it go and the entire
mechanism just slams up okay and then
she goes it she looks over her mall
thinks better of it and then walks out
the front door okay
scowls at some ragged-looking hops from
last year that are still on the trellis
she hasn't cleared them away yet
exactly right she goes around the side
and looks in and you can see very
plainly scraped scrabbled chewed an
access point from outside has been
almost surgically established by what
looks like animal that's that's that's
sufficient I mean there's a lot of
scraping and what you'd think would be
teeth okay orange okay be a minutes it's
helpful but oh the whole what about the
bite I'm scratch marks do they look like
they came from a large animal no no no
okay okay so we got like a squirrel
infestation problem going on hey I
listen I just I just give you the amount
hurt and cancel I just give you the
information okay you know I don't
oh I don't know to do with it I'm a
passive you know agent in this is this
Jerry or father well what's the
difference really inter
okay so you've this this is the where
the bin where you keep your nuts
looks like somebody's gotten in and
eating all your nuts the hunt she looks
back at you just is that is that the
case yes Rosie okay alright well she
reads there's there's a bin around the
edge underneath a an EVE full of
firewood and she gets a few pieces snaps
them up and then basically just tries to
stuff the whole with the wood okay oh
can I do a I'll just try a survival
check mother test yeah you win
local local squirrel nope that's the
point it's a florida squirrel that's no
good okay so Rosie's kind of helpless
here this is not this is not her Forte
but she does know someone who's pretty
good up in the wilderness so well right
here the boys doing while I'm up
giggling yeah you might be giggling nice
I'm serious as a heart attack in that in
a room and I'm like I'm upset and to the
two of you ice I say were you doing
there we don't want to split the party
when he shows up disrobe and return plan
a is on before done we have to be ready
for him he might know the test market
better than us that's true
almost certainly does when you hear that
long just keeps going nope nope no no no
no no no no she's get a little no song
yeah okay voice you stay out there and
wait for oak well not deer could you
come down outside meet me out here yes
she charges downstairs goes outside yes
check this out so as you as you go to
the front door and open it profit is
like saying realistic and then she holds
the door one goes okay all right her
faces her face is hard oh so sorry for
your loss yes so she she she you can see
she passes you and sort of takes up an
angry position behind the bar and around
the corner you see Rosie B singer who is
not your grandma's grandma not not in
this season yeah I'm inspecting like
trying to do this like detective work
yeah CSI red alert you yeah CSI red
large put up clearly I'm not even
looking in the right place I'm like I
picked up a leaf and I'm like yeah yeah
I'm holding up to the Sun I'm checking
the keep a shadow that it casts and I'm
like no some trials yeah exactly
I come up and I see that there's a hole
on the side of the thing right look at
the scratch marks and I go oh
interesting
you take oh six to survive yeah and I
say oh looks like we got a problem
wait you think got a squirrel's we got a
squirrel problem not even that anyways
North oh no no no it's like a it's like
a displace your squirrels notes I know
it's a large words red squirrel oh but
the larger risk oh so you can see the
the claw and the tooth this all makes
sense but there are other types of
scrapes
around this sort of portal they've made
into the nut dimension why I live there
that's not a real eye I should not have
dammit it's not I should not have said
that I don't want to confuse it but but
that is it but there is another type of
there is another scraper that doesn't
that is that is not made by a squirrel
Oh bored
it's like bored out it's not animal oh I
see so there's some there's something
that looks like maybe a human agent also
made this whole sure or some kind of
Robo squirrel Oh
Robo squirrel nice did you have for
summon squirrels as a forest friends
thing oh yeah I'm wondering if squirrels
the consequences of our forest friends
yeah I think you killed most of it was
squirrels at one point yeah sure
definitely birdies but yeah but there's
tracks yell or sure it wouldn't be weird
exactly it wouldn't be weird to see them
obviously in town like this town is out
and there's trees exactly but by the
same token this is an especially well
traveled squirrel Highway I better turn
the great scroll I look at this and I go
well we have a score problem but more
importantly we have an oak problem what
are we doing out here
oh I explained I explained now here it
comes
prompt thought we could make one an
acorn dipped in gold and travel to the
oak dimension ourselves so we came to
check out the nuts the nuts were gone
that's a we've got a sort of a yak yak
shaving situation happening okay yak
shaving day it's a deep cut what if we
what if we get all together and we just
asked the squirrels to come back and
give us the nuts yeah we could do that
or we could just go keep waiting for
okay
yes this is a dumb idea yeah no I really
like the squirrel idea Rosie I like it a
lot better than being in that room they
are 100% naked I know and I'm missing it
not much to miss what are you doing I
mean you realize at this point I have to
guard dinar I'm teaching you Boulder
knife parchment tail Boulder beats knife
oh he's parchment parchment beats
Boulder tail beats everything yes oh
yeah I've never tailed you said and you
keep losing the guy he doesn't count as
a tail it's not fair for one because I
don't know what he is you could be a
tail of a larger being we keep going in
circles about this by right of like you
know the transitive property is not in
this room we think we can make our own
port keys if we just get some acorns do
you want to help with that or do you
want to keep playing your children's
game how how quickly do you think we can
do it because I think that's a better
plan but I'm worried that we're gonna
just miss him maybe we save somebody
cover the front door or something no you
have proper keep an eye on it maybe
yeah well have proper keep an eye out
you know do you guys mind putting your
clothes back on so this is all happening
in your bed wait so and you fill us in
on this yeah you're mentioning squirrels
so we get clear and cool and so you're
outside with her yeah we're absolutely
you're having a conversation yes
auspicious out the window and says oh if
she leaves and then comes back with a
small Warhammer nothing like her
mother's mom oh she's like yeah where is
like she hasn't left the house much
let's get her let's get her some fresh
air
we're just gonna go get
a clown story all right a one that goes
absolutely we'd love to have your
services okay you can see behind the
glass like her hair is getting a little
bit it's in sort of a middle length she
hasn't she hasn't she hasn't shaved it
in a while she's been busy doing
something else but it looks good nice
nice that's great
she looks like a like a brother like a
proper grin yeah okay so the guys can
decide if they want to come down and
join him but yeah I I come down I say
that's a better plan all right let's do
that
we need to yeah you know what I mean
like hell he will show up either he's
just gonna show up here because we
brought him out where he'll show up here
by himself either way he will be in this
room I was talking about squirrels a lot
in the car yes I'm assuming so so let's
yeah I address as I walked down the
stairs
I don't care okay yeah yeah I joined
outside yeah okay uh well it looks at
everybody she is all right I'm gonna ask
the squirrels to come here and hopefully
they're gonna bring a nut with them and
it's gonna be everybody's responsibility
to grab their own squirrel and get their
own nut if Dad killed a squirrel there's
one thing I know it's that I can get a
nut oh this laughter is in character
okay everyone's gonna grab a squirrel
yes and then I go everybody try and help
get this with getting his squirrel when
you're flying in a plane and it's like
please apply your own but someone just
grab my squirrel oh okay well I gotta
yeah oh yeah yeah sure that horrible
scary thing okay and so at this point I
want to use one of my ability for a
source for runs can do and I want to say
to just shout out to the forest
bring me my nut
[Music]
just like out in the street Thank You
shadow Council exactly exactly
lentils so you summon you summon just
this phalanx of squirrels it's like
imagine imagine if you will you play
never ever play animal crossing it's a
joke no no you play the animal crossing
you know how there's like trees and so
you can go shake the imagine that
it was a squirrel tree imagine there was
such a thing
and so squirrels are just raining their
tails flipping in the air and they're
just running and jumping toward you and
they're just cavorting all around in the
street who's trying to get at these
who's trying to get at these squirrels
I'm gonna try and get into the squirrel
I'm gonna go for one with the little
tippy cheek okay so I mean yeah I'm
gonna we're just dropping this do I have
to yeah no this is not a I'm getting it
I'm even tried to catch us yeah
it's impossible unless they're those
real chili can I use it you can't use it
get it yeah told them to like go into a
barrel or some surf on these goddamn
here this is like a rocky chicky chicken
chasing a girl 20 but let's just see if
I do any better I don't so you you pick
one you grab a squirrel and pick it up
yeah and it just on your palm oh it
looks at you and then puts the hand over
its chest and bounce
very impressed and I got I look at it I
can't talk to it because I can't speak
with a nose now and then I go like this
and then hold out my other hand like
cough up he looks at you bring cash and
he he puts this little paw just on the
tip of your finger yeah and then I I go
I go he's just oh okay
and then at this point I stick my finger
in his mouth and check his cheeks
storing some goodness up in there it's
just he's just he tries to go with it he
tries to endure this probing to the best
of his ability but there's not a nut in
there well alright go ahead
I'm on strike I'm going for one with
chubby cheeks thinking the chubbiest
have chance just alright whatever looks
like it's going on dudu advantage - OH
10:10 Dex check oh no that's a real
show kid thanks go further I go for that
one with the chubby cheeks got away from
me yeah
I guess I should go on for the obvious
visual cue yeah I'll go for him right uh
aesthetics he's a slippery bastard no
it's Dex
well no no athletic Johanna I'm okay
listen I'm okay with this skill check
I'm saying tell to me describe for me
how your athletic prowess is going to
enable you to succeed in squirrel
oriented sports dinara is deceptively
quick cat-like very athletic
burlesque squirrel yet he's essentially
a giant squirrel for being via squirrel
yeah yeah you should use like persuasion
I try to convince them I'm a squirrel
yeah kind of push out my tail yeah I'd
be like I'm one of you and try to lure
them in I like that better that's very
good it's very good you knees advantage
persuasion check with advantage on the
squirrels I'm gonna try to convince them
I'm of them Thanks okay I love it you
are insane 21 pretty good that's your
persuasion plus
six on my persuasion wow you took it no
not that one not that one
all right well know that he is a
persuasion engine right yeah he's a
persuasion and intimidation it really
hikes is a christmas i exactly life so
yeah so am so you so so you have so you
kneel down your tail rises up you sort
of gesture at it like one of these all
right I got one of these to think about
it for a second right there's a couple
squirrels will hop over to you because
people who kneel down historically have
had nuts for them yeah you want you want
to take one just take a look at these
jokers I'm gonna assess them yes what
any of them obviously holding nuts
holding any whoa
any y'all holdin any scores down a party
party
I want my line up you can see I'll uh
I mean I'll try to barter with them Oh
oh my god Oh satchel agreen bringing
yeah I've had that green green yeah it
was Chekhov's green got that early on
it's been sitting on the mantel yeah
exactly
the payoff yeah finally got you sprayed
it to a squirrel for a night oh no no
dude this is true this is truly the
final medium of humans through yeah
right here we have discovered it tonight
hey yeah absolutely so you there's
definitely some of this out yeah
obviously there's a bunch of these
freeloaders right yeah but you
said a wall along play no no you got to
pay to get in here friends yes build a
velvet rope
yeah so so you you establish a decent
sort of you know grain Lapua Reno there
right there there they're coming over
there grabbing product there they're
stuffing it in and you can see one
that's already got a little chub in that
cheek zone and he's coming trying to
fill up
this green I'm gonna snatch his ass up
quick I'd see it no no what do you
thinks this is I have a real snatch him
DUP - yeah alright well this one I'll go
no outside food no outside food yeah you
gotta take it take it
yeah he's just he's just what just grab
him you know and then just and I hold
him like this and they just squeeze a
little moist
is it an apron yeah yeah yeah my mouth
okay Sophie Nast slimy wet ACORN but
ready to roll yeah your acorns awesome
on the green pile cool
there you go paid your way there bud
yeah you squirrel
yeah I'm in my mind I've just I you know
in the in the manner of those you know
those trash pickup Spears
I've just stabbed through through a pile
of dead squirrels around you just it's
not it's not working like they're a
little bit quick I can't make out the
you know the cheek situation so feel
like everything yeah okay I try one more
thing
maybe let me let me see if let me go see
if he's getting anything on his rod here
yeah yeah let me make it a let me give
that an attempt yeah yeah I mean it
could be you but you're actually like
legit trying to it tackle you do you
think my advantage
okay yeah yeah well we'll figure out the
other screens later but but yes yeah but
a missing your if you're trying to do
real attack this is this is ineffective
though I realize how absurd this is yeah
so I whispers I just titanate all
of them while I was considering that's
an tacular you know if you want to sift
[Laughter]
it's how but it's luck we got a more
secluded area I would have done I'm
going to I'm going to return the Gotti
to his serpent for me and won't have him
hunt I'm gonna instruct him you seek you
seek that that acorn sent and and get
more than one if you can just so we have
them yeah yeah what would kind of rule
would that be sure exactly so so
basically you take him you communicate
this to him and then basically you just
throw him into this squirrel ocean well
I was gonna say I'm like don't let me
throw it I'm not gonna throw it because
I'm I know that a snake object it's just
there's got scattered oh yeah I'm gonna
put him in the in the grass nearby he
can choose the path the talk did you set
him yeah let's just go set him down yeah
I don't need to do this part for him
yeah he's quite capable well he's P's a
big boy yeah and him if I'd you know
exam they are of course so micromanage
yes see so you sort of like you like go
into the alley looking out you could
pack sit down yeah walk out nonchalant
go go child nobody has to know
right and then immediately it's like a
sheepdog like he comes out and he's just
shaping this firm ass skittling you can
hear his you can hear his sort of
jeweled belly on the cobble as he's he's
going through it's just squeaking and
then let's see how many of these
he comes away with scoop
them up just a gentle hold he comes away
with one now should we see what kind of
nut it is no we should literally I made
a nut table this is like yeah but you
see that that plump I mean it's just
limp right you don't think it's dead but
you think that it has decided that it's
that not moving is the right play yeah
you'll squeeze five pine nuts those are
expensive
exactly right you sit around and spit
back out there so so ligarius last
attempt have scattered these squirrels
hither and yon you have an acorn and you
have gold you think that you could make
one porky can I get some perception
roles from you and from Rosie oh god
damn how you like a 20 I do like a 20
you look at 20 so you can see at the
base of a tree so the rest of these
Scrolls have been cut they've actually
it's sort of like filtered back out into
the natural world that you summoned them
from but you can see that a couple
squirrels slightly different coloration
hmm
have are engaged with one another
chattering at the base of this tree oh I
want to go I want to go run up on them
okay like instantly right so you see you
can see one of them from his mouth
produce an acorn and you can see another
one produce five almonds and they make
the exchange very quickly and then huh
start to hop away I know right now I
know we are trading I go we need other
nuts oh do you want to go after the one
with a corn and I'll go after the one
that has the yeah almonds it's like a
it's like a it's like a County Fair yeah
I love it
there's a lot of pigs a lot of grease
okay I want to try and grab that one
with the the nut just yeah what I just
try to grab it I'm going to use my
anyway your skills you an advantage
give it a skill that would give you a
better a good Plus slide it here it
wouldn't be hard
I think sleight of hand is probably a
pretty good force Brooke for
squirrel-cage AG you have a bag that's
slightly like the same size as an acorn
ya have a lot of dirt and it's roughly
the same are we right outside like we
didn't go that far right yeah I just
want to kind of go back in and give a
little heads up to it be like okay so
comes back in that room yeah that's very
good so you're able to you're able to
catch just the end of his tail yes
it's just be just like the whole front
of its like this trying to get that
purchased and he just got it like this
oh that's a fair question
no oh my god it's like a wringing out a
towel I know I take the nut and then I
he's just like no I know but then I give
him three of my good berries I'll put my
his misery lose like what is it 95% of
the nuts that they bury oh yeah like
they don't know right so anyway I give
him the good berries and then I'm like
Ted on your way no you got my not nice
got your nuts
Rosie is chasing after the one with the
almonds because she figures even if we
can't get a make or maybe we can trade
with these almonds mm-hmm and I'm going
to do i as I'm running sebastian pops
his head oh yeah yeah and he whispers
intimidation and I think yeah you got
this one and then I run in front of this
squirrel I cut him off and I squat and I
say Google's nothing I'm gonna do this
with advantage oh that's pretty good
don't need it
no I didn't okay so that's a 23 okay and
also if he wants to out an acorn
cuz he's so scared yeah well that's what
I do know it's a good like a pistol yeah
yeah exotic I know
pop noise yeah it's a spice weasel so no
so you get him and you shake down this
squirrel yeah four five almonds yeah and
then I'm gonna go to get okay we got a
business change the squirrel exchange
here can I get a perception check it's
not great it's a four okay I perceive
nothing did a auspicious do any squirrel
checks to get her nut no no she's she's
watching the door yeah verify that okay
I have my five little elements and I'm
waiting for a squirrel oh you're right
maybe maybe bend down bend over like
you're gonna give it to them I bend over
and I do like a little bow I'm looking
at you what do I do is it like this the
happy squirrel
I saw the squirrel bow to you I'm like
squirrel bowing nuts
I'm just looking around are there any
squirrels near me no and honestly you
think it's a little odd before the
before the summons before the forest
friends yeah it's sort of in that period
between the seasons where many creatures
like that are already are just waking up
[Music]
I'd knock on the tree okay wake up good
nuts
if these almonds gonna need an acorn
wake up wake up wake up wake up
do any of them wake up the ocean in the
trees then I get we can I get some
perception from you
Dragonborn narcissist janar Blitzen I'm
perceptive is she sorry moe no no really
nein
you could several name is zero table oh
boy
make me see whatever you're the
perceptive one I can't be great at
everything
okay so we're a we got two of them
you're looking good yeah I'm fine have
yeah I got my nut it's like this side
over here
I got mean that so come back to LA okay
okay well what should we do we need nut
for the first time I feel like an idiot
surrounded by dead yes there's gotta be
a better way to do this this is the
general store open sitting on so much
gold she has to own that horse
I was like burned locate object I can
look is there disturbed ground could I
do like a survival check to look for a
disturb you can you can only newly
buried you can do all princess yeah just
we just go the grocery store has an 18
here's an 18 it's an 18 is an 11 plus 7
or my survival I sure so you are you are
down looking for you know for lack of a
better term squirrel sign mm-hmm
and you can see you can see what you
think might have been caches mm-hm
but they're freshly dug like they're
they're dug up I've done your hand
through the soft soil and you might find
a cab but you don't find any true nuts
and in fact you think that the traffic
is such in town and through these areas
it's dense as it was over around the
side of the droning courtier and you
think that you might be able to follow
this oh okay you might actually be able
to follow this path it's it's
substantially Trung yeah okay so I look
at Algy you guys I go I go I think they
went this this way I think this is the
way that they go follow me to the nut
trading place huh nice I got my almonds
I'm coming up yeah I see if I ever think
that they might like well you got those
five pine nuts immediately I was before
I knew more grain nice oats around so we
follow yes exactly
so you are you're following it and it is
a circuitous it's like the it's like the
sort of
sometimes I wiggle my foot when I'm
talking I was hoping that was the puppy
know so in it's almost like it doesn't
it's like spycraft or something okay
where it's like this is this is like the
path that's sort of like circuitous
tortured path you would try to enunciate
if you were trying to hide and you
thought that you were really smart and
you were a squirrel sure it's like
straight little loop yes straight it's
like around the tree and then keeps
going the same way yes so you can so you
can follow this path and then this is
sort of in a cop's sort of past the
Northeast so as we know the drunk
warrior dnc sort of around that central
circle of red larch living it's sort of
down in the southeast portion of it so
cops just on the outside of town to the
northeast very near to the lighthouse
okay that Rosie founded to take care of
fall apples but out in this but you can
see that there is a not a full clearing
but definitely the impression that you
would get was that these trees were
paying a tree homage mmm in the center
of this path what you think you think
that it be you think that it's not
something you would recognize if you
weren't a druid I think like you you
might notice that it was sort of a
separate thing but the idea that it
exists in a continuum with all these are
living things that's it that's a walnut
observation what kind of tree is it that
particular tree is an oak tree but yeah
our problems may be solved should
anything still be on it because we all
know oak trees make acorns learn that
from a puzzle room is just getting into
it
so one that goes ah ha this one this it
is a certain type of tree name I will
not speak but it will lead us into that
other guy who I hate my walls do we see
any are there any other ending that's
not a one but what you do notice is that
high up perhaps 20 feet up no visible
branches around that tear of the tree
you think that you can see an entrance
into a tree into a tree squirrels nice
interesting no it's not human sight
that's too much now at that precise
moment I will pause the universe so that
we can do our commercial break thank you
so much for coming back and hanging out
with us here at the C team we will be
back momentarily after we go to the
bathroom we return now to episode 2 of
testy teams entitled plans within plans
wow I like it
yes master
[Laughter]
nothing when last we saw our heroes
nothing honey
they were at the base of a oak tree
completely stripped of its tender fruits
and there was a an aperture high up in
this tree that was noticed just before
we left for commercial break now I'm not
saying that it's an important whole you
know alright yeah yeah I'm just saying
there's a whole like I don't know what
he's right we should just go home
let's go back to that why not a long
rest why not one rather
I'm the closest one to be in squirrel
sized say well we got a legate and we
got a bluesy sense John and that's a
bastion and I can you know I believe
that's true look I in Louisiana the best
races it's true and but I mean a
squirrel would be afraid of legalities
certainly but would they be afraid of a
weasel only one way to find out well
wild shape is this shape I mean it's a
cool it's a cool shape yeah okay I hear
you have to be a weasel
it's worth a try that's why yeah I don't
know let's try it Oh weasels are really
good squirrels yeah being sighs you're
not wrong as their natural enemy
they're only natural enemy no it's fine
no easily diseased weasel like you have
squirrel and weasels basically Satan
well then maybe I'll drop all is not
yeah all right so I'm in a wild shape
into a weasel the illusion imagine it
[Music]
noise it makes
and then I want a Swizzle up the side of
the tree just look how do you want to
come with me for muscle well I was gonna
say it's like you go first right okay
and then it's like I'm one of you but
like my skews like your scary friend is
but I got him don't worry is Beck here
but if things go south then I just will
coil and we're just like roto root an
entire tree out and just get all the
goods no it's good it's good for you to
go because if things go south - you can
tell us and then we can chop the tree
numbers yeah you're pretty soon fire
well it's a very good trick I can't do
it but you guys can hear me I can right
so tell me more about what the sweetest
of wheezy is doing supposin up the side
of the tree and going to the entrance
and taking a keen smell which is a
perception check that I have an
advantage on when I thank God for you so
plus seven six plus seven thirteen the
number yeah yeah yeah well it doesn't it
doesn't require a supernatural sense of
smell you know to pick up like twenty
squirrels Oh any nuts it's just it's
just that waxy you know squirrel Musk
all right it's like in your in your
Wiesel Ian form and the weasel part of
your mind that you're on constantly sort
of trying to apply pressure to it you
know it's good eating
mmm you know I mean this is you you wait
all your life for something like this
that's like clumpy squirrel man I'm
slowest I try I really try that's it but
I want to take a peek in see if I see
any nuts in there you do you see a nut
or two you also see many squirrels and
it's just that that shift from daylight
into the darkness of the of the room
there's a lot of fine details you can't
pick out but it is not hard at all to
detect it doesn't require a roll I want
to emphasize this no roll is required to
detect the two razor-sharp dinner Forks
not pointed directly at your snout
[Laughter]
dinner Forks but this isn't sound like
no nobody no no but they've been Motta
they've got some aftermarket mods can I
talk grouse have been on reddit I mean
they have figured out some terminal
and squirrel they got a same language
right I think so
the language of squeaks right ravenson
mustelids they can talk to you sir
mollusks well no it's probably likes
it's probably like some of the some of
the old English dialects where they're
basically different languages but you
can still understand each other
I'm coiling my way up the tree not as
fast as you that sounds good
right there's a but you he there's a
voice sort of in the back of the chamber
hmm this emits a sort of a mourn'd low
chuckle and he says letter yeah all
right I'll walk in
so as you yes you pad in put those those
clogged fingers up on top pull yourself
in there are now more Forks even more
dinner Forks aside
just just right at every part of you
that would be the least able to resist a
fork mmm these are like brushing just
brushing along this side as you're
moving I they mounted inside the tree or
they being wheeled over here being
wielded by squirrels and it's a squirrel
guard in the back in the back of this
sort of enclosed shootout space what
Booker I'm in just having a good time
missing this sometimes I see the Chris
face and I don't know what it portends
so you can see that in the back imagine
like a like a clay pot okay there's sort
of been warmed up but the the front of
it has been broken away and then seated
atop a pile of warm dry leaves you can
see an ancient squirrel a truly ancient
squirrel hmm and you can tell and he's
wearing the cap of an acorn at jaunty
beret and then there's three squirrels
on each side of him and they're each
adorned in a different type of nutshell
hmm this is the greatest moment of my
life
Wow yeah
they have a bartering system yeah and so
they are looking at you and they are
very curious as well to it and the voice
of the voice from the from the Acorn
throne says speak your piece I need a
two acre that's four to go for fifty
three get one for safety I need two
eight ones okay that's not gonna fly
you're gonna need to do the voice the
whole time this is straight wonderful
thank you love it yep
yeah that's it yes I this is
role-playing yeah hey this is roll I
just like it - he he throws his head
back and just like the of his
laughs just comes bouncing off every
angle inside this is it uh is it
nighttime inside this enclosure outside
no okay
there's there's a light shining in from
outside and so he's just like looking at
the other nut princes and it's like
whenever his gaze reaches them then they
have the appropriate response oh yeah
but a suit but he's looking over here at
these winds it's like these guys like
okay all right hahahaha
Gordon I want to I do it mentally but I
judges say and I want you to imagine now
I'm the DM I've done this the branch the
branch that leads up to the to the
entrance
there's no branch oh how do you yeah
okay then I'll just go right there I the
the head of ligado comes up from the
that the base of that opening and I say
to you oh they like shot things I know
I'd like shot things too so and this
mouth is ready - OH -
for sure and so I take a quick glance
back and I see the look obvious there
and I say again I'm like I need a two
acorns or I'm a turn you inside out so
good threats there yeah yeah exactly
with right away I brought my demons you
don't bring your demon snake to a party
for nothing like anything yet it's just
here and occupying the entirety of the
entrance yeah yeah yeah he he sniffs the
air a couple times he says you don't
think I can smell the Enclave stink on
you hard are like every other natural
creature cast aside promised your
protection while forces annihilated the
entire world and now that we have come
up with a system that allows the five
nut houses to prosper you're going to
come in to my throne room and steal our
wealth the mouth on the gaudy he's dead
he he he steps up and he walks over to
you supporting himself on a spoon he
takes a few steps over to you he says
try to grow to your real size in here
see what would happen
that's that's okay you can go you can
leave now
dinner Forks glint in the sunlight
[Music]
multiplying the guy's numers ah yeah
this is ten thousand for bingo chop that
a tree is a party line opener now you
can be yeah I'll open it I'll be like
what's the play
I respect what they built
they're just squirrels with better
society's grand scheme of things killed
a lot today looks a lot of dead
squirrels in our wake just getting to
this tree you know I think you need to
take one chop at this tree hmm I think
you need to take it down and just scare
them just scare him I want you to put I
want you to put the fear of you in them
all right dad I can do I haven't met a
squirrel I can't scare I just look at
the guy you get out tooth brother
toothbrush but I won't with a spiky side
yeah I was thinking like if I had to one
strike I would smite this but I won't
I'll just give it a good just to shake
the out of it I love it so you feel
do you feel the the impact of what you
are certain is toothbrush I'm wielded by
a dangerous and a deeply unsocialized
young man its shakes and he is able he
catches himself on his spoon and he just
shakes his head and they all scamper
behind the throne picking up nuts as
they go
and then you can see one by one they
certainly go down into a set of tunnels
that are inside the tree we're only
asking for ten acorns it's just what's
ten to him so I look at the can I go um
I go what's it gonna take for me to walk
out of here with two acres I tell them
about my almond I say we got 500 and
some green and some gray and then we'll
chop the tree down so so you're sort of
looking and you can see that him and his
entourage yeah have cast down this thing
at the mention of almonds hmm you hear a
sound coming back up so when he emerges
you can tell he has something like a
pontiff's cap but it is all of brilliant
bleached nut shells mm-hmm and he says
he says I cannot I cannot betray my
father completely but I am NOT unwise he
says I have nuts nuts I'm willing to
share but there is a task I would have
you do what do you want he says there is
a place we squirrels call the black
Valley mm-hmm and in this valley there
are treasures beyond counting mm-hmm but
it is guarded by a mighty beast a beast
we tell our our kids of mm-hmm sit what
what kind of Beast
well he doesn't talk about it I mean he
he a shudder goes through his body and
he says a beast that could do this and
he turns his cloak falls and you see
three claws right down the back and a
raking angle and he taps his Fork a
couple times on the floor and says I was
not without valor but this creature is
impossible to defeat I can't see that
he's just bring me the beasts head no
but I can't get you any treasure from
inside there that you want and he says
all right let's see if you can do as I
ask
hmm he says I would like peas done peas
on earth peas in a cat's head we got it
we could do it no worries the peel of a
potato done carrot and that's that he's
just now he's heat now he's reaching
sounds like there's a kind of soup made
from berries I would like you to bring
me that soup juice yes okay and I'll be
and that's it there's a thick sauce so
rich I can I can only carry so much
grandfather had it you said it was
delicious
okay do this in one trip that's great it
must end more thing you can do it
do not go back to okay I'm gonna go get
the stuff you stay here I'll be right
back and I back out and see if he's
listing anything else so you see me as
soon as you're leaving out he's bounded
back down okay great perfect
so I wheeze outside Sealy Gaddy make our
way down and then I just look up at
Rosie and dinar put my little we don't
have it here I list everything out right
yeah
peas potato peel hey I translate for you
because you're still in was a farm burn
just put them in there yeah the bowl of
soup symbol a sauce that's it I care how
are we always doing quest for animals
why are we getting bossed around by
animals counter-plan
I just go crazy in murder office guys
wow they're squirrels
there's no reason I'm looking right at
you there's a principle involved a
certain point you don't have to do this
just they can't understand yeah that's
true we can just talk right in front of
them what about them mystery squirrel
what if we take an acorn dip it in gold
we all put one little finger on it and
then we're there
do we really need for acorns a quarter
of me to end up there I don't know how
it works well that's true we don't have
an acorn is spared well everybody else
all right let's go to the store yeah now
we got to go on a quest because the
rabbit's took all the carrots no I know
how this works I think we come back with
onix's head instead this was easier
[Laughter]
bring it up I mean that's something you
get a winch
well back across the street you're on
Accord rummage through the garbage heaps
yeah we do you know what they like all
right so we do that will you that thing
then we went in and then we bring it all
back and we put it in a tiny little
backpack and put on sweet wheezy
yeah real slow climb a tree weighted
down by all this stuff Jerry's looking
at you like maybe we didn't get the
stuff we didn't get the stuff do we know
not hard okay okay
no no your place shame oh no Jimmy
was the best game of all time I'll tell
you why and then we'll keep playing to
Israel so Shenmue is the best game of
all time because there's a point where
you need to go into a dark place and you
have a flashlight but the flashlight is
out of battery it's like this is a
regular problem and then you literally
go to like the corner store and buy
batteries yeah and then you put the
batteries in there and then you can go
downstairs like it's not even a
joke and it's like it's also like God
when is the bus gonna get here and
there's like a bus schedule yeah
and then you need to get money and you
go into your forklift job it's like dude
it kicks ass and you get fender the long
chop it's awesome so that is exactly
right so you come back now do you do you
do you overdo it like do you get like
three scraps of potato or like yeah
I think I do oh yeah like it's such a
humble little ask and they're just
squirrels that's fine I just bring the
garbage can yeah just like you can have
any of it here so how are you gonna how
are you gonna prepare all this like um
what does it look like I think probably
it's it is like a little sack that's
packed with extras of everything and I
add some stuff in there that I think
they might like that maybe they haven't
tried before we got some like kale it's
wilted its kind of gnarly but they're
squirrels yeah we've got some almonds
just some almonds in there yeah yeah
some mom some cheese iced I stick a
little wedge of cheese in there and you
guys are all judging me I'm like this
shut up all right
nicer than the yarn us thank you
I'm delighted like I'm not
I mean I'm mad that this is taking so
long but I'm also so excited to spend
time in the presence of such small minds
where this is a huge ask the challenge
your brain isn't even large enough to
imagine the thing that we can't bring
you know I like that Carthoris is just
feeling superior to a squirrel
well like let's see what they do with
this look at all these treats and it's
impeccably packed up and tied Oh
and then I you're still busy right so I
will tie little ropes to your arms so it
is a little backpack and and it's it's
got a little tied top and it's it's
sealed with love dude we've done it so
we've created the ultimate Dungeons &amp;
Dragons campaign I like to think it took
like six hours cuz it's like perfect I'm
like miniaturized version no no you got
like a little eye glass yeah there's
tiny food YouTube videos I am real life
obsessed yet those so that is what's
going on in my head that's like Johnny
burrito you're working your ass off it's
it's nighttime nice all right I'm so I
took a rest yeah so you you get some
rest okay
basically you get some rest your you
have made the ultimate rodent care
package you've attached it to another
creature yeah
no it's it's time to time to make a
delivery yeah yeah sorry so as you are
nearing that's it the throne room you
can see you can see servants Oh ready of
the almond Prince even even out here and
they are ready to accept these offerings
outside of the court fantastic alright
so take off a little backpack tonight
hold it up to them have one weasel
figure yeah one little weasel hand on it
so one of them one of them accepts the
bag mm-hmm sniffs it sniffs in Rosie's
anxious it's like watching to see how
they just like you can see just like
right around the moistening yeah I know
they're honourable so I'd like I know so
he he looks over to his associate and
nods and he gives you an acorn say this
was for two acorns this is not this is
not a what we said this is that other
deal that we hate one acorn there's five
almonds that's the law I appreciate that
you gave me this but I can't just give
you an acorn ruin the economy not
there's five elements in there listed
off all the stuff you got yeah this is
the problem with fiat currency yeah yeah
yes no no he needs the blotchy yeah well
we use it let me tell you why it's great
we have nothing you wouldn't want to
unsend yeah that's like it spreads
out flat hmm and they see all these nuts
and cheeses and soaped reeking potato
peels yeah and it's all just in a slurry
in the base of this thing warmed by its
close proximity to a weasel oh he's a
warmth exactly he he takes the Acorn a
second acorn out and then just places it
on the ground and then he kneels down in
a worshipful way yes - no it's just like
scooching things around on this rap
with their noses the other one is just
watching it and he's just like needing
his tail with delight and desire I
turned back into a human
immediately oh my god wrap it up quick
yeah they wrap it up that this up
in the science they're just like yeah
yeah yeah before you change your mind
you exactly miss running away and
there's like peas and garbanzo one
behind me so I have these two nuts I
hand wonder Rosie and hand one to get
the rest and then I go what are we doing
just absent-minded weird sure we have to
go find our friends on the test market
oh yeah I have as we'd go back to the
joinin courtier to put gold on these I I
have so many questions for you about the
nut princess I'm I'm I am inquiring so
many I'm like what kind of nuts were
they a weakening oh I don't know they
were insane there were a bunch of
nutjobs yeah well the good news is is
that because I'm in this form and have
my bag with me we can apply the gold to
them before we even go inside I love
gold I have all manners of banks let me
show you those my inks real gold yeah
the cat's just caps need to be gold so
I've got turquoise crannies in okay
silver this is gonna go on forever yeah
they're gonna end with are these all
melted tourmaline and then I take the
gold one and unscrew it I take mine
carefully dip the catalyst and ice and
then I see it was like a gold leaf yeah
thank you ever seen that
oh yeah oh yeah have you ever seen yeah
those videos mm-hmm dip your nut I dip
my nut to bag it right in there no yeah
so I also like the same yes I also do
the thing I do it as well
with great pleasure a double dip and
make sure good base come down yep
nothing to say about that yeah do you
have your tools yeah uh we did this
outside we did the second we walk to the
door yes should we yell in there and
give everyone a heads up oh we're about
to do well they're not gonna know no
they'll just watch us go well the
Prophet knows we'd still profit I'll
watch my room watch okay it's on at
first
watch that stair yes doing that yeah
switches got our eye oh yeah oh yeah
when I suspected profit and you've
you've seen the relationship since
you've been back profit has a profit
keeps a pretty firm eye on auspicious
all right by going test market I can't
believe we're volunteering primarily
going back to the test market no one
wants to do it less than me I just it
all sudden hits me I'm like why are we
doing this all right this is the MINIX
we saw ahead we cheated basically I mean
we're going back we know the exam that's
true answers so then it's true okay
let's do this I said I go through first
all right so hand me your as you're
walking through individually you're
experiencing that same cold sensation
and as you are walking through walnut
auspicious at you in that moment it says
oh no oh geez
and so as you pop in you are present in
an inn called the drawn-in courtier and
all the patrons of this bar are drawn in
quarters and like ends little bunch of
little ends I love it yeah they are
drinking drawn and courtiers from
smaller drawn in quarters it's great oh
boy somebody replace all the texture
files yeah yeah exactly it's like it's
like when there's an error on a window
and you're like trying to move it around
it's just more and more everywhere
so some of it yeah exactly
so then the drowning careers look over
at you there's their beams and glass
sort of creaking and they raise their
drawing courtiers to you as you come in
do we look like ourselves yes as much as
much as that might delight one no no in
fact and what's what's different here is
that this drawn and quartier
historically looking at the window you
wouldn't see much right the previous
adventure this this drawing courier
appears to exist in a place you look out
the window and see and as near as you
can tell infinite
not necessarily defined plane of colors
hmm interesting
okay well in that in that sort of
formless expanse you can see various
shapes just sort of moving of their own
accord but there's no there's no up or
down their their motions exist according
to some physical understanding that you
are not familiar with okay I'm at that
window well I care about these ins
I'm gonna go sidle up to an inn they
greeted us which one
but looked like they were into me about
the in the in the in behind the bar says
what would be this is a drama courtier
it's all frothy Jonica so he grits he
because he was just sort of absent
mindedly cleaning a drawing courier
behind the bar and so he he goes back to
our drawing courtier and pulls out a
thick thick glass of drawn courtier and
sets it on the drunk warrior Cheers
yeah yeah he is a his shutters sort of
flap with delight yeah you seen anyone
else come through here he's like you
know we don't get a lot of visitors yeah
rains it pours
yeah right tell me man classic classic
and then roofs keep out rain anyway Wow
building yeah I own new whores floors
are clean a room square footage I'm
lovin your buildings inside a building
is weird to them open-concept yeah huh
all right so yeah so wait did you go
yeah yeah she's just out a dad running
courier and they looked mm-hmm let's go
yeah yeah let me to finish your drying
courier well obviously it's rude not to
right yeah it's like it's like you can't
drink you can't bring it with you like
yeah I try to drink it liquid it drawn
in quarters
everyone would be like water molecules
are just little inside it's like I don't
know I mean it's like it's like drinking
a hamburger hey hey I love this it's
like think about drinking such a solid
thing yeah but it takes work
but it's not as bad as you would expect
like a duck can taste a Johnny -
standing there gonna be like when do you
like die like I want to make sure this
seems like the kind of thing could this
would be like oh is this how alcohol
works in this realm I so I do ask before
we go yes it's the drunk or deer yeah I
I say what how do you differentiate this
is it cannibalism why are you not
offended that this how what you're the
same object that he's now ingesting oh
boy I think they are you're the same
object as him yeah yeah but I don't eat
him when he dies I will eat him oh it's
true we talked about God oh yeah I miss
our friendship pact is it he says you
know what I think you need tricorder
make it a double make it a duplex very
he sets him up pushes him over and I am
going to use my cauldron ability because
they've filled up super fast that was
busy hooking everybody up with all this
crazy squirrel but whenever the bar
fills up I get to do something cool and
I have a table that I can do it from so
out of combat table is different from
the in combat table and so in this in
this case you can see the facade of the
drawing Cordier behind the bar taking on
a slightly different shape he's like so
was that guy a friend of yours
oh yeah best friend really yeah okay
what do you you probably want to meet up
with him fast and yes so kind of a rough
neighborhood I agree he's like well you
know I got a dude up a dinghy out back
that's what your let's yes what's it
look like go look at it
all right looks like a dinghy you want
to take a a guess and what it looks
I wanna see the ocean yeah sure the
water I say thank you thank you for your
kindness though still mentioned it bring
it back when you can
happy to what a nice turn corner yeah
right exactly is this the trunk or
nearest fan
what do you see this is the nice one
yeah yeah this is the grandad run
accordion obviously you know you pay a
little bit more but yeah so you leave
out the front door and then the ground
itself appears to just be they imagined
that you would sort of measure that a
child had drawn a chalk line around the
drawing courtier and then it has been
placed somewhere and that's what it is
except that the space around that land
exists again in this undifferentiated
silverish expanse that goes out and then
you know much you know much like you
would have a dock or something of that
nature like an ocean side you know like
on lakefront property there is a dock
literally suspended in the air
projecting out from this you know piece
of unmoored real estate and next to it
there is a tiny boat it looks for all
intents and purposes like a tiny boat
except that it appears to be okay doing
what it's doing which is to say being
oriented in space hmm okay all right
it's comforting I mean like I say when
you look out and you see the strange
shapes that move in this infinite place
it's like it's like that episode of near
the end of the finale of Star Trek where
it's like typically speaking in Star
Trek
everybody just fights in a naval way
yeah but then sometimes looks like
what's like well that's how it should
always be right yeah and it's just like
that when you look out there there's no
rules just right it's like the Outback
Steakhouse yeah it's like a conceptual
Outback Steakhouse
what did you say so that is the Olive
Garden yeah Kate sorry Jerry
and at this to this is an infinite press
next Howdy's cool treats I get it
actually I'm a Dungeons and Dragons game
designer now and that is the Outback
steak and boats and boats can be
lycanthropes oh no no we're bow we're
boat don't be the first no no so he told
so but you feel very strange
Rosie looking at this boat attached in
this place okay I would love it if he
would give me a history check I would
love to take advantage on that history
check oh I would love to give you
advantage or a rate thanks Council
shadow council damn that's nice
twenty-one cheese so as you as you walk
closer to it but you you are getting
what you know would commonly be called
the feels sir good there just feels okay
there emanating from this craft
interesting and there's a friend for a
second you can see yourself young and
you can see your hand on this tiller and
then you can see your father in the boat
with you and he says a boat is a boat is
a boat dad did used to say that a lot
yeah okay do i does though does the
image show for anybody else doesn't no
no no no this is just this is just
something that you see here and does it
persist as I get close oh it just
flashes no no you just you just know
that it happened okay you know that it
happened okay I think I know how to
drive this boat and I don't know how to
explain to you how but I think if we get
in we'll get to where we need to be
don't I come it's me it's great looking
you out yeah you seem to know your way
around boat yeah alright you're okay
yeah everybody's gonna have to make some
space
get cozy folks all right I want to like
wow while we board I want to grab my my
and just see if I get any like I want to
understand the nature of this space its
plan is it anything that resembles that
you know contorted you know extra
dimensional space that I've been in
before imagine the sense that you get is
that they're like familial that this
these spaces are related yeah you think
that you think that when you were in the
test market it's possible that you are
seeing it in a transition state where it
achieved a kind of maximum chaos but
then that had to subside at some point
it can't always be a place where every
thought and word becomes constituted hmm
so this is either a new place altogether
or just a decrepit version of the other
space okay delicious I'm on board but as
soon as soon as you as as you have as
you take it out and you're just
meditating on it's you know impermeable
truths it's almost like the way young
people for example imagine if a Ouija
board were real that kind of tug where
it's almost just the level of instinct
it exists like you've ever had a
gyroscope and tried to twist the poles
it's like that
like there is a place in an orientation
around that it wants to be is this
within the confines of the boat no no no
it's in the confines of this place okay
being a tug already yeah it's like what
he's 560 I mean yeah yeah I'm man no I
know my dress tides the 380 middle aged
I don't know if that means we should go
toward that or do not go to it you
what you feel is best maybe we come back
maybe not we got a job maybe I jump off
the boat soon who knows dinars there
really is a theory it really isn't a
place for a dinar in here yeah no no
you're trying to figure out her husband
yeah where is the Norwood go inside this
space yeah it's probably enough for
Justin are ya
we're not that big though we could just
Senate sit on the back ER oh you guys
could just swing behind you could sit in
it yeah just hold on yeah it's pile up
one one elf on one knee the other elf on
the other knee you can turn yourself
into smaller animals you get smaller
that was my small one did that I already
did that quick Ned got us here quick nap
yeah you crocodile it up no no only got
big stuff sorry remember I took all
those big things and I was like oops new
small thing yeah yeah the trial app
scenario we're gonna have to file up
yeah I will
well not not I'll do the shoulders not
the lab okay never the lab I will never
sit on denars laughs hold you like I'll
do like a baby fine except that I don't
accept being held like a baby she's like
it's curled into a ball and first it's
like she doesn't want to be on her back
so he's trying to maintain like on her
side the whole time like she has any
it's like a side plank yeah she's
working her core her core is engaged my
girl absolutely whatever space there
though yeah
okay so yes sir yes oh yeah and rest
your hand on the tiller yeah is is it
indeed pulling me toward this sense that
good threats have well no as soon
whenever he whenever you have it I mean
it feels like you're placing it in the
right place it's like you have the right
shake yeah and then and then as he's
holding it out you guide the boat in
that direction I just used to throw the
tiller and you just want to go there
nice okay you remember it's like riding
a boat yeah right do you remember you
remember that it's just about wanting to
okay right and so I'm remembering an
ability to drive this boat that's right
I don't actually have that's right okay
um that is correct so don't be confused
that's like literally what happened nice
you perceived it correctly so but this
the air itself is pulling the boat in
this direction
after you've guided it away from the
dock this thing is pulling you at
greater and greater speeds until it
erupts into something like two
shimmering black sails your third does
to her does alright and then it sort of
it like beats so it isn't like a classic
sail it's not catching something
it's just beating and you can feel the
you can feel it pulling it I mean it's
just it's so difficult to tell what the
speed is when you don't have these
reference points yeah and the reference
points you do have are at odd angles we
feel acceleration okay you are getting
to hold yeah yeah and so the only way
that you can know eventually how fast
you must have authentically been going
is that there is a point in the distance
that is dark in this otherwise sort of
like silver edged place and it is
getting closer and
closer and closer to the boat until it
consumes almost the whole of your vision
and this is a place that you have been
before this is the very Cathedral of the
earth you have been there as well
Walnut during the battle with the
lighthouse creature and the boat is
pulling itself up to the bottom as
through this aperture in the base of
this entity that you have a complex
relationship with to say the least
you know I'm well there's no place to
kneel I crouch down on you and I'm and
I'm and I'm looking up expectantly I'm
trying to show that deference I'm trying
to soak in as much as I can of this is
this now is this the red tinged that
shape yes or is it the one that I was
shown which was which was blackness
which I saw beyond sight yeah exactly no
this is this here is a is that
crystalline palace where it all occurred
to you sorry the way that you perceive
it is slightly different from the way
that everyone else perceives it but you
know exactly what it is and you know
exactly way it is two of you have never
seen this before
so let me give you the extra details
that you might need imagine a kind of
octagon made of sheer amethyst whose
walls rise a tremendous distance toward
a kind of crown sharp blades and then
the both that you are captaining has
gone underneath it and then you you are
able to maintain a kind of plane and so
the cool when you get underneath it you
can see that it's kind of like tilting
and maybe even listing
in this space actively or is it dr.
can't that let's you would note I think
you wouldn't know it appears is not
stationary ah okay and and this is
floating an avoid that seems boundless
yeah it could appears to be boundless
okay I'm gonna whisper down to wallet I
think my Leakey crucial we free next wow
that's a lot that's a lot that just came
out of that mouth uh I look at I look at
this and I go isn't it your turn I don't
know what it I don't know what your God
is named I don't either
but she says a lot of things sometimes I
will so I will reach out and see if I
can know I'm shuttin up into the like
you enter into the yeah the body of this
thing yeah well yeah as I as I as I'm
meditating I'm trying to see whether or
not the ER will communicate with me
directly as it once did
yeah absolutely so you you present
yourself in the cathedral that is this
entities body and last time it was full
of rejoinders and crafty language dark
speech and this time there's nothing
like that your steps echo on these hard
walls and there is a chamber an
additional chamber that you did not see
when you were here before and as you
approach it you can see plain as day a
symbol that you know with your eyes of
the rune keeper the symbol represents
the person of oaktree strike that is a
game for this week
Kate Welch yep yeah it has been an
absolute pleasure shadow council may our
labors please you we're gonna take
another quick break and then we're gonna
come back for Table Talk as we have done
so often in the past thank so much
hanging out we'll see
you