time is the enemy the pastor threatens
the fastest weapon you wouldn't make it
past a second and as the question
play it brash and reckless to choose a
cautious solution you saw was prudent
enemy sepulcher poker - don't become the
putrid it's that well-fed I pursue in no
mountain too steep for dungeon too deep
to send expendable marks up to the top
of the peak of beneath they see Yugi
they come like sharks to it while I swim
in that line even like Carl Barks
through it so send your national parks
drew it I'll send him home in a natural
box with a close tie but most of the
parks included save your breath for a
cleric confessor death is a lesson and
life is attended professor but if you're
seeking my official advice sign on the
dotted line English of the choice what
do you think about Hunger Games
we're on over to later thanks thanks for
showing up cane Welch I did the whole
thing by myself this time all the HS
don't see see you have done well you
have pleased me and you will be rewarded
now
hello gain a level hello no no no no you
gain a level from Kate oh no it's a
zero-sum game it's 2018
listen I am Tycho Brahe of Penny Arcade
pax I am also a minute us Howard drun
CEO of acquisitions incorporated but
today I am Jerry Hawkins and I'm going
to run a game of Dungeons and Dragons
for my friends to my right Dragonborn
narcissists esperan Denard with Sam wait
for me I'm not doing any yours you're
not gonna do much either right so things
are things that started out well huh to
the right of my right repping the
natural world walnut dog grass right
that's it I'm nothing for you today go
cry easy you do it cuz you like it it's
awesome I set the mood to my left not
your grandma's crema
except for those rare cases in which
she is your grandma's grandma Rosie bee
stinger whoa here it goes
under control I got you like ready
player one my left emerging is though
from a mist shroud Chris drown together
just right there in that shroud now we
do when last we saw our heroes they had
recently any rate half of them had
recently emerged from an ancient elven
reverie
yeah yeah well I wasn't bad I mean it
was it was it was bad it was good for
some and worse for others what was
learned was a great deal of information
about the Enclave of whom walnut is
essentially the final member or so we
thought ho ho ho grove keeper in the
layin
having shape-shifted into a seed to last
lo these thousands of years the party
learned a lot about maybe not themselves
you know a little bit about themselves
as well what she did before that knew
exactly what she did before that was
kill cthe wrists drought and exactly and
then because she was asked nicely Sheba
grudgingly resurrected them by stuffing
their mouth with valuable gems mm-hmm
it's a new technique give it a try at
home it's the new stuff you guys had a
job chomp oh yeah basically their mouths
were transformed into EPA rock tumblers
no it worked out great and what what is
before us now is that cuz Trish brow
dinar Blitzen still lying on the ground
coughing coming to to their awareness
yes yes they're all on the same boat
yeah you three were in that boat alone
now that's a fun boat walnut done grass
and Rosie somewhat exhausted from their
efforts of illusory warfare still
standing over and grove keeper in the
land still trying to take all of this in
and then as she as she looks down at
cthe wrist robe and dinar Blitzen still
coming to she kicks to through strobe
within the hip hmm Wow
hard is dead again he's dead no no no no
just like why is this here the same way
that you would kick something that had
been left on the floor
do we all still look like it's just
gonna happen yes but she just doesn't
like this one yeah yeah she to tell for
whatever she oh she was not confused
about who people were I think you
suspect she's been at this sort of thing
a while and she says I did not endure
3,000 years in the Underdark
to speak to these men I am going to
arrest and I will return at a time of my
choosing and you see her reverse the
process
as they are still coming to you see her
reverse the process that results in her
becoming a seed I pick it up immediately
pocket road yeah fuck Mueller yes she
will she outranks me by at least a newly
a billion million billion million yeah
she ground Rep okay with the natural
world she did yeah I picked I pick up
the seat and I put it in my satchel
where ceases the tale isn't like he's
like like protecting oh absolutely
yeah I mean there's a the the seat
itself has sophisticated worls like the
name is zerah see yeah has sophisticated
tracks and channels in the shell of it
and seizes the tail can just find a
delicious little nook just to wrap
himself around it still talk he still
talk to it can you confirm with it every
now and again was talking to you and we
couldn't yeah right that's true I did
awaken my news she's kind of a speak
when spoken to
I'm just I was just curious yeah so you
you feel you feel a little worse for
wear like like a long night of drinking
you feel a little hungover essentially
but you're coming to now on the floor
like a long rest full no did I rest in
peace Oh anyone yes well I put some some
stats first when we come back with
Bonnie just a face yeah she is she has
brought you back with the correct amount
of hit points oh okay okay yeah I know
I'm gonna wake up from this hmm we don't
first no okay I really thought about it
so I've been kicked was I awake at that
point yeah just kind of like oh looks
like it just came halfway through it's
just another another interruption from
the material world yeah I am like that's
still it's very vague to me like I hear
that like I'll come back at a time of my
choosing
oh yeah you didn't turning into a seed
but as soon as I'm able to stand I I say
Miley
was it a god now how did I how did I
screw this up
how have I failed it no no no are we are
you dead are we all did
no we're not we're not dead sorry I did
everything right I thought I was no I
didn't have enough information you did
do something right that was a member of
my order I thought I was a member of my
order of which there was only me but
only and then I'm noticing janar on the
floor but only struck us the two of us
not you I'm good there's a matriarchal
society so what those can be like cig no
surprises like that's actually like yeah
say no more I got it it's a bit more
rigid than mine apparently like I was
never heard all right
not yet no we're not we're still down
here yeah they're just not as efficient
so she was not a god she was I know
anger no no no did he know we never eyes
on the whole time yeah inappropriate
hand gestures she popped out how do
takes a new book out find it how do I
make sure that doesn't happen again
before you need to interact with this
seed oh I tried to make it clear to her
that you two were important enough to
live and so here you are and she's kind
isn't she yeah just um you're gonna need
to be important enough to live that's
the number one thing to write down I
promise him cannot make the thing
that'll never make it
all right that you tell me if I seem
like I'm going down the right of the
wrong path as far as that's concerned
you may have a better grounding in in
all things seed oh well I mean there's
only so much he can do she really you
know could see our true selves and your
true self is timeless enemy for her
people
I mean maybe genetically but it's surely
this this iteration is wrong take time
to know me feel like I'm apologizing for
a racist grandmother plain white I say
if need be I think I think I could
protect you from her and she knows that
yeah yeah no just like every face baby
everyone believes her I bet you can't
sweetie what are you doing I the dinar
would not want to admit that he would be
like getting a punch can playing it off
like that didn't hurt and be like I
dozed off there guys I'm sorry sorry
that was that wasn't that weird
narcolepsy but I'm better now oh sure
thing about me being great yeah great a
great narcoleptic yeah I go down yeah
full health so catnap yeah good but yeah
I don't know what you heard but when I
was alive that what you guys started to
move Rosie went toward dinar like
instinctively as a protection thing to
be like oh my gosh
the moment you start talking she's like
oh right this
yeah nevermind looking good feeling good
let's go it's not gonna jumping-jacks
visibly tattered and hurt you decide huh
tasteful emerges you can you can hear
his footfalls on the stair from above
that brings him down into the sort of
main foyer and he has he has draped in
the finest there moth-eaten but he wears
it right
like he wears these moth-eaten silks in
a way that you think could could bring
it back yeah yeah he just just draped
just just all the way around he looks
like a it looks like a delicious like
soft like man
imagine a where soft-serve right imagine
that he was exposed yeah exactly so
there's just something delicious and
creamy
I was imagining like like those like
crepes you know a real thin and just
kind of draped all over him and you
could just sort of like dessert you want
like a stroopwafel like that right here
the mind yes for ending the tunnel where
yeah what's the status of the cleavage
and bellybutton windows oh you know he
is no he has mate he has made absolutely
sure to retain but it's like it doesn't
look like there's any effort like that's
the key it's just the rap but it's
always there like just like like this
energy source is that always ready to
receive but but yeah exactly so he he's
just he's just waiting to see what's
next life has been very good the last 12
hours or so and he would like it to keep
going under how he escapes no lands
notice I guess but seems like no it's
her baby she might be able to see she
Mabel to detect the IQ
well it doesn't explain dinar and he
spits out of joy I wasn't even I was
fine shoo them all the time yeah it's
freshens the breath
spitting jewels it's like it's a new
term that he just invented it means
doing great okay
life is good I'm spitting jewels crimes
okay so you have something that moral
wants right
Yeah right now refresh Chris I so I've
retrieved
oh the the knife from previous is still
here yes all right I get a good firm
grip on that but uh my things indeed we
need the knife that contains the
laboratory mm-hmm absolutely
and velvet the softest ghost has two
pieces of friendly gear that's right a
gift to he's and he still made himself
look like in you know a corner table or
something during that yeah something
good something nice yeah make yourself
something nice how happy are they it
would be appropriate the crate yeah how
big is that it's it's substantial but
the banners themselves weigh a lot less
yeah okay so you just wanna leave the
gems well no I want to take there's no
those in though yeah DCAM Sabrina yeah
yeah what kind of what kind of kind of
money's are talking about gym wives but
in terms of the witch gym is we talking
about where you were saying box gyms and
banners note the gems are a part of the
banners
okay rip those out Jerry encrusted ah it
was pillaged pretty bad before we got to
him sorry no I wouldn't I know wait a
minute hold on and say what am I saying
I would have no problem ripping the
jimmies no you Stefan
but morale might want them in fact when
I get more money with the entire I will
ask I guess we'll see
do you want these you know finish these
she's a gem now I got plenty
at that point yeah I've been pretty rude
to do it and that's I would their bag
difference yeah
[Music]
killing my mother was therapy enough
woof
yeah much people pay for that sort of
thing yeah that's that little edge
closure they do pay all right your
father come in to possession of a member
of my Enclave and I don't know
and they might have talks and the fact
that the when I spoke to the seed she
seemed to indicate that she didn't know
who it was it could have been my father
but she was not specific I asked but
they all look the same
no and you do have you do have excerpts
in your book from your father as well
that's true I mean I assume it's him
yeah yeah okay so we've got that we know
where to meet Laurel all right then
where we proceed oh except for one thing
I look as we're all gathering to go I
say wait wait wait I come back and I
look at the spot where I fell I start
looking in the dust
it's and I like they Tetris and I kind
of drawn I've done drawn unity or waste
the point is to draw a unique one we
already knew that that was one of them I
was supposed to draw something that I
hadn't seen yet and that would add
information I've just drawn something I
already said we already knew this about
I love it I love that you died poorly
did Denard draw anything duck
yes great a macaroni duck yeah so that's
just I'm just personally I'm just upset
with myself that I couldn't come with
them better wait you die you get
resurrected and then you spend the first
10 minutes which is
beating yourself up for various things
with your diamond which you think she'd
bring back again
there just have another round oh I don't
think I would push my luck if I were you
okay okay
she's probably anything yeah she would
pop out you when you died there are the
dents in the sea this one's a good way
I'm looking at it actually it's very
much sure he's yeah he's 380 years have
you know really brought him closer so
tinge so you are as you shuffle out of
the lowest place in what was once house
Ruth Lee is there anything else you want
to do before we continue it's a long
ways away from the rest of the campaign
setting and so if there's anything you
want to it's very far away not for Rosie
but you're not obligated to well yeah
they're both good choices just like in
telltale right sometimes the three dots
is a really cool choice so just what is
there a timer doesn't wait to like runs
ads like well you will let's go you're
not picking anything no I think I have
everything I want this information for
Carver goal yeah is the most valuable
but she's so far yeah absolutely
so as you it has already ruined exactly
that's a no one crossed them so you you
found your way up here with the use of a
device that Carver Gaul had given you
but you remember more or less how to get
back down and also from this high place
you can see the road quite easily from
here obviously this has become a
dilapidated maze but there's plenty
there's it's probably easier to descend
and it wasn't it was to get up just
because it's like you can sort of see
the mouse maze and from up here
and you can see trundling a way
from the living healthy part of Galla
death you can see a tiny spire at the
base of this hill being drugged along
the road by a strange little hand and
you assume that if you were much closer
to it it would be larger makes sense
things aren't that different leeladhar
no you're not
do you think they would be as we're
leaving I want to wait until you you
three have kind of gotten some distance
ahead of me and to stop next to the
corpse of your dead mother and to just
look down on her and say quietly you
failed
he won and you lost
and she doesn't spit as she considers it
no but her mouth is because moistened
yeah you see with the anticipation no no
those days are behind me worth it she
straightens out to her full two foot
eleven and a half inches and carries on
good thanks
thanks guys that's our show hmm thanks
so much for you know so as you as you
continue to sort of Scrabble through
these you know false hallways and dead
streets writers don't writers don't like
their chances you can see it they say
sort of watch in fear curiosity it can
be hard to sort of map exactly what that
face is about as they look down from the
ruins of buildings and from dark alleys
you can see them sort of like move back
on their legs but you can get down to
the the road and intersect with Morel
strange cart if you'd like to it's one
option okay you captain I don't think
there's anything else of note here
there's a little part of me as tempted
now though not and now I could
communicate with them no it's no we
already did it and let's get out of here
hey spiders um so as you as the party is
is getting near the the road the hand is
pulling the cart and then it stops I
think it starts to pat on the road and
then it paths toward the party and then
immediately starts to pull itself into
the ruins again and you can hear
clicking and shouting from the top of
the tower down at the down at the hand
oh it's coming in hard oh it's coming
for the party who knows who could say
yeah so easy fun pulling pulling pulling
and the fingers just coming up and it's
just a little group little groom on the
side yeah turns you around a little bit
picks me up brushes you off yeah I just
think like a piece on a board just
getting yeah he would Donora is acting
like he's good with it
nice okay it is a dragon hand it seems
like you'd be into it
Jinora is putting on a brave face Oh
buddy
so her what she referred to as her
father's sort of walk in a kind of
Chevron out in front and so they look
over toward the party and nod and wave
and what you think is like a their
version of politeness but it looks
murderous mm-hmm
but but you've your experience with them
before has led you to believe that
that's like their gear like even even
when they're trying to get customers
they have a certain presentation well
yeah you want to know this
there's some good stuff in there it can
defend it exactly yeah
they have a template and so you can you
can hear you can hear clacking footfalls
from the open windows as someone is
traversing them and then Morel pops out
not completely out of the cart but at
the window where tasteful stole the
potions mmm there's sort of like a
service window basically where she can
operate the store without bringing
everything out and we've returned you
can tell you've sort of can't have way
we appreciate that we have items from
house really hey the eyes thighs widened
you'd think that they widened a little
yeah it's just like human yeah it's like
if you've widened and then like she had
the presence of mind to just decide that
was the new level of width
my eyes are yeah yeah this is just
Justin I think it's normal
trinkets from a now at long last well
and truly dead house and and I sure
velvet up who offers his his where's the
the pieces he's been carrying who has
the banners will offer those as well
well the great thing about this is it
comes with a bonus item and I pull out
the family ledger and I go funny thing
about this I'm very excited about her
keeping skills at this point she hands
her the banners like could not tell us
about those she's like when the banners
went away from the house they made one
wait and then when they came back well
you're talking she is saying something
to the Derg are just sort of like
whispering off to the side like looking
at you listening but she's just like
pointing out of these and then pointing
at the tower and then like circling them
and then doing this Oh totally and then
one like goes on a really long
explanation of this discrepancy and how
she found it anyway that she closes it
up and she puts the book on the pile and
how much was that discrepancy again six
pounds interesting sixty pounds an
interesting way oh four ounces she says
she says what this is that this ledger I
mean this only the most bizarre ruined
house fetishist would be interested in
something like this but it's so
immaculately kept except for that one
thing but if you're saying that no one
wants it then I you know would disagree
and think you should keep it because
it's very nice because she's low balling
yeah yeah yeah she says okay well maybe
I'll find somebody who likes math a lot
of people like math in Mathemagician a
mathematician might like yeah well I
guess fine all right I'll take it back
no that's listen I mean this is just
wait for you honestly like I'd be happy
to hold on to it I'm just saying that
there's a lot cooler stuff that people
usually bring me and it's it's not like
this that's that's all I'm saying
like customers who was not there for the
six pounds of Revelation so he's putting
together and and leans conspiratorial
over Rosie and says exactly what I was
[Laughter]
in one and one last thing well it just
puts her hand on the ledger and then
looks at morale and she goes listen I
think we both know how I think we both
know how great of an item this is those
banners are fine but this ledger it
really tells a history walnut right yes
all that dumb grass
yes you're scaring the hell out of me
well good yeah you puffs up for test a
little bit my Rosie like give her the go
with it thing and she's like hmm and
just like puffs up like tries to be
really tall I mean you know she still
looks like Cathar so you can't really
look she's still like the Derg are have
begun dwell this conversation that's
taking place just this battle on a brand
new field they have taken them and
they're sort of carrying them piece by
piece higher up into the tower and you
can see morale to continuing like that
looks still weirded out quote-unquote
still finds this interaction very
strange she goes back and there's
there's multiple cases behind her for
transactions of this kind and she opens
one that has three separate locks on it
and places it inside and then closes it
and then Bree does all the locks can I
do
kind of a perception checker you can
this is dungeons and fucking dragons
like you can roll that I see one I
support you 100% in this endeavor and
every time you roll it could be the
shadow Council games riches well I'm
gonna just I don't I want to get seven
well that's very good
yeah 2026 is there anything is there
anything on the apparatus or anything
going on there what do you wanna know
just give me give me more details I'll
give you more details any smudges of
anything well that's very interesting
you can see with this is a good roll if
it hadn't been like this it wouldn't
have indeed this juicy you can see that
there are marks underneath the lock when
she lifts the lock to read to fix it you
can see that there are smudge
is behind and underneath where the
fingers would touch the case mm-hmm the
finger would touch the chest yeah
behind it so I elbow Rosie and I like
give you the eyes like what look at this
and then are you saying are you seeing
it
no I leaned over and I was for you I go
it's the same paint that I found on my
glass in there Rosie gasps more
theatrically than she intends to no I
mean no no and as you say I think she's
wearing a disguise
there's a sound like a sail catching the
wind oh and these massive Ruth Lee
banners collapse from windows and
fixtures all around the tower it's a
bold move
Wow for all to see
Rosie looks she she kind of squints and
I immoral and puts the banners looks at
you says kind of felt like their persona
non-grata here maybe not the wisest
choice I'm not gonna be here long where
are you going
wherever I won nice I'm moral cold blood
do not hear them yeah yeah okay con that
doesn't change the fact that these are
parmesan croutons yeah think about it
like that
what about it whap addict okay - sure
she has her own reasons do you want to
confront her I just want to ask I just
want to say moral I know we're just five
people wearing the skins of five other
people therefore people wearing the
skins before other people here I look at
her like gravely yes I have an itch on
your ear I hate it
the ear comes up uh never mind I'm
holding my own ear like
[Music]
my ear underneath erm I just hope
alright doesn't happen all this so I
start multi racing my yeah oh yeah no
it's gonna it's gonna reveal skins
freshest lay my dinar is so excited
because he was like on the verge of
getting hysterical okay if he had to be
in someone this other skin any longer I
thought usually like peeling things
no he's too bad um so she gets this ear
and she goes oh okay that's great um
well I just want she's like it's a
dangerous place to be you yeah you know
what you're right that I do you think
sure you're right it's a dangerous place
to fly those banners to let them try
okay
I mean eight do wear gar ain't gonna
help you out much in the Underdark
I just got to know why do you want the
banners more she leans out of the window
and looks up and says just like the lip
what are you gettin to read off this at
all the read I'm getting is that they're
not our banners anymore and they
certainly aren't mine they're of
historical no but nothing else you don't
feel any ownership of them I mean there
were your families ah any ownership I
felt I left behind when I escaped and
vowed never to come back here you
feeling any animosity towards them
I would I would probably strip those out
get the thread out of there at take the
gems make something nice out of that
it's useful pull that up sell it so here
you're keeping up facade oh yeah I mean
trying to bottle in the rain terms of
China Reed yeah I'm furious
those are my banners no in terms of like
what's going on with us with morale I'm
Karissa is like again theatrically
inscrutable like it is her business and
weed and I don't care
or he may be interested in doing de
regarding yes and sitting there waiting
for the end of the sentence like a trade
cart passes by on this road from gala
death and there are whispers from the
top and at these whispers one of the
Derg are just nonchalantly brandishes
his axe and the whispers tamp down
hanging out hold on I did not name this
house hang on a second edition
hello rawr hello it's like the first
program everyone writes hello I kept
trying to come up with a Kuya like like
try to put like go and McCaffrey style
like throw some like apostrophes in
there and I was like Hello rawr maybe or
Paula over our I don't know but that's
really the name of the town I need to be
seen not heard yeah before it's meant to
be spoken by a goblin yeah right that's
the other way it's true there are times
just butcher it that's for sure the
beautiful goblin Lee well lasting how do
we get to her room
hello right that's quite a trip this
whole Underdark thing's been kind of a
trip
so are you equipped for them I assume
not I have a variety of products
obviously and by by this point you have
received your money back for your
purchases like the things that you
brought her from how smoothly like
substantially out class
that probably potions yeah give us sir
give us a quantity of gold piece here
450 I think was the that was the yeah
the knack the amount we again that
squares no sup she's not she's you know
no sure she's how much for the banners
pom-pom now super cool banners and don't
forget about that ledger yeah yeah
that's a value-add see somebody gets its
evaluated yeah I oh just waiting for you
the tech tag in bad cop yeah no I have
you know a really good idea um but you
mean you have you have techniques
powerful techniques certainly for travel
sure but I've never been to hell you
have indeed when you came to this place
to begin with and found yourselves
inside the ample torso I am of Bell GOG
mmm I thought this is that out of my
mind this is the hobgoblin city of
horror I think I liked it tasteful and I
go back home bud hmm anything he smells
always ready okay yeah I see flaking it
won't be good you don't seem to you
don't see the he doesn't need st. Ives
apricot scrub it seems to be lasting a
little bit longer on his frame have we
all flicked yeah but at varying levels
and then the more you worry it in a
specific place the stretch here and more
porous that jerky like strip becomes
raises grooming you in a flash vaccine
to our grooming sesh the shoot she's
like oh your message she's just pulling
she's playful just sheets yeah and it's
really satisfying it's like peeling
goods
I'm simply a good it's a good good
sunburn or it's like it's the cover on
like a like a 4k HDR like it's a big
sheet like this I think I'm gonna go
paper and oh yeah someone's fallen house
okay so big sheets the whole thing yeah
just two holes for the nipples I'm like
there are some funny mammalian just
things that but now that you got a ting
impressive can we get a ruling can I get
a ruling
what's honestly like if there's things
there's things about the way Dragonborn
function in five well yeah I mean we I
prefer our cannon for these dragons sure
they're special dragon say you can do it
better than those other guys I'm not
saying that I'm just saying it's that
dragon that said to like the peeps like
the wrong daddy prong to people daddies
what you see that guys that two-pronged
prong yeah that's a plus I'm saying I'm
saying that we bring in that deviantART
audience you know what I mean
in any case yeah yeah we couldn't even
talk about this my character do I say
look like yeah
1pp like alien second P becomes a
crossbow like it one can go back in and
like No
no it's worse it's worse it's worse it's
like this it comes out but it doesn't
like shoot and it doesn't like it kind
of falls out and then it crawls away but
then immediately gets legs and stands up
right it's like knapsack in a very small
box trained just like we we it's so slow
all right here all right are we gonna
let's let's go here we're now in the
hole yeah yeah and we get on that little
train and do a real same way you do a
bite well that's just an innocent heart
okay yeah Oh for skits like you told to
tasteful that's yeah I'm gonna tell this
we all hold hands are peaceful oh yeah
it's the seance again mm-hmm tasteful
it's been kind of a day and you're you
got it I gotta say you are making that
mothball fabric work it's looking he's
starting to look like it's like the like
the selfie app like with the sparkles
like as just trying to tell the story
like they're way too big yeah he's
beautiful sparkly and I I tell him I
spend a good five minutes telling him
how beautiful he is and like getting a
little graphic with it and then I ends
twist and then we got to hello
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's impossible I can however they both
sweaty and dry I think it was slower
than if we walked perceptually it felt
like a thousand years
well tasteful happy yeah he seems he
seems happy you don't know if he
understood a word of it honestly I'm
like mater some of the adjectives wasn't
for him where some of the adjectives
were of market you know what I mean got
those five dollars you know what I mean
no um so the place that you have been
here before you ran away with a bug was
in there tournament arena right and so
when the soap bubble pops you are there
with tasteful now in this new
configuration there's loud noises of
preparation clearly they are preparing
for something in this town it's not as
much of a ruin as lower gallery earth
but it's definitely not like the
maintenance levels are not high mm-hmm
they're not that's the takeaway what are
they working on is this a market place's
no no no you can just you can just hear
banging and hammering and lots of
yelling at one another yeah but then we
got to hell or or and then what happened
oh then this is this is what you hear
outside the thing I will do cruddy on
you anybody out here that we can guess
we just got a walk-in Oh just hoof it
yeah we're wasteful is weirded out hmm
he's just like got it he was wearing it
he was wearing it well and now he he'd
has gone a little pale and he's just
just looking around you think that you
think that this you think that his life
might have been very different before he
met the party was there tasty very
tasteful yeah tasteful I feel
responsible for this
yeah that's why he's reward yeah Wow
I mean he really what could I teach him
now it's so far surpass me what do we
see well here there's there's not a
whole lot in this area the gates to the
left and right are open ranked and yeah
I mean you just choose a gate and then
I'll tell you what you see I want to
march up to those well okay okay a
little thing here
so when let's say you guys were with
tasteful well you know walnut and Rosie
worth table I see what's going on around
and I grabbed you aggressively by the
back not intentionally aggressively but
he's like - Bing doesn't know straight
and it pulls you back from the crowd I
go limp for sure yeah you ain't sure in
like in in a moment of like one-on-one
miss I'm just like and just like his
eyes get super wide and he just goes
like I got everyone convinced you know
expertly that I didn't die but we died
dude like we died and he just like has a
mini breakdown like and just like not
good just kind of you just had a dry run
through it you see failure usually you
don't I don't think I've got quite right
yet you guys if you've died what did I
see something yeah when you say I didn't
really see something you see it
oh I've now recalled what I saw yeah
okay I didn't see anything
hmm
there is it doesn't the time scale
doesn't appear to be fully linear but
you are given a walk through
by a figure whose face you can never
quite make out but whose voice is deep
and resonant taking you shelf by shelf
through the books and study apparatuses
a pro-rata asparagus yes inside existing
inside the laboratory it's almost like
being led through by your by the head
librarian basically says so this is you
know for investigating events of this
nature some phenomena are tricky
which is why I've arranged it so that
when I have a question
I can stand at this point in the library
and I can look around at each shelf and
this is the perfect place and then he
kneels down and looks at you and you are
very small and he is very large
impossibly large
and he says from here from this point we
can see everything so halfway through
this conversation your eyes got to focus
yeah I owe ya I didn't see anything it's
you had to see something this is amazing
it's great it's great to die no like
dinars like thin veneer of
overconfidence is like wrong yeah I know
he's like having a crisis of conscience
here I don't know yeah he's like tells
you like goodnight my father the knife I
saw it I understand
oh let's do it again come on yeah
you're like grab his hands and he to say
as they start shaking because he's like
those those dry ders we saw on the way
out I just we had to fight them I can
fight them okay so like a fun hearing
net and I'm a better understanding of it
yeah okay it's it's new to a lot of
people I can come back and come back
down let's let's let's hear a while
among the living
stay as long as we want in most cases
that's good stay as long as we want you
don't have to go back to you oh that's
good we're done that reassures that
we're dis lightly
no no it's finished it's finished
yeah sexy growl goblin beast to attend
to you see also experiment iams
comforting another person can can assist
you when you're feeling troubled I've
noticed then because I see how because
you'd then even know what advice to get
and then you realize that you could give
it to yours no no make sense well fuck
if I go over to him and I say hi friend
what's wrong I can maybe you can and
then you do that he'd do that for you
then too like then you'd have it and I
just look so you confused and then just
kind of looks around it goes what do you
mean I'm strong and good live forever
you like going for a hug and he's like
well I'm the best always be the best and
I'll never die and I'm invincible
you're very good very good healthy back
and just see them huh games and our
screaming I'm the best like yeah okay no
out into comforting you so I am I'm like
he's great
he's good guy over here very dear string
but the face is like a smiling happy
thing yeah but for some reason there are
tears you need it so much yeah
at the left gate then you can hear him
before you see him crying out and
singing like with joyous singing and
some kind of like a like a 2-tone throat
singing type voice you can see Carver
ball in his arraignment come around the
come around through the gate and he
raises assists so his his holy symbol is
a massive thing that he wears he doesn't
wear it as an indication it's almost
like in the same way that you would like
cover yourself with ashes or sack glass
like we got millstone but a big way
exactly he wears it to be a weight and
so it is still chained around his torso
and it hangs down and he lifts it with
some effort and kisses the face of it
and he says you have returned
Carver go and Birkins we have returned
with good news tell me we've recovered
these from the let's see oh wait so when
I was in the knife I did not like crazy
shit this awesome shit we got this so
there's a room in here I died it was
fine it was so much fun yeah what
information what what can i what can I
give you what is he specifically looking
for well he wanted the anyway you want
so he was looking for he knew that there
was something in lower calendars right
which is why he gave you that okay
because you already discussed this
outside of it Oh closer and he was after
the symbol indeed though yeah some some
icon some remainder some remnant that he
thought was no in this place of where's
where my notes okay okay okay
I have good notes what do you need I she
has fucked up notes yes but for once I
took some pretty good notes I so I look
around just let me know how open air is
it's relatively well yeah yeah right
yeah I say oh no I have something very
special for you just a mana and I get
the knife out and I just go you shove it
in my head and my I assume I'm
transported to that immediately like you
you are Chris through the through the
crack the only causality that I know is
that when he does this Oh what else pops
out and kills my friends so I'm
immediately like stats out yeah yeah
this is total risk grabs the knife
plunges it in and then you seeketh risk
go and the knife is just there yeah by
level but I don't spend long because as
soon as I'm in that room I'm gonna grab
that the book of unity that was on the
desk right and and back out through the
door assuming that I can carry objects
with all this absolutely so yes yeah
yeah yeah so objects can sometimes leave
of their own accord yeah well it's not a
informations free what degree man sorry
let me take a Bitcoin yes it's so I yeah
I emerged seconds later and so as you do
he is at a different person a different
perspective from you so as you saw that
the dagger went in and they remained
there Carver call is just his his his
mouth parts are engaging in some kind of
behavior and he is just looking at it
from all angles trying to trying to
conceive of this instrument hmm don't
don't worry so you grab it and come
right back out I just come right back
out you come right out and then died the
dagger is just right there to grab it
again this is a great night
but I think this is even more
interesting as far as your purposes are
concerned I hand him the book so he the
the symbol on the front of it the symbol
of unity is reflected in his own
agreement in multiple places right
everyone loves Raymond so I mean all
around it he is you know
the closer you get to him the closer you
can see that the symbol is there in many
places some of them are very rough-hewn
maybe with a fingernail some are more
reverent and perfected but he's just
he's ensconced with it and he begins
flipping through it hungrily and he says
and he snaps it together with both hands
and he says I believe I know it's a
place where the ritual must occur yes
yeah these things must be combined and
only once they're combined can we free
that which endures that which makes
sense we have been preparing for your
return and we are nearly ready to go my
return Oh will this from this trip yeah
of course
that's some grater where is this place
he says it is please don't be done no he
says he says it is little-known but it
is in the gleaming lake that burns
beneath the city of regular nor off hmm
that's as good a place as any you know
more about it that's stuff he says he
says we can leave he says we can leave
at any time
I suggest we leave now I may confer with
my Patriots even I'm sure they'd be
amenable already are you near others
what's happening room are you all right
there's no sexual tension this time
around there was some heat they're just
happy to like be with each other
that's just romantic yeah yeah what does
it have to be always at that pitch
there's got to be some sort of under bed
I mean right comfortable in the silences
I go back I kiss I'm full on the mouth a
tentacles a part of my check for and
it's just like it's just like a noodle
it's a dilute moves done just like the
nice
so I come I come back I come back to
where everybody else is and I I say yeah
he wants to be in free God's from this
angle
yeah and what's to perceive now should
we I don't have anything better to do
yes okay so there is while you while
you're so while you're taking this vote
pays off who you might recall from
before the two sort of two poles of this
army he was the one who's who you had
allowed to succeed he is coming in
behind Carver Gaul and there is another
group of Oh Josh would you please have
kind us to hit the cauldron place
so there is another group of them
pushing in the other gate and you can
see them beginning to fill in even in
the stands and Azoth says Carver gall
we're done we're done serving you and
your imaginary God we're not going
anywhere we're going to take the carts
we've provided and we're going to leave
what do you think about that go ahead
Josh thank you
this can't be his first Goblin uni right
he's a mind flare like super strong yeah
yeah he turned he turns around to Azoth
and says you serve at my pleasure buddy
what keep what force can you possibly
marshal and he says your own force now
today and on both sides they start to
push in on the party hmm friend my sexy
new friend God as far as that if I see
this happening there's lots of stuff
there's all yeah exactly
so much stuff how many are we talking
about his full force is now is now
stunning seeing ya marry well we should
go tasteful burst out it says hold we
must all fight together
tasteful is trying to get behind you but
it's not possible because now they're
all around
he is try he like goes and tries to hide
behind each person very briefly he tries
to hide behind Rosie but he realizes
it's the non-starter doesn't think I can
protect him okay the reality though is
that you're this you're one of
the fighting service yeah yeah is there
anything you want
do I it's it's I have to do it now that
it's come to mind
what does carver Galway what is he way
gosh all told with his Raymond and is
weirdly big focus mmm probably a hundred
and eighty and what can i what stats
wise what would determine how much I can
lift strengths hands well yeah with my
hands you know lots of people that's the
only way it's gonna work yeah but at
least one strong boy yeah okay well I
guess that's true I could do it that way
yeah it is you're one of the strong boys
I met I can make you strong oh oh yeah
that's a great idea
so these so these goblins are are yeah
goblins and hobgoblins specially check
the crust of over the entire goblin a
catalog right your vast reserve in Japan
when they got all the different flavors
of KitKat like that but I was I'm sold
out in Bob green tea goblins here
[Music]
make me strong I think you strengthen me
you're good-looking
everybody seems to like you don't know
oh I'll never be strong there I rap to
you and I clap you on the back I give
you full strength at the moment you do
that I'm I use a mask of many faces to
transform into a very tall goblin oh
that's because they're shorter right I
mean I said yeah okay so like a
bizarrely tough ass Hobgoblin is this
sort of thing we're talking about here
oh okay okay so it fits right in which
if that one fits the no we did yesterday
okay Hobgoblin Wow they make a big show
of it I fooled you Carver Gaul and I
awaken mind him
leave this one to me I'm the I'm the
angriest with him and I'm gonna try and
pick him up and just run away with it I
always come my forces you Dragonborn
Goblin you others that are here too
let's get this guy and Madam justice to
be served in the truth
Hobgoblin fashion I hate him a lot you
know I'm Claire this is actually working
yeah this is you standing here in the
middle of this arena having literally
just hoisted up Carver gall and put him
over your shoulder now azoth is trying
to is trying to regain control Hayes ah
thank you for your help but I'll take it
from here
I am your champion now he will be
punished swords and daggers are going in
the air I like to I Kappa commands on
exam they're ready like they are ready
to die in your service what do you tell
them I'm gonna say cheer oh yeah Joe I
got it pays off nobody has a search area
doesn't work no that's not gonna cut it
I know I'm saying his save is not
getting played and he says yes yes no
longer will we be yoked to this madman's
disgusting beliefs I am my god I like
the goblins stuff like you not this
thing okay everybody everybody is still
everyone is begin to filter out there
right exit down to the main road after
you and a zombie still yes Pied Piper
Ingham that's right
onward stop chasing us that's a good
idea you're working can you guys make
anything I can do stuff so I can cast
fly on a willing participant how much
can that can fly yourself
I won't him carry whatever the heaviest
or whatever the strongest person can
carry : sneer why I haven't tried it
down here but we are saving a mind
flayer can we're saving a friend yeah
but he could he's very strong right I
don't know I'm I'm new to this game I
don't think they're super strong no
that's right there they're pretty
formidable in a lot of different ways
yeah other ways of lifting things to us
yeah looking emotional can't equate he
is just like us he is just like it'd be
like carrying a snake on your shoulder
like he doesn't know this is not a this
is not how like mind flayer parents play
with their children this is not this is
probably the first time a Mayan flare
has been carried like this picked up
yeah like so on the road what is in
front of whoa where would we have to go
to lose what's the first corner we could
turn that the truth is is that heading
south from here tastier Rindler north
right which is where we need to go okay
well maybe we could deal with them then
can you know like scare them off with
somewhere can you scare him off I was
wondering can you do any in anything
environmental landslides in I do have
that kind of stuff but I was thinking
that maybe you could just command them
to go back to their homes okay you know
that's charges or if if Carver Gaul is
amenable I could I could cast fly on him
and just say just act like you're being
taken and then don't just come back and
go no just trying to sell it
oh here's the good news I don't have
anything because we did a bunch of stuff
yeah he says he says that's a good
question I really also not have as much
as I thought Trevor Gaul is just flopped
over the
hop and he says put me down if you
please I'll shoot
should I just put you down should I make
it look like a struggle yeah
put me down whoa okay he unfurled he
twists around and assumes his normal
shape and he walks up to a zhou na
Sothis whoa and Carver Gaul just know
goes oh dang the do you see all of it
these tentacles are out and there's a
moment like a shrieking moment on the
part of you don't know if it is a Zhou
or if this is just the sound that
accompanies this yeah but these
tentacles wrap too around the back of
the neck to around the back of the head
one over the top and in seconds there is
just a sack of meat that has fallen off
of the front and keep picks up a zoth
sword and holds it up and their swords
go up as well I'll do it oh I and I just
dropped to my knees like oh mercy you're
right you're the true leader of this
group I was unwise to to try and make a
show of it even as strong as I am you're
the best one for me you got really like
up in there did it smell yeah it was
warm he tells them to get the carts in a
but you would describe as a darkly
encouraging way
and after a brief time I don't know when
to let go of this I know exactly so
start to go get carts dispel it so
various carts that they have you can
tell that there have been fresh repairs
but repairs again as happens so often in
this campaign these are in quotation
marks this is just pieces of doors and
windows that have been nailed on to what
you think might have been perfectly
functioning parts yeah it's just
something that they found it's just
something to keep them busy yeah yeah
exactly
yeah exactly it's the door to nowhere
and so this caravan and this massive
group of people are on their way down to
ring Leonora over in the car I'm gonna
take a moment Carver gall and just
apologize oh you're a series of a fault
I think of my feet and I assumed that
I've never led an army before and I
assume mutiny happens often and no yes
means so you're so you're inside like
his slightly nicer cart and he says I
have to eat one every ten days hmm
welcome mutiny well-timed yeah so near
lunch so halfway about halfway down
there wagons are rounded and groups are
sent off to get disgusting bugs another
gross shitty you know I'm talking about
yeah definitely oh you know they'll do
in a pinch
yes can I um can I roll to eat a bug you
can roll to eat a bug you can also get
the rescue so crave ah I will take
advantage one bug eating yeah all right
mmm the juiciest burger
okay okay so it's a thirteen plus my
wisdom dexterity yeah
yeah nature nature I would say choose
the right bug because the 14 that's what
I'm hoping
yeah yeah yeah choose the yummiest bug
yeah exactly
so there's a bug you kind of have to
like chuck it Oh like there's just a
slip underneath the bug and you just
have to reach in and then just pop yep
they pop the grabby oh yeah yeah yeah
too little flexing it don't tell me you
never eat bugs but they were like and
other stuff oh I offer you a bite like
bigger bugs no nutritious and I pull out
a little smashed rotten disgusting with
some good beer like fermented yeah and
it like it's got like that's sickeningly
sweet tang to it yeah I start much on
that nothing no this is better isn't too
dark it is too dark and there are there
is lint that's but it's fine
oh yeah suit yourself are you
envisioning like a very strong like a
grasshopper leg which is like kind of
like a the chicken leg I'm in motioning
literally just like a lobster meat yes
oh is this this is exactly what I
thought yeah just a big old chunk of
meat mm-hm
I mean lobsters water bugs yeah yeah our
spider white exactly it see glistening
out where exactly I don't think any
lobsters lobsters corn no no same thing
who does disgusting yes so as the dental
I as the crowd they dismantle their camp
large portions of it seem to be left
behind some of the carts no longer a
hundred percent work you would say and
you can see the bridges or one of the
bridges the Northbridge la that makes up
one of the districts of Wrangler Nora
don't tell me it's the orb and Hills
District
the architects who can solidify shadow
stuff by singing to it mmm Wow
he's just ailment here my only district
we have not visited is the eastern tier
mm-hmm
just some facts about ruler not exactly
it's like you say you could you could
actually run a little tour yeah for the
for the Hobgoblin things that she does
she live their whole life uh at the
western district we have the rift
hunters mm-hmm they get food for the
districts you can see the just off in
the distance you can see the central
sort of capital so whirling around this
massive lake but they decide to make
camp on the shore of the lake of radiant
mists and you can see that when the when
the capital city returns and then places
itself on that little hook because it's
just weightless city functionally
speaking you know well hundreds if not
thousands of cloakers fall off of the
city just basically just like drop off
of it so it looks like it's like when
when onyx came off the table in the test
market yeah it's like that it's just
they're all just dropping down like this
and you can see that when they drop down
to the surface of the lake of rayon
mists they're all basically drinking at
once and you can see that cloakers can
indeed crawl out from the bridge city
that they live in as well and they are
drinking as well and to the extent that
the level of the water
is markedly lower
and you can see right on the edge it
looks it looks like a it looks like a
painting from an alternate universe sort
of religious study book Carver Gaul is
pointing out across this glowing lake
and he is pointing at this sort of spar
that has emerged just the top of it has
now become visible as this water level
has lowered and he gestures you over
Karissa okay
yeah I'm coming over what's in this lake
well there are many things in this lake
we won't concern ourselves with all of
them he says that there is something
like a cloak ER that never left the
comforts of the water something like ray
but they are it's a ray how would I
differentiate them from a race I would
say that they are like a an occult ray
but say they're like a evil ray I could
do that right hates the living Sam yeah
he says there will be there will be time
to worship Dark Gods with these Ray's
once you have accomplished your feet
this is a time of prophecy go thrift
route feeling here will to feel oh no
you don't feel anything
yeah you go numb no no you when you roll
to feel you want look okay it was a golf
yeah
Raven one I'm afraid of my center yeah
yeah what are the steps exactly he says
he says that I believe that that is an
entrance to the underground caverns who
steam warms this entire lake but the
material a topic we have no name flaw
and
we believe that I have endeavored to
pierce it hmm that's that skin on the
top it doesn't cover the entire bottom
of the link yeah yeah this this
basically this bar is coming out and you
have a hard time seeing where it goes to
beneath but like the steam and light
rising up there there geological
phenomena here you know that the surface
only suggests and thus far does it look
like it's it is geological or that it
came from a ship or something no it it
definitely looks as though it is the
result of a process okay hmm it doesn't
look like although that's super cool and
altering universe we run that adventure
as well hmm is there is this lake filled
with a substance that is not water no no
it is it is water okay and the creatures
that live in it are aquatic creatures
right okay they are unlike those which
you know
so what's what does carve a girl's
problem start trying to pierce this
surface it's the material he says he
says we have no name for it and maybe
they you know better okay but I think
you have you have something I did not uh
I have regular mouth
yeah okay did you not see me eat a saw
yeah I know if it was a mouth thing or
like I don't know it's a mouth oh cool
yeah sorry I think you're embarrassing
me I'm for my friend okay uh so can we
approach this far you can you can hear
the water the water level is low enough
that it is actually possible to get out
to it and and see it I mean you'll be
you'll be up there's you'll be waiting
pretty deeply but it's possible long
there yeah is it just high on me yeah
you you really need to be carried
well it yes for a mother can I read on
your back please of course let's get
down okay
yeah so you're in a great time yeah now
I am bone dry warm yes weirdo Lake yeah
after you stranger squid man oh yeah no
I tried just stride right out and I'm s
yeah your cloak just rides on top of the
you know it just spreads out behind you
and floats on top of the can't wait to
chair this this mound the water itself
so you think hmm
ELISA is telling maybe it's time to stop
the show in just what Chris did listen
while we discipline cthe wrists you get
a snack do as you will this is our break
we'll be right back with more adventure
I'm going where hello this is Jared key
organs and you're watching the sea team
which we take a moment to to give props
to the tegu tavern are there people
there are they doing Denny and yes
Taylor Danny on Taylor downtown Seattle
and they're showing C team finale today
and next week they're doing and a D and
E adventurers League hosting I'm gonna
be there so do wait
next Wednesday here eaten in Denny's the
main thing is thank you so much those at
the techo tavern and also everywhere
else for watching the sea team hope you
get after now the tech meet a Verne
you're fine yeah yeah what do you know
but what are you drinking at home yeah
yeah
no you're calm like follow subscribe
button lashes are heroes oh they had
waded into Z glittering steaming waters
of the lake of radiant mists we bring a
second I can't wait to look at this
mound yeah
Rebecca this is which is why we had to
this is where we had to stop the show
it's it's fine the second time oddly
yeah next name is okay we're off so you
can you can see it and then essentially
it's almost like it almost looks like a
creature because it's been you know
created as this process of you know
accretion it almost looks like a like a
eel or something reaching up from the
from the base of the water through the
smooth stalagmite
exactly exactly in the material you this
these are the sorts of materials the
strange alloys that you saw when you are
in the city of the Golden Door city of
Alcazar so it is shining there in this
light I just want to wrap on it rings
spook answer I take the literal pic from
my hang it around if you want that's
gonna happen as a puzzler maybe the
right note I wouldn't wait he said right
though someone say me that was a great
joke laugh
does it need to be struck in any
particular way guess you're gonna have
to I couldn't tell you does it require
strength or is it's the presence of the
tip desengao here play Dungeons &amp;
Dragons please play it that's what
Carver Gaul says yeah I think you're
Larry track here we go you look hacking
car girls ii shrugging him once
that's just tentacle yeah somehow
somehow hugh managed to make his
tentacles shrug but they get it but
actually honor should be yours he is up
on the shore back here waiting waiting
remember when he was like all the
weights off me
this is numb okay so just doing do i
need to run back up there
well we'll find out be patient with all
this dinar i don't know what's coming
trying to be comforting but none of this
is understand that you're like walking
around looking for a pickaxe no it's a
good like an insert that it goes
directly in like there's no place for it
yeah
all right I just with a feebly I just I
bring it down but it's more like a like
a firm tap like a stern strike yeah yeah
like I'm ten breaks and you're winded
now yeah yeah your your cry of strength
when you do it clear so how close is
everyone to him so I can I can figure
out how much damage good question get
the mind flayer across yeah yeah well
yeah yeah I tried to strike it somewhere
like it like I love it
no no still you so you bring it down
with all of your no my scholars strength
and I want to hold on say I want to use
scholars blow so at the second level it
breaks like glass so you can tell even
just looking at it when you're trying to
find the slot to place the pick you can
people have been trying to get here for
a while yeah like there there've been
curiosities about this there have been
several Hardy attempts when you bring
the tip of this pick down what you guys
see is like the spark at the tip of like
a plasma torch mmm Oh like it's just
like a bright flash of color serene
country and it goes and like you lose
the pick like you go like this and it
just goes through and you hear it go
with the some of my my battle cry is
clear and drop the pick so they're still
they're still like I say it's like glass
that material has been have you've seen
the effect of gallium on steel no Jerry
oh wait I think I I think I have it
looks like it rots it yeah yeah and so
there are still chunks of this thing
falling in on the side you have not hit
it again there it's like tin foil in
places yeah this is an instrument you
know designed and for a singular purpose
and it has it has done so hmm so this
hole is just like I'm it's just it is
just like a mouth it just extends down
just into the gullet and look back at
the shredded mind plague I just again a
read on him is he surprised or is he
happy was he mad as if he's just he just
looks like a silhouette like he's stock
still good stalks doing great I'm gonna
communicate with him yeah okay he he
doesn't he doesn't respond but he's like
just go in okay
[Music]
why I trust in this at least this point
so yeah I walk in is though are there
any like is there a as I look over this
now crumbling barrier is it just a drop
is there a walkway it's just a drop but
it appears to dip down from the light
that just surrounds this place mmm
it goes down and it seems to get goes
down into a tunnel at a grade I was
lying now I would we could slide your
host line or I was gonna make a
staircase yes please oh wow it's it
seems nicer yeah and also less scary
mm-hmm so I'll use Greer mantheon hook
it up make a shadow staircase make it a
big staircase because I want to summon
Steve a big staircase just for you right
me ask me a reindeer science rated yeah
we could have to get them you're gonna
have to get a bunch of people in yeah
it's already been inspected oh really
all taken care of yeah yeah that's
that's a that's a good power all right
so essentially so you're doing - how
mean how elaborate like to get the
handrails coming out like are they to
code yeah they are in fact excessively
safe - I think there's no reason to have
a railing here because it's not that big
a drop but I want my baby to be safe
exactly it's like this is this is this
is what you would do if you were making
it for your grandchildren
exactly there you go so it is safe and
you just extend your awareness you let
the shadow tell you where it is pooling
in this place and you create that
platform and you head down
it is not right here down here it is it
is in the tunnels away from the light
itself I beckon to deny our conquest
thus you come across doctors over here
okay right on the snoot oh I'm just
gonna go ahead and whip up a glow man
just to enjoy some of that light it's
hot let's get them ABS a whole this
whole shoot there is a like there is a
gruesome wind this isn't a mouth blowing
straight out and past the party your
robes are going to recap a Bible can be
amount Pierce the amount of that that's
real tip hot shoot yeah
then a scolding wins as well yeah this
is this is Duchess of Dragons oh yes can
you imagine that as a as an
advertisement like you're flipping back
and forth like an e GM or something like
that it's like like an old school yeah
advertisement this is a dragon Oh
somebody's imagination was captured so
glow Manas is perpetually surprised by
everything he just has a sort of his
default look is just everything is new
well like if he mean if he had exactly
yes this is if he had a consistent shape
well yeah but if he had a consistent
behavior or demeanor when I bring him
about it's like a a mime that tries to
show to the audience what they're
experiencing so it's a lot of like whoo
yeah yeah for the podcast
Curtis is Fanning his face yeah and
chronically ringing yeah silly gestures
Thanks yeah someone Clarke Moore at this
point it's pretty cramped here it might
not be at the
this right here I'm saying that we can
continue on maybe there would be a
better space right now but we're not
like on the lip of it work yeah thank
you and we're going right down yeah I
like that
I will wait then I'm proceeding yeah
exactly
well lead the way mentally so I need to
know some important information it
happened a long time ago
you still have a sample of the Zager
Nezzer ale huh correct in Africa I
recall it is Muslim there were multiple
scenarios where you had you had failed
which in that case was winning and then
you had also had a chance to view it as
well yeah you gonna build a home with
Cathy you think this is starting to look
very similar of Cappy doing freaking out
like spinning around well it's like um
like what just like pulling up and off
and then settling back down keep trying
to get away like oh no you know drink
you stay right there
[Music]
[Laughter]
so down here this is the the corridor
that you believe you saw are one very
similar to it starting to see some
bioluminescence in this place so at the
at the idea of that this is a familiar
place yes in stings yeah get that flask
out open it wait a minute this it's from
the dream do you take a sip all right
here so let's get what was the mechanic
again exactly so it's just a
Constitution check but I wanted do you
want if you I lose don't want to
all right so let's can you use it to
test disadvantage can you take this
advantage yeah is that what you want
yeah I want I want it to function all
right well one of them Goliath the other
thing all right doesn't this advantage
me oh that's very bad okay 3 and 1/8 for
the broadcast roles so you
Wow you grab the flask you can see he's
twisted the cap off and then you bring
it up to your mouth and nothing comes
out and then a some kind of like fungal
plug gets the loose is that too much one
episode the scoby without a plug maybe
this goes hot straight down and then
it's just following that it's just this
you know body heat temperature ale
following it back and then you bring it
down you look around and nothing has
nothing has happened the rest of you
seeketh risk hit the ground so and now
so you're just looking around as though
nothing has occurred but there's no one
else here with you okay that's what I
wanted verifying and I'm in the same
space like I Mark like her there was
some mushrooms there there was this
there and it's the same it's the same
place one must be dreaming they didn't
disappear no too little time passed they
wouldn't ran away they saw me it just
this alright so you spend the rest of
your time in this vision I'm just
playing talking your way through
watching the movie memento I'm like ah
just trying to yell and maybe it would
cross and we'd be able to find the dream
me so you're using this as a scientific
yeah triangulation breathing out far off
William so then you you peer review this
is you come to that you come to and
everyone is around playing on the
everyone is looking down at you in a
pile on the ground it's no time to party
well here's the question play it brash
and reckless which is a no here's a
question
did I recognize any of that in my wall
you think it's the same place
sure but do I have a better idea of the
layout of it I mean how much we'll see
you only you only had a few moments to
wander yeah it can't really be used to
sound it out like okay no worries and we
didn't hear anything
mMmmm no well you hurt you hurt
someone's life snoring got it did work
all righty never mind I guess this is
the place it's very similar to any rate
great I think is I'm the wrong barometer
we should be paying attention to to your
you can you get up you can actively sea
Cappy like bubbling up and then
flattening out with a beam what is it
boy on the well this can't be have a
particular expression on his face right
now like wide-eyed mmm good wide-eyed
well you it's hard to tell with a you
know bipedal mushroom but you you have
spent some time in there nailed you
think you then be good you think that
this is not a bad sign okay you think
you think that joint may be occurring I
can talk to them as when I drink I was
able to talk to him then yeah no it was
a good answer and then I drank it and
then we had our vision quest where yeah
where you look like Freddie Mercury yes
however he just drank the last fungal
plug so unless you have it all going
there okay I think so but I could let
the plug open your mouths a bloody sir
tap outlets left the plug is at the top
maintaining freshness yes there's
probably another swing there is a like
maybe I have a swing it'll get you there
enough to ask some questions
alright yeah every I mean you want to go
right well I'll see what's going on with
her my buddy here my sweet boy
all right like a landline you want the
yeah I want to make sure I'm like Chris
I roll like a champ all the time so I
need
handcuffed myself 12 yeah I missed the
table that's great 16 yeah I can't not
win yeah all right
we'd have to like open the flask and you
lift the inside and rip the other side
is it a wineskin just like turn it
inside out I'm licking edges that's it I
eat it I eat what's left I got the key
first special seven so you hit it what's
plus five yeah and he's just flat on his
back too but like like you would be in a
coffin but just like our I'm straight
down oh yeah exactly yeah exactly and
you are you are here in this mysterious
place with the massive hulking
attractive form of this my candid friend
Freddie Mercury that can't be pretty
much all right so he he looks at you and
you're trying to parse the you're trying
to parse exactly what the emotion is and
he reaches up and stretched us out until
he can touch the ceiling and then he
reaches out with his other hand and
basically forms a column with his own
body hmm and then when he closes his
eyes you see eyes erupted all over his
trunk wow I got a lot of latent feelings
on Sonny what could it mean
yeah take another swing you know you
know I talked to him as soon as soon as
this happens you you can see the place
bye
that color of the air begins to shift
well and in this state I asked him and
you want to be left here is this it
this is where I'm meant to go this is
where joy can be maximized no we've had
a good run buddy no I wouldn't I
wouldn't not give him what he wants yeah
remember all those times we had
well that's plus one strength you gave
no I can't stay here with you but I will
they be here
so the montage is yeah but it's a closed
out of the top of your head and catch me
I can tell the background is changing
there in different places but there's
not very much of it to look at it's just
[Laughter]
it's like Oh out of focus in the
background something they might have
been a tree we're gonna forest that time
this constant focus the top of Thor's
head
yeah yeah okay all right well I just
wanted to confirm before I leave mice
like daddy knew well my stats in life my
friend
yeah he's been there for a while
yeah he's kept in our same now dinars
extra crazy language yeah probably just
mean you hairball feed the Oh care boy
yeah this one take care all I have left
so you'll even be you'll even beat down
I'll wake up and confirm to everyone
that yeah this is cappy's place this is
the spot this is Carrie style yeah for
the time being in the dream did he
indicate a certain spacing with the
beers on the ground he seems he seems
fine with this region all right whatever
it is in this good but just kick it's
throwing a frisbee yeah all right yeah
so I will remember you do to do to do to
do ah yes I'll find a nice propria trock
come on disappear
all right that's nice it's ring piece of
shit you mean you
it's stupid on the rough he is rapidly
beginning to build mass underneath and
beginning to extend up and then there is
this the air begins to shift in this
place as well and you can see you can
feel like there's actually like visible
dust mmm oh yeah the spores yeah that's
his way of saying yeah that's like an
mushroom way of mushroom left now yeah
the mushroom version area isn't it -
radar love yeah it could be you know
spore in the air so it's like 99 left I
love the line so this the cavern chasm
down here is has begun to widen which is
important for some yeah but it's also
begun to fork and branch trees - no
soberly that no no no so whatever
whatever process maintains this bizarre
lake also you must create these strange
steam tunnels mm-hmm
and there are many many of them well
we're talking about his we're talking
about that which indoors indeed I'm
gonna pull out my little Andy sigil that
he gave me and see if that trick works
again we can use that of a compass down
here
sure so when you withdraw it and hold it
forth you can see that just the being a
much smaller version of that same symbol
on a lighter stone that breezes down
here just begin to move it and then it
begins to push against those forces and
lead you through caverns and as you're
doing this you begin to hear
a voice everyone can hear the voice but
cthis hears it clearly and loudly you
can all make out what it's saying but
not with the same clarity that kiss has
so I did for the record I do playing
Steve are you Steve fine Steve where's
Steve Steve I need you now more than
ever Steve feeling really alone
that's your sponsor he's feeling he's
all freaked out because he died and now
he just lost his friend and as an
indicator that things are not great
right now in denars head he does it
first try and he usually misses and
messes up for 10 minutes in yeah it's
just like any get so first try this need
it's need so the voice says what do you
think will happen if you release one of
my charges you know that your own power
is a function of my body as a prison
correct you understand that you grow
less powerful with each of these
tantrums
how will it be at the end cath wrists
drab now your Labor's such as they maybe
have their amusements but in the end it
will be a god vs. immortal no matter how
many of them you free how do you think
you'll fare in that contest he wants to
fuck this guy how are you able to give
any meds yeah yeah so so at my regular
speaking volume I don't lose my voice or
anything as if it's conversational
I say no perhaps not a god
versus immortal but a much larger mortal
versus immortal do I owe him and
the the whatever deal I struck with you
is erased from my mind now but you in
any case we're always an intercessor I
will not have your power to draw upon
any more but true power would be my
reward so you are saying these words and
the texture of them is altered by the
volume of the space that you're in and
near the end they are clearly echoing
off of a much larger space so the heat
has increased to something on the edge
of bearable at this point the deeper you
have gone into these caverns and you
have entered into a have you ever
cracked open a geode I've seen it done
yeah
so imagine that you are walking into a
geode hmm so that surrounding you and
there is there is a gentle light in this
place its origin is unclear but there is
a gentle light coming from these
crystals can I get precession chicks
from y'all motherfuckers so the light
the heat you and you it instantly you
are all completed not my best work 14:18
or is that gonna be come on 18 is not
enough for this what so so as you as you
are moving through this place even this
even in the floor there jutting crystals
that are emerging and so walking through
this place is actually very difficult
which is to say it's difficult to rain
but it's also just fucking hard it turns
out to walk inside of a geode no matter
what I might have thought when I was
coming up with the adventure so there is
like a pronounced tinking on the jar
that you secured from with juice with
with the juice inside but also the
strange were mmm inside that's always
curious and clever and when looked at
from different angles appears to be a
different physical shape all together
right right so you can hear its
agitation in your pouch so to speak
we've had mounds we've had pouches it's
and the second I get into it class did
that too so I feel that worm rambling
around in my pouch you know I'm talking
about well I mean trying to think like
yeah for whatever purpose serves us cuz
I hadn't actually put it in my bag it's
still in the knife but well I will I
will retrieve it now and yeah what is
the let me introduce it to this space
with the jar closed still absolutely if
it's if it's tickets yeah can I get more
perceptions from my friends look two
numbers I want I'll take advantage and
1515 that's gonna be accumulative
nineteen okay kneeling down with this
jar you can see in the crystals
themselves you can see the reflection
but you pick up on something which is
that each of them is slightly different
their reflections in each of the
crystals
don't comport you can see that one of
them looks mostly correct but each of
these crystals each of the other
crystals is showing slightly different
versions of the same scene there is a
version where there is not a dinar and
the rest of you are here that's a huge
boon obviously better Rosie the last
version scrabbling let me add but yeah
it it wants very very badly to get out
and be in this place I'm going to
express this to everybody that look at
these look at their reflections there
now right this is some kind of a some
kind of a funhouse
I think we're looking at like the where
all these all these planes of reality
coexist and we can enjoy each one like a
like a bunch of security video feeds I
understand that I don't either
it's just syllables I don't know what it
means one of these ones said it all
disease is the one where he's not in and
he's like I think these are different
versions of health this is obvious
horribles some sort of horrible
situation all right hey would be
possible to get initiative rolls
versus that worm yeah via worm take an
advantage yes pardon X what's your 17
weird we wrote the same thing two three
dude this is this is the work of the
Hertz alright wait don't you get like a
oh I'm a two actually because I get
minus one yeah I get sick so yeah we
won't produce at it again
come on ego let's say so probably go
first you had really good reception so
you can so so you are looking down
approaching this with your what's the
mind of a warlock and anarchist trying
to examine each of these each of these
phases each of these interpretations and
in many of these interpretations you can
see members of the party being slain so
the farther away you get from where you
are actually looking you are starting to
see cascading events where it can't be
it can't be parsed or perceived mmm just
it gets it falls it gets more and more
off the rail basically yeah less likely
that we live indeed timeline you win
yeah and so the reason why the
initiative was so important is because
there are the the crystals themselves in
their natural form are like a milky
quartz but more and more of them are
beginning to have you ever had like a
flower who was who drew the drew water
up but it was like dyed water and so you
can sort of see how out of the petals
out of the edge of the petals you can
see the dye these crystals are beginning
to take them on an amethyst hue inside
this place and they were beginning to
ring and shriek in discordant ways
mm-hmm rosy be stinger yeah I was gonna
posit that Chris could go first since he
had such good perception we have the
same deck I mean I'm sure sure sure yeah
that's easy-peasy it's just like anybody
what do you think we should do
I stabbed the wall mine what to do I'm
not what's the worm doing as we proceed
and we're seeing these these colors
start to shift and these violent scenes
in the dices
it's it is I mean it to the extent that
it's probably difficult to determine
what a worm likes I don't know where
needs yeah we don't want to so you can
tell that it's but its shape is
increasing in complexity hmm the fractal
worm a little boy is it faceted faceted
you know it is not hmm it could not be
less it is it is the antithesis of that
of that model for life okay it is
absolutely organic I'm gonna use
awakened mind on it on the worm yeah and
I'm going to say here friend however it
wants to parse that yeah that is why I
expressed it begins to blink ever more
insistently against the glass and there
is a tiny hairline fracture hmm yeah
yeah you can just you can say something
if you wanted I love it that's that's
that's so good wrist
[Music]
careful friends you wouldn't get cut
yeah I'm end all right so let it Shh
I love it Rosie B singer ah so you are
so this sound it's like a one-level it
could be like a meditation chime but
there's too many and they're all set
just a fraction of a tonal pitch apart
so this place is too vibrating in a way
that seems inherently on LG
I break the glass jar with the worm in
it oh yeah tell me how it looks one okay
so I'm you've mended it I'm talking yeah
and it's going to go and it broke a
little bit yeah I'm like no well we're
not done we need to learn more I'm
marched right up and I look at you and
I'm frustrated and there's this like
stormy look on my face and I just go and
the crash yeah another just the worms in
your hands Oh God
oh it's no I'll explain why okay let's
find out yeah okay so you've you've just
blessed it the top of it shears off the
jar and it's split now
yeah worms like hang in here and there's
some glass there's to me everything that
has happened in this place in this cave
that we've been in has been like it's
copy telling you that this is where he
belongs and in Rosie's head this worm is
saying this is where I belong I'm here
to fight whatever this meat and mouths
voice is she's pissed off that a god was
talking shit to Carissa
and she just she wants to she's doing a
little chaotic good so she thinks she
the bummer is you know that I wasn't
talking back to that God like with it
wasn't threat as what I believe to be
true yeah well no yeah I agree I agree
you it was it was a good report yeah if
we could star Mew that's it wait other
guys have this problem yeah that's true
okay but at any rate if there's if
there's a relationship here between you
and this worm Rosie is not receiving oh
yeah yeah it's it's you got a minute to
say your goodbyes yeah well I'm no fan
of the worm I don't know anything but
this worm yet I could go to become a
great family know your inactivity in the
face of facing worm in the face of worm
and worm face I think is something that
would frustrate roasting it she'd just
be like oh come on that's fair yeah so
Rosie you have the first opportunity to
enjoy this Cameron yeah it's my pleasure
it's all down to the dice so the
this amethyst color that has sort of
traveled and maneuvered around these
crystals it's starting to collect in
some of them and when it when it reaches
a point it emits a beam that fires into
another crystal until it begins to
ping-pong around the cavern itself and
comes right for you
basically hmm all right AC silly enough
yeah sixteen okay okay here we go now
now here's what I need you to do I need
you to strike go through strobe with
your staff okay a real hit all right
take extra is there objection
is it just like um it's your real attack
with all your real stuff okay
is there a reason in my head I'm doing
this it won't matter if you don't hit
how can I take this in pants oh yeah oh
you let them do it
at the head that's a good idea nella and
you're also damage for Chris risk oh
yeah I'll just roll just a little bit
yeah keep it low keep it low yeah hey
six six points
Shane it's very good like smash of the
journey
yeah
there's no effects on this note I need
this saving through so here's here's
what happens the beam so you go over
your it's time to regulate sometimes
grandmas are required and you bring your
staff and just shatter it shatter the
glass like all right now we can progress
this process please and when you look
back at Chris's face it is not his face
it is it is like a statue like a cruel
faced amethyst statue that just taunts
you with its with its gaze and its mouth
and droops open and before you know it
you
have brought the end of the staff up
into that face it's just you cannot look
at it without attacking it I think and
so cuz Chris that catches you straight
in the face and you spit blood out of
the side of your mouth and in this place
that blood hits the crystal and then
begins to run together into a single
pool and that pool skitters around at
the bases around the tips so to speak
and then collects on a crystal that you
can see in the ceiling that hangs down
walnut on grass it's broken you dish
just a minute I'm gonna as I see her
smack right in the face mmm and then the
blood behaves in a bizarre way it does
I'm gonna step in between cutters and
worthy tasting rosy and just be like
what is wrong with you that's it
that's reaction yeah well I mean we can
we can talk on my actually yeah yeah I
want that to happen yeah I want that to
happen yeah that's the type of game I
run there's this nasty a statue talking
shit well not talking about like with
its eyes as you're just as you're
gesturing its q3 strobe oh yeah yeah oh
uh oh well that's not great look out for
visions what did you say no that's what
we call them but we don't call that
I saw a face in amethyst staring at me
begging me to smack it in the face so he
did but it wasn't Contreras what a world
it was it wasn't I am sorry about that
okay look out
so my my whole thing no no no you play
someday that's me um my last question is
our bugs animals bugs animals is a pop
tart of ravioli
yeah I'm an example of this spell I mean
what are you wait trying to do talk to
it but you can talk to it okay
yeah if you if you want to try just
kidding I'm trying to do something else
and it was sneakier you know I always I
wanted to talk to it so I talked to you
and I try doing the diplomacy stuff in
the turnaround look at the worm in your
hand
and I go and I just say I say are you
our friend or a UFO so worm the worm
what I'm just worried what does worm
sound like what does it sound like that
me like I know like the sound of them
like if you can get as close to whatever
swarm is look maybe it speaks that like
I feel like in Thailand yeah she went
try to communicate
I use this creature talk to a worm you
can try your damn said you could do it
alright yeah what am i rushing you like
a water
it's a huge problem so um so you you
sort of you get down to look at this
creature and you say are you you a
friend or foe mmm-hmm and what you
received back isn't language but it
shows you the next Star Wars me oh my oh
nice good it actually turns out good
no no you see yourself in a traditional
enclave funeral and as you are placed in
the ground
you're the soil over the top rain falls
on it and a lush carpet of grass begins
to grow and flowers and trees and fruit
children running on it and that becomes
a part of the forest
okay then slash is playing in front of
the church if someone dies over an
accident to take over no no but there's
important ground so I think like how
transported in my when I see that do I
just see it or do I like feel that
happening it's it is perceptual okay
so we'll only be just started with like
taking it back by that
and I guess not say anything just kind
of stewing that for a minute getting
that juice so wait one that goes
grandmother cool it whoa yeah and then
she that's really serious and then
silence okay
don't are blatant kind of at a loss what
to do here what's the blood doing that
the blood has collected in a specific
place on the scene on a particular spot
yeah I mean but the ceiling is not high
in here okay it'd be easiest for you to
see it actually yeah so you can you can
examine I will do that exactly so give
me a perception role man you want to
goose it because this is some sort of
fight Burling and I don't have a very
good perception 12:4 for when you're
looking at it you can you can tell that
what's happening
inside of it differs slightly from the
rest and that particular that particular
stone shows the group destroying it like
now it is now time is begin to move
forward destroying that crystal okay and
then it goes dark but it's just cycling
through that moment again and again hmm
I tell everyone when I see I've just
been looking in like yeah see any weird
stuff in your blood alright buddy your
Bloods weird man 3 sick I think it's
trying to spawn I think that that is a
shameless baby
Oh nigga wants our blood to juice these
crystals up and I don't look how the
worms involved maybe he has the sweetest
blood of all yeah and then I'm freaked
out and grossed out so you take a step
back from the blood cuz I want to be
close to this thing should we destroy
that bass yeah I mean we could
I mean it's showing it breaking and then
stopping and that's it and every other
crystal is showing us all dying
different in different ways
yeah sometimes the party composition is
different mmm is that crystal familiar
to me at all
I tell you mission well it's red and
it's above us and that is also the
qualities of my long-lost homework star
so I didn't know if there were
relationship that's very very good
thank you there do I recognize its
position like this if you look around at
where the the color is gathering here
there is a case to be made that it
reflects the home word star okay then I
would campaign that we do not destroy it
okay
that's Rosie hmm yeah I mean you got to
do what you got to do if you see some
messed up stuff going on in there then
mess it up but there's no immediate
threat I'm
I'm one for all so you could just read
ten ours Oh less nevertheless
braggadocious more than normal
I got self-absorbed Hamlet oh yeah skull
holder ya know cuz Joe this week we've
already heard like just hi worm you
still down we've already heard about
what is the one doing by the way like as
weird as we've had a couple seconds pass
and there's and it's been in hurt but
like but he has his action so oh I see
yeah boom action where does it fall in
the line I have him with my rest of my
NPCs oh okay okay I just you know it was
just a lip in there boy well you know
it's not damaged I assume not why is
have to be Telegraph's I'm just gonna
put the joke out there and nobody
talking the same well it was it was
stone and blood somehow combined those
the the the ones that we met in the in
that in the prison that stomach said as
much if this thing gets enough blood I
don't know what it's gonna do all I know
is that it seems to be pleased by
absorbing what I got in there and I want
to deny it I say we break that thing I
say we break it I love it let's see what
you got sounds like great to be a
decision made yeah bryggen as much as
all that yeah oh I you know what I never
did
there was no recovering the the pic I
don't know where it ended up down here
huh I assume that if you walked by and
you would not leave it that's making us
okay so maybe the truck responsible um
let's see here do you guys get magic
spells I got a lot of you girls picks
you got
I think you're right like if I hit it
with a star which I'm not supposed to be
using that party really around yeah
great gonna be the worst thing to do so
let's say so let's sit on that one then
fun could be a funny plot point yeah
yeah we can progress this thing we can
yeah let's start defining the rest of
the season right now whoa sound good
don't do it all right do it
reiden work you guys are on my side yeah
tie shoes cuz there's just as much
indecision in the jar yeah that's what's
holding it as there is even going like
one do this thing no we're tried
different way first get to it my way I'm
going to do this no more Spurs on it
whoa on that wrist on the crystal I'm
gonna get up I'm gonna get up close to
it tell me tell me what you say
[Music]
the only so until you're so you're
looking up at the crystal mm-hmm and
you're seeing your own face reflected
yeah but it's it's either a couple
seconds slow or a couple seconds fast Oh
like you can see them it's not exact
exactly yeah yeah yeah there's the first
thing here mind the only young that will
be fed today are mining and then I
reveal my watch of like the belly of a
possum there's just these little baby
it's possible for all things to start
and I love that so what what's the
what's the crystal wisdom object and so
it doesn't it doesn't react in the same
way I'm just gonna determine okay what
kind of damage attacks why don't you
give me the damage that it takes all
right well it's gonna be fun that's when
5d6 oh yeah materials have their own
shit I guess I could have hexed it
beforehand but that's okay okay I'm
acting rashly so hexing a chair yeah
quick ad Thanks yeah so thirteen and
then here's one more Oh sixteen so nice
so you see your own face you see your
own face like burst because you're there
with this curiosity and cleverness and
when you speak through it cracks
immediately runs straight through it and
then it explodes Josh can you tip the
coding place no Rosie but she's not
breathing
I haven't openness might get some that
blood back yeah yeah so you're healing
you're making money
No all right
you gotta get so rich that your blood
makes blood for you exactly nine points
of damage for each party member for each
party member from shards from shards so
as it as it explodes other ones just
basically just random intervals achieve
some kind of point some some vibration
point and start hurling jagged glass
into the party thanks Josh
be nice now so but these but these
lacerations so you can you can see them
like just along along your arm on your
wrist in the back of your hand you can
see these cuts and you can see the blood
running freely out of them hitting the
ground and then joining your friends
blood as it travels and runs through
this the cavern made of crystal and on
the opposite wall to the right at about
eye level for every non rosy you can see
that it has begun to pool in each drop
that comes to it just makes it dance and
rise around this crystal rosy be stinger
yeah do we win so we got another blood
crystal blood crystal at about five feet
high yeah okay whoo well don't hit it
and everyone's not bleeding yeah please
this is probably really a pain I
actually think that rosy would would
delicately hesitantly Traverse this
quartz crystal terrain to walnut and try
to bind your wounds I know just like the
foot tip on that yeah and it's it's not
that you you can't survive nine points
of damage but just that the blood is was
that our city I say grandma
the worm showed me my own death well
your own death is about to happen
real soon no we continue this I was
buried and I was buried in a ceremony in
my Enclave I am Kate by the way he loves
this Rosie's like we could talk about
this later sweetheart thanks finding you
out doesn't I'm saying we don't die here
okay that's great I'm really happy to
hear that but the worm told me that's my
I love it
so cathuria this this worms so you have
whispered into this you have looked back
down and as I've said each angle seems
to be slightly different even though it
appears to be a physical object or a
creature yeah and it begins to travel
from its current location into the base
of that broken crystal hmm so it moves
according to some rule that it knows
there's something about this space that
it knows that you can't perceive and
like at odd right angles jagged motions
and then it moves up it's just like like
slurped up like spaghetti that is its
turn yeah yeah get dad's linguine
father's linguini
Rosie be stinger here my worm so don't
these after this first pass of shattered
crystal other crystals have begun to
behave in different ways some have begun
to leak out a crystal fluid that
solidifies and then begins to whip in
the air some have bloomed like flowers
and it began to fire something like a
pistol out of them like that like P is T
il oh it's shooting pistols like pistol
pistols shooting gun yeah it's a gun
that shoots a smaller gun on you yeah
and it is firing a it is firing one of
these chunks of crystal at you
I don't like it it's a missile attack oh
you don't say it's been a long time
since I'm inspired or miss with me
alright so I can deflect them you can't
with as a reaction I can reduce range
weapon attack damage done to me if the
day which is negated I catch it and may
throw it back that's exactly right
okay so how much damage did it do seven
points okay I can't like I can't take
advantage I'm on a 1 d 10 okay mm-hmm vd
20 hmm okay yeah that's true okay here
we go I'm trying to get ten foot seven
points now hmm it's a monk level plus so
that is a 19 right yes it's going it's
basically like lethally targeted right
right for your neck basically and just
effortlessly you pluck it okay so you
can either return the favor or you can
keep it as a cool memento I'd still have
my crossbow but no they I could
misinterpret that as someone firing at
Walnut so that is going to get thrown
right back
I'll use my dart attack okay so that's
gonna be a five points of piercing
damage okay so you throw it you throw it
right back into this crystal and mockery
of a flower and it it basically goes
right into the the center and shatters a
bunch of the ordinance that was inside
the the bulb there is another beam that
is firing out at Denar look out for that
beam right now dinar AC 18 yes okay it
is this beam this glittering beam gets
lost and refracted in your scales walnut
don't grass haha me generating like I
said so it's still the best
I look around with the party and I go
what do we do yeah really fight and we
stop bleeding stop believing let's just
run away I wish I went to NAR
all right Rosie's res go wild look much
like we gotta get out of here okay what
are we supposed to do down here yeah
it's goal who wanted it done whatever it
is the ritual is broken we're down in
here we're trying to free that that that
which endures my almost like elephants
are evil yeah but we do have to free it
if we want to do it in the right order
what about your sigil can I do anything
I don't know I'm also yeah I want to
posit the question I was Ryan like see
it so we're seeing multiple reality is
in universes you're the only two that
I've like experienced anything like that
you morning I guess I saw this thing I
didn't know what it was there's the only
one that knows what it was it's true I
just like oh yeah man I'm sorry it was
he who sold out yeah yeah that's right
hmm it was the messing up that affected
you yeah I understand what's being
presented I don't know if I have time to
pore over every facet and find the
effective one yeah
I'm saying this the last white one in
the whole place I don't to look at any
red ones anymore what is the word I know
what this is what this amethyst are
doing it but he's gone right well yeah I
slipped up in there of his own accord
yeah I made a decision and I commend it
yeah we're great work Premium this
crystal zone what work would be done
here that would free a thing what work
would be done in here that is not gonna
please the to start Fingal it breaking
some crystals yeah there is a crystal
that is the correct one and we have to
find it and break it would love to
destroy all crystals um no but so I look
at Thurston I say what are we what
should we do Rosie what should we do you
don't want to break that ones with blood
in them we know that much yeah that can
we bring we see other realities in these
other crystals maybe the reality we want
it's one where we're accomplishing our
goal right there we go bust it open a
great idea I can do
can check to see if I see anything
that's good
your servant walnut done grass is that
good now this is the portable Elderwood
Academy it's it's got dice in there yes
mom it's so it's ready to go with you
you can put a keyring right around on
the side so that's super cool and we'll
give it well give that to someone out
there so in this in this forest of
increasingly violent imagery you can see
a lysse so you are drawn to a specific
image but you know in a moment you're
part you're trying to parse all of these
different crystals and you can see a
crystal that has the party in it so
there's there's so many different
versions but you can see one that has
every member of the party upright and
alive mm-hmm over the body over a body
that you can't see because the position
is behind the party mm um so I pointed
this I say this one that's my turn nice
dinner boat simple this one is in break
password okay so what do we do with yeah
how can it I mean yeah yeah just break
it open or we kill anything it is not us
yeah I think we break it right
smash voice man yeah you know she'll
Joyce yeah
yep I'll hit it okay with the toothbrush
I know what that
yeah that's debating whether I would
like punch it or something but yeah yeah
yeah so property damage exact says but
we'd like that we'd like to find out if
anybody gets anything cool
okay I'm gonna go through the whole
alright just well it might dodge ya know
is I got a Dodge but I want to see if
somebody get some dice all right
four nice nice still it'll move yeah I
still hit it with four right oh yeah
yeah okay it's so good you distrust yeah
Pierce I do need damage though all right
sorry yeah shit woman he was great by
the master so see I can't lose right
yeah sorry ten 2d six plus three plus 10
so 10 13 23 that's quite good you thrust
your blade directly into the center of
the crystal yes this has been a very hot
adventure a hot shooting here and as you
so as the sword goes in it goes past the
rock and into something that feels like
flesh Oh yucky and when you pull the
sword out hmm
black liquid flows into the chamber
along with the sword hmm
and you can see writhing in this black
liquid hundreds of these worms your
friend and as they as they rise they
begin to coalesce into something and all
this black fluid flows together with
this the structure they've created to
make something or someone and it is
essentially imagined like it's like a
wing case like like hard
firm wings a vile
Qinghai containing and then as the wings
open and fold down you can see something
that looks like a bipedal vulture like
just like just like ragged feathers all
are just bragging for this all around
and then what happens after that is that
from inside this creature another
emerges it stands up out of it and it
could not be more distinct from its
progenitor this is something like I've
never know if I'm pronouncing it right
it's a satyr yeah I see that why and I'm
like man I could translate all kinds of
the lyrics to Disney's Hercules he says
a satyr so that's how I know yeah they
do their research yeah exactly man this
creature is winded also these are white
wings and this is I mean it looks it's
perfected in a way something like a
statue down to the curly tousled hair
sharp almost elven looking ears but
clearly not elven in stature or demeanor
and it's it's it's it looks like its
face looks like someone who is just who
has just woken up and they're looking
around the room at the crystals and at
the people who are in this room and it
doesn't know it's not sure how to parse
it if it's just sort of chewing words in
its mouth hmm
you speak do you have language just
the first sentence I have ever uttered
congratulations that's a good one it
closes its eyes and holds its hand out
yeah in the air
and then proceeds to walk out of this
chamber the way that you entered into it
what are the what's the crystals doing
not the crystals themselves are winking
out like Christmas bulbs they're like
that purple is trying to rise in
intensity and then it like dims out to
nothing and then it seems to attempt it
again and another crystal and that
crystal - loses its vigor so so he's
it's got the cool backwards legs yeah
right right hi so hot like half a
centaur yeah and so he's making his he's
making his way and like I say every now
and then he has to support himself on
the cavern walls it takes a moment to
examine his own form you know its
follow-up yeah I yelled to him and
celestial cuz I speak selection it's
very quick with the reindeer I'm just
like who are you okay so you hear you
hear Denard
singing in like against the against like
the rock of this of these tunnels as
we're going up Wow
it's you've given all of a sudden and
then it and then the entity responds
we're in the same almost like harmonic
tone is he says I am that which endures
and I have endured long
it reaches over it's walking up the
stairs that you've made and then you can
even you're coming up behind it you can
see that it walks up out of this
out of this place out of this low place
and as it walks up out of the stairs it
simply takes its next step into the air
mm-hmm and then it looks and then it is
just taking all of this in clearly still
light would like a baby like just trying
to understand the stimuli and then it
sees this massive army this loves loud
clamorous noise and just out of
curiosity perhaps goes toward it and you
can see you can see Carver gall just
exultant his arms up in the air and he
is greeting that which endorsed in some
guttural deep tongue and what happy for
ya and he says he says and then he
switches back to a language that is more
generally understood and he says it is I
Carver gall I have served you well I
know that you have suffered long in your
imprisonment and in your torment and
because I am a great servant I have
brought you this feast and he holds his
hand back at his armies and tasteful
looks over at him and understands it oh
he understands it and like a bullet this
new entity beautiful been emerging from
this terrible place launches over and
then as it as it as it it basically
becomes a line and then becomes whole
again and then as he moves over he way
he makes his arms wide and just engulfs
them
and they immediately begin to hit the
ground so you're now out of the tunnel
you're seeing this occur on the beach
you can see that they have that this
throng has hit the ground like they are
tearing it themselves in some kind of
anguish or agony and Carver gall is just
exalting he looks like he's been hit by
lightning like he's just laughing
against the against because this is the
this is in the upper dark so against the
low wall against the low ceiling there's
just this this sound that punctuate sit
and then you the shrieking and screaming
stops and Gaal says and says it now you
know my reward where is my reward and
that which endures looks at Carver gall
and tilts his head completely without
comprehension and then leaves and one by
one
the army that was behind Carver Gaul has
begun to rise up off of the ground and
it recalls something like the potion
that you took they are they are not what
they were this army is no longer a
rabble of hobgoblins and goblins in fact
you don't know if there is a category
for what they've become they're tall six
to seven feet like an elf against the
radiant lake you can see that their skin
clearly has a green hue green like a
chlorophyll type color and they are
helping each other up and they are
speaking to each other with care and
concern
and there others there's no cruelty
there's no savagery in their behavior
and you can see tasteful look out toward
the party and his body has completely
changed it's green he is tall the ears
are sharp and this is his this is his
true form that he has discovered here
Carver Gaul cannot make sense of this at
all he does not know where his reward
could be and you can see him reaching
into his belt for a sacrificial knife uh
does he look is he looking at tasty oh
absolutely
anybody anybody close to him looks like
they would probably do oh okay
how close are we to curve ago probably
40 feet if he's looking at my ward I'm
gonna wild shape nice and deal with it
into a bear and just get between him in
and tasty okay yeah I know we're just
any of these creatures yeah like these
gorgeous beings yeah yeah like I say
they're speaking to each other in soft
voices there's clearly a lot of
confusion yeah but you you don't you
don't know what you have just witnessed
no yeah I see violence and I see
innocent people so and when I hear I'm
talking about rewards I go like well you
know technically I'm the one who let him
you don't want to let him out I mean if
anyone's gonna get a reward I said you
could there's all kinds of shadows in
the Underdark okay so it's 60 feet
okay so you've broken into a bear run
you are splashing you are the splashing
through these shallows bounding toward
him you are warping from tiny dark place
to
tiny dark place first route
oh are you absorbing yeah but I mean I
will no I'm not gonna misty step up to
where everybody is but I'm going to call
out to Gaul I would what purpose would
that serve the knife what purpose is
served by this your God is free it's the
tip of it it's a like a has long blood
channels along it it's clearly a device
that has seen much use and the tip of it
shaking in his hand you think you may
have him on the edge of something here
yeah if there's a wake like because I
wouldn't be able to contain it to convey
like I want what you just received I
want to know that my god has been freed
you have done this
rejoice gosh
the reward is in front of you I start
laughing at how ridiculous it is like
this is incredible we witnessed what
we've seen imagine what could be written
of this what could be studied of it it's
never been seen before the knife falls
out of his hand and clatters against the
stone floor and Carver gall drew it of
that which indoors collapses to his
knees in tears shadow council huh
mayor livers please dad was definitely
of the first part of the season I hope
you've enjoyed it we're gonna come back
here real quick for a bike sighs a
budget Table Talk
but I wanted to make sure that we got
through the main beats of that so that
we can start the second season we're
gonna be back on full-time for your
viewing pleasure on April 25th but in
the intervening period we've got all
kinds of cool c-team shit for you
including a podcast that we're going to
record tonight talking about the first
part of the season don't go nowhere look
back inside
you