time is the enemy of the past it
threatens the fastest weapon you
wouldn't make it past a second as the
question
play it brash and reckless to choose a
cautious solution Esau was prudent in
any sepulcher poker to don't become the
putrid it's that well said I pursue in
no mountain too steep for dungeon too
deep to send expendable marks up to the
top of the peak of beneath they see Yugi
they come like sharks to it while I swim
in that money build like Carl Barks
through it so send your National Parks
drew it I'll send him home in a natural
box with a close tie the most of the
parts included save your breath for a
cleric confessor death is a lesson that
life is attending professor but if
you're seeking my official advice sign
on the dotted line English of the choice
hello
I'm Tycho Brahe hey penny arcade and pax
children get your shit under control I
was being good teacher
as usual left side of tables got their
shit together get this new kid you got
something there's new kid came in listen
oh I'm Tycho Brahe hey of Penny Arcade
impacts I am also a mini face Hereward
run CEO of acquisitions incorporated but
today I'm Jerry Hawkins I'm gonna run a
game of Dungeons &amp; Dragons for my
friends to my right
Dragonborn narcissism yo dinar blitz in
[Applause]
ya - the hell wrong riot of my right the
sorcerer supreme strips now to the right
of my right of my right repping the
natural world walnut dawn grass
that's right now to my left
yeah but exactly this is very upset yeah
any trouble to my left not your
grandma's grandma except for those rare
cases and in which she is your grandma's
grandma Rosie bee stinger are these
signals is this but something's gonna
happen like try to get under the table
to the left of my left emerging as
though from a mist shroud yeah you you
pull the hands away right away yeah
you're a being polite through all that
does all had horrible meaning should
have warned you ahead of time that these
creatures that I have you know I've
introduced you to and put you very very
near yes our strange beasts and they the
excrete thing yeah oh yeah yeah oh yeah
all the time
we already told her the show is
extremely horny so well I took an
opportunity there to add you thing I
know that there's I know that there are
enthusiasts yeah and there's no
representation on the show so let's get
to it yeah yeah get the ball rolling for
us friends six boxes come around six
boxes no but they're like boxes but
they're like their leg or bipedal no no
no they're like the football it's like
the captain of the football team at an
all fox high school yeah yeah he was
attractive to everyone huh yeah woman
okay we're gonna roll back in now I'll
talk is gonna be a lot of iffen just
keep that in mind
Hey so when last we saw our heroes they
had taken a delightful tour
around the cloaker city of wrangler
north where our own rosey beast and you
learned something very unique about the
staff of the master that is to say it is
not 100% a staff in the classic sense it
is in fact a coherent lozenge-shaped
shadow and she learned this because she
made a special friend at the end of a
bridge where one often finds good
friends sighs II Selmer a sort of shadow
enthusiast for lack of a better term
yeah you were able to bond over a shared
interest in the plane of shadow some
overlap there you were able to ride the
state capital portion of wrangler north
around an incredible underground lake
imagine a dark Disneyland ride and
that's more or less the scenario you
traveled through multiple districts
eventually coming to land at the sort of
district where the shadow weavers hold
sway now obviously what you learned from
scythe is that their society has broken
up into these casts but there's
representation for each cast in each of
these but in each of the four districts
one of the casts hold sway we did not
explore the eastern district that is aa
great we're looking at all these
districts but when do we get to
districts actually did and when things
had wrapped up at the end very near the
ends my cauldron tipped obviously shadow
council merrily was pleased you you were
able to secure on some kind of strange
mission a variety of odd not wholly
euclidean toys for the youth three of
them three of them scammed oh yeah
absolute
absolutely he seems to think that the
entire surface world all the towns he
knows about or right by each other he's
got some misconceptions just
geographically generally speaking but as
the game was wrapping to a close sales
in the shadow Weaver district of
Wrangler North had started to be what
started to filter out a bit and it was
becoming much quieter in this place but
as I suggested before there's a lot of
strange strange business that takes
place inside this this realm walnut on
grass yes of the enclave pax anima you
hear ask richest Grich mm-hmm
inside your level to document see
satchel okay I mean litter oh that's
that's a very reasonable assumption I
mean I I don't know I mean I'm I'm
experiencing all of this with you I see
I'm curious about what's in there as
well
well so I open it up and I take a look
let's let's gaze there together yeah oh
yeah it's marvelous at the top in in the
secretary ins fine hand you recognize it
instinctively having seen it many times
prior it says that the requested help is
now imminent omen has authorized the the
use of an incredibly powerful sorceress
a term he persists in using though I
have told him many many times sorcerer
is appropriate for men and women so look
at this I'm just thinking it's amazing
it continues down I think it's just like
it's like you know as a sorcerer of some
renown a creature originally
of the inter planar hub of sigil her
powers are considerable and it is our
belief that even a momentary application
of her mystic prowess will resolve any
problems that you are having in the
Underdark and allow a quick return to
the surface okay well not knows what
half of those words mean but she looks a
letter and she looks everybody else and
she goes she goes Oh head office is
sending us an expert and it seems like
their qualifications are just off the
charts amazing perhaps the most powerful
magic user we've ever seen I like it
there's like maybe there's something for
you to learn here this is incredible I
can't wait woman finally pulled through
there's a note there is a note that is
additionally written below this that
says it should be it should be
established that she is roughly on par
in terms of mystic power with that of
James dark magic which you are which I
believe the party is familiar where I go
and get this she's better than Jim done
his power but not him as you're reading
this you look up and you notice that by
and large the populace has begun to sort
of filter out and go their ways you know
either
cloakers leaving their sort of helm
shaped roost shops and slithering inside
the cracks of the central area the whole
place is sort of ringing with that hum
but there are groups of what appear to
be drow soldiers tarrying much longer
than other groups
and they appear to be looking around in
a suspicious way looking over the people
and groups as they leave and they're
very very intent that you can tell they
are
they are assessing the situation with
with profundity you begin to hear
another sound almost at a almost
orthogonal to the rest of the hum that
you know from your friend Rosie
maintains the shadow stuff it's a song
that the cloakers sing that scythe has
learned and this new sound is to serve
it like a low wail like like a prisoner
at the bottom of the well and you know
it's very close so you're not a whale oh
yeah something brushes against your leg
okay
it sort of skitters out from between
some crates and you can see this
faceless creature sort of looking
sightless Lee around the dark cavern
only a mouth stretched open wide on its
face it says it climbs out rushes past
your boot leaving some trail of
something along the right edge skitters
out damn near the center of this
thoroughfare and at the sound of this
horrid wailing this growl contingent
begins to swivel their heads toward it
with something like interest in
something like terror sure looking over
across at another one of these Helms you
can see another sort of stretched
faceless creature mount to the top of
the helm and then look down and see what
maybe it's only friend in the world and
it says
[Music]
and it skitters down the face flops down
on its back rolls over closets way back
out to the front and the two of them
begin to dig furiously into the shadow
stuff that makes up the bridge hands
pull their way out of the tinier end
that they have made two more of these
creatures begin to only late at one
another and then it is at this point
that you see the tip of a hat emerge and
you see a creature that you think might
be a person but you would have to get
closer it could be an ambulatory pile of
trash like a shambling mound it sound
like that maybe a tailor is maybe an
elemental made from tailor scraps you
can see basically sort of pushed from
this little rend that they have managed
to make in the physical properties of
the shadow plane oily black smoke
accompanies her into this place and as
soon as the work is done
the creature seemed terrified by what
they've accomplished then they begin to
skitter away leaping on top of Helm's
jumping out crawling around trying to
get into cracks cloakers don't want them
but you can see like a cloak ER but like
in like a dentists check it with a
stethoscope mmm but inside the flask is
Strix and this this entity that you see
now just laying before you flat in the
middle of this rapidly emptying scene
but 100% definitely attracting the
attention of this contingent of trou
priestesses and soldiers over here fine
Chris would be better at knowing
exact like ranks and Peschel ons of
these people they're Ravens you decide
how many are they 5.6 this person is
their clothes are slick with blood oh no
like this this person has arrived
this person has arrived very near you in
more or less just a pile of bones and
shredded robes well I thought it was our
sorcerer everybody just laughter do we
also we don't immediately our problem is
the drought that are paying attention
right like we don't want the attention
of these drow no for blood can I try it
sighs anywhere near me yes I was
watching all this with some interest
okay I'm gonna try something which is
just pulling the old lady Bluff card
just like oh no that shadow experiment
didn't go well at all I'm so we'll try
this one again let's clean this mess up
don't worry about this I'm still hurting
I'm new there there is a woman was just
frost white hair who with a sort of
headdress that goes back silver legs
meeting in front of her face
looks over it's all that's required is
that she look and it in an instant her
retinue has formed some kind of a
protective barrier in front of her like
all that was required was that she think
for a second about what she wanted them
to do and it was done in an instant so
you are ear moving out yeah I'm just
gonna try to like protectively collect
this pile of trash and just to just to
get the drowse attention away from us
just to be like ah this wackadoo old
lady doesn't
control the shadow so she is she is in
absolutely miserable she okay but have
the drow stop pay attention but right
right now they are maintaining what they
see is a defensive position against
whatever sir shenanigan yeah has been
maintained here okay so this is clearly
an organic creature that is losing its
life matter yes quickly okay hey can
anyone do anything about that
can I look at this this commander yes am
I able to identified the priestess yeah
it is it somebody that I might identify
other than that she's a priestess no you
don't there's nothing particular about
it okay okay I'm just familiar with it
that's what she is
yeah oh yeah their raiment and and the
Raymond and literally every micro action
of her retinue communicate that she
exists at a pretty robust point in this
hierarchy I'll go to the pile of meat
and cloth you can see like the bugs have
just started to leave her there
abandoning spiders and like a couple of
some snails too and they're just like
they're like op time to leave are you
okay she's she's yeah I don't think
she's okay she's okay alright I guess
yeah okay I'm like trying to rifle
around and there to find a pulse
well the merciful thing to do my swords
your rifling around your finding like
jars of tongues yeah absolutely
just like random piece like blades that
don't have any hilts hilts for no reason
that's yep no pulse though well just get
digging the way it was summoned was
creepy and gross so no reason to think
this is on our side but
also should probably heal it enough to
get an answer
yeah what would your God want you to do
I would lay on hands like just a couple
HP's you like get a straight stop
coughing blood and give me an answer
okay but not like strong enough to
attack me you guys Leon yeah yeah yeah
yeah like that I don't know you look
like you're in dire straits yeah so like
three oh great thanks hey there's more
where that came from they tell me what I
want to hear first three is free he
wakes up at you this like looks around
immediately grabs your face and just
vomits on you all right are you here to
save us
oh no oh no oh no was it oh no
do you know an omen yes personally grabs
your hand it's just like she's like yes
I know omen I know I know I'm very well
so well
do you recognize each other from the
gift giving thing is that in the Canon
Canon no is it in Canon is that an else
world is that it is in Canada okay
all right in Canon you guys already know
all right okay well it's dark you're
freaking out imagine a dark Christmas
right we just say once you've been
hailed and then your form then we
recognize that form yeah yeah right so
then she feelings hurting monster um so
you wouldn't happen to be this great
sorcerer from Sid Jill would you yeah I
mean I great is not a word that I
usually hear so maybe
well head office said that they sent us
an astounding sorcerer that's going to
help us with all of our problems over at
the great like cheese great what they
make this ones are drow no wait now you
guys all rushed in to the center of the
drow circle right I did not rush in
I've been Ohio today behind good that's
Frank smart and I had to get these these
drow out of here so I am going to you'll
see no strict surround you the the
ground begins to stretch a trace out
around you and little dust is rising and
it is the symbol of loss hello I'm the
DM you roll and then okay from the from
where I was standing just behind behind
behind the group right I throw it back
my hood that I might cover and I now
appear to be a much darker drow woman oh
and my voice didn't change so you can
tell but on how I approached and I say a
blessing of a blessing from our great
and incredible evil Spider Queen I love
it
this one I have conjured for my use
stand aside
I will take this ones leave of me for me
I'm trying to speak like a very like
under common yeah the most the most
highbrow
Virgil necktie no no Salvatore you can
yeah exactly
you're pranking the art of the a double
art yeah yeah so at this truth that
authentically bizarre suggestion of you
know describing the events that had just
occurred this sort of phalanx continues
to move forward toward the party and the
priestess just walks at a leisurely pace
behind this protective sphere but not
addressing not addressing no just
looking upon you with some curiosity she
says sister I see no raiment of the
priesthood upon you I called to our
sweet delicious arachnid goddess that we
all love very much very fond of and I I
made the request of her that she bring
this thief back to me for my personal
brand of demented justice that all
drought practice just as you and I do
regular old rau and I see that my prayer
was answered what did you do with my
things
I'm very of course cross with you she's
just Kenny when they're bow though and
she drops a fireball right there yeah
initiative careful spell so it won't
it won't hit you guys but it'll hit okay
oh hey that's also gonna be a that's
gonna be a fifth level spy oh I know
okay I know I know you get down yeah all
right now what are these numbers I got
here yes
five yeah so 606 as well
twenty dinars the caboose cheese
eighteen here got a seventy I couldn't
wait to get that ball get that ball
having a ball 40 damage so him and the
drow behind him
yeah so every drought here out here
you're saying that you're offering a
attempting fall bargain of fire damage
for all drought that you can see and not
the people who were around you from
acquisitions in court yes okay
I'm sorry sister the brain would you
make any sort of saving through with
this all right you guys saving throw
bonus from me but unless of course I see
your pet do I see your pet Ola gaudy
yeah do I see you ligadinho would
recognize you
you I'll shoot here's the thing if I'm
killing no no it's okay as part of my
disguise I would hide the body
oh no yeah yeah there's no way you're
gonna bring a crystal snake ROG blade
person's no way it's like don't mind
this I'm having I'm gonna explain the
rest of their me yeah exactly
no so but there is such a thing as spell
DC yes say yeah so you do you can't take
half of that damage if you save against
you I save against Constitution against
my spell save DC you 16
you get me wrong you get our protection
from me because we're close
yeah friends like emotionally yeah which
is my charisma equal to my charisma
modifier and I'm charisma charisma Chris
Kodachrome prismatic spry 9 yeah that's
three but what does it mean three give
measures three to my decent oh that's my
savings here plus three if you roll the
dice D 20 and just add three yeah and
then if you get better than 16 you take
half damage advantage yeah let's take
advantage and this way that's what it's
for I mean yeah okay okay so that's
pretty solid pads 15
I remember you're adding three okay 19
okay take my Oregon damn ticket here I
took this order for a reason
well that's a sizzler believe you me I
feel that all right
things were going south and she just
wanted to solve this problem and she
figures a quicker she solves it but more
likely since she gets to believe and
hopefully not find her pretty dead
accurate yeah please here I'm doing to
do a lot of math back here yeah I'm
sorry no no it's it's all it's all to
the G that's the first fireball that's
ever been on this show you see you start
you started shit off right over here
okay so that is the that is the scenario
so this so you were able to find some
pocket here in this heat shimmer and
this just just concussive wave of heat
and fire just hits right on the front
and that wave just bursts out beyond you
everyone else in the party the the
members of acquisitions incorporated
specifically team C with a license to
the desperate valley somehow exclusive
ice and somehow well the wild card is a
real thing
somehow these flames just ignore you you
can see them shaped in real time via
some mathematics you can't comprehend
you are not in you are not in this ball
of fire oh no he's easily targeted our
scream they scare do that does dinner
scream is he scared of fire
yeah yes I just don't like sir Gregory
cool game sorry Stan Sandra clicking the
one who's care what is your character a
reference to is already Joffrey what a
job well you know it would catch us all
off guard right I would be like I should
not have healed her that one's on me
guys that's my she's rash for the note
not here to help
oh yeah absolutely now we are an
initiative order so this has occurred
this blast of heat so all the targets
that you endeavour to incinerate are
still standing in various levels well
yeah exactly
it's like in the same way that it's like
the way that you might order your meat
at a restaurant it's like you can just
sort of tell from the target okay that's
medium well that's you're seeing a range
of cooking styles available we're not
here next up is Kath risk drab I so I've
turned from the blast and I'm charging
and I'm and I'm physically like shaking
from that wave of it oh yeah I mean you
have never like this is a level of
outside of the sanguine lift itself
outside of the god of meat and mouths
this is a level of this is a level of
mystic power that you have never had
trained on you I feisty one I love it
[Laughter]
yeah I have to I don't want these drow I
don't know actually I imagine I mean
I've done it before
yeah yeah the other card I don't have
that card now okay but I put on a show
like shoulders off haha but I want my
and I I want to use awakened mind to
speak with you like I'm hearing voices
again she doesn't deserve to live
anymore
but stealing that the clothes I love and
for the madness within forgive me so I'm
like I say he loved I'm trying to decide
if you're play dead
and I conjure the glow man but the
dancing lights just as a light yeah I am
and I throw it with like just toss it
off this this magic toward her that I
try to flavour to look like it's some
sort of damaging spell and it hits you
do anything just hits me I'll do my best
I mean I don't know what's going on
anymore here I'm hearing voices I'm just
like is it my time just fall over and
I'm like maybe if I die here and she's
still kind of talking so the ball goes
out and then glow man in his finest
performance it's sort of like it forms
the figure of the glow man to your
proportions and then shakes to sort of
give the impression that you are being
electrocuted okay
[Music]
yes rosy bee stinger how can you top
that performance I would like to I I
think this yes attacked would be very
upsetting and I don't know very much
about this pile of garbage but I do know
that Christmas is is clearly damaged
because hurting so he's a grand man see
I think it's time it's been a while so I
think the thing that Rosie would do
would react rashly and that would be to
as as she's she's still trying to play
up that this pile of garbage was her own
fault
yeah and so it just gives strix a panic
attack for different ways and we're not
coordinated okay so after that after
this happens she's like haha
I'm new and she all of this goes on in
like a second and then boom it's grandma
man see and shadows and are coming out
to look like the little critters that
dug holes but they're there they're
assembling in a variety of places all
over to draw the attention of the
drought yet again as though they're
about to open more rifts and drag really
this is very cool I think that that is
really great so they are so as this is
happening like in the first couple
pockets a few more pockets your if
you're finding ways to sort of draw them
in from offstage right we've always been
there it's just this is their time right
and you hear sighs next to you just
chuckle yeah so they're other and
they're all just chewing and scraping at
the ground and they're making sounds
like oh yeah so three or four three or
four discrete regions and so basically
in mechanic's terms it's it's sort of
drawn the attention of different ones to
different groups
so this is this is obviously something
they can't tolerate at this that this
four threshold is too much size says the
moment you think this isn't going your
way please let me know
will do walnut unrest yeah I am go up
two strikes and I'm the worst actress
known to man it's just really important
that you know that and I kneel down and
I like hover hand touch her like not
even not even touching he'll have her
hand and go oh my god she's dead
I want to do that I got healing work
looking at you and blinking take 10 HP
oh yeah that's real teen HP she's mine
she's dead yeah she's my god she's I am
from the city of doors can I see if any
of these drower bloodied we're really
bad oh absolutely as I suggested okay
there are two you would describe as
greedy medium will buy my one of them
probably oh yeah okay great so they're
pretty crispy yeah yeah but about half
of them are in a deeply fucked place
okay and I'm pretending that I've heard
two different I've seen like two
different executions of plans at this
video and I'm just watching this app and
like what is happening like so so this
person is not this person there's
shadows coming around I don't know what
I'm like look I'm getting healed and my
god she's dead I don't know what it's
very complicated and I'm so overwhelmed
and just so emotionally distraught that
I just throw another fireball in the
drone from the ground just like
let's see a regular firewall no not a
fifth level fireball and I do X careful
spell you this time because you talked
to me and I'm like oh yeah I gave him a
present
what's careful oh it's so cool how does
it work yeah would you would you'd like
to tell yeah wrist wrap about about
careful sorcerers have but she's saying
this in her mind as she's casting and
she's like so sorry turns out this thing
where anything you can catch the spell
and it's like super strong but it took I
was around everyone and it's like super
magic cuz I know magic excited about it
[Laughter]
26 math I count on my fingers at 86 yes
I did transfer yeah this is no this is
not fuck around times yeah 26 you said
yes yeah and your your spell same DC is
meanest shit mmm-hmm
and as she does that she's kind of just
like sure I'm trying to intimidate them
and just be like please leave please
stay please my god she's so dead come to
life
yeah uh-oh from the dead she rises
[Laughter]
alright
two of them two of them are now no
longer a part of the fight at all one of
them was just blasted back over a
workbench and you can see that like that
as the flames on him they catch the
shadow stuff of the market on fire but
it just rests inside the flame it
doesn't appear to be consumed in any way
it just burns in a quiet way and the
other one is wildly batting his robes
and falls off the side of the bridge
down into the water below you
do a Wilhelm scream oh absolutely yeah
license but it does it does occur it
sounds just like the Wilhelm scream can
I roll for an intimidation track all
these guys at home look I would love to
see what that looked like
please leave yes oh no I mean I get it
+8 but I only attack all right
there's been a lot of a lot of heat and
a lot of fire and I think that's the
that's the big thing they're hanging
about right now Denard Blitzen so how
many are left there are three left very
less the priestess and the priests
Loretta knew okay aren't they assessing
the situation are they looking at us at
all I mean we didn't do anything
none of us did anything other than her
so it's like are they even consider are
they are they battle ready well what you
have are they ready to rumble or they
like this thing just appeared and start
shooting fireballs at us well you have
been I mean you have you have ridden
many many hours
certainly before Rosie learned her
cartography spell their ritual you have
spent a long time in the back of a cart
with Catherine robe and your impression
is that the level of nuance you're
describing where are these people in
this group of people that you all see at
the same time getting down into the
granular aspects of who did exactly what
is something that happens after everyone
is dead okay all right so but I like
there there oh no thank and a rumble no
absolutely yeah and this is this is I
mean you are you're seeing aspects of a
martial tradition that are complete my
new sword positions okay shield
positions so this is a ground tactics
this is a shitshow unlike every
potential possible level where and
Dennard is the one that's like rational
in all this I love this a little irony
in all this so all right everyone's
going crazy so everyone's just gotta
cool out everybody cool out so if
there's a boss and they've got
subordinates then I'm gonna dominate the
boss yeah
you know entitled yeah kaminju conic
entitlement yeah yeah the priestess
I'll also decrement my by one because I
used advantage I did I have four got
more yeah here
so tell me thank you um tell me what you
what do you communicate to your new best
friend uh well so I establish a a
psychic link she has to do everything I
say I don't have to verbally say
anything this all can just happen in my
head we are now super best friends um I
would tell her to cool out cool out I
would say be cool are you talking to me
yeah no no I say verbally to you to be
cool I yell everybody cool out to the
group and then I tell her psychically to
tell her people to stand down uh I got
him this last for a minute okay not
literally a minute right yeah no II take
up to a minute
no duration of the minute No ten minutes
yeah I got ten minutes with her yeah
clean clean so she's locked up so I just
want to stop the fight
cuz it's crazy I don't know what the
hell's going on shut up spiders and
fireballs and your don't look like
yourself fighter let's go I'm confused
yeah this is like a Bugs Bunny dressed
as a girl barely so let's stop she the
priestess hisses at her retinue you
think that their words
yeah but the overall effect is is just
of like two pieces of stone in an
ancient trap sliding against each other
one of them appears to not wasn't want
to listen mmm
and as he starts forward she has just on
him like on him right from behind as
he's moving forward she reaches a foot
forward and just rips him pushes him
face down close out a ritual dagger yeah
and pins into the ground with
Oh boyfriend yeah just keeping Isaac I
solved everything it's getting worse and
worse and he you can see him sort of
like reaching in to this gaping wound he
rolls over on his back and you can see
that he's trying to hold something up
weakly and he can't he can't maintain
the strength it is his hand his
collapses on his chest it's a wedding
ring I love you priestess yes dude I
will she killed her fiance Table Talk
I will talk about my eyebrow
character that I had in high school and
it's gonna it's gonna get pretty real I
can't wait you can you really must yeah
actually all right
I'm you know keep going the way when do
I stop getting to do stuff well no I
mean you if you use deescalate accompany
answer exactly yeah yeah I mean right
now she has she appears to have this
mechanism completely under control
save the day again guys the decision is
to acted unilaterally and fixed
everything
stop shooting fireballs oh no no no
we're best friends for 10 minutes yeah
can I gather Strix into like like come
with me and we go can we go into the
shop we're live in the cloak just yeah
just hide in one of these yeah oh she
likes that instead you're just like
Grandma there along yeah it's just yeah
who's there oh no nobody so so she is
her her arm is around you oh gentle
soften you're obviously much taller than
she is huh but you got that hunch yeah
she she grandma's you in as a verb okay
right into the helm and inside there
hanging from the ceiling is what you
know to be an incredibly powerful
monster uh-huh called a cloak ER and as
you come into this
[Music]
you'll be safe I do I say they're cool
it's fine okay I know I know I know they
look they look see there's cries into
your shoulders our party's almost
[Music]
suckers jabbering at you and at scythe
yeah and syv is trying to respond yeah
exactly so they're now they're doing it
back and forth yeah
can I tentatively reach up to give the
poker a little scratch because he just
shakes like this and then you see him
you see him well he does is so he's
hanging upside down and he's looking at
you and then at a certain point he just
kind of claws around the other way well
I sure you into the corner I take off my
shawl turn around she's like rubbing it
on her face is getting dirty that's fine
it's not great it's not a great
condition I've never washed it all right
so hopefully you guys have followed me
in no I think I'm gonna stay out with
the priestess and cuz I don't know drow
stuff so I'm gonna need you to help me
exactly hey Josh can you tip my cauldron
please what maybe your back the the
ledger yes begins to jump oh no
inside the bag like it wants to get out
I grab it and open it you open it up yes
and in almond ron's handwriting's which
of course you know it says what did you
do oh no oh no I write in it I say we
have before you have even finished it
says what did you do right I sent you
one of the most powerful sorcerers on
Faron
[Music]
he's not mad he's just straight up
she writes um she writes we have
received Strix the sorcerer she is of
great help and then and then she says
she says any further orders how are you
that's not what I heard really really
tiny like so impossible small what did
you hear that's the bet the very last
thing mm-hmm
it says it's possible to lose document
sea levels the page tears itself outward
Oh
crumples itself up and throws itself
away thanks Josh oh man um so at this
you see walnut looks and goes that's
interesting and she like this and then
just kind of like walks off a new
direction and then you hear just like a
really gross noise you can't really tell
them it is it kind of sound like
somebody like heavey when you close the
ledger like a sandwich for like ten
minutes and we've already got two party
members crying she's cursed so um your
new best friend so it's it's me and her
yeah and one still living guard Illidan
gargoyle and you very confused about
what's happening yeah but he there has
been sort of an object lesson and why
you do what she says Yeah right on the
ground
yeah and she says obviously I know why
you're here and what you're doing here
and I know that it is for a little
yeah but there are those of my order who
may not appreciate the new ones now and
there is every reason to believe that
they may be coming here shortly
oh well that's good info that's good
because you like love we can don't like
others that don't like we don't have to
lie ok 10 minutes we're doing we could
drop the facade for 10 minutes I don't I
don't think it's a sign yeah I don't
believe you if you say that to me I do
dinar says it today I know we've got 10
minutes you can't risk that
all right so but I'm confused
yes I didn't hire you for your brain
you're a very foolish boy but larger
muscles telepathically like get her to
like flex on you priestess thank you for
your thank you for your assistance in
your and your warning go with with loss
and may each of her eight legs and
circle you in that comforting embrace
and made her spinnerets mid rambling and
then pull you aside and I go we've got
like eight more minutes and I don't what
she's gonna do when this wears off can
you make her forget the whole thing
you make her forget this whole thing I
don't know maybe she just stabbed her
well she can't fight back I don't know
what she the Israel does can you tell
her to drown herself in this guy let's
get that man we could try is that what
we should do I don't know what what her
station is I don't know oh I know get
her to give us those those priestess
robes and I could wear those and look
more official and then then drown her
you can find another way to do without
no I'm that's fine and you make her
forget all language so that she didn't
do anything
no yes dummy actually help men in black
powerful is dominate person dumb good
and read it but dominates pretty power
handles yeah we did my chose that on
purpose it's pretty sick
just creature just it just has to obey
everything it has to obey everything I
say but when it wears off it's done yeah
so I don't know if I can
walks everyone back your what is it your
alignment doesn't I don't remember what
it was something about your actions
should dictate your alignment not your
alignment dictate your actions right yes
well sometimes right this is come up
before where I have to go I'm the moral
compass I don't want to tell someone to
kill themselves and their subordinate if
I can avoid it
I'm looking for some insight here buddy
okay here's what we're gonna do you get
oh he's he's wisss hit her soldier that
remains with her is whispering to her
very intently and then she shows me she
look she is just looking at him
imperious lee what's he saying just I
tell her to tell me what I'll say
he says that he says that I've lost my
mind was he no no
yeah um you're gonna take that guard
yeah I asked her are you gonna take that
from a subordinate tell her this he
stole your clothes make her give me her
clothes and then she'll be there look
I've been really useful she can take
anything like super Burt mine are I'm
not getting they're mine that's true
here's mine hers
probably not in great shape but it's
better than no better than my rags all
right happy medium both of you get naked
absolutely switch-case John in a
moment's notice ready for this you know
first you get naked does it get to nails
and you're like look you didn't even
tell me yet and I've done it okay sorry
I'm gonna go along with the clothes
switching let's say that happens right
then and there
okay so in front of this soldier just
for her part there's no there's not a
moment's hesitation like there's none of
the none of the strictures that would
apply yeah like it just like it happens
basically in an instant and the soldier
immediately turns away and sort of
boughs his head polite guy okay
so all right so I'm gonna I'm gonna put
her investments on if mine are any in
any good shape I send the cloak is okay
I'm gonna assume you're gonna keep the
special stuff like yeah shadows on
Domino just wear it beneath I just want
to smell like burning but now I have a
good story so I don't so I'm wearing her
vestments mm-hmm have her put his
clothes on get this guard to destroy
your clothes on no I don't want to give
him his clothes like still crying like
he's naked and just explain to somebody
like how like how to make change in a
way such that the other person who gets
back yeah like just a bill rather than
coins I take her clothes I give you a
2001 you give me a five yes his clothes
come on he gets one boot I think that he
is responsible for all this just stack
them up and put a big trench coat on
them let's go I want to come back over
to them and be all business yes there
were more professional all right well
back to my half-naked drought here in
the confuse soldier this is great
perfect it's perfect I come over I look
at them I look at her and I just start
tying them up with rope no actually like
cut off parts of my rope so that we can
just leave them tied up
grandma's rope grandma's right actually
can we can we get shadow guy can you ask
shadow guy dad sighs watch them or
something yeah I'm not gonna ask him to
do that get him mixed up in all this no
look they're gonna get out and they're
gonna chase us this has happened the
last time I use this it's true what can
I get both of them tied up absolutely so
I get both of them tied up and then I
tie them back to back to each other
and then I just look at them and I go
tada and then I get out a foreman I
start documenting exactly what's so he
so he basically tied back to back yes
Aniela Street yeah yeah yeah in the
middle of this what did this sort of
arch it's like a sort of like a
european-style like bridge yeah market
your bonds out to change of clothes in
the middle of street - yeah this is
super super French so you see the
soldier sort of like reaching down into
a pocket in his cloak and he bites
something and pulls it out and you see
that it's like a it's like a ruby on a
thread mm-hmm
and as it catches the lights around here
you can see that it is sort of casting
red light up on the ceiling smacking
that different points it good it just
goes to - okay down into the water I
want to get down in space and be like
buddy I'm doing everything I can not to
kill you
thank you you're great it's gonna happen
you're forcing me here buddy um did I
see that thing roll away into the water
oh yeah totally so time to do some crash
don't get any tracks game we're fucking
up no I
rabbit out of the water yeah bring some
trash okay what is it it's down that's
down there a bit so it's basically like
it's anytime you want to you can have
laser Zeppelin nice you know what I mean
I think it's the back for more than yeah
it's like a fling so defensive it's a
defensive flare got it like a signal
basically hitches an amplifier slight
okay all right I take that well that's
not magic why are you guys here I just
yelled up at home Wyatt what do you want
why are you here why are you fighting
growl oh we weren't fighting growl until
you arrived
she's like big chase like it's like that
that blinking guy I like it yeah but
there were drow yeah that is true do you
want to explain they were armed
well York alright I assume you're gonna
exposition here for a second but I want
to try to strip whatever drow raiments
are left on these corpses to make our
disguise plan more because now we can be
the retinue for our process yeah yeah go
ahead
oh yes good idea uh we're here I took
from my my book no she's like staring
white I was like it was like blinking
really well like please tell me we're
here where we are here because we've
been sent on a mission of discovery
it took my former hometown whoops in the
Underdark which I don't like either okay
to find evidence of the best and truest
patron of the mall the one that I I like
mmm some barmy power you worship yeah
[Laughter]
it's the best one I'm used to hearing
that but mine is really the best one
that's the kiss risk difference she's
like well so we need disguises yes
so fireball might not have been the best
idea no but you know what we didn't
communicate that to you I don't I was
dying how exactly I don't I don't blame
you for any of it okay thank you you
made me that that big going to do this
goal and I'm just sorry I didn't
recognize you when you were a lady
[Laughter]
basket lady that's a good lady just are
you snot a lady anymore you're a pretty
girl I'm gonna hang on to this as long
as I can okay you know I'm still a lady
just right now so when you talk about
disguises on my alright I'm saying here
to help I have to I'm just gonna prime
you guys real quick but I have to get
back to my party because we were stuck
in the shadow fellow we have the death
kurtz
everything's bad our Barda mad he has
the ring of winter these are all very
bad things so I'm going to alter self
into a drow so now I look like a lady
drow okay and yeah hair yeah pretty much
just looks like Strix but she just gets
white hair and drown colored skin and
there's like alright you you point me in
the right direction I will fireball
whoever needs me fireball
I have other spells if you need heels
I've got that ready I'm ready
I am ready to do this also just like ask
your boss to like send us some money
because I don't think we have any money
he just played songs and people threw
money at him and then we took it but
weird things really bad well we had no
money we couldn't I got yeah I've got
tons of money I got way mean you have
tons of money is that the first time
I've heard no I got my hellos No oh yeah
definitely has money all the gambling
that I do all the time he's definitely
told you about it many times and that's
kind of how you met him was he threw
money oh yeah sorry about that was
talked home sorry about the ocean
I don't know when the company airship
let me tell you about it wait what with
the last night with the last few minutes
left with the telepath goodness me I'm
gonna drag the two of them in a building
just there now they know the road yeah
building you guys were crying in Kelly
asked the cloakers to watch him can
anyone watch them can you want to eat
them
this is classic okay this is classic
single Private Ryan I'm gonna let this
soldier don't either shoot us later yeah
exactly so basically you you drag the
two of them yeah into one of these
aviary things and as you bring them in
the cooker that's hanging in the top
turns around and just begins to
immediately moan like at full blast at
you not me yeah you know inside cissus I
don't I don't know a hundred percent
know why a lot of this stuff happened
things a lot happened out there that I
mean I would prefer that it hadn't
happened yeah both you you if you want
you can take them with you or whatever
but this is gonna have ramifications for
a regular Neurath for weeks like this I
go put yourself to sleep
I bought the soldier on the head and
they will run away I'm really sorry
I'm not asking five to be a warden or
watch over these people clearly our
problem but I do offer sincere apologies
and we will do whatever we have to
he says Rosie do you have to understand
this is precisely the sort of thing that
makes physicality so unpleasant you're
telling me you don't got to tell me
twice
he looks at he looks down and then he
looks up at you
and he says you know there is another
way that we might and as he says this
you can hear the snap of a crossbow
string Oh No um and as it flies toward
him in your awareness of where shadow
and material hinge he makes a very small
portion of himself shadow and the bolt
passes clean through his eye and back
through his head and then he comes back
together he says as I was saying you've
created your friends have created
incredible problems for regular Neurath
if you could please go it would be
incredible obviously I can fix it
that rather not now you're gonna make me
take all your shit okay
Oh like the one person that she's met so
far this year it constricts here all
this yeah absolutely
oh no no it's my fault that's my fault
I'm sorry I will allow you to share the
blame no no it's all my fault
I'm just it's actually all my fault I
should have communicated to the group
what my plans were we can all agree it
was everyone's fault but mine I fixed
everything I can keep track of this
Suzanne she strikes will Polly more
first back into she could probably work
a staff and the different fun things
into a frying pan and just be like you
need me that to kill those drow I do Wow
oh yeah where did the crossbow yeah
we're under attack
absolutely rosie has deflect missiles so
she's on guard for there she's ready
yeah okay so you're gonna smash some
drought with some yeah pans you're gonna
come from well I have a shit also will
catch on fire cuz I have green flame
blade my hey my pan catches on fire some
people really useful it's not do that
but not what's the point of espionage if
we're just gonna go around murdering
your own frying pans like the staff just
goes back to a staff never mind
this is great I just really wanted to
beat someone so you can see so it would
be difficult for heavy carts to move far
into one of their regular Neurath
districts especially the shadowy verse
one because it really is a market full
of buildings and roosts but down near
the end of this bridge you can see that
there are two carts sort of a gleaming
black but like more evil than your cart
okay that sounds imagine that the evil
is oh it's a good Dark Eldar thing
that's got the skulls and shit
yeah that sounds Walters hell it's got
the novel horn I'm sorry I was
distracted
oh these cards for our user for our doom
these free card swords they got people
enable what I was yes I think probably
they belonged to the contingent of
soldier APRI cysts so they're they're
ours now that's us now new cart yeah no
copies this these carts have active
drivers and there are soldiers emerging
from them out onto the bridge Rosie over
here I'm okay I I changed my my mask of
many faces to now look like the priest
assumed
was in charge with my back to them and
when I turned back around and say this
was a drill and you all failed get back
everybody crowd in a one cart as a
punishment and go back and tell them
what you did
you are not worth just an e go a get out
of here time for you to leave now from
an order from me
you're a priestess dad yeah you being
wound there being wound up like they're
winding crossbows and basically getting
ready to go to work
really yeah bill did you just you can
hear serving that was a white why is she
speaking common I'm speaking the deepest
this is terrifying I love it I love it
but you can maybe if they have to notice
something it's dead I'm putting a new it
it's the Shibboleth yeah right I'm
pronouncing things differently yeah it's
like no you idiot it's like it's like
imagine how much colloquial language has
changed in 200 years yeah yeah yeah
that's like this was a drill
including this this is my real voice no
it's very much it's very much like
fellow kids yeah well she's like
commanding them with gestures just like
making us well not in they're forming
things and then it's now it's just
yammering and rambling just like
anything I can draw upon like my
memories of when I was a student when I
was a student of law yes and these
spheres but this is like this is
militaristic right I don't know oh no no
no exactly and you know and where where
you had been situated in the hierarchy
man this is not this wouldn't have been
your life eh you wouldn't have learned
to this part yet and even once it had
happened you wouldn't been at the helm
of it yeah so this is me trying to act
like I know the
language of ordering soldiers to do
something so they're they're not buying
it they're just continuing exactly like
just basically like taking up positions
five tugs on the back of your robe
yeah pieces that's an odd for the
podcast
he's nothing behind it he's suggesting
that she go this way okay I go that way
yeah exactly
so you go back into the roost he just
draws a door and pushes you guys come
out of the back of it if none of this
stuff is real I mean now you know the
whole city is yeah it's just a construct
that's maintained by the singing and so
be ho behind this you can see them over
here you can see that the carts you are
afraid that you see additional carts oh
no coming up this long road that goes
along but just to the left of this you
can see that the lake of radiant mists
has some kind of stream or even river
that travels parallel to that road and
goes down so as I said before I say
because it's such a weird place I always
want to go back and make sure that I'm
given the information that's vital so
the last places that we've been have all
been the upper the upper dark called--
earth is in the middle dark so it's
elevation is actually lower so basically
the lake of reading this is almost like
a caldera or something full of water and
it's basically running down fast and you
can see it turning into Rapids the
farther down it goes is they're going
toward or away from it is going down the
hill toward the middle dark and yellow
doors okay ah okay in the meantime while
you're doing this just as flavor
I turned to like good job everyone let
us pray I start to do one of the longest
prayers to law that I can remember okay
it's like the old like the dinnertime
one
right it's a full 45 minutes it requires
a fork stations yeah everything I
remember okay while this prayer is going
on constricts get on her broom and see
where this river goes absolutely all
right so you're gonna you're gonna grab
your Nimbus 2000 yes yeah whatever
you're doing okay a bad game sounds like
it under brew but is still a drow yeah
yeah normal drowning to do she's a test
tube's keep praying so you're able to
you're able to come around these
structures here and you can head down
and see that this is it so it is a
winding hmm it is a mini winding thing
all right
treacherous okay but it's definitely
fast and going the right way
do I see any boats craft you see the
crafts that people attempted to travel
it with they're not they're not in the
they're not a hundred percent great
they're not what you would call boats
okay
now their boats like in Clips right so
yeah I'll zoom back zoom back and plop
next to you guys while you're still
praying okay can we hear a little bit of
this prayer is that is that asking too
much definitely judge definitely do the
okay gesture okay yeah you returned the
tear from the third leg delivers glory
in battle and prowess and sexual arena
is barbed and poisonous and mushrooms
are growing on it it's the bountiful
legs that we all enjoy our meals from
[Laughter]
good sturdy foundation you get a lot of
shifting sands here in the underdog you
want to get that looked at
we buy a home an evil Hut's home
spider leg six
this has sub legs on it mother has done
before me and mine speak under common
either so it sounds really good with
horror okay no with absolute like horror
and revulsion okay sir like not doing
much no no no two priestesses move out
and in under common mm-hmm if you don't
have it don't know it gotta get it plug
your ears all right one of them says
hold and the other says Oh what sounds
you will make in the torture rooms of
men's Ober Esmond indeed and have I made
sounds there often that that is the city
where I'm from I've been sent by your
good sisters there to seek heresy in
this dirty place it's gonna be it's
gonna be like this and then just the
hand it's held out like this then she
goes like this and brings it up and then
creeping around the sides of the bridge
climbing up to the top two massive
spiders like crawling over one another
in their zeal to murder you yes all
should see the glory of loss thank you
for your assistance would be much easier
to find these wretched ones with the
help of
this parent uh popping up I would like
yeah and I'm like oh so I'm gonna like
I'm turning my body to the spiders
coming up and now I'm walking backwards
as though I'm in rank with the with the
priestesses who are who command them Wow
incredible
I'm just like admiring these these
beautiful dark barbed creatures oh yeah
their mouths are wide open and it's like
imagine that there was like a slider for
how hairy a spider could be delicious
it's the maximum Vidya hair works yeah
crank
oh yeah it's it's Nvidia there works on
the Titan 1080 yeah you fly back Friday
night wrestling yeah I came back and I'm
just listening I mean now we have bigger
problems but you have two giant problems
yeah can I can I get your attention and
ask yeah did the word that where does
the river tip I think it's going where
we need to go okay so all right I'm
gonna turn to size and and say I'm
uncertain and I know he's mad at me but
I I say am I am I ready to try again
do you think he says I didn't hate what
I saw okay uh in that case uh we're
gonna try view that granted Nancy yeah
the in in the helm right this shop
indeed in our last game she tried to
make a small boat indeed and it turned
out to be a very big boat you're right
so she's gonna try to do that again with
singing to the staff of the master
circuit is like make it flying the
waters real rough oh I can I can try so
tell me about this boat that you make
using the material substance of the
staff I assume yeah so it's just like
last time a choppy it's a choppy
situation so your parents you gone away
for a week's vacation yep good job beat
situation um so but Rosie knows how to
navigate waters obviously so she's gonna
make something
sort of more whitewater kayak than
anything else like up too wide a Chevy
Volt lat
yep with that can handle the bouncing
currents and with enough room for the
five of us to sit and be safe in and
hopefully not capsize and that's that's
what's in her head as she sings to the
stash so yeah exactly
you're pretty yeah and so as you as you
say it you the staff is this is just
perfectly light in your hand and as
you're holding it up you can see that
it's sort of flattening out and coming
up on the sides to make this sort of
flat rectangle and but there's no like
the distinction there's no weight change
at all like you're holding this solid
physical object and it is now like you
have to lift it up over your head
because you can't hold it out here
anymore like you can easily hold it
because of the weight but it is now big
enough that you have to keep it up here
okay alright so I have this giant boat
over my head I guess and tricks the
suggestions like that's a good idea
but I don't know how flying boats work
so I give it wings or I try to and
that's probably not gonna do it but I
can't make it magically fly I don't
think so it's got two very cute little
cherub it's like a big whitewater kayak
with adorable way I like it yeah she's
just really impressed Wow good magic
think you're just learned neat okay so
it is okay it is down off of the edge a
fair bit out from behind these right
here and clearly just for your part for
your understanding this situation out
here is not tenable you know I'm now I'm
not backing away cuz they haven't
stopped okay so you're backing away like
maybe even into the doorway of life
these things and it's just a head
coming in too many eyes mouth wide open
thick gouts of fucking shit coming out
and I'm just gelatinous like you have no
idea fuck it is still shouting like as
it is in the lore as it is in our
beautiful literature as soon as the boat
is ready by the way Rosie's gonna
whistle cuz we don't we don't have an
agreed-upon signal yes we're dingdong
they don't have that sound down here
typically so yeah get on her broom and
just like that's like like like just
hovering around like this work yeah you
told I was going to yeah maybe we both
do to these drivers collar it's like
it's like I wanted to like I could turn
this around I remember the prayer I
remember all of it exactly so tell me
how you tell me how the party
transitions from the bridge with the
boat down to the mouth of this river yes
along this edge imagine that is just a
ridge of those tiny shops and crafting
areas just behind them the bridge of all
these regular Neurath districts sort of
curves down to the land that's attached
you on each side okay perfect lunch yeah
that's that's what I'm gonna I'm gonna
push push the boat about halfway in the
water and wait till everybody gets
aboard and then push it off and jump in
yes there's about I mean there's a
significant drop between the layer
between the level of the bridge you're
on in the water below okay
um how deep is the water can I tell but
this is gonna be near the shore of it so
okay okay
you're high so probably then the thing
to do would be we all just jump in right
yeah also we gonna do we're gonna just
drop the boat and then all hop in you
know at the same time yeah all right we
do so you take this thing thank you and
so you you drop the boat off yeah and
it's like a paper airplane you drop it I
think us there's a go downstream oh no
it just it's just sort of taking its own
sweet time it's like the way a leaf
would fall I think okay okay yeah but
it's like it's like trying to push an
umbrella in a windstorm way it's just
catching it folks under pressure ask
Rosie asks tricks like can you hold on
to the boat for us nice ride he was also
really shitty because it's but she's
like did it wrong and so the staff
polymorphs into this room and like
explodes sometimes so just like holding
on door I got it all right jump in oh
yeah sure
it's big enough for Clark morale is
around I can fit in it too no well then
I say distraction boy you jump off your
distraction playing use turns back oh my
god and then it's just like as
interesting as your as your eyes who go
below the surface you just hear sounds
thanks well we go and before we take off
I scream super loud tasty comes running
over it jumps off the side and I him
catch him full round yeah exactly
he's my god you just catch him around
catch him and then right on the shoulder
like a baby oh yeah
BAM anything yeah
so tired he was lost up there I know he
was lost up there he was eating he was
eating shadow stop I didn't say I'd be a
good gobbling warden I said I will wreck
on this and say him and Clarke Moore
wandered off so in combat tricks is like
we have a lot of bets too we had to eat
one once so the natural the natural
inclinations of the water from the lake
of radiant mists is starting to tug the
boat with increasing speed into the
mouth of these Rapids shadow council
mayor Labor's pleasing this is our break
don't go nowhere because I'm going to
come back it's gonna be white water
rafting time oh hello I'm Jared cave our
canvas welcome to test C teams last week
when last we saw our heroes they had
just entered the murky mouth of an
underground pure excitement scenario um
a lot of excitement everybody's getting
cranked up I was having a good time too
everybody's having agree exactly rosy
bee stinger utilizing her powers of
shadow that she learned from Sevilla
summer was able to manifest from her
staff of the master a massive boat
scenario the likes of which you've never
seen never supple you know what it means
so the scenario is as I've suggested is
that the natural current from the lake
is starting to pull down this hill that
we know leads this river down into the
middle dark which is where the town of
gala death and indeed the district
karissa is from lower gallon earth
they're all situated down in that realm
imagine it's like the
moment imagine a dark roller coaster oh
right we're sort of starts out yes and
we starts out with the chunka chunka
chunka chunka chunka and then there's
the moment where you are no longer
engaged in a plan of any kind now you
are simply at the mercy of a natural
phenomenon and that is the occurrence
that has happened here now hovering just
over this boat which you are free to
name is is strix yes don't get a - now
no stress you are up high I was thinking
actually trying to like use it pretty a
rudder for them oh and just kinda like
steer the boat we need it back that's
very cool
so she's got like one leg in the water
and it's just like smash against rock
she's like oh wow I love it under a
broom so here's the situation I want to
help her but I don't worry you'll be
able have an opportunity to help and oh
yeah it's like this I need to know who
is looking out in the front I need to
know who is on horizonte right and i
need to know who is helming in the back
now it sounds like you want to be using
your broom to help us fix any problems
that we might yes yeah exactly
cuz you're you have a different
perspective on this whole thing all
right broom all right so it's like so
I'm just seeing like rocks coming up
like a video game and I'm just like yeah
like trying to push them to the side
exactly right so to me that sounds more
like to me that sounds more like you're
engaging in the sort of lookout position
yes but you have a little bit of height
so you might be actually up near the
front holding on and sort of like
pulling the bow that's true yeah in
different directions yeah right so who's
gonna be at these rotors so I think
there's actually three or is then she's
gonna be watching from the front and
then just like just like in a raft
situation there's a bunch of people
paddling based on whether they're being
told to do
yeah so who's who's got Oris and who is
gonna be driving on the back oh maybe
there's four ORS each person gets one
and well most really angry things
getting your frustration out with a
[Music]
[Laughter]
strong boy yeah you know I was gonna
like can my flavoring of fly work down
here because I would want to I mean if
Strix has it covered that's fine but if
I but if I can fly and do similar and
get double that guidance or is that a
thing that wouldn't work well here oh
you know what and you wouldn't work
because I can fly but when I'm encircled
by the tentacle I'm numb I would you
would have to use me as you'd have to
attach me to the boat and then I would I
would tell the tentacle where to fly me
but I have no agency of my own in that
situation exactly well here let's do the
complications already this is all right
yes let's do a round of these dangers
right yeah I'm gonna be the butt about
okay so you can so you basically you're
gonna be back there yeah they're gonna
be basically have the rudder which is
perfect for Rosie right you're rowing
you're rowing you're rowing and you are
watching for shit and right Rosie in
strikes are shouting Oh 100% you guys
are basically like the bright seem that
holds this whole fucking thing together
yeah and I'm yelling boat terms at you
which Kate doesn't know but Rosie knows
a ton of them so it's like starboard any
of those they're just like hey Barbie
what isn't the dead ball can something
like planer can - yeah it's like we
can't understand there's Heather no at
all but but that doesn't keep you from
commute all right so all our people need
a d6 you need a d6 as well Rosie got the
helm now you are not or personal that
you are as a lookout why don't you grab
your massive damn money down there that
we're flexing on today all right
now your task should
you choose to accept it is to find
evidence of bad things that are
happening and then yell those things out
all right to your friends this is dude
listen I'm having a great time
now here's what I need you to do tell me
what kinds of skills you have that you
think would be would make you what makes
drinks
that is to say good at this sort of
Crowsnest eternal well she's scared of
everything
okay she's hyper alert so yeah so if so
hyper perceptive basically yeah
perception perception is a great skill
unless there's something else that you
think that you can make a case for oh
yeah they might be superior well I would
like to hear on the C team we are very
much about flavoring skills okay we used
I think that we used religion to serve
Kate yes we used religion to serve cake
and I think that's like the high point
for the C team I actually I have a
pretty good survival survival but
because of me being afraid of everything
I also got that for surviving 50 years
in burrow via I'm bathing in blood not
aging yeah yeah you need a lot of ones
its +4 okay absolutely well here listen
so you roll that you add the skill that
you you like I like perception or
survival I think those are both
excellent in this case whichever one you
like best which everyone use is higher
doesn't give you a better chance to
succeed right you roll that and that
will tell you what happens all right
okay that's a nine yeah so nine talent
all 13 okay so you are hovering just
above the water
your hand is sort of back on the front
of the boat the boat nose in beasting
your terminology and you are you are
basically tugging this craft it's almost
like a hydroplane in the front little
wings you're lifting it up a little bit
wings are doing their right and you are
assessing everything in your hyper
paranoia that has not gotten any better
since you arrived in the underdog no no
right just came from the shadow fuck
exactly it hasn't gotten better and
you're seeing a lot of wrecked boats and
rocks and you're able to avoid all of
these things but you have missed the
forest for the trees no because there is
actually kind of a it looks like it just
might be a Eddy but there's actually a
whirlpool Oh what I guess over on the on
the right that is hidden another boat is
going right into so here's what we need
helm yeah I need you to roll your d6
okay
no no because you know you don't need
advantage for what you're doing sick
do you have rolled a six now rowers you
need to roll a six also can you take
advantage yeah you can take advantage
for you like I would like to take
avenged so close okay chefs five five
you take it you can't think I'm gonna
take advantage that's up to four though
right to away from six exactly Oh some
for the pocket so the edge of this boat
like the the rear right edge of it is
being sucked down into the bottom of
this central Worrell now you can just
see the dark eye of this whirlpool down
in the base from your from your broom
you're able to tug the ship the boat
just out of it it's incredible lightness
is helping you here and you're able to
pop straight out and go in the front now
you Newton under the three of you
succeeded all right a just a wave of ice
cold under dark river water splashes in
on the party so for this next one you
have disadvantage which means you need
to roll your dice no no no that was that
was that that was that first part now
everyone else behind you is soaking a
sweat
oops we have to which six your six or my
sister even know if I've seen an ocean
more than once but I'm not sure water do
you think water is you can't even water
alright got that wet dinars like I lived
in water that's how much I don't
understand this she's the right person
to be guiding it it's water yeah that's
what we feel like right now okay so now
that you you're you've pulled it up and
just over it to the front of the raft is
just skimming the water
I need another check for this next this
is feeling more surely surely good
Shirley Shirley healthy not you because
you didn't get ice cold oh good council
Mara labor squeeze you your servants
tricks has delivered you a boon keep an
eye on that in there cool presents from
level up and elder would both of which
are at Emerald City Comic Con this
weekend you should definitely go and say
hi they have a lot of cool shit I own
tons of it now so what so what you have
done with that is you have actually
wiped out their disadvantage yes right
so now they have straight roles on alert
and it's good so now it's just like yeah
exactly so this so you're you're looking
for whirlpools you know that they're out
there somewhere you don't know what the
source is there's a lot of better that
you don't get but you know that you want
to be ahead of it this time
you don't see any whirlpools which makes
you a little nervous some but you don't
have a lot of time to be scared about it
because the rocks that are coming up
here are like the they're like that back
plates of a Stegosaurus like these are
these are rocks that eat boats
these are starveling rocks they're long
to feast on boat
helm what is the target number six no no
you roll oh I see
okay oh I'm sorry sorry for rolling so
grass before four
all right we have three rowers what do
we get
I'm taking the advantage again okay you
should even need it you might give a
twenty role again also take advantage
yeah guess you don't need to take
advantage is hurting we're two got then
we got the number oh well one of us yeah
yeah yeah okay coming hard then skip
good be super bad all right um so you
are looking over at cthe RIS who is
engaged in some kind of a Socratic
dialogue with his or dinar is is doing
that thing where it's like you're
paddling like mad but you're not
actually biting the water at all like
but it looks like you're doing a lot
yeah it's mostly outside the water yeah
but the forum is right but if it was a
foot below that's all we need he's gonna
sweat oh yeah it's like vascular so
you're able to you're able to set things
up you're able to set things right with
Rosie on the back
steering you're able to help navigate
through this nasty sharp forest of
stones it's at this point that I
remember that I'm scared of the water
yeah she doesn't wanna get up there
right any part of it but no no whoops
okay that's your soda stone from omen
distracted and protective instincts are
over tasty may be kicked in it's true
yeah yeah she's got a paste tasty
doesn't know what to do on this boat he
is just running around between everyone
on the boat my brow
this is my brow so engaging no so he'll
he'll sort of clamber up onto the back
mm-hmm
and he'll he'll take a kerchief and just
polish your forehead somehow it's like
more greasy than it's somehow gotten
worse
perfect it's about the service he's geez
to bring words of you think maybe
encouragement you don't know a hundred
percent you don't know a hundred percent
now beyond this I need another one of
these roles ma'am
drinks come on be as paranoid as I know
you are the stone that is that is quite
good yeah um so you you're able to
you're right at the front of this thing
you're just sort of like weaving in
between these stones you can tell that
there are good strong or is cleverly
applied maneuvering the boat through
these sharp plates the issue that you
see next is that you think that there
are another range of rocks but the
closer the boat gets you can see slight
movement on the stones and you can see a
light glint on a set of authentically
moist red eyes so there are a number of
creatures well I would describe them
this it's dark yeah yeah absolutely
doesn't like that I'm just saying that
like there's a bunch of shadowing
imagine imagine like a demon crawdad
nice and that's that's more or less the
situation we're talking about regular I
know they're massive Carissa crazy
if I see a massive creature coming up I
will try to polymorphic oh there's
definitely a case here okay so how do we
want to manage this we're gonna need
people to maneuver this boat and who
wants to come over and try to manage
these beasts because when I say crawdad
from hell
mmm that's this I mean I I have if
anything I've undersold it massive claws
that look as though they are mouths
themselves face yeah
eating just ten babies at a time no
these are these are these are bad
fellows all right but you can just see
that ice-cold river water just washing
over them and whatever they've got down
below is keeping them fixed right in the
in the wake all right and how many are
there there's three that you can see
okay
um I just I just go just I'll go like as
far as I can't above yeah I love it and
I'm going to we're coming back into it
yeah I'm warming a twin spell polymorph
whoa - OH - one's the old twin spell
yeah I don't have a one what are these
entities being polymorphs into I usually
go for chickens cuz I like them but it
makes me kinda sad that they're in the
water so maybe I'll go for ducks
some little mallards the chickens of the
sea yeah basically just some old
mallards are baby ducks I love it and
you still say this 16 16 yeah baby ducks
yeah you were able to get one of them
good
it's a better duck now yeah so the two
the two that are sort of like their job
is clearly just to catch boats right for
the other one to eat right and one of
them just immediately sort of like warps
and twists down and then just
[Laughter]
little orange going wild underneath but
now we have space a little bit exactly
exactly and that's deaf that's
definitely gonna help us
alright um so who is going to be who's
gonna move to look out from or cuz I'm
gonna try and distract the other two oh
absolutely so I'm just like I mean I'm
please like hands are on fire like sorry
my staff around like I like the t-rex
like in Jurassic Park
I'll go strong play mode and take tours
okay okay all right so you're navigating
oh boy and I'm jurassic parking yeah
yeah yeah exactly
well I don't know oh boy oh I was so I
was using school do you have what would
I have that would be good yeah your dad
doesn't make it oh nature that I cuz
that would be nature there are creatures
yeah weird yeah waters very natural yeah
water isn't it I get a plus forty
tonight put it on a shirt yeah um I can
get an 11 you can use your yeah okay
retroactive
yes well I didn't know if we totally
yeah you know if I could do you got
snuck in on this it's fine you can real
good no I'm not that I wanted to roll
again on that kanae's four strands oh
absolutely
thank you yeah easily so so I want you
to tell me about these forest friends
and so it's yeah so forest friends is
whatever is around is around yeah so
what are you trying to get okay what I
want is to so I'm gonna a bunch of
whatever the fish adjacent creatures are
that that dwell here and I want them to
surround the boat and just be like a
buffer to just slippery us by like oh
maybe they're really tasty maybe there's
big ones around I don't know and maybe
they're tasty and the credits want those
that's for the DM to decide what would
be really cool yeah exactly the carp
version of would man
shielding yeah yes carb man yeah um so
from the deep fish yeah exactly
oh yeah yeah the deepest fish thank you
right um so you're moving up your you
have sort of hanging on to the front of
the boat you can see one of these giant
demonic crawdads twist away and become a
friendly duck and then you see two more
just sort of rising like sort of statues
in the river and then you basically put
the call out
it's a casting call for whatever local
creature yeah is available and then sort
of like bobbing up in front of the boat
you look down and then you can just sort
of see like a glimmering silver fish hmm
and then it has to like firm fins that
come out on the side mm-hmm and it sort
of turns its it like turns in the water
and you can see that it's all eyes like
the entire front of that you don't even
know where the mouth is it's just gonna
be all kinds of sightless orbs milky
but here but here's the most important
thing about these creatures is that they
adore you they want to support you they
want to protect they do they want to
protect no no no but they want it not
you I mean but so they rise up and the
boat sort of is lifted up on the backs
of you don't know how many of these
things and they are and you can just you
can just hear like it sounds like um
imagine imagine if you filled like a
like a frosting tip with jello yeah yeah
I just imagine imagine just squeezing
out know whatever that sound would be
ELISA doesn't like this set
what can you tell me about this yeah
exactly and the the ORS are not even
biting the water like they have
basically made you know the double
crunch what do they call that it's from
Taco Bell oh yeah Sabrina no it's the
one that's like good it's got that yeah
yeah yeah what is it it's got the
tortilla and then it's got the beans
then it has the hard shell essentially
it's made another shell a ramp look
below the boats hull that's all fish
carpe Deum they're there they're moving
the boat with expert skill and then
other ones are leaping from the water
right at these demonic crawdads love it
till they're so full they don't know no
one else regular mouth and it's just a
but an endless an endless amount yeah I
can imagine it like a chain link and
it's just kind of just winding inside
their belly except every link in the
chain is a living fish it's no you see
that you see the great claws of the
creature just oh so man I couldn't
couldn't possibly was it just being
pelted they're just holding these claws
up like this and the boat is basically
just like resting on this silver wave of
moist fish watching this from the sky
and their evil eyes yeah yeah the boat
begins to move in a way that is not a
hundred percent in
it's like it's like the wheels like when
you're going and like the airport
security line just this over like a
conveyor belt and yeah so um you're able
to get through these devious challenges
and pull the rest of the way through
it's a it's a fairly significant trip
the rest of the way down but the worst
of it really is up high where delicious
creatures from the lake of radiant mists
move down and are devoured by the
creatures there so you were able to you
travel for quite a ways down this river
and your suspicion based on what Carissa
has told you is that gala doroth is
going to be west of you relatively soon
it's gonna be time to move this
contraption off of the river and get out
there do we see they like the city walls
yeah oh yeah it's much because you've
been able to see it like and this is
this is super important cultural
information for you Chris
every second you are you know a hundred
feet closer to this place like it's just
get it's getting it's getting massive
yeah in your field of vision I was
hoping that because I left when I was
Lots it was relatively smaller that it
would you know it would seem smaller
like when you go to your parents house
and like the bathroom counter wasn't as
tall as that no that's just as big and
it's an adult city it's for grown men
and women yeah and the spiders they love
yeah it's Trixie's that Catherine's is
scared she'll just like start handing
him snacks from her room define snacks
yeah just like you know she's got
cookies and stuff she's way into baking
yeah they're really good oh nice
she had them they're really stale
excited in the shadow fell for who knows
how long
but she's just trying to help everyone
but you're just eating anything she's
offering shoeing one of them wasn't a
cookie thank you just in this chain
circular foods like wait wait it's gone
[Laughter]
it was close to yeah so there's like I
almost go winding area a little little
shoal where the water is easier yeah
and you think it would be a trivial
matter to okay gets couch to birth us up
there thanks Oh words yeah heard I know
you were able to pull it out there you
don't think that this you don't think
there's a lot of traffic here this
doesn't seem like an especially well
trafficked region of this you know that
this river just continues down all the
way to a massive sub body of water south
of gallon earth but it's not it's just
it's not wide enough for commercial use
I mean it's it's good enough to secure
you know as a source of water but it's
not it isn't something that you could
use a lot and then getting back up it
would be virtually impossible so no
point yeah no it's not really a
thoroughfare I'm happy to take my time
if you're you've secured the boat oh
it's not secured it's gonna be turned
back into my ste yes okay but it seemed
better so it like we get out I assume
and then I I'm taking a lot of time
acting like I'm securing it well I let
you looks good alright this might better
make sure this is tied really quite
there I should and I don't know what you
should we really need to stay here and
check out this boat make sure there's
nothing going on the boat has already
walked away we gotta kill in here and
she's like walking
funny Razia hustle this along so she
gonna get back to her battery come on
yeah she's just like picturing them all
that this is a city as the city is a
pretty substantial space west of this
like it's in the it's in the distance
you can see it but it's it's it'll be
it'll be a bit of a walk in here are you
still you still appear as a dragon okay
she looks pretty much the same more
drowsy yeah they should all get on the
same page where are we going in guns
blazing are we gonna try to do this
espionage we have to go in sneaky yeah
ideally we'd get into the city without
encountering a guard I don't think
that's possible I know what they like to
do down here so I'm gonna have to
pretend that you guys are some
contingent of mine we have a reason for
being down here maybe I we are looking
for heretics that should play well it's
on brand yeah well we have to drown mmm
for a while longer
mouse me you're double drowning oh yeah
you guys were gonna go come on humanoid
didn't ice too big you me put a cloak on
him it's obvious he's a big walking
around melting down here so I got a
mouse a fight I know my plan was to just
be like your young Ward like I'm yeah
the priestess in training no rat no do
you don't want to be a rat no I don't
wanna be around you want to be a mouse
Branson pigeons are dirt rats and rats
are fling pigeons of flight right
so I probably worth to Norah into a rat
so may is a good this was the one thing
I didn't want to happen but it's the rat
and it's just like but it's like the
shrug but it's good by a rat before it
can be said by my row I bite or her
because I don't a rat oh yeah we're
gonna get him mixed up with Strix his
rights
yeah good know what maybe we better and
feel good deliberate
all right so I probably mark him into a
rat and I look at tasty and I go I go
okay tasty job your job is that you're
gonna have to carry me and the rat
that's your job and then you follow
let's go you follow her I reach my hand
out of tasting be like you are now my
goblin ward and I am a drow yes
something you listen to what she says
BuChE a wild shape into a weasel nice so
we have a we have an assortment we have
a kind of menagerie yeah and you two are
somewhere on either streaks or Pastis
personal or mustelids okay so we're
let's approach the game all right it's
on a whole tasties hand and I have my
cloak that I stole from where the drow
pulled over my head it's really very
long right absolutely and I'm it's like
a alright good word we've we've done
good work now we're gonna continue our
cleansing work in this in this city
right I can't wait to learn more from
your mother so much to teach you drought
I'm not gonna talk if I don't speak
under coming yeah I can speak infernal
so I'll just speaking infernal that's
good
exactly Josh would you please hit my
cauldron so the the party has recently
adopted all of its new forms and you're
prepped you're ready for a 100 percent
success in a radical new venue and
obviously I as your dungeon master
support they wonder percent that being
said the cauldron was tipped by Wi-Fi
and so I am powerless to do anything but
to reward the shadow council now there
is a group coming along the road east
out of gallon earth
a group of seven Durge are which are the
dwarves of the Underdark generally
speaking recognized Tufts early evil you
think that one of them might be drunk
but not generally and the lead the
leader of this band says listen we don't
go to make this a big thing and one of
them one of them behind says yeah he
doesn't gotta be no big thing and the
way the front says here's what's going
on
we've got bargains you've got gold I
just gotta be some way we can put these
things together oh okay
this is fine thanks Josh no no they're
lit that's one of the things that we can
get so the seven of them I mean they are
brandishing like this is the mode this
gotta be the most bizarre marketing
Enterprise you have ever seen strikes is
like probably something to help my party
yeah yeah absolutely and and desperate
she's always we're gonna die absolutely
honestly this just you know ooc as they
say yeah this is probably gonna help you
a lot it's actually really lucky that
this happened that that happened and
then this world the way it did so the
seven of the leader is like almost
taking it back like you you think he
expected this to go a different way that
he was key might have to kill one or two
of you and then bring the rest back to
the store but it turned out fine um and
they're armed I mean this is they're
armed like a war band like they're ready
to like you
would send a team like this into a
dungeon to get another party that had
died there
so they take you back back up the street
or a bat back up this Eastern Road and
then off a little bit near a rocky
outcrop sort of on the Eastern Hill well
no and you and you can see back there
you see something authentically strange
and new and I'm again I could not be
more pleased that had that happened and
then I rolled merchants because I didn't
know if I was gonna be I have a chance
to use this woman so you see what looks
to be a stalagmite on a cart with wheels
it's on yeah okay strapped around the
stalagmite on one side is a bony outcrop
that you think is must be the limb of a
large creature except it is all the way
down to the white bone mm-hmm and as
though as the party approaches you can
see that you know at different points
around this this stalagmite this central
cone there are windows and some of them
have chimneys and smoke coming out and
you can see that as the party approaches
with the Salesforce you can see that the
like a truffle pig almost you can see
the hand the clawed hand of the bony
outcrop like read like patting around
like this like imagined it has lost its
keys or something
it's patting around on the ground and
then it puts its fingers in and then
begins to drag the stalagmite closer to
the road
and then it lays down its hand and then
you can hear like the front door opens
and you see a young drow woman inside
who emerges and says did they do they
refuse she says sometimes the first
thing I have to sell people is healing
potions that could also be the first
thing you saw she says she says I'm
moral you know let's let's let's do this
correctly I'd like to create a
relationship with the customer
madam grandmother yes hello moral mom
very nice to meet you Rosie Rosie Apgar
all right
okay it's a rat I'm a rat oh yeah it
actually doesn't stop her no I was gonna
try to sneak in and steal something for
him steal something she'll kneel down
and she says moral and she says moral
i'm Strix shakes my little weasel hand
yeah and then she puts up a fist for
tasty she says she says it is my great
pleasure to invite you to my shop in
what way can I be of service my party's
dying we're in the shadow fell there's
an evil ring I thought about God
his hand with scissors but I don't know
if that's gonna work that's a lot of
bone in there
yeah oh there's also two shattered hi
assassins oh and an army of snowmen and
maybe a dragon wait my life is bad okay
what she didn't preface this with what
settle a bet for us indeed having heard
that what wears would you sell a person
in that predicament I would I would seek
a mercenary force I do come across them
from time to time I'm sadly out of stock
that I might have to leave soon I
suddenly unwillingly she says can anyone
go with you uh objects can but I don't
think anyone can go with me so my mostly
thinking object some sort of object what
about a dead body like my own I can
carry a dead body I don't taste it I
don't think that works like when I
disappear I get like drag through the
ground and there screams and I don't
know what's happening so it's not it's
not really willingly I have a bad family
tell it might be ending the multiverse
it's fine yeah she rubs her chin and she
says Sam I and it's the one who was
piping up in the back but nothing one
who is in the front she says come here
and he says why and she says come here
and so he what he walks up chastised and
she goes in to her spire and comes back
out with a potion and then she tells him
to drink it and then he pops the cork
and looks inside for a while and then
he's gonna
put his finger in and she's like no I
didn't say I said drink it and he drinks
it and from the mouth out becomes a
creature of stone Oh
mm-hmm he or she then hands you a potion
and says if you break this over him you
shouldn't be an object anymore oh he's
really big I can't carry then hold him
close Oh sleep with him you sleep with
him like a teddy plus take the
Commission's healing potions - oh I
don't be greedy
absolutely and she's like how are we and
how are we paying today straight goes
like that thing at dinner where everyone
puts their card out but she just pulls
out some mobs I think you'll find this
[Laughter]
she's like I'm pretty sure you can put
it on almonds tab it would be a
write-off
we have some in our travels we have some
disgusting coin from above ground but is
gold do you come up down no coldest
quite accept okay
the shape of it isn't that I haven't
been home in a while
yeah the shape of the shape of it is not
really of interest to me it's it spins
quite well here as you'll find now it
feels really guilty but she's like I'm
learning how to ask for help now she
says no house can we solve your problem
she starts crying she's being too nice
to her so it's just like she thinks
she's gonna get stabbed at like anymore
everything's badge is a curl up on the
ground do you have anything that could
stop time she like says from the ground
how long a couple seconds just anything
just to chop up just to take a finger
off okay all right mmm she says we have
to understand a lot of my wares come
from Gallagher directly I have access to
the wares of many of the high houses in
lower Gallagher if and beyond
ever ever since the reclamation of the
outer wards mmm everything outside is a
ruin but obviously my good friends here
can help me raid these places and so I
have a very very novel selection of
goods I can't stop time for two seconds
that's all I need
all right that's all I need it's not
gonna it's not gonna be for moss
she likes keeps digging she's like
cookie yeah which does not understand
money by the way she'd like she hears
people talk about it but she does not
understand because the only thing that
she did was turn in dead bodies for
whatever that she could get it's a it's
a great position to be in because
Carissa manages the money and also
doesn't care about it at all hmm how
much I'll drive a hard bargain
trying to put on like a friend
yeah exactly yeah exactly she says well
let's see I mean we have one animatable
Durge our warrior I see a chip on the
side yeah exactly
she does she doesn't understand money
but knows how to drive a bargain yeah
exactly
well she ate it with dead bodies just
like
you know this one's fresh yeah exactly
she has a pocket watch that can be used
to stop time for two seconds at which
point it becomes too hot to touch these
two things together if there aren't any
other solutions that you'd like to
peruse now let's continue the business
you take four hundred and fifty gold I
feel like should suffice for these who
we let let me confer with my weasel
this is holmen's fast we job just gonna
flank it over let's see what else we can
she got she understands what you're
getting in she just starts writing a I
like a write-off form and it's like
sitting there like a king at like a toy
store when like their parents are buying
them something really expensive that
they like cried for really upset about
it and the kids is getting it anyway cuz
they just won them to be quiet no she's
just like I hold up a forum for Strix to
sign
oh I'm not touching that no okay
and then just yeah that's it
I love that walnut would respect someone
who doesn't sign a contract no yeah you
read it he read bandit morale says so
what are you contending with exactly
well what was happening exactly yeah so
our bard
put on the ring of winter here during
winter yeah yeah so he's wearing it and
he's in the shadow fell and he's trying
to make a new domain of dread like straw
have you heard of straw friends don't
let friends wear the ring over winter
well we tried that but he really wanted
an ice bird so
that's why he said that good enough I
don't think that's a good enough you
know it's probably not a great situation
but we respect his decisions and now I
have to chop his hand off so I only need
two seconds to get in there and or
didn't take my scissors and cut his
finger off and then misty step out of
there and there's still an army of
snowmen to shatter KY assassins the
entirety of the shadow film maybe a
dragon
our rogue is also only has like he said
he's dying he's dead death curse he has
like the death curse have you heard of
the death curse yeah so I don't know
what timeline is Wheatstone the death
curse which is ro so really bad and
she's like continues to say we also have
these worms in us so we we don't have
souls we have souls but we got worms
shoved in us so we have evil souls in us
in case we die there's also mercy
Killers after us we killed one of the
mercy killers so the mercy killers are
after us and she's still going
and she's like there's also these two
families there's ask is external or
kapha
if they get together then that means the
world and universe and the multiverse
ends and we accidentally did that too so
that's also happening and she's like no
way she's just going all so strong oh
the Strad show puppet showed up again we
put so we killed a child and put straud
into a puppet was a hag pin
out from behind the stalagmite crawls a
creature with no eyes just taught skill
no house I mean I grab onto the door
no I'm conducting this and merchandise
exchange now yes I forego over that
corner go the coin watch it bigger than
it comes over lady just crawls up on the
dwarf I'm trying to bite and bite and
I'm sorry and another one comes back out
she's doing a healing potion
oh they're biting and nipping and she
says she's like she's like hahaha no and
then she opens she uncorks uh-oh she's
like she's like don't tell me you've
never done this before
and then just pour is it spores it
straight down and so they're like
nipping and scratching at the ground
below you like they bite into the solid
earth is getting worse and then every
time I head in to just peel up the skin
of the earth and then your toe starts to
sink into it and then the dwarf is
coming along with you like the weight of
it and then the weight of him on top
just pushes you straight down through
this whole hoof and she falls straight
through the earth and is gone shadow
council mayor ladies please yuh-huh I
want to take a moment to thank a good
friend strips over hopefully we
hopefully be setups tricks for a success
over in dice camera action or normal
campaign and Chris he'll let me you
indeed and he will he sends people with
shit into my campaign all the time yeah
hey listen we're gonna jump out real
quick we're gonna come back for some
table talk don't go nowhere