time is the enemy of the past it
threatens the fastest weapon you
wouldn't make it past a second and
answer the question play it brash and
reckless to choose a cautious solution
you saw was prudent in any sepulcher
poker to don't become the putrid it's
that well said I pursue in no mountain
too steep for dungeon too deep to send
expendable marks up to the top of the
peak of beneath they see Yugi they come
like sharks to it while I swim in that
money bill like Carl Barks through it so
send your National Parks drew it I'll
send him home in a natural box with a
close tie though most of the parts
included save your breath for a cleric
confessor death is a lesson that life is
attending professor but if you're
seeking my official advice sign on the
dotted line and this should the twice
and and go Jerry go I go great work
everybody hello at long last is I Tycho
Brahe hey of Penny Arcade impacts I'm
also a minute as Hereward run CEO of
acquisitions incorporated but today I'm
Jerry Hawkins and I'm gonna run a game
of Dungeons &amp; Dragons for my friends
specifically to my right best friend
Dragonborn narcissist dinar blitz and to
the right of my right wrapping the
natural world walnut dawn grass that
would be shirt of the year just like
well that just does like what do you
want from me left first first left not
your grandma's grandma except for those
rip she's got it prepped to except for
those rare cases where she is your
grandma's grandma Rosie B steers
we're talking what we're positing here
on the c-team is a non-euclidean dick
think about it what that's what the C
stands for you towards the language
itself yeah exactly yeah the idea
we've perturbed the language um left to
the left of my left to the left of the
left it's gonna be like this little time
isn't it yes emerging as though from a
mist shroud yeah for you you can have it
for you all right
no friends no shadow council mayor
lyrics please you we are gonna jump
right into it if you recall from last
week our heroes by which I mean the
players at this table entered into the
very gullet of the creature the entity
that cthe risk derives his powers from
now only two of you have ever been in
here and beheld this thing this is a a
brand new I mean this day started out
surreal
I would say four dinar and rosy and I
would say that it has maintained that
trajectory so you move from a sort of
silvery misty perpetually sunset sort of
infinite void tinged with silver and now
you are inside of what appears to be a
amethyst octagon and and as I suggested
before half of you have been here and
half of you haven't the first thing that
you noted just to catch us up from last
week is that there are columns at each
of the sort of it vertices is that the
right yeah weird inside this octagon
which sort of tapers down from the top
and stuck inside those are entities of
various kinds but encased in a kind of
crystal lozenge for lack of a better
term there is a sort of amethyst coffin
that surrounds oak true strike and just
like the divine entities that this thing
routinely captures his vessel contains a
symbol upon it that identifies itself
that is apparently an important part of
this process
mm-hmm because it's universal it's it's
executed in virtually every instance of
this things capture right last time we
were here I had my my physical eyes
ripped out that did happen by my buddy
by my my tentacle familiar there was
there was there was knowing and you were
able to see things that were not purely
physical in this space I decided I liked
it yep indeed I'm just gonna hang out
with it you stuck with it yeah you you
got impaled and then you turned into a
tree and you know that tree you broke
one of the columns that's true and you
freed maelys tried to is it cried shield
broken or has it there but you are
welcome to explore the space just like
in an HG TV like a surreal imagine a
dark HGTV okay come in they start
talking about the open floor plan
they're gonna bring a young couple in
here ya know this could be our first
Sepulcher no and they're presented okay
we're stuck yeah first thing we don't
want to look and see if that column is
telling a prude it's still are still
damaged do you I noticed that these two
don't seem to be surprised that we're
here uh it's possible I need you give me
an insight you are pretty you feel like
we're surprised that it brought us here
but we're not like shocked by this okay
in horror okay I'm ringing my phantom
yes good in the hand from the hand okay
yeah did you ever give us a nose haven't
explained it explain it after well if
you guys are in shock than I maybe
haven't noticed that there's anything
unusual what exactly this is this is my
thinking it's like here's grandma powers
the insight would allow you to derive
good solid info from your friends but it
won't it's innate oh I want to perceive
just gonna perception check just get it
lay the land no I'm not I'm just the
area where I don't see shit no three for
the view but the best part is that for
dinar this would be like he'd just be
like it's not gonna be that much
different from oh yeah what would any
abenney no matter what he rolls he
always feels like he actually
understands it to the maximum degree oh
yeah sure just like wow read it's all
amethyst right so we're surrounded by
purple yeah yeah a lot of red a lot of
red like right like I said okay what is
this place and I'm not asking you guys
in particular this is more of a
rhetorical question because I assume
none of us have been here before
Hawai I know this place what do you mean
real good this is where I lost my these
it's my eyes you lost him to like remove
things they were ripped out I don't know
if you remember that but oh no I
I remember the aftermath of that but I
didn't realize it happened oh it
happened here yes this is the the place
where the god of mouths seems to occupy
and imprison things that are cared about
one of the one of whom if whom applies I
was beat by God I follow brought me here
okay
is your God imprisoned here - yeah oh
yes okay but he spoke to me it spoke to
me once and told me not to free it and I
listened and
maybe we're here to finish the job okay
i freed my god just want to put that
you've been here - yes honey gods are in
this one strip one one time mailer is
not free hmm oh I see that so I say that
she was right over exactly oh and so
this entire place as described is
basically like almost the inverse of
something you would put in a jewel
setting right it's all faceted you're
basically like imagine that you're
inside of a gym that you would put into
a ring right and so when you look over
it basically it's all flawless like the
the prison itself is is just perfect
facets everywhere except for the
approach to the prison of MELAS and so
there are deep gouges I mean all the way
back to this aperture you were able to
row the boat to and emerge up inside the
the this cavity inside of it but you can
see are deep ridges scratched into and
out I mean you can tell in an instant
what these what these processes are what
created them like you know in a moment
there's no less than five different
types of claws like every instrument
every implement that was available to
Maliki or for our friends at home my
Alika right every natural and divine
instrument that was available to her was
put was put to task on this thing she's
not here anything no okay but you can
but usually you can see a Thor
sticking out just like lodged in the
crystal mmm inside here and you can see
that there was a substantial attempt to
break through and cut through the front
of it mm-hmm and you can see there was a
that what appears to be a second attempt
to take the entire prison and get around
behind it and take the entire thing out
but some process some process intervened
like stealing a whole atm
exactly yeah get all eight this time
around him up these gouges will not hear
the last time that these two that's
correct
okay not that not that they recall so
she's been real prison to maybe she
never got all the way out we did leave
yeah prematurely oh well but now that's
something he'd have been she at least
she knows where she is and has been
trying to get her out that's true yeah
unsuccessfully yeah very preoccupied
business okay can I do a perception
check to see if the floor is safe to
walk on yeah they probably know that of
course okay yeah but do you never been
here before
that's a 20 okay so when you are when
you pulled yourself up from your vessel
below you got a sense that whatever this
structure was because space and
orientation are they're not set sir in
this place this is a bizarre abstract
place even then this thing doesn't
appear to have full control it's not
maintaining any kind of static position
in space it seems to be turning slightly
and tilting and it's not
it isn't perfecting its gravity
internally so it's sort of like it's
tilting a little bit now to one side but
it's sort of like bobbing almost like a
cork in this in this abstract plane do I
feel do I feel like I can walk on it you
can walk on it but it's honestly it
recalls a ship
okay very slowly rocking ship okay so
it's an unsteady but it does have a
source of gravity hope that won't allow
me to walk yeah yeah yeah I mean it's
it's definitely odd and then we need to
be conscious of it but alright so I will
leave the boat and walk with some amount
of uncertainty at first but then more as
I get my sea legs so speak and I'm gonna
go examine Oaks prison with a great deal
of trepidation yeah absolutely
oak does not appear the the sheath of
mineral that surrounds him is not
substantial you can see around the rest
of the around the rest of this strange
vessel the columns at each of these
vertices that are holding these potent
divine entities those are very robust
they are massive in scale this is much
more like you would think of as a coffin
or it's a very very small thing but it
is translucent enough to see him trapped
inside is the malecón also that thick
well it is yeah it is very very dense in
the front you can see you can see
through them but there is no comparing
the amount of just pure volume of
material between what what it perceives
is sufficient to contain hope true
strike right and what is sufficient to
contain an entity like maelys but as I
suggested before this this place is
utterly surrounded by entities that are
encased this is a kind of divine museum
in a way I don't know how many roughly
I'm just carrying there there appear to
be eight eight others eight it's
basically it is an octave moving right
yeah including okay no no it's not
including oh oh okay but including me
including me with this and they're all
made with sighs maximum-security pillars
yeah okay
they are exactly yeah there it's there's
there's if there was a vacancy sign out
they would be off it would it would no
no it would be on as well but no as you
can see it there is there is one point
of distinction between oak true strikes
prison and the ones that have been
instantiated around and that is
incredible Wi-Fi four times yes five
bars hell yeah cool
yeah wpa2 so it's is that no is that it
is it appears to be leaching something
out oh so this entity is like draining
him of something that's that is a
legitimate interpretation of what is
happening okay
I mean it would require some it would
require some real some real specific
know how to assess like what exactly is
happening but you can see something you
can see something really imagine like
like you know you shine a flashlight
through your skin and you can see that
pattern it looks like that except it is
coming out forking and branching through
sort of the substrate of this of this
geometric entity I want to also step out
of the boat and before I walk over to
the oak column I'm going to attempt to
use awakened mind if I'm going to first
locate fear the symbol on one of these
columns absolutely Mabel yes it is plain
to you yes I want to reach out and see
if I can communicate absolutely let's
see so the last time it yeah didn't make
an attempt to talk to it it talked to me
that's right and so when you when you
reach out with your mind you can you can
you get a response but you get the
impression that it is being
Len store I think the term is per
debated
it's like muffled in a way yeah it's but
exactly exactly so you so you know that
it is communicating you know that
information is coming through but this
is what you receive Oh obviously Oh feel
free to put in the dice tray yeah well
yeah Bret's I don't know I assume that's
that's the way up sex naive he solved it
already I proceeded to whip it on and up
so the so the information comes through
and you you just you know that that is
not you know that the ER does not
communicate in this way that it is being
lens or perturbative again like does it
like fog with does it feel like it's not
of its own making
in other words like yes do I feel yeah
that it's not like speaking to me in a
code it's like I've lost all the upper
frequencies like I can hear it through
the wall and then I can't make it out
okay yeah exactly because because
anything you know how the ER would speak
to you in words of comfort or you know
if they really if the ER was trying to
comfort cthe wrists robe it would be it
would communicate something like well
there exists light and light moves and
light moves in such a way that we can be
certain right of its behavior in my
proofs first yeah yeah exactly then
that's that's how it does it it does not
communicate in ciphers he doesn't
anything like that but again feel this
is this is an incredible opportunity I
mean you're adorned with this you're
adorned with this creatures signal yeah
I'm nauseated by this like this is not
this is the opposite of what I know this
looks like a migraine written down in
words yeah I am gonna approach with my
arcane focus and
is there what's the scale difference
here in my perception of the ER symbol
on the crystal versus the one that I
hold but just in terms of like how large
yeah how its represented on them it is
exactly the same in size as well but
it's just basic it's got a vector it's
like you can stretch it in any direction
and it retains oh yeah I figured no I
why this is tough those symbols are
those symbols exist on each one of these
columns and they're all legible I mean
every one of these columns is legible to
you this is a this is a new dress of
sorts a rebirth some kind maybe at least
a metaphorical one so instead of
ignoring everybody I'm going to know
turn to you and say I need to know what
we want to do about oak first because if
I approach with my focus and things
start to happen you are all dead to me
maybe let's take care of what we came
here to do first love you too buddy and
I mean I don't I don't mean it with any
you know harm in my heart you know that
I just will not care about what happens
to this disgusting thing oak true strike
I'm not interested in his plight his
actions freeing him what does that mean
the nuts from before believe it or not
become meaningless believe it or not
believe it or not my god that is trapped
here
so should we tend to oak first only they
get him out of the way I have a text
message what about from who from Patrick
Rothfuss brah he says that right now
Rosie senses that dream isn't that's
really trying to figure out how to vape
a piece of bacon sorry back to this cool
story that's the key that's what we
needed put that in the cipher see ya
trivial I saw and I'm stepping out of
the boat and everything and emotion to
me let me go I don't know if we actually
hold any power here it seems that you
know what we thought we did was undone
mm-hmm I think we can easily free oak
and then recapture him better than we
did before
to what end but I think maybe maybe this
is a little beyond us and I just want to
set your expectations I know you're
excited
trembling set that there's truth here to
this Rosie still has her bracelet yeah
um she just she knows that you know if
you get out of hand
well continue well how are you feeling
wall nice feeling thanks briefly about
mailers thing they're awful like just
powerless like they like wants obviously
just very right I'm like preoccupied
with the fact that mail is here and
still trapped and that she couldn't do
right like she thought she did and that
this entire time she's you know kind of
sitting pretty and feeling really you
know good about what she'd done rescued
my god right I wash tag but I remember
that one of the things that my god
communicated to me was free Nayla 'the
first which is why we tried and I
assumed that it had worked it did not
work does that continue to be the thing
that we need to do did he say anything
to you this time I can't communicate
with it I got something scrambled back
what are the other gods what do we see
prevented from communicating so do you
what do you want to observe it okay so
so I mean you should definitely go to
the go to the front desk so the
concentrate section get like the audio
tour yeah no totally I do that um
pop them on mm-hmm start moving around
take sport of space yeah
you can't read the symbols around there
what do I do I see things in absolutely
yeah yeah you see all manner of creature
where's my mail within in relation to
the herb God maelys is so it goes around
male a--the is one away from there yeah
exactly there is a God between the ER
and Malin I try and talk to male it at
least just try yeah yeah yeah you do you
gather this is this is why we're here
well that this is prime prime God talk
supposed to do yeah yeah this is this is
um it's like 18 minutes yeah I mean
these are my my anytime these are my any
ties ER they roll over roll over so I
want to walk up to the prison where my
oath is and again put my hand on it and
just say you know I'm sorry what what
can I do what could I possibly do and
see if I get anything from that anything
yeah absolutely
so it's she is served enmeshed in clouds
and violet vapor but the hand comes out
and when you saw her before she was in
active torment yeah the hand comes out
and is gentle and holds itself that's
gross
never know looks so gentle yeah exactly
you put your hand out there and this
hand comes out as well and when it does
oh and you get the sense you get to you
get the sense that she wants yeah it's
like a fortune-teller yeah like a little
thicker like do you get to sense that
she has messages for your friends also I
sense that you sense that okay she wants
to talk to others through you so I'm
over here and I go man wants to talk to
all of you over here
I say say no more then I walk over and
just put my hands on your head
what is it okay it's me I would put that
in there cuz Naoki Twilight all right
the Wookiee toys milky of course oh yeah
this is your this is your theory are you
guys you over there decoding this shit
they're off by the same amount so oh so
you heard so he heard something
yeah I heard that you're a separate
chunk second here with denars hands over
yeah
am I just like mushing like Rosie get
over here all right I'll hop up on your
back and put my hands on your head it
didn't work nurse think get to work yeah
fingers in your mouth just stay put yes
yes yes I should've known I'm obviously
in concentration easier safer here I
mean you could tell in the game also
that I'm I am I'm thinking and I person
yes come here well Leakey yes my queen
she has something to say to you I I bow
deeply like like in a supplicated way
and I just sigh and then I touch him so
that yeah here yeah there's a strand
yeah you want to put in here sure what
do you got so far
looking at this already wkh has used a
lot yeah we have uh well we have exw
it's a rot for I think yeah but this
this does not match this why would it
what do you mean it doesn't miss it well
so exw using your code is haz oh sure oh
I see so maybe everybody yeah or it
could be like a low caste thing it could
be like a cheeseburger thing I'd be like
you know can't has let's try it we don't
know how it communicates has it mean
this is here no guys tell me at iPod
next I really want to stop what we're
doing and solve this
no you do not you were obligated to
solve this in real time well do that
because I'm gonna shouldn't have given
it to you should know well I think it
makes sense that I think this risk oh no
honestly dude whose 3d characters we're
doing what you want to do is like
totally okay but then they also the idea
that dinar is like I could do it yes I
wanna know you you can roleplay listen
we keep a good time all right give me a
puzzle I'm gonna solve a puzzle it is
okay okay
so I want to go over to UM to Oak now
yeah and I want to just gauge do I think
that I have the strength in some form to
get through this you could try
can i it would be completely legitimate
for you to do that put your things back
in the dice tray so that people at home
can work on a cotafamily4 fun yeah okay
for America's youth hey can I roll to
get a better sense maybe of like what
what how do you want to how do you want
to approach it cuz I am ready - I'm
ready to play this however you want I'm
thinking if I do a survival check on it
that maybe I would know sometimes ah
maybe I would know what to use here yeah
absolutely
okay I'm gonna roll for it whoo 15 15 so
this you are pretty clear looking at
this yeah you think that it may not be a
hundred percent safe Oh to get him out
and you were you also think that the
entity you are being you also think the
entity is being poisoned in some way
like this looks to you like just this is
your read as a as a druid of the Enclave
that the path of this this sort of
invasive red forking material it looks
to you like a blood poison Chris that's
going
into it just cleaning out somehow into
can I um hmm is that there are these
veins are they like about are they on
the surface I think no no no they're in
or they're similar to their underneath
if they're similar to when you saw the
when you saw the wandering crypt right
the sort of trails that it would leave
where the symbols were sort of like in
the substrate okay so you so these this
this forking fluid is it running along
these tracks that otherwise would not be
visible
it may not be amethyst in the classic
sense you don't you know a lot about
poison and life in general and you were
not aware that rocks could be poisoned
okay that's new info that's something to
find wait is it moving from oak to now
it is moving from oak out it also be
traveling into these god it is it is
leaking out into the into the cathedral
itself I don't like that yeah it seems
bad but I think it's not safe to try and
get him out you think it may not be safe
for him yeah it's very safe for you you
don't think you don't think you're in
any danger I'm okay with that
it's may leaking I don't want that
wanted to get past us sorry yeah thank
you
all right um Joyce okay so I think I can
bust him out of here and kill him is
this is this like a brittle thing like
you do I feel like I'm looking at like a
salt rock type thing yeah yeah it's it
yeah it looks like a like a glass oh can
you hear me like you know squeaky glass
I mean he can move exactly does he seem
like he's awake that you don't really
you don't see him stirring in there like
male if you see that you see the other
entities stirring yeah all right but we
can converse with with male if we can't
like I can climb in oak affect me if I'm
looking at him so I roused myself from
my puzzle puzzling yeah I'm so angry at
this right here it's talking to me don't
get to know what it is yes
did you get it yeah but didn't you do
don't you have a ability that allows you
to read languages like Vantage on this
wrist receives this he can he just reads
it right away so what is real language
yes more fun if I tried to yeah yeah I
put it back in the box if it had been
probably listen if it had been proper
you exactly if they've been proper
language listen everybody I thought this
was the but it doesn't scale for the
rest of it but there's a string this is
scale for that so I thought maybe
they're markers for different ones so
we'll see um yeah but I wonder so I'm
gonna put that down for the moment I'm
gonna stock over to oaks tiller slink
over defeated Frances Oh what did you do
what happened hey dizzy yelling at
everyone wake up the voice that comes
from the crystal is like eiseley calm
you don't know if it is because oak true
strike is an operator is the kind of
operator that he believes himself to be
and actively projects to others or if he
isn't his calm or if he is he if he
isn't some kind of truly existential
shock mmm-hmm
what's in it he says you spoke to drawn
enterprises also called alright try to
remember what could thrist told you of
that oh you are well aware though by the
end of it might remember that was one of
my favorite scenes in the holy season
where you came in at the end of the game
it's like to hold the final fight
starting up and you're at the tree and
you're like hey just want to let
everybody know real quick definitely
talk to dry enterprises try this trick I
sort of took a job with them decided not
to do it is that the same as being a
good person I don't know but I
really relay that immediately to
everybody he says that he spoke to drawn
enterprises what did they want from you
what did they want from you
well we both ended up here I have a
plenty of time to wait
it would appear what did they want from
me okay well I remember they wanted me
to they wanted me to kill someone who I
did not kill who I found it unnecessary
to kill what about yourself who didn't
you kill just I have time to yeah they
are obsessed with the wandering Crypt
towing only because of the wandering
crypts connection to this I relate that
to you did you dine with them yeah oh
yeah did you turn into liquid too
you went to that restaurant I don't
think any of those under dark delicacies
are actually from the under dark I've
only been there the once hmm but I don't
it wasn't very good was it yeah it
wasn't very good
I think they fed me something like a
something that would make you worthy of
being imprisoned by this worthless deity
I think it was important to them that I
be consumed by this hmm did they ask you
to kill you did they just find a very
roundabout way to do it I asked me to
kill somebody else it didn't come up
okay we should let him be trained so the
fingers off
yeah the fingers off that's right I can
go back to him but let's talk about it
well okay that's not what our job was
yeah I'm not a big fan of what drawing
Enterprises is after either
I just feel like if they want it it's
not a good thing there are other ways to
be obsessed with that crypt sure I'm
obsessed with it every night when I go
to sleep can't stop obsessing about it
Oh minute what is obsessed with it and
we got a lot of good work we've met a
lot of cool people nice experiences yeah
we have you can closer look at look at
this video montage I made I'm yeah I'm
Mac yeah okay so mmm
yeah no we should let him go but so
drawn I'm John enterprises wanted him
where he is right now
so freeing him will foil them yes and we
don't like them yeah and we like him no
somebody should get him now in fact if
we're going to get in trouble for not
turning oak in or letting him get away
the fact that we're screwing John
enterprises might curry some favor with
our boss it's true so let's just bust
him out
listen I don't think it's entirely safe
for him but also I don't care don't
worry no he's gonna be fine Fred I don't
care for you or this prison but you know
there's still a there is there are many
axes of benefit I think that I think we
can both agree you know here there's not
a lot I can do for you out there
Wow it's a good case very in distress
well yeah we were sold already yeah we
had a private conversation with our
mouths that can move so yeah
what's the can you give us any insight
into your prison what is s no I there
was never I didn't want to come in here
I did not study this I was not trying to
go here he was unprepared so it's it
sniffed me out somehow I don't know what
I don't know what they did to make me so
irresistible but it's it's it's not a
new problem
let's put it that way don't like the
test markets broken also yeah it's got a
back door some problems there's some
bugs and features yeah we are finding
all right all right well all right yeah
I'll try to get him out
do it do it should I give it a whack
yeah do them please all right dude let's
do a thing I will unilaterally attack
him just trying to think how a mellow I
guess in case I just cleave right
through the man is him to exit yeah yeah
all right I'll say hey hey stand back
yeah stand back from the door toothbrush
out swing low so if I do cut through get
them at this below the knee I guess yeah
non lethal non-lethal right and yeah
that's all see how it goes okay what
happens
give me a strike and some damage and
that'll tell me a lot of information
direct it well it auto connects right
he's not gonna dodge it I'm gonna use
all this information to determine
exactly what happens
oh so I'm just rolling straight for
damage roll all the dice all right I'm
gonna roll all the dice all right don't
even think advantage I want to make sure
I connect okay we'll take the and also
that you do it with precision well
that's a 20 see if I roll to go to
twenties yeah all right now let's see
sort of this tender critical damage all
right so 2d six plus three I mean well
yeah 2d six plus three slashing I mean
I'm not gonna I don't think I'm gonna
smite this I don't know what's gonna
happen
exactly this is a test swing go ahead Oh
11 okay he's cleaved in Twain
that's fine I can take him off at the
knees I can heal him here which
of the toothbrush are we using here I'm
using the the toothy side are we using
we're using the blade side okay we don't
we're not you're not trying to saw in no
I'm just trying to give it a good whack
okay gun axe game is Oak 40 whacks
exactly oh I do have a war pic shouldíve
that
yeah well today feel like that would
have been great war pic real good yeah
um so you bring pubes you bring
toothbrush down on top of this thing but
I'd done down low yeah they weren't
harvesting it I'm going out wide yeah
imagine a dark harvest that's all I can
imagine so you are able to basically you
connect it you connect with it and then
crack it and it sort of slides like a
puck on ice no but the entire prison
with him in it just goes okay don't
think but this is this is vitally
important this piece this piece this
piece of it is vitally important you
take five points of damage as soon as
you as soon as you slice this thing and
it starts to slide over you get to see
where this red material has eaten
through and you can see that it is like
almost like imagine like ice fishing
we're just right in the top that's the
central yeah hole chewed through and as
you hit him that way and he slides over
a bunch of this stuff splashes up on you
oh and so you begin to think about
things that you haven't thought of in
years there is a moment where you are
alone and the only member of your family
that will deign to speak to you you know
what you've done but you don't
understand why they're so angry and he
picks you up
and then from that moment on it's like
when you try to remember a dream like
the harder you try to remember it
mm-hmm the more the details fade away
and after a few seconds you don't
remember what you were thinking about
anymore okay so this stuff is like
separating in this yeah in this crack so
all right these are it's a this is a a
sad emotional memory that this caused
this is memory fluid ish and then in a
certain is that when I get out of this
well yeah but when you think back you
can't find the memory anymore okay so
you you just you see it's like it's like
just fuzzy like first it's the edges
like you're like back to the hands like
you know someone was lifting you yeah
and then even the memory of the pressure
on your back and the support and the
face like these are all going out of
focus and then the more you try to keep
hold of one the more you lose the rest
of them hmm oh my god this is a do I
recognize this fluid or anything no okay
no no you have never seen anything like
this okay I don't know anyway this
states yeah yeah that's all I got it's
incredibly it it someone someone put a
lot of thought and time into it so if
you imagine I don't mean me I mean
however this however this came to be
there's some stratagem that you have
stepped into the middle of yeah and they
you try to imagine you can see even now
you can see it forking out toward the
divine entities at the pillars but it is
still continuing to worm its way through
these cracks saying through the channels
right okay so they weren't it wasn't it
wasn't drawing from okay this was a well
he was just sitting on top of like I
think they fed him something and it
maybe made him poisonous to this thing
like they sent him in as a human snack
face for the mouth hey how is it going
with the code oh good so good kids you
got some hot shit I do
god damn gonna help us solve this puzzle
it's not for you guys it's for this it's
for the shadow counts yeah well I should
say well why didn't you tell us because
you're having too much fun I'm not gonna
stop you you're having too much fun well
you made this cool matrix well
actually Chris solved it but I just oh
shit right after those that yeah don't
want to know stop the podcast ever okay
okay what do you want to do with this
Jerry whatever you want no no cuz Chris
knows who you give our messages how am I
reading it okay but there's wood know it
yeah the only one I don't know is my own
okay that's okay go ahead I think it's a
lot of junk I think it was a lot of
garbage - me well mine had the X please
order it in correct order Jerry I think
I maybe I never do that is the one that
looks he has the word listen
mine's the exclamation point okay your
exclamation point it spoke to you first
yeah what was that uh and then this one
was yours just last it must have been Oh
mine was absolutely last okay
so then that seems to be the right color
it's the same thing Oh
so what sorry did I just do it I must
have just started doing it wrong okay
enough enough drama
uh guy I I who did it all by myself
apparently just in world I just vomited
out no you know what it is dude it's
gonna be totally like that grandma that
does like the crosswords oh yeah exactly
like custard oh honey she's like yeah
yeah I've been reading my whole life I
can do the jumble without even writing
anything down yeah it's like I don't
want I don't want cthe wrists to have
all the credit no Rosie okay
oh my god tell holy crap say can we have
10 more minutes of this no it's not it's
just an ad it says we didn't character
okay so how does it happen
I just I I suddenly Neal I realize what
it says I start saying the void child
the divine prison
it spray may slip the trap devoured but
not consumed but no the last must be
first could be let's read it again
that's quite good
let's move it here that's quite good the
ER is gonna have to procure a little bit
more my device for this avoid child the
divine poison its prey may slip the trap
but no sorry devoured but not consumed
but no the last must be first the last
must be first
well the last is oak it's a hen's little
stack structure we have to get his data
off first
great I'm off so he's just by the
natural listing of this thing oak is
just sort of traveling around the fluid
that well yeah what if that do we know
we saw you were affected by well yeah I
guess I would say impresses yeah yeah
well I don't know like so how would you
exactly how would you it's challenging
if your memory is immediately erased
then how would you even know cuz you can
feel it slipping I think it was it's
definitely a process it's like you know
the tip of the tongue worried yeah I
know that word I've said a million times
but I cannot recall it now yeah I think
that's what yeah that's be something to
that effect this would be jarring and it
would be then I would be freaked out
anybody yelling and then mumbling and
you know used yelling at the hole yeah
just the weight come back I you I the
first line of Lovecraft story Polaris is
good it's as if that star he's looking
at the hideously winking eye struggling
to convey something but finding nothing
save which that it is forgotten what it
was trying to convey like it's the exact
same emotion yeah that so you're just
going yeah and I say the juice heard him
yeah he burned say it's
it's making me forget don't touch it
let's make any taken memories and this
was I was decoding this happened when
you came in contact with the fluid yes
I knocked oak and slid off this top of
this well like a hockey puck and then
there's go underneath and it splashed up
okay so did some precious memories did
the prison take any damage the prison is
seeing the prison is no longer attached
to the to the entity hmm
all right slide him onto the boat well
yeah one yeah
yeah I'm really interested in this fluid
though yeah that's right I mean wait
what did you forget
yeah what did you forget Who I am
so we work together for a while
experientially I forgot something right
I am a memory that was forgotten
Table Talk II there's temporal stuff
that goes on was this forgotten or was
this timeline messed with
right right okay dad I don't know that's
that's a legitimate question that's a
good time you hear a hear almost like it
sounds like fingernails or like I'm like
what a cat is trying to move on a slick
floor and then from the aperture below
the in the in the center that central
ring yeah you can see a figure and then
another figure is pull themselves up
wait wait the same way you pull up like
out of a pool um
they pull themselves up and the second
one as he comes up immediately once he
gets up sort of rolls over on his back
and starts to hold his side and he's
he's breathing is pretty ragged he is
dressed in a sort of loose-fitting I
mean if you if you didn't know better
Rosie you would say that it was monastic
in nature okay it looks like the sort of
simple ritual garb that would endure
days and nights of fasting training in
prayer what
racist he looks to you like he has a
mixture of features okay so it's you
can't map them all correctly he's there
tall like an elf would be who but they
have a an especially pallid skintone
ranging almost into like lime green
almost okay bald head with what looks to
be sort of ritual tattoos inscribed
elven ears but sort of ragged on the
edge and they don't have a nose like we
would think of it okay hmm I don't like
handsome fella you should get we should
just put oak in the boat we should just
take him from that from the top aperture
to more figures enter mm-hmm thank you
will you really should go they do and
these these look down at their prey they
pay the party or your hockey puck friend
precisely zero notice and they they sort
of float down gently like like like like
board gods they just dropped down a
leisurely pace their gleaming silver
swords out ready to do work these these
fellows are not bald of head they
haven't they have a tall delicious
coiffeur mmm-hmm great hair yeah
much like like substantially more
ornamented of dress there's nothing
monastic about their mode in any way
they say make see nuts skin and all that
yes you think that if you were to ask
them maybe they would say that there's a
lot of fine distinctions you're just
appreciating yeah but they are well
armored they have the skin shows but
wherever there is not flesh there is
armor sore so ornate that you can't you
can't imagine how a person would
manufacture it it looks like they must
have it must just occur naturally
somewhere it must just be like a
creature they found and you know the
creature agreed to let them wear it like
it it doesn't the its construction is
profound and artful hmm like Monster
Hunter mmm they haven't noticed us or
they have noticed us and they don't care
they don't seem to give a shit okay they
these these groups of people so as they
are beginning to float down the tooth at
the base when one of them is hurt very
badly his ornamentation is slightly more
it prepares to denote rank or something
it's not flashy by any means but there's
clearly more to it
Colter you can sense the cultural weight
of his raiment guys compared to his
companion and his his young friend is
trying to help him to his feet as these
cruel creatures sort of descend from the
ceiling do you made notice oh absolutely
yeah that appears to be the motivating
factor okay so there okay so there
they're pulling themselves up from the
ground yeah they're coming down from the
ceiling and the creatures on the ground
know that these ones are coming Oh
exactly
no no no no they are from there he's
getting his friend up okay Katrina light
it I've managed this yes are we gonna
intervene well I was just gonna say
initiative is good yes weird what are
you you can always act on you on your
initiative in such a way use game I
refuse to be ignored yeah hey hey okay
those guys I I'm assuming that they're
know that the
on the bottom is virtually gonna go and
like we're fighting in and around the
boat give me a give me a let's see we'll
be the good one here
boat check reception boat position check
that's nothing Fernandez Oh Joey that
was actually gonna be my initiative role
but let's say it's the percent okay it's
terrible and I'm ashamed of you all
right now initiative for those folks at
home that really follows first I used my
turn to take a look at what's right here
so what do you have done our butts in
twelve okay how about you walnut diagram
for that's low
how about you Rosie B's here seven it's
pretty good no but you could first grab
come on 21:21
really yeah well I think it's 22 a job
plus three oh yeah 22 listen you did a
great job
mmm and I appreciate it so so the these
these creatures that are now descending
at a rate of their choosing
have begun to mutter to the other to
their opponents apparently at the base
yeah and if you if you look up through
the aperture that exists in the ceiling
as well there is a shape there that
takes up the entire hole okay with
something beyond no it's the apertures
not wide enough to take it in
there's just something occluding it up
there does it appear it let it like like
hovering over it like if it could climb
in it would what is you know it's like a
it's like a imagine that this it already
has the cast of a beautiful perfume
bottle just imagine that there is just
something that can perfectly fit into
the top it's just massive okay
gosh do I waste this good ol we want to
do gang because my answer is just to
talk to these people we're going
very weird I my instincts to be like
what are you doing here yeah you get it
out of the way if they're a grass I ball
hit okay uh let's see if they can
understand my speech friends you may
enjoy your quarry at your leisure if
you'd give us but a moment to load our
cargo into our vessel and while you're
saying while you're saying this it's
sort of tilted and like behind you okay
Shh
sliding big wind upside think of what an
unsatisfying murder it would be to have
your your prey knocked aside by this
careless crystal prison let us load it
and and be gone and oh well the the one
nearest you
near the the event horizon mmm in the
base of the structure doesn't look at
you he is keeping his eye on these new
challengers to leverage a piece of
street fighter nomenclature we've
entered for lack of a better term hmm
yeah I get it
yes you know that he is speaking to you
but he does not look he is maintaining
his his attention right on these new
foes and he says so you're wasting your
breath they won't deign to speak your
tongue and he's but he's speaking mine
clearly okay alright
he said that the injured guy yeah he
says this is this is not your fight so
we should leave them my recommendation
well where would you most like to die
thought about at this point it's not in
this room Chris definitely would have an
extremely specific answer yes I got
asked gets so excited he were like oh
thank you for asking one finally uh let
me give me let me read you my screenplay
actually New York yeah
yeah exterior shot a handsome two-door
we see a young Chris me with that shit
all right
I think that there's two people here who
have like actually written screenplays I
mean I think that that's what we were
seeing there yes
where would we most like to die um he
said he says if it does not involve this
place there are two exits mm-hmm you
heard him I'll help the boat are they
descending so in such a bored way that I
feel like I have time to parlay with but
they have I mean they have an initiative
and that's when they'll act Oh can you
can you see my UI goes beautifully from
this News Corp yeah manufactured by
clues Corp industries what were you what
were you here to do what brought you
here
steal something is it important yeah
we're in this we're kind of in the same
boat
aha fast friends so listen you feel just
sort of you feel like that pressure on
your mind
from the earth like not communication
just presence just awareness presence
yeah Center oh it's like I feel like I'm
being judged
exactly and so this thing starts to spin
like a tilt-a-whirl oh no hmm hmm get
that we'll get your bearings do we have
rope let's try on the lashes or
something okay
your grandmother's rope stuff yeah I can
look at it back when he you got he
proofed Oh
okay yeah yeah wait okay now the rub is
never okay something's gonna happen that
rope one day and I beat this today's
that day yeah okay yeah you can't send
that out for rope season it's just like
you need buy the rope yeah exactly no
it's like it'll be the framing device
but no so this this thing has begun to
really really move like it's like um
it's like when one of the big kids comes
over on the playground like one of the
big kids and it's like too much okay the
issue is that it is moving in space and
it's not a hundred percent yeah it isn't
a hundred percent lateral yeah we're not
gonna get our like you can't just hold
on cuz maybe it'll shift that way yeah
so we're gonna have a heck of a time
managing that crystal exactly you can
notice so you see on his chest you can
see that he has he is wearing something
that looks like a medallion but is is of
novel make so a medallion round it's got
something cool in it right this
instrument for a lack of a better term
is almost like a circle of beads and you
can see his fingers moving very quickly
around its edge like spinning parts of
it around and he'll spin part it around
flip it turn it reverse it
[Music]
no do I recognize these gestures do you
think that you think that these gestures
are forcing or something like them are
probably common too
you think these gestures something like
this are probably common to sects of
things
nice do you reckon you recognize them
I see I think oh can I do a history
check to see if I know anything about
this garb or you sure sure sure
it's a 21 mm that's quite good
thank you there is a there is a so this
is this is all gonna be footnotes this
is gonna be like in the the parts of the
book that would be like directors
commentary for a DVD right you you're a
well-read woman you have had a lot of
time to study religion and there are
sects for a lack of a better term that
torille is not the only place where gods
are worshiped there are other places
other realms other gods and occasionally
their documents find their way into even
the prime material plane from other
places and you think that it is an
unbroken circle of Zartha mom so it's a
device of meditative practice for those
who there's a sort of a bipartite a
bifurcated race of the gifts RI and
another race that was not in the
document that you read about but they
broke off from them and this is
basically like a holy fidget spinner oh
now I get it
hmm I got you so this thing is now begin
to turn on its axis you can see oak true
strike sort of like lift up oh my god
get it off that off the bottom and then
so
strike up high and then bounce off and
then bounce on another side and then
bounce on another side and when it hits
the last side it shatters hmm
Ochs does the whole thing shatters all
the structure and its contents well
shatter what so is he just a exploded
pile of meat that is now whirling around
in chunks of glass inside this space
hmm Oh was obliterated well wait we
didn't save him this is a time to puzzle
I got I can't I can't heal that I can't
lay on hands bad guys can't lay on here
I'm like grabbing pieces click so high
I'm trying so dinar blitz in it is your
turn you are get oke precious yeah my
whole plan was gonna be to try to move
him in that towards the boat that's gone
so you were very near to this hole that
exists in the base of memory zapping no
no memory stabbing thing is over here
separating so this hole is in the base
of this Cathedral which is where you
came in yep
and when you look down you do not see a
boat well so we got a you do not see a
boat but every rotation of this thing
you see what looks like in the space
outside of this realm you see something
that looks like a like imagine a puddle
like in a parking lot that is sort of
has a whale rainbow mm-hmm that's slick
on top of it so it looks like so like
every two rotations you see this
disk of color is it familiar to us as
what we drifted through like that that
field that we came here that we saw the
boat you it's right yeah absolutely you
have seen these from time to time and
you are welcome to interact with this
conceptually well we got one more we've
had this before they do something yeah
get out well yeah we were here too we
were here to steal something we were in
here steel oak back
are these the security guards
essentially I know that what this is
here's what I'm thinking I don't know
what like I let me know I mean obviously
my turns done I could cast fly on you
and hopefully you can carry us out of
here I don't I can't do it yet but I'm
worried that this if I were to give it
to you then you would be set in some
absolute coordinate system and then
would be destroyed against the side of
it as it moves relative to it yeah can
you rez people from pulp that's my
thinking we save a piece of them how
much of him is on us yeah - we don't
have any yeah I don't know how rez works
any boat shaped you could get some and
and securing some is not a terrible idea
some of the pulp is head floating no no
cuz you know how did this like oak with
Pope yeah yeah that's where all the
vitamins are though yes head floating
around me paper it or that's the biggest
what's the biggest thing she's
completely just mulched even get some
ground beef just you can reach it you
can reach out and get a chunk you want
me to do me tell you what exactly
whatever say what's your oak table
you're here you have an oak table here
let me make a real quick Oh chunky table
alright put head on there I want a
chance to get his head but a portion of
his scalp yeah close enough you're like
I was wait oh wait it's just like
sifting through it it's like what are
those lily machines part of a foot no oh
alright conveyor belt oak I'll
the Pascal was it's just it's it's
actually a really fresh way to get your
own yeah all right I grab a scalp okay
now we'd I defer I don't know
did we want to fight these guys I don't
want to fight I want to we want to
defend these guys at all well you are a
paladin so what would dinar do there we
know they just admitted their themes so
Phoebe you know that lawful good right
now yes today in this space and this
real we're on the road where is best
friend was just exploded and he's all
executive heartbroken
all right he just wants to get out of
there all right we get it
yeah you might take it out on somebody
at that point well who's he gonna blame
the person that made the person go crazy
those guys yeah I guess that's true yeah
get him
is that what he would infer Sikkim boy
I'd seem to have a when they showed I
feel like this is just gonna get me
killed
look alright in presenting in for a
pound
pull you off can't kill two main
characters in one episode right I wear
is that's right put his scalp on like a
hat so power myself oh I put it on top
of Kathy I guess yeah yeah so Kathy's
got like cuz okay a pretty nice hair
right so now it Kathy's have some sick
hair oh it's lustrous yeah mr. potato
you know it is it's pro-v yeah pant in
scaps freshest layer and then i'll love
for my action I'll cast protection from
good and evil and myself okay we're
gonna Rumble all Rumble well sounds good
shadow council mayor leavers please you
we have reached the break point feast
your eyes on these delicious commercials
unless you're a seven which case feast
your eyes on some cool art we will be
back very very shortly don't go anywhere
hello I'm Geoffrey K Hawkins and this is
to see teams know when last we saw
heroes they were suspended inside of a
God's gullet
which had rapidly had been transformed
into a kind of chipper shredder
yeah the very next action
that we have Denard Blitzen took his
turn the very next action is on my
initiative tracker is a piece of plastic
with three skulls on it but you might
not know that what it says on the back
here is bad guy yeah yeah spoilers
obviously so what occurs here is a a
Cirque de Soleil tear Marshall
performance hmm that occurs on surfaces
off surfaces the things about this place
that are off-putting or abstract are not
abstract to these beings this appears to
be they roll out of bed and see
something like this it's not it's not
surprising to them at all
so there are stunning stunning blocks
incredible blows and these two these two
forces arrayed against each other appear
to be as something of a Marshall stand
still
there are I mean they they're not
enjoying this in any way there's zero
respect on either side this is this is
not like when you took your test inside
the staff of the master and found people
willing to teach you and you know
instruct you to the best of their
ability
this is murderous rage but executed at a
similar level of skill on each side
including the the wounded one he has
found a new strength perhaps from his
circle mm-hmm so that is that is what
occurs there is just a whirl of blades
Rosie be stinger yeah you can see that
this this thing is continuing just to
spin and whirl
you're like a old hand on the deck it's
absolutely no problem your feet are
certain ensure on the ground and then
this thing is starting to slow down and
you can see that it has begun to point
at this at this kind of gauzy
rainbow seemed mirror down through the
bottom of it okay so as I'm staring this
fight what is my motivation can I can I
get like do a con check on these and see
like am I would we be able to take them
if we join this fight oh you just want
to use my size him up yeah listen this
is grandmother night sure knows how
okay she knows how to read a fight right
and she knows how she knows if she could
take him right euphemistically that's
speaking yeah there are four of you and
then you know you would choose one of
these two groups and then there would be
six of you that's true
you like these numbers okay um and you
are holding out right you're ready to go
yeah what is walnuts expression what's
she what's her body language she was
like ready to go before this initiative
even started so she's looking toward the
exit she wants she wants to run go go
fight or go run I mean ready to go ready
didn't go like are you ready to go I
don't think that I honestly think she's
at a complete loss
oh just exploded and she's like all of
her ideas that she's been like yeah
pooling about like for vengeance or like
pity things to say to him when she
actually got to stab and I'm just went
out we know yeah you know I think she
could say them all now the end of the
day and could say it to the scalp from
where I what so I like the odds but more
importantly I did not like oak however
he was a member in good standing
she was my great friend alright and
that's right was he no longer a member
in good standing I know he was supposed
to get taken in he was revoked he was a
while longer and I think snow I remember
in good standing look at God standing we
had a conversation he and I and we were
gonna start our own team
okay he was a member in good standing me
here's in good standing a team to know
do if you want to help poor people Oh
stand by you but I think that's the only
motivation is that these these are folks
who speak our language and who are
geared in a way that I recognize as like
a fellow ascetic and so there's an
injustice here that I'm not into so I
would I would go okay hog now go hog so
I'm gonna run up behind these these two
that are fighting on the ground against
the wing at Angel types and I'm gonna
tell you I'll say you two won't be easy
for you today and I'm gonna throw my
staff of the master Cole just dude just
write in the air yeah can i yeah yeah of
course you can use the drink okay that's
not gonna do it
the next one is a 22 hit God and then
yeah I think that's that's all I can do
from down here that's quite solid okay
so then I'll do a that's eight points of
damage very solid nice okay so it
connects it connects with his right
shoulder like in the middle of in the
middle of him trying to dominate this
field and it sort of spins him around
like one full rotation but he after he
turns on this axis he like sort of
reasserts himself that he's got some
kind of a knowledge about this type of
wire fighting but it's just it's the
spin and then the solid stop is a it's
not physics as you understand it but he
definitely spins in the air walnut on
grass I see what's happening here
and I want to look at one of these land
creatures and I point at it like like in
baseball yeah I point right at it and
when I do a silvery beam of pale light
shine shines down home in a five-foot
radius and a 40-foot high cylinder
centered on it dim light fills the
cylinder it is Moonbeam and it's
important
for me to tell you that I'm casting it
at the third level please do a
constitution saving through all right
hmm can do like it and how wide is this
thing is five foot radius 5 foot radius
5 foot radius that's good stuff that's
actually gonna that's gonna clip both of
them good
so the night fails okay how about the
warrior okay the warrior it rolls even
worse if you can believe it
tell me what happens that's unfortunate
because it takes two d-10 radiant damage
unless you cast it using a slot of 3rd
level or higher and the damage increases
by 1 D 10 for each slot level above a
second it's written yeah
good lord you exploded them yeah 1414
and oh honey wants dude this damage is
old enough to drink huh Wow
anyway this is it continues so if they
start their turn in it then also Dan
knows okay this picture of walnut like
not water fine super like oh my god oh
just exploded she's covered in like oak
bits she sees rosie go and she's just
like wow but what's cool is that so this
this shape that you're contained in is
sort of tilting but this cylinder of
light basically goes from the top into
the aperture down through the bottom
so these and the entire thing is bathed
in silver light from this just like
divine rod of moonlight iam Tamara dawn
yeah exactly
so it's great so even in mid even in mid
air so there they are seared by this
cold light yes and do their best to not
be seared anymore charissa Doral
delicious just so you know so they the
the night in the more elaborate of the
armor that definitely made
impression mmm the other one is
terrified yes and by this amount of
torment yeah well it doesn't she's never
done it before I should just let out
this evil like the face doesn't change
what the laugh is out that's right that
was her first Moonbeam yeah do you ever
forget Moonbeam you never forget you
never forget your first movie I think
we're gonna run for that portal right
then I see I think you just leap at them
and you fire the Moon at them the whole
we're leaving guys right well I needed
was some you know dead matter I was
gonna use this guy if he if he died oh
is it time but we got a mess of it flow
out of air yeah let's have it
well and you're literally in the agency
yeah that enables it that's true and I
don't forget and I got I got the herb
watching and I want to time to go to
work like hoping that that's cool thing
to say and I'm gonna do that attend
tacular spectacular absolutely now
tentacular spectacular I goofed around
with this so using the regular
tentacular spectacular right typically
used to require a check at the outset
now it requires a check if you want to
create persistent structures and even
simple devices out of the material right
so you are welcome to annunciate for me
the coolest tentacle what I want imagine
that there is like a subreddit that's
just for tentacle like amethyst
shredding tentacle fiction there is yeah
there is no is there subscribe it's a
moderator actually what I'm saying is
that you should feel very free to
enunciate a profound level is there have
we seen a have motion of this room to
indicate that I mean we haven't gone
flying
in the air yet none of us none of you
have no just bizarre exactly exactly and
now this portal is visible down here you
can see it further through the lower
aperture of the structure but the device
is sort of rotating on an axis now okay
what I want to do is orthogonal to that
axis I want to this guy
I want to pop these tentacles so that
they emerge into these monofilament
wires pieces of oak oh god to spend
themselves across the room and let it
cook these fellows that are in the air
oh my god she's this is why you're a
fine no like a monomolecular cheese
slicer soon as I can get it my good lord
you have a darkness to you so I'm gonna
offer I'm gonna I'm gonna offer them
some saves but I'm not sure if it's
gonna know that is horrible
and you suck well sorry originally it
was gonna be like well I'm sure I could
get a number of them like visible and
but strong and all that but no I'm gonna
go for it like hair thin and if we can
you know wire just Oh Garrett Garrett
wire in up there okay well this so it's
3d twelve let's see if it's so far you
have a seven and a twelve Jesus
good lord
okay so that's twenty for him so the
gifted warrior ii so he had just been
basically incinerated by this angry moon
light and he had sort of in the zero g
he had sort of like drawn himself drawn
him said incinerate me and so then he's
sort of like flexes and then pulls
himself back out of this and it puts him
at the axis just as these just as these
like you know near to monomolecular
wires like shredding wires of life force
and blended with liquid
this is Chris just exactly industry
remember so this thing is spinning
perfectly on a single place like you
would this is what this is look at that
sort of product you would purchase like
at midnight Yeah right I mean you would
you would want this we're inside a
slapshot it's the bullet yeah good
imagine the dark Slap Chop so so this
these these blades just dismantle him in
in seconds in the second oh no and if
you order right now running water white
Senate edge of the dry cloth is stupid
not to buy this here so so now that the
knight is trying to get out of this edge
cotton he's getting even worse ah all
right good warn ya the soccer game no
that's yeah that's no that's 23 into
play you turned it up yeah so it is he
is doing his best to invade them and he
evades most but some of these cut deep
and you can see that it just it comes
around like the meat of his leg and then
he is able to avoid being having it
separated but it just goes around the
bone on a certain axis cut that denied
what said yeah roses like I just wanted
you guys to scare away this guy yeah
this blade like in the course of this -
I was like hulking up like my friends
dead explodes alright those guys were
you just killed the good guys or I could
just finish the other dude off is he
still in fighting shape does he look
like he's done with the rumble you he
wishes that it was over well yeah
let's make it in four I'm gonna make it
over yeah Denarius man dinars man that
Oaks dead and he was the one spinning
his thing here's the money is it still
spinning like is he staying
he's that's the more like it guys on the
ground yeah yeah yeah his videos yeah
how they're both doing good guys doing
it too well I think it's just a good guy
I know this econ he's the one who killed
oak oh you think he's doing this to spin
their vessel yeah I don't know I'm
telling you interpret it
oh he sees when it's spinning he sees
one thing spinning season spinning
Occam's razor yeah this is vicious
manner yeah it is
this is Occam's type on I will grab the
hurt guy and put him to work I'm gonna
dunk him in that pull a bad memory juice
try not to get any on me are you serious
yeah the good guy yeah I'm a good guy
no the bad guy he's in the air he's a
guy who's legally he's still flying I
can't close the distance you can some
care huh I guess I'm gonna run into your
blades
I tried taunt him haha I put him up in
there there's space so as long as we're
not up on this like in the upper third
of the room I could compel duel actually
maybe I'll come calm down call him down
make him go through though I want to see
what the actual movement restrictions
are yes no no no attempt to compel a
duel on a creature one creature he needs
a wisdom saving throw for the duration
he has disadvantage on attack rolls on
anyone other than me must make a wisdom
saving throw any time he tries to go
anywhere that's not towards me the spell
ends if I attack anyone else or if he
gets to slap chopped yeah if a creature
friendly to you damages the target but
this is right oh so we just back off
yeah okay but those this spinning blades
count or is that just a and
environmental at this point it said an
environmental hazard it's like if he
can't if he can't go away from you you
and if he comes to like they're both bad
yeah he's not physically able to get
away exactly so he has to come through
the blades it's like yelling at him
across a bunch of rosebush well and
there's no gotta come through the but
there's also this pretty consistent moon
rock in the middle of the fucking you
know when he starts his turn if he's in
it this is not good yeah did you take
your movement to put the Moonbeam
between you and him and then say come
here yeah might as well right yeah
maximize it all right so you already a
word yeah waste him safe
wisdom save we used to save now he's
very good at wisdom well so let's see
how it goes he's so wise he's wheezy
what's your spell DC 14 okay to - all
right got him Jerry wanted it to happen
this is too exciting we will win it it's
too exciting thumping my chest massive
sword just out like this
yeah calling my shot exactly he is he is
doing everything that he can to Z I got
a peacock around like to beat here's a
round hole yeah he so he is found a
knife Jagger nice leg idiot yeah he is
found a place here a place of safety
where the shredding wands that Karissa
is invented don't get him he cannot move
away from you and if he moves toward you
he gets shredded yes does he have to
does he have to come toward you I don't
think yes to succeed or wisdom saving
through ya not make them you must make
up wasn't saving through each time it
attempts to move to a space that is more
than 30 feet away from me so if he wants
to go away he can't right otherwise he
must yeah he has he's compelled to duel
he has to kind of get over it's got to
get within 30 feet of me okay okay can
he do you from where no it's it's
it's the fact that it's just got to get
in my space there we go
I respect the whole no idea it's old
it's bad you and me mano a mano let's go
uh yeah hey Mick Jagger stretch no
that's 23 that is the last part of his
stuff so so he pauses and you call him
out and then his brow furrows and he
moves forward strategically and he's
just about got it and then it's like
it's like he has it until he does it
right he's gotten through a lot of it
and then all of a sudden it's just wrong
and he gets caught sort of on the edge
of it and then flung into the rest of it
so it is continuing to spin up there and
then down at the circle he's the other
monk is continuing to just spin spin his
device and he says be praised come on
cool is it my turn are we still an
initiative order uh it is the initiative
order is done because there's no one
here who wants to kill you okay great
hmm that was my question
yeah he's a little monk dude one now
killer yeah okay but it doesn't seem
like it yeah what were you here to steal
yeah my first question yeah were they
here this deal yeah Rosie's addressing
and tending to the one that looked
exactly they just say it's the same one
that's that's spinning it and you notice
that he seems like his his wounds seem
better okay uh and I put my hand gently
on him when I said there's there's no
more need for prayer anxiety you're safe
there's always a need for prayer oh of
course
Rosie's not a tremendously religious
person yes she always remembers that
other monks are yes I a so of course I
mean that prayer yeah that's the good
kind that you always need she's trying
to get into late chill with the spinning
yeah jello what about what this guy said
yeah what are you here to steal him
steal so he speaks in a language that
doesn't parse to his to his assistant
this much
much lower rank like that as soon as as
soon as these words are emitted
he's just snaps right to attention comes
over and then sort of ritually prepares
his robe like tightens the belts like
fastens everything up make sure that
everything is exactly right and he says
some blood some blood not much
whose blood my blood
it's like if it's not in our studies I
got okay hey he says there's a market
for God's blood God's blood mm-hmm
where's the connection so that market
what he says I take it you've never been
here before
no I point to the memory fluid is that
God blood no no I didn't think so I know
it's not that I was testing you and you
passed he says there are it's an
incredible material and it has many uses
and this is a great place to give it how
do you get it out of these gods well he
says so there are gods that float in
this place dead gods like islands and it
is possible with the correct ritual in
preparation to extract some of that
essence do you know how to get the gods
out of these pillars if you can get the
blood out can you get the data he says
they say he keep he is walking around he
says this is an odd place have you been
here before we're not in this room but
on this plane oh yeah the astral planet
I see I don't know why I start getting
accusatory okay that's not you've said a
man oh dude he what he walks around is
his hands are folded behind his robe hmm
and he is looking at the pillars and he
says this is not yours it's not your
vessel no never touch the stuff yeah
we're here to steal God's it's
interesting though that three of the
pillars that were here before were
directly related to us and things that
we care about so is it theirs do they
still are I mean there's still more
pillars here that you can explai can
examine it and support you like yeah
well that's my doing conducted can I
just walk around and let's let's rattle
them off yeah absolutely yeah how much
oak this red oh I have to like what
exactly so but so as as he is walking or
as he is walking around um he like he's
sniffing the air and then he's like it's
like tasting like a me no no I could
Chuck like a like a professional like
taster yeah he's just like he's so sick
he licks his finger he's like rubbing in
the air and he's tasting it and he's
furnace brow he's just he's walking from
pillar to pillar and he says there's
God's blood here I don't I don't know
how you would extract it oh we don't
want the blood yeah we're usually around
he's like this constitutes a substantial
find the structure itself
yes the this god of mouths which we
currently are within god of mouths
that's just no poetry there no but
that's what it's him yeah so from the
earth moving around in a circle and you
see the earth and Celestion which is
another symbol that you have I'm
familiar with celestine Obama geez thank
celestion the next one is indicated as
lolly pool
Lollapalooza airs Lollapalooza oh it's
an incredible inter planar music
festival that sounds fun this one yes
the little is there the next one the
inside you can see a just like a
nonsensical undulation of polyps and
wings and then as you pass it the shape
seems to change into a yellow garbed
reagent and that's the symbol in the
front of that says Hester hmm I had more
time yeah the next column says Habakkuk
there's one being 1k I think wolf yeah
the next one that you see inside you can
see a war forged it looks sort of like
if something like coriander's form
imagine if there were a human version of
that construct hmm interesting
and it's designee is this is the only
one here that's designated not with a
name but with a number this one is 148
okay and the next one is male it's
exactly right and then with the last one
is not a name but a term or title it
says that which indoors mmm friendship
technically or is not a name either from
what I understand yeah it's just a
symbol that means that yeah yeah I'm I'm
I'm like kind of sad as I walk around
because I recognize a lot of these names
and it's like where we went to UM my
family we went to Disneyland Disneyland
and just see Mickey for the first night
no
we went to Luxor in Egypt and we saw um
we went into the Tut wear or the tomb
where they have can cut down there yeah
I know which isn't usually not open it
was so strange to see him like all small
and like this is what does I read about
a lot in your history books and stuff
like this is the same kind of feeling
like Celestia does in this thing like
who knew and I'm a little disappointed
that he could be caught ya know I don't
understand by this thing yeah exit
through the gift shop exactly I know
they got it's like you can get little
mail ifs you know what I mean come dare
me into the machine and it will press I
didn't do it presses out the symphony or
doing real copper piece yeah I want to
yet so you've if you can extract blood
but you don't know how to extract it
from this crystal guy yeah he's like I
know I've never seen anything like this
we don't need to get any from the dead
no he's over in the front of Maliki and
he may lift and he's just like tapping
on the front of the careful I think
she'd be quite unharmed well I'm just
saying be careful you don't know its
place full of surprises he withdraws his
long finger and then finds another
column to tap that doesn't elicit this
kind of response like he's like no
there's God blood there's God's blood in
this room
what do you mean this gods what's
floating around in the air we're
swimming in it oka God
well we're inside the god of mouths yeah
like we're in his body somewhere so it's
like his tummy
exactly baby surface but it's not
bleeding who was chasing it system never
you mind
who died in here cool people recently
killed your pursuers you're welcome they
were not gods
yeah as you see a God died is what
you're saying there is God's blood
sometimes the two are connected how
there was an elf who exploded a few
minutes ago but we don't think you tell
me about him
shit I was just joking but Oh God I eat
something strange okay true strike here
yeah the scallop is there God's blood
here he takes in yeah I don't like that
and you know but it's gonna be Bonin
it's so fun if you tell me you'll like
it I will keep this a little cool like
cooler than a living human should be I
guess listening to the podcast Ryan
keeps trying to touch Jerry so gently he
went right into NPR the cool he
literally like straight out just takes
it and licks it hey well my friend there
anybody anyone's gonna lick my friend
scalp it's me yeah yeah but you should
wear it broke off like yeah yeah I just
thought it's a hat on a hat it's literal
and he says this creature has been
adulterated this creature has been made
into a kind of bait and this dumb god of
mouths fell for it Ede hmm really don't
like him get around why is it not
responding so there is a purple comb you
know so there is a like a low sound that
appears to be coming from a great
distance but its presence in the room is
very very real and it's getting
modulated higher and higher and tell it
as something like babies cry
no hmm and so the spinning like stops
and then chunks lately shredder
shattered glass is starting to fall out
of the starting to fall out of the air
and then reassert itself gravity is now
back on the menu and you feel that
pressure again from the ER an urgency
hmm an urgent womp-womp-womp
but I want to I'm gonna reach out to it
again and see if I if that that garbled
language is still there there isn't the
language but there's just a push okay he
wants you out we should go yeah what is
it what does that code take in the void
child the divine prison its prey may
slip the trap devoured but not consumed
but no the last must be first yeah so
I'm thinking the last to be captured
needs to be the first which he's sprung
maila so it seems that the ER told us
last time right
so main list is alive in there when we
were walking around did the rest seem to
all be alive yeah yeah but all in
various states of of dream okay none of
them are like tortured like the first
time they saw them either right yeah
exactly
right right now like when this thing is
so sort of listing and not manifesting
its full power mm-hmm
they seem to just be more or less
sleeping restlessly this is nothing like
the torment that may with experience
yeah she's not being actively tortured
right now I want to leave I want to find
Brahma I don't want to figure out how to
get me off out of here now that there's
not that evil sort of poison seeping
into them do you think that talking to
me life will yield something
intelligible yeah I guess I could go
over and just before I one more time
yeah and say like mail how can we help
you um
so that you you say with the hand hand
goes here and then it stops at the at
the sort of crystal and edge but a hand
extends out Oh what through the through
the face of the glass and then she takes
your hand mm-hmm
and then like scoops both of your hands
into it and closes her hand around it
and you are set absolutely at peace
before you come back next week level
your character dude know so yeah so
where this cycle starts and stops is an
open question but I think that yeah I
think that you have you have read and
assess the information from the earth
correctly okay right that's one
interrogate this guy well we may be in
come with us so now so now his his feet
are starting to get unsure on the ground
he says this is a God do you say we're
in a god now it's a it's a pretty busy
God as I understand it and then maybe
returning its attention to this space
that's incredible information thank you
I thank you for your time this is its
stomach yes is that correct
it's a God that's in prison to the gods
mmm and you be helpful we were in
freeing these God's to us yes well maybe
at a later date I feel anything a very
robust schedule hmm and he says but you
met I have something that may be of use
to you really yes I saw you that you
noticed my circle I did notice and he
holds his hand out to you okay and then
as the hand is out here
his assistant places a circle in it so
it's less though he gave it to you and
he passes it along
he says you strike me as someone who
could use it thank you
I've done some reading about his earth
Aman and I really hit the eyebrow is
like okay he's like he's like all shit
came to play he says that's not in the
dialogue his language though yeah I know
I know them on just from literature but
I look forward to getting to know more
about the earth Aman on a personal level
it's like it's like you know I want to
bring onna invite his earth Aman into my
heart exactly
thank you that's genuine like I said
Rosie's not a religious person but it is
academically very interesting yeah Healy
she nuts and he says yes and then he
takes a step back okay and the whole he
drops out and then you see him and his
in his companion just deftly avoid this
slick pool that exists outside they
don't elsewhere talk to they pulled out
of mounts right now you do it or you
don't
oh no no no we're we're good oh yeah you
want to go yeah it's time to go let's go
I feel great everybody yeah that's wrong
do you know jars and stuff on you don't
you
we got a jar Bible here's what you
always taking samples of stuff you
should get a sample of that memory as
well yeah and that vital SAP I you
reaching the board no I don't like that
but I feel like catharsis maybe wants to
put some in the hoards person bag yeah I
just want to dump a like a portion of it
without a bottle the note that says look
out before I have a water skin that I
had been using for the NEMA's ear water
and it is nothing isn't it right now oh
I have my water skin I have any bottle
also that bottle might be yeah yeah
maybe to thank Kathy
dump that out yeah all right oh no mmm
you know it's no good it's not you're
right it's not my brand
hey hey now before we go down into this
hole is anybody thinking about the
separation the red goo Goo's we're
talking yeah what other good wasn't well
cuz there's the memory goo and then
there's also oak know that oak oh I see
do we want to collect him up we go no I
gotta get a scanner I just want to make
sure everybody's getting everything they
want to it yeah we could take more
chunks of him I guess does anything
survive yet it is nice yeah oh yeah yeah
all right with the mess yeah yeah there
are a pair of knives I wanted tonight he
meant the most to me sure yeah there
there are the two knives that you found
a lot of a lot of the a lot of his
equipment has been damaged by this
process
and also the rest of the Slap Chop oh
well not all right goodness gracious
um there is also there is also sort of
poking out from this muck is a gold ring
with a red geminate ah I went to you
like this looks a little bit like
alright good looks like nothing you see
anything I take it no it was stupid
where's the quarry I never loved to eat
it yeah no reason if you go huh that's
what I was gonna say yeah now you've got
a feed that horse I think I'm going to
use I'll have emptied the ink bottle I'm
going to use mage hand which I have now
whoo so that get full right to the brim
a little bit less than that come up with
a cork in of that of that memory juice
engages tell me how you are protecting
your
I am standing at whatever the max
distance of nature which is 30 feet does
it it doesn't seem to have any of its
own decision-making skills something to
leap up like the blob well no no it's
it's actually like it's trying to get
its GED I see like a traditional school
environment not did not work for the goo
but I respect it I let my parents wait I
still wants to it still wants to make a
life for itself
you know um let me think here I do cuz I
don't want to just make a chain Plus
bottles pretty smooth yeah that's why
that don't wipe off the excess shake it
loose it yeah exactly using a chain is
good yeah
how about gonna be good is it good okay
that's a quick thing I do you said down
to you mage and the lid seal it up tight
that's mine yeah yeah yeah easy called
in your corner I'm gonna make a quick
note about that that's great and it just
comes open later yeah oh man in your bag
oh no I'm not a bag at all I'm a beast
now alright we've properly looted the
room no no that's for remembering to do
it right there we go okay so the god
blood oak true strike they were acting a
little weird about his blood said he was
some kind of they suggest that there was
something else about it yes they seem to
be experts in this one he said it too he
said he was poisoned er yeah we fed
something right
so should we collect some of his blood I
mean is it a bloody enough scout oh yeah
my head Canon I'm just soaking no no no
in your mind you should be picturing
like like a sack of pancakes in the
syrup but like not like at home like it
the way it isn't a commercial in my mind
have you seen Carrie I'm like it's not
much but it's fine
yes you're just fine with it let's leave
this horrible getting ass jump through
let's go through the slick alright
yeah okay tell me about how you're going
through this like in terms of order oh
okay I need to know like where you end
up in the trap yeah so well yeah we have
to it can be like a Laverne and Shirley
thing like maybe you're like holding
hands and you just like I'll jump in
yeah like a ring we could its previous
if we have reason to believe that will
drop down without any agregate because
if we can drop down find a strap
otherwise we'll fly you can go where you
want okay okay let's just drop in okay
let's ring it let's try you know the
order I'm just curious
okay for my co first what's it I'll go
first
mmm-hmm I'll go second I think most
agile should go first I'll go third it
says God knows no the last must be the
last must be first in all things I don't
know what that means but since he's
asking orders right I'm like oh I don't
want to go last all right yeah I am last
so Rosie yeah yes just you you you just
looked over at dinar yeah and he's got
like some hair yeah and skin on his head
on his Cathy on his cap yeah and you're
like that is that is something no thanks
this is your your position on that and
then as you as you pop your way through
this you emerge like in the side of
another person so what yeah so as you as
you come through when you materialize in
this next place you are taking up
another person space so you know how is
it really personal space is a very
important concept right hmm you know
what I mean like you want to make sure
that you're get your granting people
room to be themselves you did not do
that in this case no it's not
intentional no turned off no clip is
turned off and exactly start the reactor
keep up in and then you're here and the
rest of this
sort of like curtain this like beef side
is sort of like slipping off the front
and that's when walnut comes in to
another side and then like you're on two
sides of this what give this chunk and
then cthe risk comes in behind and it's
a dinar exactly dinar in the back and
he's like hey
and then Chris comes in to the front and
then the remainder of this of this sort
of delicious fresh Curtin mmm just sort
of slips down on the front of you now
let me describe everything else that is
occurring in this scene that's the thing
that comes everything first you yeah
that occurs to you first okay like
that's the very first thing that you
notice just like a cold not fresh meat
whoa this is like the big Montana it's
like you're wearing the big Montana yeah
that's nice where do we just have this
right let's find out so you look around
get your bearings and you can see it is
very very dark here
there are torches set so often in a kind
of wooden octagon so you have left one
optimum and you have entered into
another rough-hewn octagon but beneath
your feet is a stone and well trodden
dirt there is a musty cavernous aroma
mixing with the smoke of these open
fires and these torches and you are and
then but around this wooden octagon our
stance almost like bleacher stands and
there are goblins and hobgoblins with
their arms raised in triumph about yes
about 50% of them you would say are
excited at what's happened
and the other half feel like this is
some bullshit and it's you that's coming
across right away you know that they're
like hmm I don't know if that's the
right play I don't know if I support
it's like I don't want to win that way
you know what I mean
exactly Oh
so we materialized and interrupted a UFC
match and killed one of the combatants
and so the other and so you're and so
right across we use this there is still
you know portions sort of slipping off
and falling to the ground and somehow
your opponent is nonplussed he's he
looks over and he is just echoing his
half of the crowd and he's like look
look at this how Bell GOG is this yeah
how Bell GOG is this sorcery he's
transformed a one-to-one match into a 1
to 4 match with his surface wizardry
again up again oh boy this fix
I'm from the Underdark and I had to
interrupt that spelled I mean make sure
that everybody knows that you won friend
you're the best
this guy cheated and he paid the
ultimate price okay we're refs were all
arrests everyone this is our F is a
sting operation you need to be strong
you need to let me know which parts of
these are bits okay then which parts of
these constitute the real response when
I that you are giving this purse I have
enough information when that is what
yeah exactly so he thinks that this is
very Bell GOG right hmm ice yeah no I
say this this is what I say I'm looking
around what is the what is our this
opponent look like I assume he's a piles
of meat around
the Goblin yeah so at all
basically a massive it's like a hot it's
like a goblin that's like been juicing
yeah you know what it means we're with
them goblin fighting Commission the GOC
yeah we're the GFC yeah surface yes
no he was going you're 100% right on him
he was gonna do that you need to try any
try and you try we're here to crown you
the winner right I am willing to roll
persuasion on this baby right Rosie saw
mature G to make the sound of a whistle
is there a way to put like rest yeah
okay so I just want to check in real
quick with you guys and I also want
checked in sir with the shower council
and say okay let me make sure I
understand this so so what are you okay
so you have emerged through you have
interrupted somehow you have interrupted
a session you have interrupted a
person's whole body and what you're
telling me is that you would like you're
telling me that you want to suggest that
you are representatives of the goblin
the GFC Goblin fighting us that'll shake
out commission commission what we have
to do is get out of this scenario but
yes yeah trying to indicate that
controls this neat pile maybe he was the
instigator of it he's he was the he was
the one who's cheating yeah
already been arrested yeah we're here to
let you know that and and to crown you
the winner
you fought fair and square yeah dog
fought dirty and we didn't like it
yellow and yell this partly to him
partly to the crowd you're like let's
hear it for this guy great job
yeah great great fight exactly exactly
working with us on this yeah thank you
you're like this guy and he's like a
sauce
yeah dick sauce your your enemies off
Asia your ex Aussies hazel Hayes off is
the winner folks let's hear it for him
huh wah wah wah
ok ok all right it's just a well-fought
I'm like you know do we know yeah it is
Wow while we're distracting them with
this BS can I do a perception to see if
I can find an exit yeah I'm gonna take
advantage on that role okay so I just
want to be very clear yes they really
really want you to use draconic
entitlement I know but I'm just saying
that's what that's what they want
okay so that's a 19 on a perception to
find the exit just to find it no moving
yeah okay yeah you can see so it from
the inside
it looks very stable you can see every
one of these but there are two where
where those death section of the octagon
is clearly hinged and there are massive
hobgoblins ready to pull these things
open at a certain time do it I find new
exhibit I'm is it you can do it you can
do it you like I'm just saying you're
gonna get might even with them I can't
read the crown I think what we've said
why would we have reason to lie yeah I
know he's giving us an Amy's buddies in
he's playing along now maybe some oh I
tried they don't believe it
when we're trying to convince here what
am I like the Commission you heard what
we say ders yeah the people have spoken
just saying okay so there are hobgoblins
over here yeah manning this gate this
gate over here there is a troll oh okay
manning the other game yeah yeah yeah
whoo-hoo yes like they're in charge he
has like the two fingers and he's he can
clearly just like a dollhouse yeah just
very dainty I'll open that roll I think
that's the guy we just destroyed look so
who looks like they're in charge who's
what authority figure me give you their
perception 1908 absolutely I think it's
better than that though isn't it you
know I'm flat no mater
there is a box seat oh and you can see
you can see another Hobgoblin up there
with his arms sort of folded over a
staff looking down at the crowd trying
to do a trying to take its measure
mm-hm we and we're it like you're down
here like looking at the being very
professional look into my eyes come down
near you and I'm like for walnut
notations cuz this is clearly not up to
code and I don't understand when you're
James I'm doing actual form feeling you
just see you just start doing your
regular job my job yeah that's good but
that's good because that's what we need
right now so perfect
yeah why wait what's the read on the
situation the read on the situation is
that people are waiting for this guy's
okay huh all right fine I will dominate
rush here we go that's best I get but
talk about your nude your chronic wait
exactly yes yeah yeah so he'd basically
he can yeah in combat out of combat he
basically gets the effects of the
dominate spell yeah which is which is
amazing because it essentially initiates
a psychic connection between you and the
target that lasts as long as you're on
the same plane and you do they do the
what you want them to do yeah it's a
difference we indirect entitlement is
that there's no is that we're not doing
a save yeah when you turn on the dinar
charm yeah
it happens so so how do you so how do
you work this thing so they're this
troll is like
mm laughs and these hobs are like mmm
well after all the bullshitting yeah we
just expunged and then we're I'm
assuming the crowd is sort of on the
side the other fighter is identifying oh
yeah it's about 55 ones kind of lying
feels like he's trying to get the most
out of this yeah I well if I correctly
identify that this guy is the head
honcho like I say standing arms folded
over his staff there's some kind of
skull up here yeah this guy mean
business I'll preen my way over that way
I'm working up the crowd and uh and I'll
I'll dominate him as best I can be like
in that right buddy right he's
everything I said is right isn't it
there's a there's a there's a shudder
like you can see the robes just sort of
like rustle like when you select with an
animal gets into a topiary like the
robes just sort of like from the bottom
to the top and then he's sort of like
and he's like he raises his staff and he
points over at the hobgoblins and he
points over at the troll the hobgoblins
open it and the troll doesn't do
anything and then he gives the staff a
couple shakes and then the troll opens
it right up and you have your choice of
exits from the arena and then I don't
counsel and then and I say and we get a
bunch of gold for our time right this
sting operation right yeah can I get
clean yeah he nods he no he nods a
couple times and points a crooked finger
out to the side where which side you
gonna go out closest to the money he'll
deliver the money to you I mean all
right non troll Sancho be safe but you
know yeah see you go over there you go
over there there's a small chest sort of
like carved wooden skull you lift up the
top of the skull there's a few gems in
there chief they're Jim's it's very nice
nice we'll work out the monetary of
particulars here in a moment but come
feed that horse show council mayor liras
please you thanks
much for coming and hanging out with us
this through this Thursday just
Wednesday on Tennessee teams and
absolutely blast was had by all stick
around for Table Talk we're gonna dish
out another one of our awesome Elderwood
hex chests to somebody in the channel
could be you could be you let's find out
we'll see the second
you