time is the enemy of the past it
threatens the fastest weapon you
wouldn't make it past a second as the
question
play it brash and reckless to choose a
cautious solution Esau was prudent in
any sepulcher poker to don't become the
putrid it's that well said I pursue in
no mountain too steep for dungeon too
deep to send expendable marks up to the
top of the peak of beneath they see Yugi
they come like sharks to it while I swim
in that money build like Carl Barks
through it so send your National Parks
drew it I'll send him home in a natural
box with the closed tie the most of the
parks included save your breath for a
cleric confessor death is a lesson that
life is attending professor but if
you're seeking my official advice sign
on the dotted line English in the twice
yeah I am Tycho Brahe hey of Penny
Arcade impacts him also manifests
Harewood drawn CEO of acquisitions
incorporated but today Jerry Hawkins I'm
here to run a game of Dungeons and
Dragons for my friends to my right hey
dragon board nurses Joe Bernard in my
mind I went right to the hit start
coming and they don't stop coming right
to Amy right - yeah let's get the baby
bump out of the way
Amy's not real wrapping the natural
world walnut dog grass the strength is
that sacred place yeah exactly at F
forest that's the whole planet Earth to
series on Netflix which is only six
episodes or something but now I feel
like a really good insight into to my
left not your grandma's grandma except
for those rare cases in which she is
your grandma's grandma Rosie feasting
I'm running out of things to do here so
I'm gonna go yeah b-boy style attitude
but yeah you have to bring in you're
gonna have to bring in props like cheese
graters
all right great laterally to the left of
my left emerging is though from a mist
shroud Chris wrist round yeah
everybody everybody gets it now let's
see before we get into the scenario I
would be remiss if I did not do my
utmost to serve ELISA our producer oh
there's a big list of things I have to
talk about you know what I mean
nonstop torment no actually it's the
sponsors maybe that was the wrong way to
introduce by the chocolate covered fruit
baskets so the giveaway they're the
worst they don't taste like chocolate
fruit and fruit why don't you just shoot
me in the praise anyway the giveaway is
we have four de Lorean
edible arrangements middle finger emoji
is the single I'm getting from now two
things one so we have the eliwood
Academy mini hex which is actually up
available on Kickstarter right now
they're actually super cool and I was
overjoyed to see the messages coming
back from people who had gotten their
prizes we send them we still be send
them to you right away after you get
them we also have this massive gauge
this is the Purple Rain 45 millimeter
level up dice that is the size that we
have at the a game show a true artifact
for your home it weighs at least 40
pounds it is definitely dangerous do not
put it in a sock and use it as a pit ran
with it yeah well do that that's it
that's the only person you're allowed to
pulverize with this sock Dyson replace
your sock full of doorknob with a sock
full of 45 millimeter Purple Reign dice
bubbly available it a great kid love
like pick this up no no yeah no it is a
wrecking ball now let's see I'm trying
to think what was the other scenario is
that everything Alyssa
Table Talk okay I got it oh yes thank
you and no in Table Talk we have that
would be awesome
actually time saver for me so I have a
simulator whole universe over here and
the least you can do right yeah exactly
this is a good little No we have special
guests Gavin and Dave who had a lot of
the design scenario that surrounds the
streaming experience you are currently
enjoying they are going to come in and
then Kate and Amy are gonna leave we're
gonna go see helton look I support you
100%
I mean I can I can make second make it
happen I can try to put something
together for you so you can get so you
can be making your way downtown
lin-manuel miranda is a genius pave
paradise and put up a parking lot all
right in the immortal words of Aaron
Burr okay maybe that kind of game I
guess we'll see how it goes
friends shadow council revered shadow
council mayor Libre Spezia when last we
saw our heroes they had just emerged
from the Dwarven a stronghold in the
Underdark of Alcazar where apparently
they're coming had been foretold and was
literally written into the bylaws of the
city that people matching their names
and descriptions were to be given a
mithril pick there was a lot of
arguments about whether or not they
should get it in the end the sleeping
king himself or rose from his 75 year
old slumber handed it over went back to
bed
classic scenario you see in pretty much
every D&amp;D game it's just right off the
shelf it's like it's like meeting in an
inn you know it's a good like I enjoyed
going through it
I've read about it yeah she was a movie
it was a deus ex napping but as they
emerged from the aforementioned
stronghold of Alcazar they found
themselves face to jowl with a goblin
oyd host and you know they had every
reason to believe that this host was
there you know with a with an intention
to annihilate the party what happened
instead was that they engaged in a kind
of ilusory battle yeah exactly yeah
slightly lesser known a little bit a
little more indie right and what should
emerge but the person that had been
dominated previously by Denar Blitzen
utilizing his draconic entitlement power
the direct result of this scenario was
that he didn't seem to mind and in fact
was curious and even interested in the
process of the domination which made it
weird
yeah I mean it made it weird right away
but they had begun to engage in a
dialogue with this individual who turned
out to be a kind of druid that they were
not previously familiar with and indeed
when the hood of the robe was removed
they saw an illicit beneath it so this
is clearly an individual who doesn't go
in for stereotypes that's not what
they're about the very last thing they
said cthe wrists said are you a seeker
also noting that there fahsai had some
similarities asking if he was he was a
secret also this entity said no we have
found each other that is what happened
last time thank you so much for coming
out
we'll see you again next weekend week we
can we can just start playing from there
that is the scenario gathered throng and
revered shadow Council we can I'd be
happy to simulate this universe for you
for as long as you feel like it really
low particle effects
LOD obviously at about 50 feet
everybody's just a gray box I'm sorry
also a mouse and the person have the
same hitbox so I'm sorry I think I'm
sorry that's just that's how it is right
so we're so he where we left off was the
fileted handed me this indeed he handed
you something like a small exactly
imagine imagine imagine if you were
imagine a dark portable version of the
focus ring then yeah right
so I met imagine that imagine that your
pack imagine a dark vacation where
you're packing for a trip but you know
that foe sigh beyond a certain size or
weight won't be allowed on the dragon
I'm having a hard time that I don't
think that's a good metaphor that's what
I'm saying is that imagine that imagine
that so the scenario is that this is
very much like the the focus that you
had with you when you left the Underdark
all together it is crude but obviously
sacred in its way and he's sanded it to
me I assume he uh know what it what it
is but I now as a gift I guess I I
inspected I see that it's got that unity
what am I getting from my focus do I
feel an affinity so I feel a movement
indeed indeed so in your in your role as
sort of mystic seeker trying to define
the parameters of a religion that as far
as you know you were the only a tarrant
of I could find right
the you've had a few experiences like
where other symbols that seem to be
contained within the amethyst prison
this meat and mouths God they have a
kind of relationship to each other
that's physical city will die that's
right yeah yes exactly you know
ordinarily I would I've thought about it
had some time in my mind it felt like a
week even though this is seconds I love
it
but this revelation might be the only
thing that would keep Carissa down here
and rather than immediately say okay
that's nice goodbye I have to go right
so what if what are all are you doing at
this at the site of this horrible
creature who I fear also well yeah now
I'm compelled by every reason yeah and I
can't believe that this is what's
occurring right I don't think I've ever
interacted with one let alone been given
something nice by one yeah I got present
yeah you certainly know about them
though right
yeah I know they're that you should
avoid them right that why she shouldn't
accept gifts from them but now that I
have there's a drow version of the like
looking a gift a cephalopod bipedal in
the pressure yeah in the cross own yeah
I I think right he's just waiting for a
signal from you kill ya growling I'm
I've taken my my focus out and I've got
his the the smaller one here and I and I
I look at him and I ask have you seen
this have you seen this glyph the one on
my focus Joey
absolutely yeah he looks at it with
instant recognition
I mean it'd be like showing it like
maybe like showing a person here like a
like the McDonald's logo or something
like that like their recognition is is
instant and profound
he loves it then I am really reaching
for my for my book and and summing
through to that that well-worn page and
I'm saying there are more do you have
more these are the one that I found this
this one unity this one is you have are
they're more like this yeah he says he
says they're only two that are of any
import to me
these yep he says he says in the same
way that you and I are brothers these
two symbols are brothers in a way and
they shall embrace us brothers and run
after I give him a hug
no I but before I do that I am like
weird where did you find yours suppose
it a black altar the stone yes yes but
it was not always this it is only bit
has only been some two hundred years
before that it was a wholesome and
sacred place corrupted somehow
absolutely I know that his power remains
but he does not answer that which
endures indeed Hayes been imprisoned
somehow I don't and I don't know that is
a present I don't know that how did you
see such a thing in escape how could you
a mortal creature escape a prison
designed for gods I say like with some
humility and realizing what it's about
to sound like because I have the
greatest God of all on myself because my
patron the one that I seek has protected
itself by also being imprisoned maybe in
the manner that
yours is better than the one that ate it
- he's great I bet huh
I've been to the prison a number of
times no date I've been there I'm there
all the time
you stay yeah in the prison they've been
you don't know what you don't know what
human or you know mortal creature
emotion
he's currently doing a parody of right
now that tentacles are just going every
which way he's throwing his head back
and there's a sort of like harsh
staccato bark that is ringing off of the
ceiling are you okay are you he says
listen there is clearly much that you
did not know about that which in doors
says that which endures in the ER are
like the opposite parentheses of the
truth so you are suggesting that your
divine patron is superior to all because
he was devoured first I not sure which
parentheses he represents he could be
the last one he could be the terminal
one I don't think so
I don't think so my conception of this
long may it endure is that there is an
order a natural order to this
consumption and it must be undone in the
order of its consumption the ER hasn't
been worshipped in the Underdark for a
thousand years whereas not two hundred
years ago my own patron spoke with me as
I speak with you now says
the ER the unknowable represents the
systems and the thoughts of the universe
that which endures represents their
inevitable dissolution into chaos you'll
have to excuse my passion in these
matters you are excused you have to
excuse my creasing passion they are
brothers and like like any other like
any other pair of brothers they have
their squabbles just like the silken
robe yeah like just a cascade of silk I
like the idea that we're we're not like
we're talking very close so close that
it is just making out around the edge
[Music]
this way he says yes it's it's no matter
I in order to help yourself you must
help me so I have we have no quarrel in
this Oh completely understood they in
the only time it spoke to me the the
being behind the ER commanded that I
free another God first yours seems to be
the correct first in order
I always did you receive a gift in
hilter's are yes from who came in there
so he is like like this this face is is
soft goofs you think some of these
sounds are laughter mm-hmm right is this
correction it it just an imperious
gays just over and then all the
tentacles like shoot out straightly and
then he looks he looks back to you and
he says a gift that is given by a
sleeping stranger I always assumed the
words were for me I assumed that as his
servant in the Underdark this this
system would be to me to interpret and
reify but that may not be my role at all
that it may not but what a relief I
would say it is I have felt the mantle
of prophecy lo these two centuries the
idea that the idea that someone else
could handle this is a great comfort to
me that that's good news I amassed an
army I did I did everything I thought
was required but I don't think it's my
prophesy at all ha mitt is there could
we use your army if we owe I don't think
so
they are quite unruly and I suspect the
places you'll need to go may require a
bit more deft touch than perhaps a
thousand goblins and Hobgoblin skin a
mass or they're yours eyes Oh quite and
quite in every way who did you back in
the wrestling competition they seem to
enjoy it oh it doesn't matter
mm-hmm that's what I thought
it doesn't matter whoever and listen
whoever whoever succeeds will serve me
this is like a pair of shoes I try on
and in the same way it did not matter
whose prophecy it was I we will
undertake this we share the same rule
we're all pointless here they're all
God's shoes oh we got the shoes of some
greater being he's a bitter laugh he
says he says there is a process
by which these gods can be removed it
has to do with some studios inverting
the process of their consumption somehow
so you and you have it you have the gift
what is it it's a pic of mithril of
mithril which I mean it's expensive
mmm I think that it I think this er say
he seems he's a little like his eyebrow
equivalents are a little bent right now
yeah now that I know what it's supposed
to do but it should be capable
yeah capable of doing hmm maybe there's
something else that's special about it
I'm I'm gonna remove it from the my
mouth bag yeah my cross act my in my
hordes person bag it's a little cross
our stuff Allah and sniffed a little
radula sort of seeking and ready the
opposite today young one give it up eggs
have puking so yeah it's like it has to
kind of like its back yeah you asked the
arch yeah like you can see the form of
it coming up I think getting things out
of it now obviously what we described is
that it can it can why the aperture can
widen and you can get you can gain
access to your the boxes that you have
right but I think you would I think it's
just this funny if we allow ourselves a
little bit of head Canon that says that
in order to get the things out you have
to play it sort of like a bagpipe but
you just have to get in this like and
they come out wet oh there's no reason
you open it up as dry as boning yeah oh
yeah what does it make sense it has to
do with its internal storage good I
don't know about but membranes yeah
probably
do they could do a better job it's true
so I hold it out and this is what we
were given this was the process
that's a common object I think if the
doors knew what it was capable of they
wouldn't have handed it over
they were found a way to ignore their
prophecy I don't know maybe they have
all the gods they wanted maybe but
honestly we've been trying to figure
this out too because the prophecy says
this will burnish the tattered crown
this is a this is a pic it's not gonna
be burnishing shit no no it could be the
tattered crown describes the imprisoned
God could be said the burnishing itself
is the release a process which you are
us seem appear to have well in hand
oops uh Noah Bleeth oh I wouldn't have
thought it because he says there is a
piece of information that I can give you
yes yes no before watching from this
before no no it's like we finally found
like the way to get kiss RIS and Kris
involved with the game it's like this
slimy under dark rot priest is his
Brahma basically definitely yeah I think
there's been a long-standing question of
catharsis sexuality and whatever this
entity constitutes so he says he says
now in the time before it in the time
before there was one who was said to
serve that which endures he hailed from
the city of Galan earth really
interesting he says at night I can't
imagine how that would have been you
conceivable for it for a drow to serve
any entity but loath but I see the you
stand before me there are very few of us
but to each their own I guess is there
may be there may be more to learn there
there may be something else that matches
up with the quatrain oh that's good
there let's head that way as I always
intended I think no inconsistent mind
he's so consumed by this idea that now
he's completely rewritten everything
that's happened here mm-hmm
to that no I I did want to go this was a
good idea
he's retcons it like the whole thing
yeah he's not ready to admit help want
to leave that would be stupid to leave
the answers of net resident it's they're
thrown blame you're you're the ones who
didn't want to go I say go from the
start and everything conspired to get us
to leave you know I mean my feelings
about it didn't help but now my my eyes
are open they are and then there's
nothing in there but yeah staring you
can you can see right into that
impermeable darkness oh yeah that's
great
is there anything but the audience
should know about calendar 31 oh yeah um
it's it's uh it's where I was a young
drow and where I escaped from near there
is where I found my chunk of the black
altar that I had I'd carry with me it
wasn't in gallon earth I was just
nervous it was very close to it yeah but
this is was where my my house is that's
all my family houses okay well it looks
like so happy for you that you get to go
home she's like homecomings are so
important
I don't know if I've mentioned this
recently but I don't have a home must be
very nice like still have one to go back
to I don't I don't have a home by choice
you have one I had rather that not be
how its ordered I'm just really happy
for you but oh you talk but none of the
four of us can go home no dude I
actually literally saw the skin response
on your arm
I saw the skin response on your arm
sorry um family trouble and God Tropes
yeah gt's but with that understanding
then we have another option I I know the
way I thought I you just map that route
backwards now you guys know exactly yeah
yeah exactly
you know and you're I mean it's like
your neighborhood to a certain extent I
mean it's a several hundred mile radius
but this part of the this part of the
Underdark is not unknown to you
well is it downhill exactly exactly yeah
exactly so it turns out it turns out
that there are various elevations inside
the Underdark yeah oh that's so I paint
a little scene really quickly yeah
please I can tell that you this is the
place that you've been avoiding and that
now you've resigned yourself to it so I
come up and and very like gently lay a
hand on the side of your cloak and say
no matter what is waiting for you back
at Gallagher's you still have all of
your friends here with you and I point
to a walnut and dinar and I want to
imagine that dinar is like having a
burping contest if the goblins or
something we go in somewhere she's like
I have friends like you're not really
listening no I just need
I don't know you have me anyway sure
what they would say if they saw
non-drought in called earth well count
sounds like a makeover episode I didn't
happen yes I believe that you will be
made over into corpses I think that that
is the transformation it's very striking
they they'll move that bus uh-huh I
don't think it's I don't think it's safe
to return hmm with me oh it's not safe
for me to return I also AM concerned
that I will be destroyed on site so I'll
be making liberal use of my mask of many
faces you are a drow and this is a drow
City why would you be destroyed on site
us no chance yeah we get it yeah I
didn't I didn't leave in none of the
best circumstances I didn't go I didn't
say a lot of formal goodbyes the one I
did say was sort of yeah in action was a
theft I I stole from the adherents of
lost temple to fund the earliest part of
my escape from the Underdark
and I spent a century or two worried
that they would come for me above ground
and they did not but I don't imagine
that they'd be pleased to see me well
sure but the statute of limitations must
have expired on that crowd by now oh the
drower long lived and very litigious I'm
sure I've always read and not to be fair
I deserve these are in mostly fairy tale
books I've always read that the drow if
you commit a crime the drow don't catch
you you've got away with it
and that
something that they're like hey nice job
is that not the case we can hope for the
best we can just carry that in our
hearts and it's possible that things
have changed
I don't know culturally what they're
like at the moment I only know what it
was like when I was at what our youth
okay maybe a theft is acceptable no
maybe it's written upon can be legalized
yeah yeah so but yeah there are various
reasons why I haven't wanted to return
home and even and and those returning
with me might be looked even more
unfavorably upon so we need I don't know
that I can recommend that you would join
if we if there was a reason for you to
come we would have to think of it before
we got there I know I would be
sympathetic because this is like when
very going towards janar oh yeah froze
up and didn't want to go back so I would
commiserate be like I I get it look I
get all right serious recommending we
don't go yeah I'm just thinking
murder-suicide we always talked about in
the back of the card
no I produced the two knives that
prepare you like like we've like we
discussed this may be the time Rosie I'm
actually gonna try some shit on you stop
my staff clap it on the ground and look
at you and say you have a decision to
make right now is your desire for it
enlightenment more powerful than your
cowardice and I'll even do an
intimidation check I'm not if you listen
I'm all about these I'm all about this
you gotta jump in yeah I'm gonna do okay
so what I'm interested to see here
because I feel like what manage another
12 oh my god nothing is scarier than my
family
[Laughter]
anything you have to roll the challenge
that yeah I'll do it do an intuition
check okay what do I don't know what
that is it can be good on Catherine
insight it's like yes right okay I got I
got no modifier there I will not take a
this it's a push but what it yeah did
you kiss that you kiss the defender okay
that's just like risk that makes good
sense anyway because I'll say no it's
not I'm I'm ready to go back upon my
step on the ground also just going back
in front thank you like Japanese
compounder but no my cowardice is about
young guys being slaughtered on site not
means they'll take a little time with me
I'm concerned they will kill and rider
you don't kill me with a blade they will
kill you with a narrow here here's a
thought would they have any prop Rosie
you can disguise yourself right
I can minor illusion but it's no mask of
mini faces well you could look I don't
know
Jinyoung did I could pull up like the
hood over my head and try to be like a
kid there we go okay um I can turn into
a small animal and I can also turn any
willing creature into a beast what of
your choice something small
sighs oh like maybe a rat oh you're all
right a chipmunk rods are noble
Chipmunks are cute I could do the
killing rats are cute yeah then I would
make a good two month now they carry
disease there are lifeless pigeons
whatever problem with surface agents of
the dirt just goes on a 10 minute long
radical rats and pigeons nothing I say
pigeons same preacher there problems
with I mean we could tuck those away
anywhere you know it only needs to work
long enough for us to explore around
guala Durst not live there it's the
elephant is still spear
do you know it give us a you can provide
us as much information with where this
person might be their name and so forth
then we can minimize the amount of time
that we're there it will be aid and
return well he says well I he's because
without saying I'm sure that he's
somewhat famous among adherents of my
faith he risked everything to seek this
truth and for that we honor him he was a
the lord of a house called what was it
Bruce Lee rahu loosely there's a lot of
vowels that I don't honor in the drow
language he he must be dead I'm sorry to
tell you he's dead but that doesn't mean
that his rest search is necessarily gone
just like I'm just passion if you could
see the through that my skin color just
drains to a lavender he says he says
he's his friend that's my family house
it should be it should be a matter of
great ease to secure what you need then
it never is with my family and I only
knew them a short time but that's more
actually more specific information than
I wanted but more information is never a
bad thing it's very necessary he says
Arabic he said he says he says friend do
you seem troubled
I suspect that
no wait maybe there is a way there might
be a way my sister I I haven't spoken to
her in forever but she may still be
sympathetic to my not living there he
says perhaps perhaps she is the that the
cornerstone of a magnificent plan agreed
agreed
new friend agreed new friend and without
any of the the potential strangeness of
only having met and elicits this one
time and all of the stories about them
I've heard a green new friend and I put
my arm around and like and Pat like yeah
but as one would a brother there's a lot
of the shape of the body you think is
actually just the shape of the garment
like you you reach every you feel like a
flop you know exactly like like the body
underneath this thing is much more live
and soft and thin than the sort of
boning and structure of the garment of
the raiment presents sick too soft too
warm okay does it does it appear that
when when he puts his arm around it is
this indicative of like an illusion
doesn't strike you it doesn't strike you
as a loser II you think that it's it's
not it's a loser II in the same way that
like makeup would be illusory right it's
just like yeah is there three illa kids
in a trench coat is it is it in the
council walnut gained one more level
and now I get to get this light I become
the creature I fly out of this game from
creatures since she'd light alright okay
wait we have our task then I have to
think of the best disguise for myself
that's slowly the issue so you you know
that you will have a a reasonable a
healthy period of time to discover right
your optimal level of trickery
because gala dearth is a fair way south
of here and there are portions of that
trip that require very particular travel
because the Underdark is treacherous
even with even when it's well mapped
right but there are parts of it simply
can't be crossed there's just massive
chasms without anything like a bridge a
chasm that's a hundred miles long for
example that is definitely between any
kind of straight line from here to
gallon earth the path a the the path
that makes sense that you'll have to
take is going to be a little bit further
east of there okay but you know that you
know that you'll have many sleepless
nights oh sure fabulous night yeah
exactly
no no four days and five nights in do do
I know like in like on that route back
what other like major cities or
settlements for might we encounter yeah
you will you will almost certainly be
very near if not directly adjacent to
ring lor north which is colloquially
known as the city of soaring shadows
can't be all bad but it's it's it's you
know it's on the lake of radiant mists
does that does that get anybody create
that dude you can get shrouded up in
this mist
illegal there I might take a mist there
couple hours ep
misty Eliot miss me with that shrimp
commercial it's so good it's it's so
good doing so alright so we've yeah I
I'm gonna i saw help take the there's
nothing to lose at this point like I I
would want to do it in the elephant's
presence this my focus has seems to have
a affinity for other so now that you're
holding it out yeah and this is the the
newest incarnation of the focus that's
true
is like it's like a naked hang down like
this but it's like a necklace that who's
where the symbols are sort of exist in a
continuum along the side of it and so
he's I mean he's he has clearly never
seen anything like this he's seeing all
these black chips and you know chips
basically of these larger structures but
his he's not a part of this continuum
that involves a prison and a bunch of
gods and all this kind of stuff he knows
that his God was sequestered somehow
mmm-hmm but he doesn't have the type of
knowledge you have about the rest of
this stuff he is he is gobsmacked by
this if he had a gob Myro it would be
smacked by this this bizarre artifact
you've been coming glean together since
the beginning of the campaign thank you
for your gift thank you sir your time
may be free here
thank you for your moisture thank you
for your for your tentacles as well
thank you for the dreams I'm gonna have
later
whoa what what is your name friend
this is I am Gaul I am I am a carver
what do you call a carver a druid
hmm we have a druid I have a dress the
most walnut shit just off from this site
he says oh I am aware we did
exhilarating battle the pleasure was
yours I'm sure she thinks about her
illusions he's really proud of that ones
first time she's done it it was pretty
sweet it was it was a really cool fight
one of the coolest fights I think in the
campaign and it was not even the fight
or real so so yeah yeah but you can you
can you can that he's the respect as
definitely it's definitely there they
grappled in a completely bizarre arena
there's a lot of hooting and jibes from
the location we're not from from the
Blowfish no the the gathered army the
fam go there they're moving in a t
system friend a moment and he turns back
over he holds his hand out and the
ground beneath the armies begins to
rumble
and vibrate and they are sort of like
piling atop one another and trying to
make sense of this situation and when
the rumbling stops they're quieter feel
like I don't need an army anymore
goblin a single Goblin he would about
you
pet Goblin I mean he's a druid and he
has like a whole army of goblin so oh
it's a dream it's a Carver and a walnut
no this is walnut this have that
conversation that's amazing
it she likes it and she goes you know we
might we might have need of a goblin and
you have so many maybe it's that you
could spare one I I wouldn't miss a
goblin okay well do you have a specific
skill set in mind one that don't get
your hopes up ya know just um your most
ear yeah just your most eager boy some
approval yeah a young hungry job is to
be hungry the rocky of goblins yeah
Rocky one though not Rocky three Iraqi
for you really gave it up by then don't
worry about it I want your rockiest five
most gobble yeah you could have said any
one tommy gun not tommy gun anybody but
tommy gun so he looks out into this this
ocean of his and then he starts pointing
his fingers through the crowd and as he
does so what it's it's something like a
finger it's finger Ian let's say I'm
guess yeah and so as you sort of it's
almost like he's riffling through a
library stack of magazines
I guess he's pointing through there
goblins are coming forward and
presenting themselves and then he's he's
free he's very abrasive frees the finger
back it's very thoughtful and he points
that one who seems I'm gonna say it he
seems smaller than the other goblins
that's okay could you just say that bad
well well I was just like a like a CSS
like
so very exactly right yeah and he skips
over to the party oh well let's get and
he shares a couple words with Carver
gall the Carver golf says what is your
name he says I know I can't see the
skipping guy yeah he says he says he
says you are to go with this new army
now and he looks back tasty looks back
at his fellows and he looks over at you
guys and erupts in joy oh good
I go welcome young tasty okay-y ung into
into the arms of acquisitions
incorporated you are a temporary sub sub
intern here's the and then she takes his
hand and she signs it and she also
smells tasty wrong maybe it's so wrong
that it's right yeah it could be a Lea
it could be the Goblin version yes
to tasty - yes Oh Oh young tasty are
you prepared to walk into the mouth of a
god meat first wait he asks everyone
this yeah me too
oh yes yes
is he laughing meat for him every
palpable well were we gonna do with them
well I just saw that we're in this place
we could maybe do with something that
looks like it belongs even a little bit
as long as we're in the the places where
they're kinda you know preferred once we
get to my town I don't think goblins I'm
gonna do it
feed and walk it big responsibility if
he's not useful we can send him packing
or we can even dance tasty we should at
least save them till we get into into
town and then we can kill him in sight
of some of the guards in order to show
that we are not aging so think we had we
had this conversation like if it's like
a circle of four and he's right in the
middle in his mouth his mouth is wide
open what a champ we could pull out
Chewbacca
Death Star thing where we handcuff him
and bring him into town with you
disguised as that we we have some kind
of goblin with information yes
did he he did something what would be
bad what don't your people like sunshine
goblins it's probably wonder why I would
bother bringing him in instead of just
killing him so he's obviously guilty
no one question about that goes yeah
he'd be a thing you could snack rifice
at an altar I don't actually I'm not
sure how DM cuz Chris doesn't know how
does loss feel about goblins do they are
there any worshipers in the among
goblins yeah there are some okay there
are some but I doubt that they're that
prized yeah that's not the cream I
didn't Bravo but I didn't know don't
know there's all kinds of creatures
especially you know superstitious
creatures that you know when presented
with you know worshipping and infinite
eternal spider you know there's
something about that that resonates
mm-hmm you know it is it the path is not
without its virtues certainly can you
describe tasty yeah yeah just described
Casey just give me give me like what
what he's wearing what his eyes look
like relative height to myself hopes and
dreams yeah exactly
so he is about he is just about your
height okay it's like without the bun
okay right so up to the top of the head
without the bun with a bun you're
getting bonus points taller I'm taller
right that's all that matters exactly
taystee has incredibly sharp rat enabled
ears along the bottom fringe with what
appears to be a random sampling maybe
even of handmade rings three on the left
ear one on the right none of them are
gold you're not sure what metal they are
there's nothing especially valuable
about them except a tasty in terms of
the armaments two daggers hmm
in terms of the armor it is it looks
like hand-me-down leather armor and you
can tell just by the look of it that it
didn't serve whoever its previous two or
three owners were especially well but he
does have a pair of decent looking black
boots
well worse comes to worse boots boots
you guys there's the reason rosy is like
actually taking an interest in this guy
what's that oh it's the only person to
do these things at your high place yeah
yeah we see a lot of things I still I
have an almond from the net prints
debacle and so I I offer I'm like I
actually don't know what goblins I try
this so you should you you hold it up
yeah and I let's just try to give him a
snack he takes it and he goes and then
he hands it back close enough all right
he takes a couple chomps in the air he
sort of mimics you but he feels he feels
like he's done his duty by this yeah you
know what to do this is great this is so
great yeah and now he's got bored right
so it's he bonded to walnut like how
they life mates now this is just step
one in whatever we are gonna need to
fulfill this prophecy okay it's just you
always want to have a net pocket
gobbling yeah we have that first line
the blood of a friend I don't want that
to be any of the four of us yeah look
what you did walnut okay so can I pick
him up
no can I like grab them around the waist
like is it you can a couple try got the
legs okay well sorry I look at them and
then I point I pointed the beetle and I
go up again alright killaby though oh
yeah yeah yeah and he and you see that
it's often little goblins because there
are beetles in the in the yeah entourage
issues out there as well and it's often
beetles driving them you know there's a
goblin and there's a beetle on the
goblin with rains but then there's a
goblin on that beetle yes as well and it
goes on like this a 10000 times
subatomic he knows exactly how to do it
in fact what you see is that they sort
of in a very sort of like Titanic way oh
they sort of hang on to the they sort of
hang on to that sort of rhino beetle
prowl and they just sort of lean left
and right oh and they can so they do so
they don't have to don't have to rub
that beels channels like some videos
you know maybe I would oh maybe I would
have been tapping on it so much feels
like Oh removing that steering new
driver yeah maybe they can go faster
okay well I'm a I'm a piece we all got
something to that exact yes oh he's up
on the deal so he's ready to go he's
wheeling this thing around to get the
party I have an appeal yeah Clark Morris
is here as well I'll ride clockwork
white boy okay I'm on the beetle but
proudly is myself not as a small beetle
this time yeah okay bye now
yeah yeah I mean I'm emboldened by all
of this like okay maybe we can do it
maybe it's not as bad as I think you're
gonna have that beetle shape just in
case I got it I dialed 9 one Carver Gaal
says that when you if you ever need
anything or if you're stuck in some part
of the process you can always return to
the city where you first met him that
heap of ruins high up which he says is a
town called hollow rar and he emphasizes
he emphasizes that he did not name it
that it's a very old name and that you
shouldn't blame him
if it's hard to say no I wouldn't I
wouldn't dare like I wish I was having
to return to his home then my dumb
families so Wow
he says you would not be you would not
be welcome no nor would I and it seems
like we're in the same place I wish I
could send you on a on a on a mirror
task where you have to do something for
my rugs I understand how this works
do you want to come with us
he says now that I've created this army
I don't know what will happen if I don't
maintain it constantly I feel like I
have a responsibility to these beings I
think that someone else could take them
and probably do a lot of harm yes
goblins are a big responsibility
everything that I expected occupants you
will file my quills you'll wash my inks
treeless this is God this has to be true
you will refill my ink pots by 6 a.m.
every day you're gonna scrub all my
vellum and then you're gonna scrub my
vellum scrubber and then you're gonna
scrub my villain scrubber scrubber Selim
yes I have three if you have a problem
with that I didn't think so
it's standard press and the beating 10
a.m. beating you drop the manual on a
film yes you will read this by dawn it's
the first three pages are meticulously
written out and then it's just like
pictures and they're like well it's
dream journal recipes recipes for sure
very nice
anyway that's what I got for you
actually so he's yeah tasty is just sort
of almost like a like a flag on a on a
prow he just sort of swings down here
guiding it oh yeah it's it's it's a
beauty it's it's a thing of beauty so
you know that the best way to get across
the lake of radiant mists is going to be
getting some kind of a passage probably
across that massive body of water but
it's not it isn't a place that you have
a tremendous amount of experience with
so there's going to be some there's
gonna be some key learnings once you
arrive there sure yeah
so it's a it's a fair it's a substantial
path from here up to the edge of that
Lake I mean it's gonna be probably a day
or two s travel because be good because
you haven't been to this place yet and
you can't cast a magic bubble spell
someday oh if only yeah I thought it
when I come back that I'd I'd have that
in hand but back sooner than I thought
yeah do we like how how much rest is a
beetle require do we will we have to
make camp life cycles only 24 hours
every day you have to get a brand new
one so while your so while you're moving
on the beetle sometimes he'll tap the
beetles head a couple times with one of
his feet jump off and you see that
beetle just continue to go in that
direction so he's running off and
grabbing fragrant mushrooms' stalks and
other types of deeply unpleasant
smelling food for everybody else oh yeah
there's a there's there's its peak home
that's why I can tasty mm-hmm has cruise
control oh yeah absolutely and I'm but
to all today's beetles I'm saying I mean
some of these mushrooms something that's
better than that stuff the dwarves were
trying to feed us you see them this is
Underdark cuisine yeah exactly it's
fresh its natural its local its local
right you don't have to dress it up with
anything it doesn't send you into some
kind of mushroom ROM no no we don't eat
those you can if you wait you know but
yeah I just Eve it's just like like rich
and sulfurous and has that there's that
nice
it has that nice pop like as soon as
that as soon as that bicuspid
gets through the skin it's just like
there's a little there's that moment of
pressure it's like is it all there it is
and then if the mouth it's like tiramisu
like if your mouths open a little bit
the spores pose real oh of course yeah
no it's just what you don't want to
begin with you're like trying to get
trying to get oh yeah exactly you don't
want those sports to go to waste
yes it's it's definitely sport biter
situation but you had mentioned the
mushroom realm that brew oh yeah and as
you are yeah this place definitely
brings you back into that yeah mine
space look so much like Cappy so when
you have been in the surface world Cappy
generally speaking is benign well he
just C sleeps most the time anybody
knows every now and then every now and
then he has opinions but their mushroom
opinions and yeah he doesn't share them
with other people down here you can sort
of feel him shimmying and jostling so
that he actually can turn independently
on top of the head that's how he wasn't
the Shadow Realm oh just do it everyone
why livelier yeah so he's he's
definitely taking in the sights and his
the cap has definitely has a clammy yeah
cast and you still have Oaks scalp on
top right yeah don't give it it doesn't
it will not stay on there anymore
I don't know oh no no no you had seen it
before
exactly it's too slick mm-hmm and just
as you had seen it before where before
it was like just raw flesh and it was a
good fun joke you were having it yeah
you were enjoying it Oaks expense or to
honor him that was honoring it's up to
you no I'm sorry no Gennaro is like no
couth day like oh yes sure you'd loved
oak is now something like a basketball a
soft basketball covered with black hair
it's growing a new oak oh it's good well
kept in a bag incubate like a mother
handle its egg like yeah I knew it
starts checking boxes it's this flesh
lump but with hair on it and be like so
wait it's just not on your head anymore
yeah I think one day it's not on my head
and it's just in a bag I'm just like
because I would like some like it hit
some God desk blood tinge or whatever
was inside it so it's growing it might
grow and oak back maybe I don't know
it's like Shawshank where the guys
feeding the bird in his pocket right
feeding the hairball this flesh ball
like sprinkling little food yeah just
[Laughter]
running your business drown I okay so
I'm I'm spending a lot of this journey
as you know as bolstered as I seem to be
early on uh snacks yeah I'm I'm also
very quiet that for long stretches and
during that period I'm trying to decide
whether or not I should try to message
my sister and even in my you know crazy
fantasies I actually message other
relatives other people that I made know
that might still be there and I think
not okay so what you're saying is that
this is exactly like real life yeah
absolutely every way oh yeah right
coming to dinner
should I want Nash you tell her now no
ah stride I won't they if they don't
know I'm coming than that
won't upset them now I shouldn't they
wouldn't help me they might help me
though
am i go this all out loud I'm tired and
I'm like I'm talking about it I not
instantiate about it there are no
friends in your body
yeah I'm that's how I'm choosing to
spend the the bulk of this trip are you
trying to find a suitable alternative to
your sister anybody but her
I know that that's probably the easiest
one but I also know that she doesn't
have a reason to necessarily help me
like I don't know what's happened in the
last 250 years you know do you really
don't I do not yeah so I
I've decided no I I probably I should
I've decided that I'm going to keep
thinking about it and know when we get
there the right thing to do or I don't
or I won't know what's the class
structure I'm here who's in charge it's
so okay yet you want to do that in
character let's slice what dinar would
you like I'm royalty who's who's the
fellow royal need to talk to well first
of all I don't anybody except drow are
killed on site essentially or maybe
eaten or tortured or I don't take
they're not fond of visitors it's a it's
a matriarchal society and pretty much
everybody worships loss the spider
goddess she has lost way down here and I
don't think that they would appreciate
you whatever you think of as royalty I
don't know that it would hold any water
down here and I also um should I just
lost my train of thought come back to me
now you will just see Kath rest the rest
of this show where I'm at oh it was that
um
it's a it's a matriarchy what does that
mean it oh it means it would be like is
that the women have power they're seen
as the the superior being sounds great
and the males are seen as a speed bump
in the lineage they could still make use
of themselves in some ways but we pretty
much all had the understanding that
we're you know mulch for that garden
that's sort of where we the station that
we have usually it's a large family so
although my my parents only had the two
of us first I know know that has to be
true because my dad's dead thank you how
did your dad die Oh in before my own
eyes he was they decided that he was
inadequate to be a servant of loss and
he was sacrificed in front of me but he
was very reassuring about the only thing
now I see that I was gonna tell some of
their emotions I see those the concern
I'm like oh I'm fine he was very
comforting toward me and my sister at
the end we've made us understand this
was the best way to go about it made it
under made me understand that this was
coming for me too if I wasn't a good you
know lost worshipper and I get it I got
that as if kids we all know that but
you're not a lawful worshipper no so I
don't want to go back they know you're
not alone
oh I assume they know by now they didn't
I didn't say goodbye I just left
no I think they stay in a worship loss
so this bug is working it is this bug is
is working it's buggy a off and so like
I said before so so the Underdark
is the Underdark as we know but there's
multiple levels imagined art layer cake
right thing so you have like a dropper
you have like a upper dark a middle dark
and a lower deck I just want to make
sure everybody knows we're talking about
yeah so places like Alcazar because
they're lower are I know that those are
both full ride making a native the word
okay that's like the upper section and
so you have traversed that and the
section you are in now is still
technically in that upper altitude realm
which among other things means that the
ceiling here is relatively low for a you
know a deep spooky cavern right it's not
a comfort it makes it obviously makes
the whole thing seem worse yeah it's see
it seems like it just we're just right
there all the time but you even here in
the upper dark there is a rise that
clearly is moving up and you can see
what you think might be the beginnings
of a bridge or something in front of you
and it's lit from beneath and there's
like gouts of steam and mists that
surround this massive intricate object
this path that is been leading out over
into this was radiant mists yeah I
assume what does Catherine know about
the nature of that of the radius yeah um
there's a couple things that he knows
things that he's heard anyway give me
that history check and I'll tell you
oh I will and for this one I will take
advantage wait where's my where's my
goodies don't you give all they'll be a
good one
I'm an advantage so that's a real six
and then that will be it's not any
better so it's a ten
it's my kiss trap you know that it is
that it is the site of Ringling or
ethnicity of of sweeping shadows rising
shadows swear I chose blue shadow I
think you said swirling shadows yeah I
see you were Letendre that's why I don't
know if you had if you had rolled higher
I have soaring if you had rolled higher
warring things would be very different
now you piece of shit but you know that
you know that it is a it seems like a
strange idea but that doesn't mean that
it's not true it is said to be a city of
cloakers right good and so a cooker you
don't cooker is like do I know what that
is yeah three is not good enough
no cloaker is a creature it's like if
there was some kind of imagine a dark
job orientation video right right so I
imagine imagine this is like one of the
things that you would worn like a brand
new dungeon ear like day one yeah
these creatures they like to hang up on
us the lack type they like to fall down
like a cloak they are in fact
indistinguishable from cloaks when
they're not being doing their weird shit
and so this is a creature they're not
evil but they are a strange and alien of
mind so they're incredibly difficult to
communicate with or even understand any
kind of overlap and what you might want
that they want and vice versa when they
flop down is it just teeth in their than
the one they have yes they have a face
inside
they're teeth going crazy ready to chomp
down I spent literally four hours here
200 years ago so I don't know this
bridge this would have been this would
have been where you like this would have
been where he went to summer camp or
something like that right the old boat
still there yeah exactly
um but you are starting to get a very
odd back of the neck sensation rosy bee
stinger hmm
the closer you get up and the beetle can
get right up on this this bridge is a
very very wide thoroughfare this seems
to have strange cracks in it at what
seemed to be regular intervals okay
and also the entire thing seems to hum
like a at a certain pitch like the
vibration it's a it's a very low base
vibration it's not quite like a rumble
it's constant and it is it appears to be
coming from the bridge itself
oh absolutely
but there's so there's something about
it in particular that that has a greater
effect on you and the more you're taking
in this this situation at the end of
this bridge you can see that this bridge
goes up and then you know several
hundred feet out just stops oh the
bridge literally goes into open air and
you can see that at the very end of this
bridge there's always like a dip like it
goes forward in this would dip in a
ridge and then seated out on the bridge
itself is a man in a simple grey robe
and sort of clinging to him on all sides
appear to be like strands and ropes and
trunks of shadow that just reach out
from the ambient air and seem to want to
know him doesn't he seem into it he's he
is complete is perfectly still
oh and he's he's standing no he's seated
I think he said it did he visited he
stated right there is it facing as he's
looking away he's looking he's looking
out over the the lake Aradia mists and
did this bridge used to connect to
something is this I knew you knew about
the bridges and the shadow span was
pretty pretty famous but that was
hundreds of years ago you don't you
don't know what you don't know what has
changed since then
okay apparently a lot they didn't bother
to like mark up the entrance to the
bridge that it was out there to do that
so we've made it all the way out here
it's good yeah it's I mean it's a long
long way across this this thing you can
see a few you can see a few docks and
various stages of disrepair mmm wood
split down the seams boat chunks public
works we need something juice so funding
well do wait do I know anything about
the way that this man is interacting
with shadow you you have never seen it
like this
exactly okay and you you think that you
would be you think you'd like to know
more okay about that all right
maybe we'll have an opportunity to learn
more
after the break hmm hey don't go nowhere
we'll be right back punks welcome back
my name is Jeffrey Kerr Arkham's sorry I
don't know I feel like I wanted try to
be professional for five seconds I see
now that was a terrible idea
hey um what do you love me to mention
that I forgot oh no I got it
if you have questions for the delicious
designers that we're gonna have
available for your interrogation during
Table Talk Gavin and Abe throw questions
directly into the chat with the hashtag
question indicator and then our precious
inky bot will digest those and then
we'll see them at the very end it's been
great now let's tap all the emotes you
want them to make exactly its non-step
we'll go through every single one no no
no no you'll have it you'll have an
opportunity to talk to these powerful
creators ask Dave why the overlay is not
made of jade instead of wood
well that wasn't interesting that one
there was an interesting period he was
like he's her wait is there wait he's
like right now I'm thinking about kind
of a jade thing and then I was like yeah
my don't just bail just remake the whole
campaign I don't care I'll just maybe
I'll make the whole campaign about Jade
like let's do it let's fucking go ho ho
anybody else that would be deep sarcasm
remake the whole campaign then yeah no
man I read that no no no I think for me
it's like that's that's the fun part
like that's that's the dark souls of
dungeon master you know yeah
no it's the dirt that's that Dark Souls
of Dark Souls comparisons now Rosie be
stinger yeah yeah you are seeing this
individual there's an intimacy and
simplicity to the interactions that he
just has with this the ambient natural
shadow of this cavern so one of the
things right so Rosie's ultimate ability
relies on her drawing from the plane of
shadow and creating this doesn t shapes
which I have not used my new version of
my grandma manse my new grandma man save
with just a little bit tweak
but its limit worked little twerked
Rosie so I guess I see this guy and he
has power and manipulation over the
shadow that I have dreamed of I suppose
because he's able to clearly do it at
rests at will for a longer period of
time and the manipulation over that
plane of shadow is part of why I had to
leave the monastery and so learning more
about this technique which I thought was
esoteric and frowned upon
certainly by my Master's means that I
slide off that Beetle and I I get down
off this beetle off that beetle and I'm
like I'm walking toward this person with
no thought for my own safety or how wise
a move this is and I haven't said
anything I'm just like oh walking
walking away from you guys instantly as
if mesmerised I think really there she
goes by everyone so weird today right
hairball with them are you calling Oh
careful she's gonna start this bridge
business out I'm sure that's where she's
headed
yeah I'm just gonna go pay the toll okay
some kind of shakedown all right so I go
to approach him with frankly no
hesitancy at all oh yeah yeah this
Brizzy beasting oh yeah so tell me about
how you enter his physical space so
someone of this power level which is
9000 obvious minimum
I know that he detected us long before
we arrived on that bridge and so he's
been aware of our presence so I don't
make I'm not making any kind of stealthy
approach to him because I know he knows
I'm there and that's just that's
monastic maneuvers 101 yeah I taught
that class so for W yeah yeah yeah
that's pretty good t8 at first then so
yeah I approached him but I say I Stay I
respect respectful distance away until
he chooses to acknowledge me that's for
me
yeah yeah yeah it never happens he never
does he never turns oh my god okay so I
wait for a while just keep springing
like and you can see but now that you're
even closer you can see with even
greater granularity what's happening so
from back here it looks like there's
various strands of shadow coming in of
different widths now that you are much
closer within 10 feet or so you can see
that he is taking thin wisps of shadow
and then weaving them into larger trunks
I guess I clear my throat over to the
sorry it's like it's like you could have
called the beginning of this
conversation and saved 50 percent of my
brain but what you chose to do instead
was laugh and have fun yep
stand by it so he's just he's making
throat-singing
noises at me yeah whenever when you when
you speak to him he's okay I don't
understand
I relate hello hello hello hi hello
hello
he raises his hands up to the caverns
ceiling which only comes down you know
it's maybe 300 feet above he says hello
it goes is he human
what see what did he look like yeah he
looks he looks human but sort of but
deeply pale like a like a grub okay look
at like a human for whom the Sun is a
memory at best okay and he is older
younger it is incredibly hard to tell
okay um it's hard to place him on a on a
linear progression okay
so he's he's he is not surprised by me
he looks down in his hand and it is not
a hundred percent opaque whoa then he
shakes it out makes a fist a couple
times it's this gives him stiffness of a
thumbs up he's clearly very proud that
he has managed to create a hand nice for
himself good job
hello what are you doing what is this
hello hello I'm Rosie I am hey what
would you say
sighs sighs sighs sighs sighs okay hello
sighs hello hello my friends and I need
to cross this bridge do you know how we
can do that yes how it's going to take
some time do you know about time a bit
okay and then it'll be no big surprise
to you it'll be no big surprise
it's gonna take a little bit of time not
a lot how much is a lot of time uh it's
relative I mean we would love to be
there as soon as possible
a day or two a day yes
oh good yes yes less than a day
okay great less than a day wonderful in
total
Dave being 24 hours 24 what mm-hmm hours
two hours
don't worry huh that's a day sounds
great
we were doing better when we had day
let's let's serious day let's use that
as our basic unitive of chrono juncture
excellent okay sighs Rosie so lovely
does his hand feel warm and cumin and no
no what does it feel like it feels very
cool no no no okay
cold but substantial oh definitely okay
absolutely and you can see now that just
in all directions all the ropes and
cords that he's been weaving are slowly
silently sort of snapping at their
extreme ends and just unwinding Wow and
going back out into the just into the
undifferentiated darkness of the cavern
and Rosie's watching in awe of this and
I say I have some contact with the
planer shadow
well south well he's a gift yes yes
that's the parent ah
it's like you are carrying a shadow with
you that's this one for me that's an
indicator okay Justin wait just when you
bring two tasty no just the shadow that
I'm casting from whatever it is I'm
light she's like she's sick he's like no
wait he's like you're the shadow your
shadow that you're carrying your shadow
what is it what would you call it it is
a
rod Oh staff Oh Steph right oh this I
show him stopping master yeah okay then
he says this is yes this is fairly
typical manifestation of shadow stuff I
would say well that maybe I haven't met
very many others may be zero others who
are as talented as you are but almost
shadow see I did I care at all and I
think that that place is me and then the
upper echelon that's fair
could you teach me how you're doing this
this I've never seen work like this
before
incredible it yes I would have to charge
[Laughter]
but I am not opposed to it I I think
that we honor shadow when we serve it
hmm does that are those all common words
yes yes that tracks yes you're killing
it hello hello okay he says no you were
you are not aware of this device that
you you're carrying you don't know you
did not know that it was a shadow
it sounds no like um I got did you look
at Italy yeah ever I snuggled it we I
tuned to it it says cool stuff beats
people up okay but it has always been a
physical object it's never revealed any
well well yes it's as real as anything
is that's that I'll grant you that right
but shadow like any other material can
be alloyed with other materials
oh my education is incomplete I confess
this is a simple matter time obviously
will be a function but we will have time
together if you're trying to cross this
this body of water we will have time to
there maybe not all the time we need but
certainly we can establish some
fundamentals
well yeah will you teach me to use the
shadow to complete this bridge well
that's not how this works
oh how does it work he says so it's look
out there look deep deep into it looking
no it's over there actually okay yeah so
in the distance out here there's some of
this bioluminescent lichen but most of
the light here comes from the lake
itself and you can see what looks to be
a like a castle or a city structure like
a massive physical structure oh except
it exists in the raw air over the
surface of this steaming lake and it's
moving towards the bridge sort of
spinning and oriented like a imagine
looking inside of a compass and you know
there's that period when you're aligning
it where the compass needle is adjusting
itself constantly that's what's
happening with this city as it is moving
toward and you can see the closer it
gets it in fact it looks like it's hung
with rich draperies on every side and it
comes in and then you can see that in
the sort of foundation of this town
there appears to be places for the
bridge so this lip of the bridge
actually lifts up and it comes to rest
soundlessly on this on that basically on
the lip of this bridge and he's like
this is shadow he placed down at the
bridge itself he says this is shadow as
well like your staff this is shadow all
this is shadow I see I think I will be
shadow
soon I'm working on it I've been working
on it I'm think I'm close but I'm not
there yet and I'm glad because I might
not have met you
maybe this is a good thing were you
shadowed before no no I just think it
has advantages I see
I'm into it I think you're right yeah I
think if I could if I could choose a
form it would definitely be in that
plane in that realm I would say you're
already closer than most come with me
okay behold says our Mountain hook it in
there my tiny little all right right up
on there
yeah you can so it's like a hand is like
in the pocket like you know there's
stuff in there probably good stuff yeah
upon seeing that you hear my voice in
your head where you taking care that's
how much does this guy want I don't
think he's gonna charge us anything but
it might it might come at a cost to me
I'll let you know
bye love you hey what'd you say you were
just watching from Lake beside like I
don't know I can I don't want to look
yeah they're doing he says he says if
you're if your friends want to go to the
same place you do they do they're gonna
want to get on this city okay um so I I
turn around I beckoned to you yeah tasty
how much what do we need to bring I got
I'm sitting about three I'm 70 right now
oh well keep it keep in your back pocket
but um I think I I think this isn't
gonna be your normal kind of cost this
isn't like a money transfer situation oh
all right well yeah yeah I mean maybe
all this profession even if we were true
that the funny thing is that even if it
were true it's like you just can't come
from Denar it's like I'm not gonna give
it to you no right so a Herbie and tasty
can easily navigate up this bridge into
this thing so imagine that this wide
bridge
a fix to this town imagine that it goes
directly into a thoroughfare like you
would see in a city so you walk directly
off of this bridge into this place but
the city itself is made of the same
material as the bridges the only
difference is that this is that this
city it has that same sort of hum the
same vibration but it is like I said
draped in just sumptuous leathers it's
like a it's it's like a place that has
been mothballed or something right it's
just like it's been it looks like it's
been covered up and then if you look
back toward the bridge as the city is
getting up you can see this some of
these some of these covers like a manta
ray just fall off and then slide from
the city back down onto the bridge and
then they sort of wedge themselves in to
these regular interval cracks mm-hmm so
you can see them they get in a little
bit and then it takes a little bit of
effort and then these shapes wriggle
themselves inside of the structure hmm
yikes indeed and as they pass you can
hear something like that low sound okay
but they're not they're not attacking us
no no they don't they don't seem to be
interested in anything except resting on
this on the eaves and crooks of this
imaginary city okay we should hurry so
he's so he's taking you he is basically
taking you on what he imagines is a tour
of a place of profound detailed interest
and you listen do you like shadow
Yeah right like you're into it like way
more than most people sir
one time I went to CES yeah you're gonna
say yes now I've read the article this
sucks
it was actually like I thought that I
liked that type of stuff right and I
went to it and I was like I wish I was
so after like three hours I was so bored
it's like that's a television are you
for fucking real right now you want me
to be excited about a television show
it's like oh here's a car stereo yeah
here is a juicer with Bluetooth I want a
refrigerator that will be my wife but
anyways it's like dad it's like you
think you're into it right and he is
taking you on a tour of this town but
it's like a it isn't like a ghost town
like a ghost town is a town that has
collapsed in some way and is no longer
functioning as a city this is like a
town that is a ghost mmm is it like I'm
it's like a model town it's like yeah I
could imagine myself living here like I
can imagine this place being populated
but it's not for living in its yeah
represents so when you buy it yes like
this is what you exactly so as you're
going through as you're walking through
the town town you size goes up and gives
one of the sort of leather wraps around
sort of like an awning because it gives
it a nice scritch oh and it goes like
this are these creatures your friends
just friends like someone you like to
hang out with like to hang out us Oh
friend like um like I like I'm your
friend actually yeah yeah yeah yeah like
we are like this he says I don't think
that they see
thing that is not a cloaker as a truly
sentient creature
oh so you're kind of their pet we exist
in a sort of inverse pet continuum hmm
occasionally I am amusing to them I
think and vice versa mm-hmm he's just
one moment and then he gives it another
scritch he says and the city is it's
sailing through the air turns you can
feel it turns slightly under your feet
and start going in another direction he
says there's a couple stops on the way
to the other side but it won't it won't
take long it should be less than a day
of course
yeah I might fascination is to discard
this husk and I I think these I think
the cloakers have got it figured out we
got something like that are you a
student of shadow as well not a shadow I
also believe shadow to be a lie and as
much as anything else as one he's crazy
why did you did you make this town I
couldn't hmm I couldn't 200 years ago
this town did not exist in this way the
cloakers lived in longer bridges than
you see but after they had sustained an
attack Vedas the shadow orb Council it's
like they're like they're now king isn't
right if imagine if you had 12 kings and
they could all become one key
if they felt like it mm-hmm I don't know
the word is for that I was the King King
feels right
super King that's American ranking
ranking yeah yes yes a Rat King
let's say now this is the capital if you
will of ring Lorne or off and it houses
the shadow or Council and it moves
between each of the districts so the
district that we just left at the north
end of the lake that is the orb Mantle's
they this is these are my words this is
not this is not they don't call
themselves this mm-hmm it would take a
minute of droning and it seems like
that's tell me if I'm wrong that's not
how you prefer to be communicated it's
not a matter of preference I would love
to learn to speak the language but it's
not impossible
I can teach you a few simple words
please a few simple words he says watch
this he says may all of your staff for a
moment um I suppose that's up to the
staff I hold it out to you he takes it
and he whispers to it and it droops over
both sides of his handle in the noodle
what goodness it's it doesn't it doesn't
upset Rosie she's so enamored of this
person it's just like do it do what you
will yeah that's lovely
you love it he shakes it out Oh a while
and then snaps it and then he puts it
back and he's like I could teach you
something like that
I could I could let you talk to the
staff it's clearly very lonely a couple
just a couple words and it was just
eating out of my palm the poor thing
well listen listen I'm gonna show you
I'm gonna show you some things and you
tell me which thing you want to learn
the most okay and I'll teach you okay
so he's like so back there so you can
see that that bridge receding like the
or Mantle's they sing to the
they're like the architects the
materials that they use are hauled from
the plane of shadow itself and they have
a process by which they can in Furman
sir solidify they can solidify Harden
very good hard many works think use they
all work the shadow stuff itself that's
but they have to sing to it constant
okay okay if they don't it will begin to
ultimately begin to lose its its shape
okay sounds an efficient it will sag
yeah the whole story I'm only teaching
so as it is whirling over to the western
side of the lake you can see another
bridge projecting out similar by and
large to the last one but there are
cloakers here it's so it's like almost a
Doppler thing it's a closer you get the
more you can hear of that sound and and
it's just echoed by the city that you're
on right and so the closer they get just
like you they has become in tune with
each other as they hang on the edge but
here cloakers are like active like in a
frenzied way okay like they are flying
up and so there are rifts that exist as
I was saying last game there's rifts
that exist in the ground but there's
also rifts that exist in the ceiling and
they are these clickers are flitting up
high into the ceiling crevice and then
they are coming down like they are
wrapping themselves around things and
then they're falling back down into the
town and dropping them off so they're
pulling all kinds of things out of this
rift
he says these are the these are the rift
hunters they provide food for the
districts and it's like when they get
back down you can see them unfold
themselves over little baskets that have
been made like little cells of shadow
stuff so it's filled with these massive
frogs like frogs that are a foot or two
wide massive weird bugs they're picking
all that stuff up and bringing it down
and then you can see they're also they
also seem to be policing the water
around the edge of the at the bottom
over the lake itself you think that you
can see other shapes moving below the
water and that's something you have not
seen from cloakers proper they this
visit of they appear to be there these
don't seem to be aquatic hmm in any way
after after a few cloakers have left the
city a few more have come back on to the
city at lifts back up and goes to
another district on the the south which
is where you can see shadow he says this
is a district of the shadow weavers
south is also the place that you were
going to be you can disembark from
basically you will be across the way
here right and you can see at the shadow
Weaver Central you can see that this is
more ornate like the other places are
more functional and he says that they
actually do a brisk trade here in shadow
stuff artisan shadow shadow crafting
essentially okay and he says that he
says take a farmers market like yes
exactly and he said he said he says he
says we can get off here he says we can
bring your leg your black Vita leg or
baa
beetle I like like orb - it's fine
they're both fine you knew what it meant
mm-hmm did I that turned it dinar I've
just while you guys are conversing and I
just like quietly III say this would
just sorta was like when you were in the
Shadow Realm is this what it was like
yeah look like this it wasn't great yes
oh is this is this reminding tonight
yeah yeah although I guess the clickers
gonna do that clubbers are new these
yeah it's like this is this is yeah he's
like curtains living curtains are all
kind of weird that's new but similar
would you prefer it with the living yeah
something else with a pulse so he takes
you down off of the off of the city
itself
down onto this bridge that's reaching
out from the southern edge of this link
and this there's a lot more bustle on
this side right potentially because this
is a more populous area potentially
because this is a more it has an active
mercantil element that does its best to
secure and and perform business tasks
they just these cloakers we see anybody
that we might know there are there are
people there are drow humans der gar Oh
in small groups moving through
potentially I look so good yeah yeah
yeah potentially - and it's a weird
product and you suspect that there is a
there is a market for it
what kind of product is it but they're
selling all kindness so just toss us
lots of stuff okay yeah all kinds and
you can and you can and you can tell
them you can you can see you can see a
drow reach over and pick up a knife and
then just sort of like laughs with cruel
delight because it's perfectly balanced
anywhere he puts it on his finger like
it has no weight of any kind but it has
a brutal a thirsting edge but it has
absolutely no weight of any kind it's
gonna say does this awaken like latent
assassin murder qualities no it's more
like I see that I'm like Oh what what
I'm wonderful clothing that could make
you're just flowing around you you feel
like you weren't wearing oh can I be
made into clothes I think it I think
actually to see a drought do that might
make just feel a little bit hesitant
like oh yeah I remember what we're going
so all the things that are being crafted
by the shadow weavers are being sold
here and the goods that we see are all
made of shadows so that they don't have
they don't have weight like that's
that's the appeal of crafts exactly okay
um there is he says there is a so you
just you're you you're asking me that
but you could you could just as easily
talk to sighs yeah so so I will say well
there is something there is another
property of these weapons that makes
them attractive for certain modes of we
know rosy hums killing encouraging like
killing death murder murder is it the
wrong one no that's a really good one
okay um he says there are depending on
how these weapons are made a ten day
from now there will be no weapon to
speak of Oh yikes okay
so they get you you're good no food only
ten days later I'm hungry yeah yeah they
have food here for corporeal beings Wow
you want shadow food or nothing yeah
that's the one thing you miss is about
the Shadow Realm yes the food Oh shadow
souffle that they just can't make it
here like a whitepaper core and it's the
one thing I miss right he says I know of
a I know of a shop here where we could
we could be intimate Oh with one another
physically we have coin as well we could
be very close as close as possible oh
good
sure yeah that sounds great oh boy
excellent currency yeah so the so it
takes you over to the the cloaker what
they think of as being useful and a
piece of architecture is distinct but
it's pretty good size for a rosey hmm
scythe has to sort of kneel his way in
they sort of look like um almost like a
helmet it clearly has a place like to
hang up inside like it has a roosting
area right but inside it has lots of
places for them to hang so that they can
sing to these items which is how they
make them to begin with got it and as he
as he walks in this is clearly that's
operated by cooker he has
clearly talked to before generally
speaking they're not clickers are not
showing their face to people and this
one is completely showing it and you
wish that he hadn't because it's human
tits so it is not good
Oh No so it's all black like perfect and
glossy leather on the back yeah it's
like in the way that became a party in
the back
yeah yeah it's a business that's in the
front it's not a business that you want
to be a part of the living mullet it's
just yeah yeah yeah yeah it's a fantasy
mullet um it's sort of like a lightly
damp bone white glistening belly with no
limbs or grab lots of any kind to speak
of and I'm a top a squashy face that
looks like a demonic baby oh nice and so
then re-save says he walks up to this
creatures helmet and he says yeah and
you are positive that it starts to laugh
at him ah like it like the faces rap and
then it falls down and rolls around a
little bit
oh it's really funny yeah yeah yeah and
he gestures he gestures into the helm
with the tail he walks in he's like they
don't they don't like my accent but you
know I I have a human throat and that's
how it is yeah let's explore
[Laughter]
sorry he's a he says he says I
understand this is strange I'm gonna ask
you here in this intimate place I'm
gonna ask you to do things that you've
never done before
strange things well try me all right he
says I need you to hit this exact tone
are you ready ready he says yes very
good now now lower if you can you can
feel you can feel the staff responding
to that tone in your hand yeah I would
like you to try to turn the staff into
something that you would like to turn it
into right now mm-hmm
okay I mean I know like just like it
didn't work okay
I think that Rosie would try to make it
into a little boat a sailing ship I
could not be more pleased I could not be
more pleased and so you're holding the
staff and you're your clothes you can
you can feel it you can feel it you can
feel the desire mmm in the staff to
please you and happy them he sigh of
Kesava comes over and then basically
puts his hand on your hand and begins to
sing with you and like help you slightly
adjust the pitch it's a specific tone
like it's a specific
to nation that's it's not it's like you
have to ask but you have to ask in a way
that's still where you still retain
authority mm-hmm like it's it's like
honestly the closest thing or the
closest thing you can think of the
closest thing you can think of is like a
parenting tone oh yeah but it's like you
just have to learn how to parent this
this creature I so and so you found a
new type of song to sing to it and it
begins to expand like the staff itself
begins to expand and grow out until you
are pressed against the inside of the
helmet you can see you can see sighs
hands like over the top of me says
you're doing it you're doing it it's
happening it's just what is this is this
what you tried to make no not exactly
[Music]
your clothes though I feel like I feel
like you're getting it I feel like I
feel like you're a good student getting
flashbacks and well this is exactly the
same like to a tee so many bad memories
on this chair exactly
he says the size says you are a quick
study I suspect you've been to the
Shadow Realm
I've gazed into it I don't think I've
been there yet yeah your contact with it
will improve your your ability to shape
it hmm excellent I would put it on your
calendar
okay spend some time there okay
I know a guy yeah boy boy boy he's like
now it's it's very important incumbent
upon you to please collapse this
contraption down back into the staff so
that I can breathe a little absolutely
I will do that how do you do it how do I
do it he's like you just try and I'll
tell you if you're doing your way okay
mm-hmm
then Rosie reasons that it's the
opposite so it's gonna be like it's
gonna be like um the mouse in the
motorcycle right I think instead of room
it's more yep mirrors so yeah she she
tries to so you disperse it you just
it's the key misty Elliott the link of
radiant miss Celia so it really comes
down to like recognizing that there is a
kind of intention in the staff already
and making your case because the respect
is already there the attunement was
already there you simply have to make a
good case and you do you make a good
case you were able to collapse it and
refold it okay so from now on if you
ever use if you ever want to use your
gramma man see you can make contraptions
out of shadow any shadow not just my
staff the staff will give you incredible
capabilities okay because it's a it's a
shadow that you're familiar with okay so
what you'll be what you'd be able to do
with the shadow staff is always gonna be
superior okay super and I'd you'll be
able to accomplish more with the same
amount yeah the the volume of what I
just created vastly exactly exactly so
it's it's there's some ratio there but
you don't know exactly what it is but
whatever this staff is the material that
makes it up is
substantially larger than it looks okay
cool
from now on just got you guys assumed
that anytime there's downtime I'm like
whispering to the staff all the time
because you're making up for lost it's
just getting weird OID yeah exactly
no so you so he he walks out and the as
he walks by the cloaker sort of gives
from an affectionate whip of its spiky
tail and he gives it he gives it a real
scratch on the back of the on the neck
part of what a cloak would be mm-hmm um
this place seems to be sinning out you
think that you think that shop hours
might be coming down to a close like
whatever time it is can we can we shop
absolutely we're in a marketplace you
were dead you are sad shopping montage
you're 100% I'm able to shop buying
stuff that's our shadow kebabs yeah yeah
that's all you wanted a street vendor
yeah there's like all these awesome
shadow things and I'm like yeah but
there's a kebab place there schwarmann
yeah there's donner kebabs there we got
there season two finally happened right
I get it
yeah we all get it I don't know what are
the stores where are the wares go out
there look what are you doing what do I
see what's that what'd you see oh I'm
gonna say roll I got a 16 you see 16
stores everything costs $16 16 right 16
of your favorite stores
[Laughter]
I don't have a missus like necessarily a
you're just being in mind no yeah and
you don't have to you're just you're
just window browsing I like to think
that when this has happened infrequently
but when the opportunity to buy stuff
has come up I would buy you buy basics
thanks for Crenn are and then when he
sees her again he gives her all toys
from his travels
they're gonna expire well not all oh
okay okay not all that tell me that it
has it has to do with how they are how
they're made
mm-hmm if he buys something would I have
the power to keep it going with song or
do you think so okay well you've you
seen the process now yeah you think that
you would know how to coax a shadow
stuff object okay classic dark teddy
bear mm-hmm well yeah don't have to tell
me what said oh there's a dark what do
they have like what's they have all
kinds of they have all kinds of things
everything you think they may have do
you think that some of these toys may
have like a like a profoundly
upper-class drow child oh yeah in mind I
couldn't afford it
yes they are you like helping me like
well I don't think I'm like I've seen so
few of these for that reason like I
might have seen another child play with
something like that once yeah it's good
so like well when I was a kid 407 years
ago this was a very popular toy like you
only had Duplo blocks but like they have
Legos on display like oh no you gotta
get bad one oh this is so insane hey
Josh can you flip the cauldron please so
not only did I flip the cauldron thanks
so much too clever rogue I literally
rolled merchants on my out of combat
literary world merchants on my out of
combat things so this is what this means
this means that there is somebody the
equivalent of which imagine like they
were selling used shadow cars and it's
sort of like what can I do to get you
into a shadow car today by a shadow car
yeah so there is someone there is a
someone so it's like a it's like a
two-man operation
there's like the cooker in the back and
then there is a general manager no
there's a guy man like us first nibblin
like a deep gnome out front
compare Lisi over the table
he he he sees you and then he goes back
into into the helm in front of his table
and he speaks into hello hung to the
cloaker and a few seconds later he comes
out with a block of shadow that he sets
on the ground and then stands up on and
he says sir
sir please yes is that obvious I see a
picture I see the t-shirt he says you
know the toys that we give the toys that
we give a child can take up so much then
he says come and look at my wares but I
would love to it says for example these
are wares
where yeah here they are this so he is
he begins to show you a set of shadow
like interlocking shadow blocks and
rings that when combined take up less
space than they should so they sort of
fold into each other a little bit so
they're incredibly complex puzzles
because the way the pieces are
interacting with shift as they're used
crazy shadow rubik's camp yeah exactly
yes exactly but it's like their rings
and so he's showing like the rings are
like inside so it's like he done does
the puzzle pulls it out the rings are a
separate puzzle inside there that can be
resolved he says good that's very cool
he says I am willing to make a special
deal just today I'm all ears I'm here
just today
heard it he says I will give you one of
these one of these I need you to show it
to a toy shop in Waterdeep and then I
get to keep it you can keep this one I
want you to show it to them give him my
card I say I don't know this is a little
advanced for her so I don't know I just
play hardball
anything else he's he's like no of my
own my own shop she has played with it
now she is an engineer I watered watered
heaps really far the best for our
children but yeah but you can you can
tell that he doesn't really understand
like how far apart things must be like
his conception of geography surface
geography makes no sense I'm trying to
haggle and it's just going all over him
like way over his head and he's like
three take three yeah okay
now we're talking please bring them with
you take three free things and keep them
there you drive a hard bargain my friend
but a bargain you shall have is like you
will make the time to come back here
boys sure thank you sir
[Laughter]
travelling toy sales yeah to you we're
gonna come across like some swirled
prints or something
hell yeah oh yeah had it any other way
now three chef's Rubik's cubes yes
exactly and if you if you do end up
getting one of those back Turin are she
will gain benefits in the real go
believe me I will that's why I got him
she's getting three yes she will be
punished severely don't be a nightmare
reals killer yes getting three and as
far as this guy knows yeah I did exactly
we wanted you probably already through
his business card
yeah I was like three of them together
it's like she can build a Varitek yeah
well just fly around
I do take his business card what's this
guy's name here's a fantasy I say sir
what's your name smell just don't ask
around anyone those okay exactly
toy boy smell what's the name of his
store smell deep delights store it all
it does smells deep delights for
children for kids season really small
seductive letters like I say this place
is this place is really starting to file
out you think you think there might have
been a little bit of like end-of-day
desperation like at least turn this into
a marketing win type scenario but as the
as the rest of as the rest of this
basically bridge dock is starting to
empty out and the patrons are beginning
to distribute down this grade and in the
distance
karissa you see a city that you know all
too well
Sean Council Mayor Labor's please you we
are gonna see you next Thursday about
this time right for now don't go nowhere
of course walnut and Kate which is to
say rosy they're gonna go see Hamilton
but we have special guests in the form
of our cool designers Gavin and Dave and
cool since since we didn't have any
giveaways during the show we're gonna do
all of our giveaways during tabletop so
they don't want to where we'll see you
around
you