time is the enemy of the past it
threatens the fastest weapon you
wouldn't make it past a second answer
the question
play it brash and reckless to choose a
cautious solution you saw was prudent in
any sepulcher poker to don't become the
putrid it's that well said I pursue in
no mountain too steep for dungeon too
deep to send expendable marks up to the
top of the peak of beneath they see Yugi
they come like sharks to it while I swim
in that money bill like Carl Barks
through it so send your national parks
drew it I'll send him home in a natural
box with the clothes Tyler most of the
parks included save your breath for a
cleric confessor death is a lesson that
life is attending professor but if
you're seeking my official advice sign
on the dotted line English in the twice
I am Tycho Brahe adopt any occasion
packs I am also a manifest Hera were
drunk CEO of acquisitions incorporated
but today Jerry Hawkins my running a
game of Dungeons and Dragons for my
friends specifically these friends to my
right Dragonborn narcissist dinar blitz
ad blocking rains day on Africa no to
the right of my right oh I totally got
it I was right there I got a hat
EDM ripping the natural world walnut dog
grass the wolf circle it's so good well
it kinda looks like a dog hey now to my
left not your grandma's grandma except
in those rare cases where she is your
grandma's grandma
Rosie bee stinger well it's gonna be
today
[Music]
to the left of my left emerging as
though from a mist shroud Catrice
drought
all right hey now I was talking to
Alyssa just before the stream and we
agreed that a primer on our rich user
interface experience might be a solid
play so here are the basics player
characters in the c-team when given
bouns buy you the shadow council they
earn charges and one charge is including
the equivalent of using advantage so
they can catch those in any time they
want to to charges allows them to use
their super ability their alt if you
will they all have something different
they all have applications in and out of
combat so they have strong capacities
for their use the other thing is that
you can actually see right around their
character portrait how many charges they
currently have you'll see a user
interface style pip and ultimately they
can they can go all the way around the
character portrait imagine that universe
but like I say well one charge
equivalent of a advantage to charges is
the old delicious delicious delicious
now when last we saw our heroes after a
raucous adventure emerging from the
astral plane
they appeared back on the prime material
but in a strange place that perhaps only
one of them would naturally recognize
the inside of the inside of a beef man's
eye less the plain yeah exactly and so
here's what happened they emerged in the
middle of a 1v1 combat for supremacy
over some kind of goblin hob goblin
horde they materialized inside one of
the competitors specifically Belle God
which Azoff called out this is the sort
of thing bill dog would do anyway
apparently classic the party if I recall
correctly the party claimed to be a part
of some kind of regulatory board some of
the party decided to do this
whatever you played along with it just
fine she didn't not play along yeah yeah
she true document see
yes happened to coincide with her yes
exactly
no so what I'm saying is that Ryan
Harmon which is sustained in our Blitzen
came up with an incredible plan and it
worked for the most part and then
whatever didn't work in a purely social
context got pushed through with a
powerful usage of his dominate ability
that's right now their chronic
entitlement so mic drop
indeed so when we left the game when
last we saw our heroes you were standing
in the middle of a sort of wooden
octagon surrounded by a sort of roiling
mass of Goblin and Hobgoblin anger you
know you're being given gold indeed lots
thoughts of God through your domination
abilities you were able to secure some
additional wealth there were two doors
that were made available to you one with
a troll one with hobgoblins it sounded
like when I went back over the stream it
sounds like you decided to go the not
troll route yeah which I mean I think
that's you know nine out of ten doctors
would probably agree with that course of
action but that is quite literally where
we left the game now the dominate spell
as it is used by Denar in that rare
conic entitlement context lasts about
ten minutes so keep that in mind as you
uh as you strategize your next moves
took us ten minutes to get the gold hand
it over we had to commit all oh man all
right so we're hustling yeah let's go I
do I do we see any figures of authority
in this hallway that's right the hallway
itself I mean you are you are in what
appears to be a massive cavern so it's
not a hallway it's not a building of any
kind this is quite plainly against the
naked air and you know we're asked I
would classically be
you can look up and just faintly see
what you believe is the ceiling of a
cavern except this cavern extends to the
utmost of your vision in every direction
that you can see I mean there's you are
a person for whom fresh breezes are an
expectation either on the top of a
monastery in the crow's nest like these
are your boat hat these these scenarios
are you know our rosy basting or branded
this scenario is not rosy basting or
brand and I would say it is there is
it's the whole place just appears intent
on crushing you that's not sky no it's
the first thing you said was this guy
tell I know what would would I be more
familiar with this like maybe like
regionally where we might be based on
you yeah you are not you are not
unfamiliar with this scenario at all and
so and how you how you how precisely you
feel about having returned to the
Underdark is is something I'm sure we'd
all like to hear you have not you have
not been to the Underdark and in quite a
while I would love to find out how under
dark we are now can I determine it from
just the the nature of the rocks well
you you know you you suspect you have
some history I will be willing to give
it a shot yeah let's see it I'm gonna
use an advantage oh you see you want to
be advantageous I will all right
it's a storied dark there's not great
okay worse so the best one was a 12 okay
so you are in you have some confidence
that you are in the lower dark so of the
of the three imagine if you will a dark
layer cake boys it's my party other kind
well as they say German like a German
chocolate yeah right but but it but
instead of like that like a pickpocket
sherry layer its terror
Yeah right just a tarragon - ya know
it's like it's terror infusion terror
scrambling but here but basically this
is what it is a sight got there I never
have a chance to say that word a sight
well I should actually occasionally you
do it's rare but it does happen
so kethry strobe the lower dark is is
the lowest essence is the substrate of
of these different of these different
layers and you are in a ruined I mean
you are in what is clearly the the
dilapidated you know foundations of a
once-great city you have a few guesses
as to where you might be in truth you
are not you are perhaps only a couple
hundred miles from your home or what you
called home okay upon realizing that I
get I've become visibly nervous more
nervous oh yeah no nervous to match my
exterior yeah you know what I feel good
I look nervous but this time you can
tell there's a subtle shift so are we
being so are we surrounded by a group
there right now right now there appears
to be a window for your escape okay good
well do escape first no no cuz what I'm
what I'm proposing is that we're gonna
go what I was hoping to be able to do
was say well we got to get back and file
these reports and we'll see you later
but I'm gonna I'm gonna pull i'ma pull
you aside cuz your price shaking a lot
of hands I I could dominate this dude
that's good can you okay we're still 10
minutes yeah if he's in charge I just go
hey dude declare me in charge lock
yourself in this room and don't come out
hello everyone I'm in charge and then
lock yourself in that room okay okay
there you go I no no no muscle that's
maybe it maybe as we're hoping to get
some more privacy so that we can figure
out what to do next I am walking I pull
up next to you and
you roll I might roll up I was hoping
that we were a short hike to the surface
but this is under under dark ah and hmm
we should consider not ever being here
especially the three of you but I mean
we may not either oh you don't like it
either
no not so much not so many that makes
two of us all right do you know the way
out
are you familiar with this in particular
uh if I know that I'm a hundred miles or
so from it would for a man I'm you it
could you know how it would work but
this is that would be a an effort yeah
we need if we would need to find a
faster way till you've done for you can
I get a Constitution check for my
special boy yeah
oh wait he finally says it I get to
re-roll on us so that is a natural one
for the podcast listeners I get to roll
a natural one and replace it with a
natural one it's not very useful
oh great yeah no yes I would I would
remove that I would get a different
trait yeah
it doesn't do harm the one is what is it
fault
that's gonna be a four um right right no
no I'm sorry it's gonna churn it too
it's it's just a wand baby oh is that
how it works - yeah in the middle it's a
huge so hit in the middle of his
conversation with you his neck starts to
go starts to go slack and you see his
eyes yeah you see his head tilt a little
bit and you see his eyes just start to
flutter yeah basically you see you see
his underneath his wrap yeah you can
sort of see you can see if you can see
the you can see that's just the
remaining flesh shivering underneath uh
and his mouth straight his mouth starts
to form vowels and gende I graduate
because I think he's about to faint
is he about to faint I might is holding
him here just over you Oh dancing but
you look like you're about that sounds
to be like you're better so all I thinks
you're about to faint may go like oh
okay all right listen I didn't know you
didn't like it that much
is any of this intelligible it has a
beginning and an end you can tell that
it appears to be it appears to come back
around okay and then fill itself out
well he does not like this place I think
we need to get him out of here
can i cartography our way out I guess
you can try I want to dominate the guy
and ask him how to count sure what's the
easiest way to get out guy I control for
10 minutes oh so you didn't have him
come down can he tell me just how far
away's yeah I'm like he's basically like
up in the stands looking down right
bring the boy yeah have the boy lay out
my clothes so he he sort of like lifts
up his the his robes around the edges
and then sidles himself down over the
edge and then sort of steps gingerly
down through this sea of goblins is
something all part in reverence did they
do they give him some room all right and
he jumps over the last part yes yes my
friend it's the quickest way out here
the quickest way yeah it would be a
considerable journey
hmm this is the lower dark that wasn't
my question knave yeah what's that
like I'm just insulting him the second
this spell wears off person so much yeah
yeah so he he takes it he takes it in
stride yeah and the same we did like
there'd be things that you could tell
your friend that you could not tell a
stranger and so this so this knave
maneuver yeah is acceptable in the
context of your enduring and permanent
friendship yep
so what's the quickest way out I
understand we're in the Underdark
yeah it wasn't answer to my question he
said we could we could he says we could
establish a caravan and have you to a an
escape to the surface world in a couple
weeks
oh that's not gonna work for me
what would I mean we're in the test
market here would be like the office be
able to help us with this this seems
like a pretty big bug in the system are
we this doesn't seem that you don't
think this is the test for God oh we're
out yeah yeah we're actually portal to a
yeah yeah I said this this there's
nothing about this that would lead you
to believe it was not the the place that
you did it you invested so much effort
to escape
yeah we've we we jumped out and we're
return to our plane but just totally in
the wrong place I that's not I suspected
that not good news look we can get out
and this is we just gotta get out of it
this crowd because it's gonna turn bad
faster that's gonna turn you so I'm
gonna tell her this guy I say that
sounds great let's do that get that all
going yeah then go into a big incident
falsely he begins to snap and bark yeah
I want him to get this done and then I
want him to go away and I want him to
fall asleep because I don't want him to
be conscious when this spell wears off
so we can go wait never mind screw those
guys
yeah so I say you do that make make the
caravan happen and then give yourself a
little rest take a little time off you
earned it how do you think prepare your
Caravan takes you just got to tell them
to do it yeah to say hey everyone get
the new stuff and go away I just need
his authority I don't need him to like
load the cart for me might be fine it
might be fine it might be fun get on
your hands and knees
I want to use you as a step stool okay
I'm gonna ride on your back
yeah all the way that you you carry me
out of here
so Karissa even through even through
your own eyes this individual has a
presence so your vision is sort of
coming going of what legardie allows you
to see and the fundamental spiritual
awareness that you developed inside the
entity so this person whatever it is is
bearing something like a heavy chain
belt that hangs down in the front and
then is cinched up high behind the sort
of behind the rib cage and attached into
this leather strap Raymond this is this
like I have that's dominated right now
exactly but the symbol that he has the
Sybil the symbol that he has is one you
are not unfamiliar with I have to have
to look up my own notes yeah I figured
out so it doesn't come to my house
exactly here here but but for our
listeners at home and indeed for our our
masters in the shadow Council can you
describe that to the best of your
ability um utilizing your utilizing your
brow and warlock skills okay
even the origin of this nomenclature
might be good oh yes I recognize this
this symbol it's a part of what I call
the tetris toe Nautica it's a series of
glyphs that are formed out of their four
strokes each and they're designed to be
made in blood with a dying hand in the
same way that I believe the name of my
patron God and his name is not the earth
I believe that his name was at all which
was
most information that could be conveyed
with a dying breath this series of
glyphs I believe appeared on the black
altar and was designed by persons
unknown to convey what was being
observed at the moment of death and it's
not sullied by you know speak to the
dead or who knows how the message does
not interpret that it's the early
observation a saw as they died what
kinds of things not this one
particularly what kinds of things can be
described by these glyphs they're
supposed to be taken an aggregate say
you would have to have many deaths and
many people who are trained to use this
language in order to form any kind of a
picture but it would be certain concepts
like fear symmetry together teeth I can
yeah you can you can try to jog your
memory with a history check let me see I
could also use my history phone history
or Arcana no I won't let you it reminds
me finding places that people died in
like Dark Souls yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
that's true it's the best it is
I think Arkana or history are both
acceptable because it's a part of your
practice I get I got the same for both
so let's see nothing that's gonna be a
ten yeah either way a slice it it's not
quitters not quite good enough but you
know that if you had a longer period of
time you could pull it out of your own
rigorous notes yeah just pull it out of
your whole zone let's take a moment time
I really think about this big joy
exactly quick exactly he's very good
never mind he should have hidden that
behind like sound that you were speaking
yes so suppose we want to think about it
yeah so so there's there's a few more
goblin oeid barks and a few more waves
of this rod uh so and so and so then
basically he used he is getting
everything together and so
to bring with us but even even at no
even if even at this level like so even
a goblin army it's really more like a
like a natural phenomena it's it cannot
be directed in the classic sense it can
be inspired with terror you know and
like a scatter Third Point you know it's
it's it's not obviously that he is he is
doing exactly what you have said but
these goblins are goblins and they have
remained so so they're doing their best
this is you know entry level all right
exactly and so then he says I shall
retire to my yurt there to enter a deep
rest you've earned it on the chin yeah
you missed here I'm just getting so the
fastest way out of here is a couple
weeks yeah let me ask you a very
horrible question my friend who seems to
be having a really hard time is it
faster if we go towards or away from
where you're from are you still in
gibbering fool yeah that's a question of
my cognizant right now see if those in
and out okay okay
haha no what's the answer that do I know
that will the direction take us like it
would it would my former home be like on
a on an artery and we'd have to go
through it or be smart to go that
direction yeah so the gala dearth that
the town that you're from is to the
south and directly so slightly it
slightly west
I believe the under South yeah yeah the
darkness the jelly the darkness yeah
it's yeah true South no it's it is a
substantial ways even by itself yeah but
it's
it wouldn't be where you would go to
leave mm-hmm it would be where he would
go to stay and be a proud citizen of
Gallaudet okay so it's like leaving
through the basement even yeah even as
you're finishing the sentence yeah I'm
like no no no I know no okay I trust you
not to the south
yours is good all right mmm yeah
North East is all right okay North West
is all right you start to tip into pure
West and East not great any southern
vector that's no halfway through this
mm-hmm
his features soften and he begins to
speak in tongues again for a brief
period what is he saying to me it it it
sounds exactly the same it sounds like
something it sounds like something you
could this isn't different I do serve
I'll check see if I know anything that's
happening here yeah sure blam-blam-blam-
wait but you know you know using
survival right your assessment situation
is that it's entirely possible that
returning here is that is that this when
encountering a harsh environ mm-hmm it's
possible for people to go into shock I
think and become unresponsive you don't
think that's all that's going on here
but you don't think it's a zero factor
either okay so this is this is a bizarre
place I mean even as you leverage your
your survival know how it is for it is
for a place that might as well be on
another planet
yes exact you know that there is an
ecosystem here you know you know that
that there's no there's no natural order
that Lily he doesn't touch right but
this is like the cousin
this is like the B material do you know
what I mean yeah this is like third
cousins you have to revere it at some
level because it's still a part of the
it's a part of the design but by the
same token this is not
this is not the life that you were
trained to Revere so maybe if we get
farther away from this spot this will be
having less of a problem if we go more
north we have a better idea than just
actually making the track you you have
you have a pretty good sense if this is
about where you think it is there is a
there is a city of dwarves a few gnomes
but a primarily a dwarven city of
profound safety it's probably the
closest it's probably the closest place
to here it's called Alcazar you're not a
hundred percent United Haitian you've
not 100 percent sure how you might be
received there how I'm idea but it can't
possibly be worse than the place that
you're in right now in probably another
hundred seconds we're gonna go to
Alcazar alright well we've got a caravan
well this Caravan is being built I will
remember to find Steve no there are
there are two wheels on this Caravan you
know it's all I need and the other half
is on the ground and it is being pulled
by a massive beetle and look you don't
Clark more and felt built
well someone Clark more he can no six
ten minutes yeah right so we got ten
minutes what's gonna happen ten minutes
do we have ten minutes with ten minutes
before a bunch of goblins only sleeping
right now and then in a hundred seconds
we'll be awake and then he'll be after
us
alright and you'll still be so many
Clark more cuz that's the kind of dude
Gary is hold on I can't do that
we like that you could be right just let
me to find out started and then
we can you know do we have a way to
maybe like sneak away yeah they say you
couldn't you can none of this is decided
beforehand you can't do it you want to
it's just that some of things have come
I want to write a Beatle I want to
summon a reindeer while I'm a Beatle
that's a row at squad goals yeah well
right the beetle in full all right all
boys room on that beetle for two yeah
you know it oh yeah
let's go on the beetle right everybody
on the beetle and there's a little cart
in the back too like a little two wheel
oh no no lat form two of the wheels are
on one side the other side does not have
wheels that's just is the other slightly
bill beetle wait is it a beetle with a
sidecar yes I'm already cool hallo
beetle yeah come on the other side cast
find wheels yeah how long does that take
only a couple minutes 20 minutes alright
let's just yeah let's
we should skedaddle before the crowds
board turns hostile in a minute that's
the top speed of this beetle have I seen
this type of conveyance before it's
reasonable it's it's for its for
carrying goods generally speaking I'm
the best yeah but we are goods is what I
said and I said we're the best I also
made a joke I'm ready to go you made it
louder it's also walnuts ready to go
Rosie's ready yeah okay tell me how it
goes
well that's show us the way yeah oh yeah
no I don't think I've looked South once
since this conversation so I'm the only
looking in the direction that I want us
to go yeah yeah North East
yes so then then I inform you that the
city's called bill kazar
it's a dwarven city we will be safe
there oh I'll hide on her blanket okay
but not here it's not here that's
primary concern okay
yeah this is there anybody near the wood
anybody is anybody to see us off and we
just have we've been permitted to just
take them no no they are you clearly
have the ear of the person that runs
this place a czar is doing his best to
sort of performative Li take on the
warlord mantel that he got like ten
minutes ago but he's he's trying to east
trees putting his best foot forward
there's a lot of waving of a khopesh all
right I'm gonna speak to him directly
yes friend you won the match he's the
winner right he's that guy oh yeah okay
I just want to make sure I had it right
he's like yeah under a sort of sinners
breath he says and I think yes you do
thank me and the others we're going to
leave now
and I would appreciate it if you let us
leave what is the term you should kiss
kiss excess head start a stall head
start you know you won't be needing to
care of him I know we will be using the
caravan but if anybody asks for us don't
let them know that we are taking it
south south yes understood deep south
toward ring Lorne or off yes I shut her
very long time he says well blessings to
you gotta go south it's great place
everybody should live there it's like
there was this thing with the cheeks get
full no no okay jump on board I'm gonna
lean back a big behind us beetle and
wave to a goblins like you're doing a
great job and then use my small night
and cut the rope that's tying us to the
caravan so we don't drag - yes Ted Carlo
okay okay like you're doing great I'm
just gonna take care of this little rope
yep got it no problem and we're ready to
go
all right this beetle gets moving okay
leisurely pace okay so you see with
youth you've set absolutely everything
up you've created the proper social
scenario you've covered all the bases
and then this beetle is doing its thing
there's almost this almost like it go
ahead
oh no there's like a bass note that has
started to creep in to the raucous
voices from this ruined city that they
live did it leave in the farther you get
away it becomes more and more of a low
tone that's great I would like to juice
the Beetlejuice Beetlejuice Beetlejuice
juice the beetle thank you yes and I did
not put that together thank you I'm glad
that were there love we arrived I would
like to know what kind of juice touch
this beetle so sweetly right right on
the right on the right on the antenna so
tenderly do they have antennae have some
beetles carapace yeah and I would like
to do enhance ability and I would like
to do the one that makes it very strong
so it can walk faster mm-hmm well so
sting yeah
yes it's carrying capacity doubles which
I know juice coriander in the past I'm
wondering if it'll give a little bit
giddy up yeah yes exactly because
there's a lot of those but a lot of
people on the bug sure and now it's like
nothing it's like nothing to it yeah
is that is that your dude is that your
assessment yeah I know a lot about
beetles very strong we don't know you
know if they have antennae
feathery antennae very absolutely so it
definitely starts to it starts to pick
up it starts going about twice the speed
that it was but now it doesn't want to
go where
you want where is it I want to yeah I
want to summon Clark more at least go
through the Meccans of this yeah okay
I'm also going to be passing that trace
on us that's a good idea track that's a
good idea too no it's not it's not
dangerous let's just kind of destroy
it's just like it's just taken it's just
enjoying itself okay mm-hmm so it is
walking on the road and now it is going
off the road and now it has decided that
the right thing to do would be to walk
on a steep grade like this it's the
beetle way I'm less - I got four I can
try it
yes and I would like to take advantage
advantage on the giant beetle hurtling
has to be turned out okay walnut done
grass I want you to tell me how do you
coax how you coax this fine young beef
what kind of deal is it
Oh glossy mm-hmm black stag D yeah it
has that sort of like that knows what
has that sort of like prowl this mutant
yeah a little snoot yeah yeah tell me
about that carapace all right yeah yeah
so I'm gonna saddle my way up to the top
and there's like a top like the bands
that goes over its head like between
where it's tied to its neck and it like
vibrates at a certain frequency yes yeah
and I start like shaking my hand to like
vibrate it and send it the signals to
like turn us assuming we're equal based
on no signs but I would imagine it to be
very cool
so you so you're basically you're using
like almost like on the top of a glass
yeah like a frequency exactly you're
trying to use its own carapace to to
speak words of direction and comfort
yeah to this insectoid absolutely so you
you want him to walk in a way that does
not involve you
yeah I would love that it doesn't need
to be on the road I'm like real loose
about that yeah in the direction and not
upside down absolutely
two rules I'm not hearing a micromanage
it's just right so you so what'd you
find
no big this is all well known to you
Karissa but what you find is that what
looks to be a but it looks to be a
massive empty cavern the once you have a
more granular picture of it there is an
incredible amount of detail and richness
so it's it's instinct was basically -
you knew that it was time to go mmm
so it's instinct was to sort of climb up
and then get away from what it would
perceive to be prey of some kind
measuring but places that look like
they're flat or like I have a tiny of a
crack or slit or actually they're almost
like two slices like a crosswise slice
of like a french bread loaf okay so it
is flat on a grade but it's not a cave
it's just like a rift it's just like a
rent so even in this even in this cave
cavern there's all kinds of nooks and
crannies and crevices yeah to get away
from okay pursuers so it immediately is
picking up what you're putting down I
think and it finds a way to tuck itself
down in low and then find a grade that
does not involve its riders falling off
but does involve not being on the road
and not being visible to traffic out on
that space so you're trying to get a
hold of us yeah you try to get hold of a
magic deer yeah
if there's a moment oh and if we're
gonna have to traverse god only knows
what's going on with this beetle so
can't hurt to have Clark more around
please we're in a fight plus I always
forget to summon him start up around
setting him out I do yeah done
was here bless you yeah so how does it
work
yeah it's it's 10 minutes to summon in
the past I've described it as a like a
full metal alchemist because I would go
back to my your anime roots anime roots
like a summoning circle kind of clap
sort of thing yeah although it takes 10
minutes maybe a little ring little spell
ring builds is it gonna shield around me
a beetle yeah it's gonna punch the tubes
through you know can't make it to dwarf
in town without a few beetles no with an
elk everyone says that everyone will get
out in person yeah name one person who
doesn't so I'll wait so didn't I respect
you're trying to do anime bullshit
thinking about it like this I I think
that it is probably actually only one
clap and then the pound yeah but I bet
that it takes you 10 minutes to do it
exactly right yeah it's a it's an
instantaneous spell just he never gets
it right it's always like yeah it's like
goofy half-formed reindeer just come and
go like no no no wait wait wait I think
somebody's trying to play a guitar song
yeah exactly
wait but it's like by the end it's just
you just like you're just sick of it
it's like by the time it's like you once
you've just quit like once you finally
quit get on your own head yeah yeah I
like that then he comes back out yes
it's like I guess I guess I'll never see
him again I didn't feel about Clark more
I'm trying to figure out I'm trying to
figure out their relationship they're
like this is like a magical space out a
magical celestial space elk right that
easier that is intelligent he's
intelligent yes he he is intelligent to
get a 1550 on his SAT he did he's doing
cancer huge uh I think that's up to the
DM on the stat stuff at least according
to the the card and everything I was
reading intelligence wise he's like
we're in perfect Sympatico so it's like
hope so when there's like a fight it's
like you there's like a mental link so
you can like both team up obey commands
and sort of things yeah so cities my
best friend yeah as long as I want
casting time duration instantaneous and
I can make him go away like
instantaneously as well go so
theoretically like if someone tried to
steal on the right away and they would
just disappear I could we could tie
someone up put him on his back having
jump off a cliff and then make him
disappear and the guy falls that'd be
fun let's do that he spent a lot of time
I have a lot about ways I can use it so
you can use so after about 10 minutes of
clapping and slapping the back of this
beetle you see you see you see dinar you
see the gnar his head sort of droop and
hang off the back you see the shoulders
slump and then immediately there is like
a whoosh of wind like the sound of a
wind chime like a tinkling sound and
then you hear the four hooves clacking
on the angle of this thing it takes him
a second to kind of adjust to that angle
but that's what their homes are for so
it's not super scary and he does not
like it here no he does not like it you
can see he's he's like snorting and
sniffing and kicking it's okay buddy
come on come on pal
first I get all excited like hey it's
always a question of whether he's gonna
show up oh my god yeah he he is Giggy is
giving you a look that says that the
excitement is is unilateral hmmm he sees
a mushroom gives it a nibble thinks
better of it immediately
i-i'll hop on him and ride him too just
to take some of the weight off the
beetle maybe it'll make it go a little
faster so he's he's key asset he's
pretty tall here he's got it kind of
mm-hmm get low they're huge you have to
help
I'll gotta get I guess I gotta get lower
arm but that's my good right beneath him
yeah just strap yourself to the
underside exactly just one oh yeah good
I know that's good that's good thank you
alright that so outside there's the this
crack that leads back
to the cavern proper there's heavy
sounds sounds of footfall and clanging
weapons that are sort of finding their
way into this crevice and bouncing
around inside there by the time it gets
to the party it's very teeny and far
away they don't appear to be looking
inside the crack proper this so you know
I just had a question because I didn't
want to get too far past it we did get a
bunch of gold before me left how much
gold do begin yeah yeah so it's a city
say even though even the box itself has
value oh yeah oh yeah there was jewels
and stuff in area yeah no no so the box
itself the it's like a wooden skull
chamber that opens up inside there are
thirty gold pieces and the gems on the
outside your guess is they're worth
probably thirty emselves
cool hmm loot the body sort of thing and
I didn't want to forget yeah or just
like have someone this is this is worse
yeah this is like having the body loot
itself yeah oh yeah right it's rude yeah
it's great you got to engage
how long does Chris have to wait before
this the meaning of this symbol comes
back down but he can he can investigate
there's no he wants we know that you
guys aren't in the middle of this of the
UFC Octagon oh yeah I'm spending some
time trying to recall or flip through my
notes right right so the sign the sign
that you've come to recognize as the ER
is really the sign for unknown or no
symbol right this symbol in your in your
study of those symbols is the symbol for
unity UN ity oh my god still waited not
here not here for me here it's not Union
here maybe up there maybe that's what it
means it's a system bullet he was able
to perceive with his weird vision we
didn't see any of these detail well
though the detail itself I mean it is it
is quite clear just like his own focus
yeah it is
though he is wearing a focus on this
link of heavy chain but the specific
import of it there are many many
mystical there are many many mystical
symbols okay yeah yeah the ER was
notable because I couldn't read it the
others jumped out at me
maybe not jumped out there was some
study but but the ER I do not know what
it means what what yeah indicates
absolutely so you you you feel that it
is time to start leading the party back
out in that northeasterly direction
toriel kazar if that's if that is where
you're intending to go it's where I want
to go but I am curious why did it look
like that that that that belt was it was
a part of his normal clothing or was it
like the wrestling belt that he had won
oh you mean you mean it was it would
have been part of something that you
would get as a trophy yeah you'd this is
just something on his person that I was
able to pursue no no he he it appeared
to be part of his Raymond I mean the
closest the closest thing that I would
describe his raiment to would be
something like would be something like a
druidic Raymond it's it was it's clearly
like everybody else in that crew that
rowdy band is basically it's catch as
catch can like it's most clearly looted
it's clearly things that they have found
in the garbage
Oh or taken from previously living
people and these were tutoring
fascinating to the guy I dominated who
had this on him was I was like the fight
promoter and the guy you talked to when
we left was their fighter that we yeah
laughs totally yeah yeah yeah that's
that's what okay so you're saying we
need he beckoned like the main exactly
that we're far enough out yeah yeah all
right I indicate that it's I think we're
far enough out now that we can take the
main path which should be faster view
some little whistles and taps on this
thing yeah yeah just just keep guide
nestle yeah it works it works beetle
love exactly right so now that you are
yeah exactly you have to keep him just
shrinking down hmm no I haven't large
insect I don't have shag goodbye Oh make
him bigger
enlarge the Giants hide you thing just
go to trade out why wouldn't I
I'm so so chorus let me guess I'm gonna
get an intellect or an intelligence
check from you I guess I'll do that
let's see Plus Oh intelligence just so
it's gonna be 20 okay so that comes back
now hang on a second there's a very
specific table that I know this chick no
no no that's not it we're gonna mess up
your scramble your brains
there's no no no that's that's quite
right now Josh do you have any special
lighting effects for the cauldron being
tipped now you've entered my dark realm
now you've entered my diagram no that's
not it no this is not your realm no this
is the obvious no this is very exciting
stop it all right Newton 365 thank you
very much for this incredible thing you
have rolled the bane cauldron hmm
exactly so so you have next time when
you next time when you speak so before
it was sort of involuntary and now you
have begun to speak only in this code oh
just keeps going huh no no I'm gonna
turn it off in a sec
well you are actually you are unable to
speak at all except in this except in
this cyclical code what do I think of
this code do I think do I know it to be
a prayer is it something I'm familiar
with it all it should be exempt thank
you very much Josh
uh can I start making a note of what
he's saying if he's saying it over and
over again can I transcribe it that is
an awesome idea I wasn't thinking he
writes guys is this like Ryan let me do
my thing
no I was just wondering it's like is it
like you're trying to talk and then once
the words get to tip your mouth to come
out weird yeah or are they all messed up
in your brain too
no maybe I know what I'm saying I gotta
convince thought you know more I see as
soon as you as soon as you open your
craw and this this is not customary of
course as soon as you open your craw it
is just an unbroken serpent of
consonants and vowels mmm okay yep can I
can I awakened mind would try to
understand it no I wanted like a
didgeridoo I don't wanna use no I want
to convey its words to people can I my
asthma or my thoughts messed up let's
see alright I can't talk at maximum
volume you hear just a look at Jamba
Juice of spare of spare sounds of a
bargain-basement audio unsubscribe I
just turn it off I just start saying the
vowels and consonants talk versus shut
up he's scaring the beetle I only care
about this beetle ah dang it
nobody here knows uh the drow a sign
language something hmm
yeah oh yeah yeah but no but nobody else
knows it I think yeah why would you they
could
to us but you could have cared enough to
learn it you could have put the fucking
time in ready I've been doing it as I
speak all the time so everybody picks it
out yeah just like the steepled fingers
right and all of that was it's a rich
communion every time he gave us all the
quick the subtle hand wringing is just
all the noises rich so it's buttery with
meaning so you're gonna you said you
wanted to try to yeah I yeah let me yeah
I turn to you yeah I've my quill in my
parchment so I'm gonna try and at least
yeah how long is this is all this is all
you don't you I can't convey that to
them no so what I'm trying to do is am I
able to reset it so I can start at the
beginning every time you start to speak
it starts over okay good so I'll just I
will vomit yeah it is you you can you
can seize it and snare it okay and you
think you feel a compulsion as you have
written it out you can sort of find
where the where the sound loops
exactly and you have a incredible
compulsion to seize your debt marker of
the shadow council oh okay oh so this is
it's it's not a language that I
recognise if I it fills me with this
dread absolutely dread would be the
right word it is it is it is it is
frightening but you you feel like you
feel an urge to to gain comfort from
this okay so it's it's beneath my
vestments and as I'm writing I my hands
shaking and I start to reach
inside my vestments and as I see the
loop and I understand that that my hand
is moving without my notice I look from
you to you and I like there's no there's
not enough time to stop me probably but
I've like my hands inside my shirt and
I'm I'm grabbing this amulet that you've
never seen before I don't know what it
is either so I'm just look like you're
grabbing an amulet is it look at you're
having a heart attack yeah it's probably
both probably and I'm by advanced age
it's just could be it likelier than ever
yeah I bulging yeah I definitely look
afraid but I don't think I look like I'm
not losing breasts like I'm not red in
the face or anything it's just it's just
fear and I can't stop myself all right
I grab the ignite yes it wants to be in
your hand yeah okay so I have to say
amulet grandeur what are you doing and
also I am I'm looking at you now too and
the more you talk to me the more I'm
grasping this thing if I shut you're
scaring the Beatles you know but it's
one of the vowels Oh Rosie what's wrong
can I show her can I bring my absolutely
okay so my hands shaking and I pull this
thing out and it's this gold amulet with
the the S symbol on it right it's true
and I look guilty but at you in
particular and I say there's things I
haven't told you and this is this is
part of one of those things and I think
that we're in a lot of danger I'm
terrified so you can so your whole
you're holding it like this
yeah and then it's sort of like swinging
from your shaking hand
and when it swings this way the text is
codified and when it swings this way you
can see it plain as day and when it
swings back nice like this oh okay
and so I noticed that the text changing
from this gobbledygook as I'm looking at
you I glanced down and I read it oh boy
okay okay that's not good more of the
blood drains from my face okay so what
he's saying apparently is the blood of a
friend by a blade drawn in anger a
remnant of chaos the hem of his gown a
gift that is given by a sleeping
stranger will burnish the tattered crown
I know what it means
me neither yeah Shelley okay so this is
once I read this out of my still in this
paralyzation know excites left you alone
okay okay okay all right
it's sort of a it's keep swinging until
it sort of stabilizes okay it's good all
right don't worry about that I'm doing
it yeah can I see it yeah sure but I
can't I don't take it off but I will
right now I'm I know I'm looking at it
over the page yeah do you wanna I'm just
drink first
yeah I give you the quell now I'm gonna
write I'm gonna write hello friend just
a test do I write the phrase yeah it's
still no communication pop you know
hello friend I think it dumps out
correctly okay they want to show it over
I want to see if it'll go the other way
mm-hmm okay all right nice try though
hmm I write at least I got this all
right great job boy a smiley face next
time I get I had your anyway back okay
you start writing messages back to his
like I can hear works what what the
grammar what what what was that um I'm
not entirely certain what just happened
but something in his foul language
that's coming out of his mouth triggered
this it's a debt that I owe you owe a
debt yeah it's pretty much the only debt
that matters and it apparently wanted us
to understand this garbage which
actually doesn't make me feel better you
know you were having such money troubles
you could have asked dinar writing
quickly that's very sweet dear right
write down why was your debt in my mouth
what didn't you like to know
that's actually my answer I actually
don't I don't know I don't know you know
as much as you guys know as much as I do
about certain parts of this mm-hmm
maybe all of it you know as much as cake
knows so Clark Moore's hooves the sound
they're making against the the ground
has begun to change sort of shifting
from the sort of like unvarnished cave
surface into something approaching the
domination of civilization you're moving
across what looks to be shattered
cobblestones in patches you can see
aspects of what it must have looked like
in its heyday but by and large you are
moving through a blasted out landscape
you're welcome to investigate it as much
as you like react utilize your powerful
skills I guess I'm in front
I'm on a clock or in front of me I wish
my suspicion is that you don't care
about any of this shit I'm in a
different vehicle you see this gone
you're like yeah I'm like yeah never
understand the back of the card you guys
should see you don't even know this
habit it's always sayings mumbled
something well then yeah if I've got
eyes on the ceiling can I observe a
rolled-up sir absolutely
you've got to what do I say big to big
old rock you think that you think that
this was probably something at one point
see this the best part is that is that
dinar fans are brass or the yeah yeah
they're very good flawless yeah history
check with advantage
hell yeah now this is gonna be this is
gonna be outside you're Ken okay a
little bit I mean under dark history
this is not I mean a check with you with
today's with the state of today's
publisher I do it then like as you are
you're starting to survey and like I'm
just like yeah let me let me do a is it
gonna be history yeah yeah would
advantage also 15 okay 15 is good so you
know that on the way you know that
Elka's are once represented an even more
substantial outpost of dwarven
civilization in the Underdark
now much of much of the city just I mean
basically war on the surface they have
ideas about these night wars that were
waged and but they think of it as
something that happened a long time ago
when if you're down here they count with
much greater granularity additional
massive scale conflicts that have
occurred all around in the Underdark
and so it's basically just like the
lapping of
against this attempt to carve a place
out yeah down here and what you're
seeing here is just is the parts of the
beach that have turned to sand basically
yeah
these are these are shattered homes and
buildings and places of Industry that
exists in a kind of fragmentary ring
around the city proper if I changed
hands well absolutely I mean no no doubt
and you can see some evidence of this so
no doubt there were attempts to colonize
certain parts of this outer city maybe
use that portion to do another attack
farther in right but you also know that
there is a reason you've never seen it
but you understand that there are
reasons why the central city has not
fallen in this way okay cuz tough and
cool no I don't know why do I know why
why you've never you have never seen it
but you have but you understand that
that it is a place of tremendous
industry and truly legendary smithing
like fortified yeah you understand they
have a certain trade in rare and some
say magical metals some that are all
some that are only produced there some
would say a citation meeting okay um I
feel like I think Carissa is instinct is
to continue unless we have need to rest
for some reason and hide but other than
that I I think are we slowing down I
think I would be like why we doing we
have let's continue on pull a couple
good berries out of my pocket like huh
anybody just top-up feeling peckish I
mean if we're gonna just blast through
this town or not stop well just nobody
living here though right it's just a
shadow no it's just
busted I mean I can't hurt unless I mean
has this yeah yeah yeah
has this gentle ride counted as a short
rest or anything or do we need to tell
all for the babies you would have to it
you'd have to sit down okay I want to
stop right no I don't either Barry up
marry me so I bury my awesome bury it
yeah you like catch it in your mouth
like heads up it's huge in my tiny hands
yes you can you can like three bite it
yeah yeah I'd like to I wish we had the
opportunity to sift but under the
circumstances I'm just like cars your
curiosity drow yeah so I'm just like
just wired just keep going - yeah what
are you doing this is your domain I mean
I guess I would follow you follow your
lead or your impetus to get to the next
place I haven't having no reason to stop
I would have no interest in ruins and I
don't think dinner I would like this
underground gross place he was doing
alright I suspect I suspect so you
continue on these roads that are getting
more and more certain and sure of
themselves and in the distance looking
up against the the cave ceiling you can
start to see a like a turquoise like a
glowing turquoise lichen look bright
like shining bright in the dark and
casting its light down over a city that
looks like a like a clock or something
it looks like it is a meticulously
constructed it looks like a like a model
of a city it's like the Game of Thrones
oh yes
when I read the description I was like
oh okay yeah you did this like 20 years
ago
yeah do I know this city yes yes yes you
think that this must be Alcazar you
think this must be it it's closer than I
thought yeah yeah yeah it's so you look
up and the closer you get to it you get
there are there assume did there seem to
be other gates you can sort of see
caravans moving out of other sides of
the city going on their own paths their
own directions but you could but you are
approaching from this side and you see a
tremendous and imposing gate I'm gonna
write down I write down this is this is
Alcazar whatever bad things you think
about me they multiply them in there I
shouldn't do the talking especially not
now yeah love yes I do sign it
exactly yeah oh yeah but it takes like a
half an hour
there is a cart a caravan as you as you
are approaching in front of you you can
see a caravan speaking you see the
caravan driver speaking to the dwarves
up on the colonnades
I think it's called crenellations mm-hmm
the castle hat yeah the ruffles and you
can do there's they're speaking in a
dwarven tongue they're very like angular
dialect and ultimately this conversation
concludes with this cart not going into
the town and in fact turning left you
think maybe to try another gate into the
same town right right it's like doctor
shopping but for dwarven underdeck gates
it's a metaphor that has a lot of
descriptive power
yeah so in what is the back of this
beetle are we also clutching a convex
not the time to talk about yeah well
what I'm trying to do is figure out like
I know that I don't know how the doors
will feel about anybody here probably
why are you down here but certainly me
they're not gonna appreciate seeing a
drow so I'm what I've done is I've
covered my my head like I'm wearing a
cloak I drape myself you could still see
who I am underneath but I'm holding my
hands together and my feet together as
though bound if you have to bluff if why
do you have a dirty drought with you
yeah maybe you could convince them yeah
tie them up with your grandmother's rope
that's true that's a classic we can
rough them up a little bit bruises and
sell it to ya
just a little just a little just a
little creative children because it's
not under a dress I put it's like way
better than I did with oak like she's
been practicing or not oh it's creamy
I'm yeah like she stays up late
it's like yeah yeah so she learned it
from a book and network secrets all
diagrams no texts no tanks so yeah he's
not real good and then I have it I'm
like great I don't I don't know
grandmother sick sweet I'll tell you
I'll tell your feet do and I and I and
I'm give I give it a tug and I'm like
nodding music what up so it's it's your
turn to be turned away from this gate
now it would appear or not yeah indeed
so you you find your way up to the front
and the designs that accompany it are
quite novel and probably worth
describing so at the corners of the O's
miles yeah exactly
no no no you need not you don't have any
so up at the up at the
top every inflection point like at every
vertex of this wall that is going out
you can see dwarves peering out into the
Underdark holding lanterns that are lit
around the edge and so in each in each
corner they seem to be like looking out
for someone lost or missing hmm I'm like
I said so the actual front gate of this
thing is iron it is just a massive
10-foot you have no idea how thick but a
massive 10-foot iron gate with it
incredibly stern dwarven iconography on
the front it is not inviting and the
voices you hear from atop the gate say
announce yourselves and then you hear a
smaller voice and a couple of hands just
upon the top assist and as yourselves
[Music]
we're here yeah yes we are acquisitions
incorporated okay you may have heard of
us we're from the surface which is not
as great as down here such a great place
you have mm-hmm and we're here seeking
what are we seeking asylum asylum from
this disgusting drow filled under dark
it when you say a Cylon oh my god but
then when you add that in like that's a
good good play to announce yourselves
your names oh I'm a walnut on grass what
walnut done grass whoo this is
unfortunate
Brizzy what about you your name hold
sway but he's he you can you can see him
sort of like
looking over and we just head it's like
just above the edge of this Oh in
granulation he looks over he's like he
is whispering you don't you're not sure
he's fucking with you
oh he's whispering to his friend it's
not there's no joking there's no
laughing one more time
walnut dawn grass of acquisitions
incorporated red large branch elf wood
elf yes you made me five gold
you made me five gold and I greet you
and I honor you
walnut on grass I've told you I told you
here I can go down the list I can go
down the list walnut on grass rosy bee
stinger Chris drow AB but despite myself
you can't see the cloak nod dinar
Blitzen
yo present ha ha ha ha who's the beetle
oh this is her be good all her be
alright hey listen bug we're not
supposed to let anybody in today yeah we
have a very specific situation under
which we can what mm-hmm oh yeah yeah
yeah no I'll see you soon
you just it's this is gonna take a long
time you're gonna see this is Dave this
takes forever and he disappears and then
you can see him you can sort of see his
head like you can see one of the going
this way and you can see there 1 2 just
sort of like running his hands along the
crenellations going left and this one is
like is he's having a good time like he
seems to be a little spring in his step
it's kind of dancing his way in so you
wait there for a couple minutes and this
gate you hear a Clank and then the
entire iron loaf
of the door just falls straight down
into the earth hmm
and behind it you see another gate made
of iron of course 10 feet in width and
it has an even more Stern looking dwarf
on it mm-hmm couple minutes later
there's another claim it goes straight
down into the earth you go to the next
one now behind this one this is no
longer iron okay
this gate has an army of dwarves on it
oh boy the the wall itself is made of a
sort of like a pale silvery metal and
you swear it is as soon as this one is
exposed to you you swear there's almost
something like a warm breeze coming off
of it mm-hmm
that slides down this happens five more
times and so each time just are they
going up behind us like locks no no you
you think you think that the
counterweight you can feel it in the
ground you think the counterweight must
be somewhere inside in somewhere it's
somewhere inside the wall no no now
they're open today's going all the way
you think there's only two of them up
there right now
and then there's some yelling at each
other in dwarven for this last one but
this last one is made of just a gleaming
it's you know that it's not silver
because you couldn't make something like
this out of silver you think it might be
mithril but a ten-foot-wide three foot
deep slab of mithril is an inconceivable
it is an inconceivable thing to be to
imagine being in one place let alone
being used as a door and you know that
this town has three locked gates like
this so by the time this is down
counterweight of this last one knocks
the first one back up and so then that
seems to sit like an almost like a
domino in Reverse mm-hmm chain reaction
so it falls down falls down falls down
and then it behind you but and then when
this goes down you walk out and when you
get into this next area you are greeted
by as many as 15 dwarven guards all of
them an immaculate plate
mithril chain axes at the ready and
their captain walks up nods to you and
says we will take you to the council yes
of course you will that's why we're here
absolutely how did you know who we were
everyone knows who you were well it's
you me yeah then to ganaron friends how
did you know who they were
yes yeah this guy yeah they say we have
been waiting for you for quite a long
time our King left a very precise edict
we have a gift for you and upon receipt
of this gift you will go on your way hmm
where gifts from dwarven soldiers of
what I own this is a good break this is
a good point to break I think for the
next section shout council mayor leavers
please you don't go nowhere we're gonna
do our special break
let's go basis of stuff gonna be
frightened we'll be back before you know
it yeah hello I'm chair for DK Harkins
and this is Tessie team's
I'll be your host year for cohorts hey
when last we saw our heroes they had
recently and in an incredibly surreal
way been invited into the Dwarven
enclave in the Underdark known as
Alcazar which can be best thought of as
a cool clock that you can live inside
and you're getting a sense of the
authentic like world-class cleverness
that went in I mean you're not sure that
you have seen a surface city of this of
this sophistication to be perfectly
frank we're talking about massive
aqueducts of cool clear fresh water
running in channels turning wheels all
around the city and if you are not
mistaken you think that you actually see
you think that you actually see water
going into individual manors and homes
yeah this like I say I mean it's it is
meticulous and considered you know in a
way that in a way that you have not seen
a surface city constructed as its gonna
say they they had to you know be smart
like so you know with that door set up
anywhere would be here but apparently
they had spare time it's like it's
opulent yeah yeah yeah exactly this ting
care will never be attacked again what
happened it's like they've if it's like
they've transformed it into a fetish
somehow right they've made it they made
it weird
yeah gross they made it weird and as you
as you are going through you can see
that as you're going up this sort of
ramp toward a a building in the center
of town you can see that there are
actually grates over the tops of these
aqueducts and you think you may see
flickers of protective runes over them
so they've they've even considered
they've even considered that something
might try to get in via this via this
this channel right
as we're walking I'm gonna nudge you and
like mmm I know
great nods Oh undo them very I would
like I'm gonna I thought about it it's
such a shame is there such good the
guard the guard said so did you did you
untie it to retie untied aunt okay the
guard says the guard that's welcome tell
you sister
why'd you do that this is just the hour
we let him walk around on his own music
you can tell you I'm over I can tie him
up I immediately go like prostrate and
like thank you for this blessed a few
moments of freedom
honey Joe we got him under yeah I mean
you know him he's under got him under
tight lock and key oh yeah I my bracelet
check this out and I took it
yep right get choked a little bit
doesn't matter if he has ropes on his
wrists or not we have this guy under
control
not to worry he belly laughs it's funny
right at this jerk let's discuss the
intersection of fetishes that could
thrist represents he's not even allowed
to talk with Kristen check this out yeah
that's nothing that we're good I'm good
on that
that's Superman so we can't get his
filthy drow ideas in our heads start
messing up our insides mm-hmm don't like
that yeah he's like we'll keep keep that
keep that necklace if they're ready he
reaches down to his belt and pulls up
what looks like almost like a little
arachnid made of
and clips hmm here's a Kyra seen one of
these can't say I have
looks great though um Ned you like he
says he goes he says if he's if he's not
controlled we will control him with one
of these and he shows it so he basically
unfolds it and you can see how it's like
a pair of handcuffs but for every finger
it's like like that yes sirs spread and
I'm like he gives it a quick shake and
it falls limp and he could have said
back to his belt very appreciative look
on my face yeah all right all right good
so so as you are you are pulled up to a
smaller version of the door that you saw
out front a more tastefully appointed
version still iron it swings in so you
think it might not be solid iron you
think this might be ironclad wood folded
card why would you put iron over
perfectly good wood yeah fuck y'all and
so exactly that's three of them three of
these letters I know right Lord exactly
it's like it said but it's like you can
see sort of like it's like the HGTV home
show and it's like these are our musts
mithril door oh yeah
so when these doors open and the guards
bring in the party
there is already an argument underway
inside this place in common it is a bit
is a mixture of whatever language people
want to swear in apparently well but you
can you can hear with a spell you can
understand most languages right I don't
like I have that one minute
here's the ring keeper usually missing
all of those I considered taking that
one but I do not have that one it's fine
that's a good idea though oh it's very
very cool
I got elvish happening under Connick as
well as common that's very good if
there's anything in there
I got Sylvan anybody wants to get it
elfin with it so there is around this
the table that they have it appears to
have a it's almost like a onyx flat like
reflective glass top almost but inside
the table itself you can see the city so
you can see all the aqueducts operating
you can see carts leaving or coming into
the town your guess is it's probably
something like the owl that you have for
the cart there's probably a spire or
something like that that it's basically
like a table but it's like the scrying
version of the table they opted for the
good one
oh yeah right it shows I forgot all
about that shitty door exactly so so so
this is this is quite a motley crew of
individuals here doesn't appear to be a
hundred percent from any specific caste
or clan this is their Smiths I mean
there's people like clearly pulled out
of a day's work in here to argue about
this situation
that you have somehow been
brought in two and so one of them as
they're calling it to order says that
you know if we're desperate we're going
to be discussing this matter a matter
that concerns these Outsiders we should
probably do it in their tongue and so
most of them agree to it but some of
them feel like that's you not owed that
yeah so they continue to to heckle about
it but what you're able to derive from
this group of people is that their king
established an edict a strange edict
that involved the granting of a mythril
pick two for specific people should they
come to the west gate this rule
for referral picks not just what smelly
one and specifically the West Gate
specifically the West Gate now there's a
period of time where there people claim
to not know where the pick is so it's
not it doesn't matter because nobody can
find the pick but it is eventually
revealed that the pic pics whereabouts
are known mmm it's good to know can't
say anything all right is it in the city
oh yeah it's it's like it's somebody's
house okay no they just trade it around
it's like something to keep on the
mantle I think all right well I like
gifts so where is it where does everyone
seem to be falling in this argument well
it seems to me like just just listening
to it it seems like they're trying to
find it so there's they're also pouring
through there called the books of myth
back and they are basically the laws
laid down by the king and these laws are
interpreted by this body
whenever he is not available to rule on
specific issues it's almost like they
all have to it's like it's like a kind
of bible of the city's laws king king
miss Veronica
miss Burt's his stuff how long ago did
he lay down his edict
oh this edict has been mr. Cohn for
hundreds of years
okay so King with Breck is no longer
with us or the Heath he is
they say resting ah okay so you for me
long-wear yeah why not a long rest
where is he restaurant I said wake him
up then in his in his chambers here in
the the city of Alcazar well he's got
some special guests should when we come
up that's not that's not how it works
Denard Blitzen how has there been an
edict for hundreds of years indeed it's
the five gold piece question yeah how do
they know how did they know how did you
know we were coming we didn't know you
were coming king myth Barack knew you
were coming how did the king myth Barack
we can't ask him because he's asleep
does this happen a lot this kind of
thing oh yeah oh yeah that's our whole
job does he have like the true sight or
something so they're going through and
there's they've broken up into like
little conclaves
sure they're all flipping over these
books trying to find some excuse to not
give you the pitch right sure what was
your question I'm sorry I was doing my
job does your king have some kind of
gift that lets him to see into time
itself
I'm just confirm is so confounded by
this I don't know how it works with your
King but yeah we've opted to be ruled by
a wise ruler
it's just I don't know how it works for
you it just seems an extra why's it
doesn't seem that way
honestly it's it seems like a very
specific prophecy and we didn't even
know that we were a group until somewhat
recently and it says those names in
there
he said I'll show you yeah let me see it
and he flips it over any it's like bits
all in doermann sir ha but I can read it
yeah exactly uh and so he directs you to
the apart and it's very like very rigid
like I was saying like angular like very
precise grammar like you've heard are
you a bird dwarven way yeah yeah slave
read this now I see are like I see our
names there absolutely absolutely
obviously they're rendered in they're
rendered in like a phonetic 3d so yeah
exactly know them yeah exactly exactly
the vowels like the vowels aren't
exactly right in the word art yeah
exactly the winged things that novellas
aren't the vowels right exactly right
but this is hmm this is this is quite
clear
it says the names that we go by
colloquially yeah not our true names
well no no not whatever not whatever you
okay now whatever you have in your
secret heart okay like literally the
names that people know you by okay okay
does it does it say what we do once we
get to pick no no no it says it's just
once they receive the pick they're free
to go this is the decree of King with
Barack free to go meaning we're
restrained like um what's the whatever
they're not you're not retained or
anything like oh well it isn't it isn't
like hey take this and then go kill the
dragon that's alright so like some of
them are saying give these guys the pay
and some of these guys are saying no but
no one's saying we can't leave I'm gonna
I'm gonna nudge you Rosie and I'm gonna
like give me a mic right down okay what
do you want idiot just all right there
are you paint to make it quick
yeah no one pay attention ways of
smacking so and I write down like like
maybe we don't want the pic until I can
contact the Home Office and see if they
can get us out of here faster
maybe we stay here until omen makes
arrangements to get us out of here I
don't I don't want I'm miserable I don't
want the pick event we have to leave
this safe city okay so you want us to
stall love could dress I take it back
from you as you take it so as you have
written that out and then handed that
back to Rosie you have read how you feel
about Rosie um tell me more okay give me
the inside scoop you want us to stall
you know you know what you're doing
around here so I look at this and I
scoff and I toss it aside this Joker
wants us to leave ASAP get out of here
with the Smith role but I honestly I
love your city the hospitality here so
nice and I'm making ugly faces yeah you
don't down
you don't like dwarven hospitality and
I'm a little bit scared now I'm like he
says he says why as much as I hate to
give you what you want and then as he
says that you can hear like a long low
horn he says when you whenever you talk
I just hear a long low horn yeah exactly
yeah
yeah he says that's our deliberations
for the day this week yeah oh no they
are no closer to anything than they were
when you guys started in here and so but
it's like well they can't just stand in
there they're the result of of a serious
conversation we were having it's like
this is this is fundamentally an
ecclesiastical conversation we are
interpreting the words of the King as
relates to these prophets hmm so so they
go around they're like them so who will
who will house them and then it's like
around around the table it's like not
enough it goes all the way around until
this until there's one person left and
he's like for him to learn it will house
them anyone even make eye contact no yep
all right learning gun how's this guy
look like whoa wait the Howsam great I
can't wait to be out it's like gossamer
he's like you can stay in my guest Manor
there's no your guests Manor
there's no situation where our names are
in the books of myth Rock yeah but we
don't know why and I'm trying to get
that first class yeah great guest rooms
main man look all right all right listen
okay okay all right hold on guards just
area more push him just bring him with
palanquin I know you got one so you know
that's not a that's not a dwarven thing
to say okay
[Laughter]
- so you are you are hustled even higher
up into like another ring of this city
that has additional protections above
and beyond the ten-foot three-foot thick
metal chunks metal slices that have thus
far suffice for the last few hundred
years and you are led to the you know by
dwarven under dark terms substantial
holdings of Thrym - learned and you can
see the the large immaculate stone
palace that he lives in and then a truly
marvelous dest manner that he thinks is
an insult but is actually one of the
nicer places you've stayed honestly
which one's his Manor the very very
large nice one mmm see I like that one
better I'm getting Airbnb you don't want
to stay with the host he says he says he
says you are not wrong your names are in
the book my name is not in the book hmm
probably should get your house and then
you stay in the guest manner that is not
going to happen what will happen what I
will allow to happen walnut on grass
[Music]
[Laughter]
rosy you know come on I think return to
learn in dinar
lissa sure all the same I see one face
it makes no sense to me
racist listen to this I will allow you
to dine in my dining hall
with me then you will retire to the
guest manor
Rosie it's all garbage
this city is terrible open bar what does
that mean
do you mind after you is there a bar
that has limitations yes there is what I
know it's a nightmare that's
unconscionable thank you
I agree we agree on this point that
disgusts me
he's like we will discuss this closed
bar in my man's later this evening
please by all means freshen up in these
smaller lesser quarters there is a small
retinue of guards you think that the
guards are mostly for Carthoris you
think that's their primary purpose I
keep I keep like standing up and like to
show gratitude but I forget that that's
not what they're looking for it so I
again will bend down and you're like
you're like so you're cranking up like
you're turning like the drought this is
like the reefer madness yeah of the drow
experience awesome city look hissing
you're like gonna eat a baby desire
bites you throw the rest of the baby
away oh the worst you know what I mean
what a terrible guess huh really
you leave me no that baby so the there
are you know in my father's house there
are many rooms like there are many rooms
in this in this guest Manor as well
there are six in total you have your run
of the place there's one large room like
a master suite and then five smaller
lesser rooms mmm you guys can argue
about it if you like denarii you can
have the big room all right
yeah cuz you got you elk and an elk and
oak scalp scalp let's go sir
would congealed you would think on more
than one occasion you have had to get
down from Clark more because it is just
like slid off like a hat huh like a
still a breeze no a breeze well I mean
it's not congealed no I know a breeze
will catch the hair and it will go down
and you swear to God that you have seen
it move a little iron giantic this is so
good so when you you so you reach on
there grab that hair yeah put it right
back on Cappy like before fresh now
smooth white skin mm-hmm underneath the
hair yeah yeah well what yeah we see I
guess I mean I guess I would tell
assembled oak somewhere it's just like
he's waiting for candle like some other
oh yeah it's good it's good
sloppy safari hat so yeah bring just
trying it out can I let me I'm gonna
write I write in quotes learn ed room
with books to say I'm an illiterate
there's learn here sure
well that's kind of why I wanted the
main house because his main house is
gonna have the good stuff in it this is
gonna be the air B&amp;B which has you know
a copy of crime and punishment so that
he looks smart and then there's nothing
else that's like it's like it's like
it's one of these it's like it's a
situation where you think that crime and
punishment or like war and peace will
like make you look smart so you just buy
multiple copies of it yes
putting different bindings yeah but this
all this just the same book yeah
maybe a couple different language
versions yeah spice it up loves this
book spice it up okay there are a few I
mean there are a few historical books
even here in the foyer of the guest
Manor
yeah
figure with a half of the house like
this yeah yeah uh is there a specific
topic you're interested in
I just want as much as I can and I would
love to find out more about let's see I
mean even the history of this this city
like what they were preparing for
absolutely well yeah yeah it's yeah it's
just like it's it's like my Alcazar by
king myth Barak beautiful beautiful wood
prints it's it's the whole nine yards
that's not actually what it is but there
but there are a few histories that you
can flip through older books that that
clearly show the old borders of the city
it's a where you're at now is marked as
inner Elka's are and these extra regions
outside there are different districts
devoted to to other types of art forms
so it's going to be there's going to be
textiles and things like that now the
hardened war ready version of this city
specializes primarily in arms and armor
[Music]
yeah my name is to see if they had
uncovered anything that resembled what I
saw that was a goblin right what he was
wearing
with oh wow ancient symbols just yeah
just ancient symbols Clark this this
this is um what it's a armful escapes us
this this book is obsessed with dwarven
ingenuity heritage primacy right right
it's on the read no but exactly but
there is there is something they do
discuss the king and his extended rests
which can last for as long as 75 years
it said he wakes up and then he spends
25 years trying to get shit back to
where it was when he went to sleep so
the town it basically has no
institutional it doesn't really have an
institutional memory it has the just
wakes up yeah well yeah and you hit you
saw for yourself what it looks like when
they try to interpret the laws they just
argue about them non-stop and there's
not a whole lot of progress and then
when the whistle blows you know they're
done when they have 75 years it's like
other things to do yeah yeah yeah I'm
night so I if I mean it is our host
still around because I don't want to
flip I know that there's there's a few
heavy mithril toed boots stamps at the
front of the house
can I get perception roles from my
people 17 yeah 7 15 8 plus 7 all right
so you so you are over as I suggested
the aqueducts are constantly pushing
fresh clear water into the homes
themselves so much that it's being used
for decorative purposes yeah so there is
a like a central fountain of stone
fountain in the center of this room and
there is maybe a two second pause and
the flow where it just goes will yep and
then comes right back up it's like the
Bellagio 30 flushed yeah where's Herbie
a God a God flushed lets me outside the
manor so you come with us now Herbie is
in a stable fetal stable okay
God flushed is the like the lessor
adaptation of Atlas Shrugged yeah like a
Mormon yeah well yeah it's like the it's
like the King James edition yeah it's
like a more digest
version okay so we noticed that well and
I'm like great what is a look at the on
the guards faces are they at all they're
used to that look there their eyes are
completely on you okay then all you're
gonna do with that book they heard you
couldn't read I'm doing that you're
gonna eat it or what I'm flipping
through it and I'm and I'm making a show
of like sometimes I've loves that down
reading it as fast as I can at one
quarter speed oh I bet eyes are the rune
keeper would let me read really well oh
yeah he was upside down so you read the
whole thing upside down I'm trying yeah
nice flip to it might be interesting to
me but and then I and then I I I'm gonna
throw it down cuz like well I can't read
yuck but I respect the book too much so
I'm like yeah put it very carefully back
torture I can't handle it anymore
maybe there's pictures in this one look
at this fountain yeah of course um I
don't know what I'm looking for just any
kind of explanation for why that flow
stopped I feel like something that we
need if the attention to nineteen who
that's quite good so tell me how you're
interacting with this fountain and I
will tell you what you learn
okay so describe the fountains maybe
this is a entirely stone enclosure so
there's gonna be a large basin at the
bottom and then inside there's almost
like a it's like imagine a bouquet made
of warhammers okay the waters and then
what the water base with the water comes
out of of each of one side of each of
the hammer so it sort of comes out in a
floral way okay and then so what
happened was that that yes is it okay I
came back yeah I'm so suppose I'm
inspecting to see if there's a there's
any kind of like blockage or weirdness
around this fountain that would explain
not even flow I'm an expert plumber I
guess yeah yeah
so how do you how do you what do I do
you want to explore there the aperture I
guess I'll take a junior plumber uh I'll
take the end of the known business and
in my staff the party under my staff and
I will just sort of nudge curiously
around these warhammers to see if any of
them come loose
oh nice so as you are beginning to work
this fountain with your sacred with your
sacred staff feel like that what I'm
lady
I'm proud don't worry about it I'll make
more of a so you you have your staff and
then you sort of you feel like an actual
you feel something a little bit like
sort of like stuck in the aperture as we
come out and you push it back in and the
flow increases okay fix it you did it
go to the bathroom in it let's love wait
[Laughter]
that's that you and so that guard is
like dinner is served
why it's dinner time it's let's go okay
yay all right we go all right I'm gonna
yeah I walk over to you because I'm in
your custody when I come I leave me by
this part of the rope oh okay I push you
to the party end I ignore all this and
just run yeah I'm rude or not I'm hungry
I'm always hungry yeah we're going to
the main Manor for this meal yeah that's
there it's a real place yeah I'm really
I feel like I'm upset right now because
this you're acting super weird and you
won't talk to me and it's like I don't
want to admit it but I'm like this is
usually like yeah it's kind of like my
buddy I was like what's wrong with you
today
oh yeah anytime I have to make a display
at like
and I'd look again I'm like I like it
okay so what you just said was after all
of this and him going feral basically
and going wow you're like yeah I can't
put my finger on it there is something a
little bit it's just just maintaining it
but it gets it gets more and more sort
of feckless and tepid stare is just
blurring the lines
I don't ever fully let the show end yeah
yeah
so the credits never roll on this so you
are taking in and seated at a wide
wooden table am i yeah do I get to yeah
yeah but it's like at the very very
opposite corner of the table little kids
chair yeah dog dish outside and the
table itself is made of wood which
strikes you as strange in this place
yeah you think it might beat up market
oh okay so because we're in the ground
wood is potentially more valuable this
is all you all you notice is that this
is not you haven't seen a lot done this
way the perversion wood for sheep it's
like a huge huge trade what brick yeah
forget about it so what occurs in here
is that a host of dishes that are
nonsensical are provided and they don't
smell bad but they don't smell good you
don't know what it is
you don't know 100% what it is okay it's
not stopping me yeah yeah that's most of
what I eat
so you hit me it doesn't smell bad yeah
so you're able to find you're able to
you take a family potluck approach
there's a lot of unique offerings here
there's something that looks like an
eyeball but it's not an eyeball who but
looks like an eyeball hmm it's pretty
good
that looks like one like as you know
appears to be I'm saying that any
perceives it has vision it's just a
thing where it's like you bite and
there's that growing pressure and then
pop yeah yeah is that flavor I just do
it all done so this he has even more
ridiculous fountains and sconces here so
he they're actually like there's a
massive fountain and then sort of
miniature enclosures just in the pillars
going down in this in this room could I
get some perception roles I also want to
advantage well I just can't we can't
this one stinks
well that's Jack yeah yeah it's quite
good so it will come in and will come
into place shortly
so as the he's doing his best to
acclimate to a radical new guest and
he's like yeah we never knew we never
knew what the what the profits are going
to be hmm and you seem like normal
people
well that's where you're wrong give me
give me an example she can turn to a
wolf
yeah what's a wolf oh man what else
what's a wolf terrifying beasts
yeah enormous was it well no it doesn't
work like that she's not your monkey
she's a prophet well she's a wolf I
guess yeah all right sometimes you know
sometimes yeah sometimes but not but not
if you need to like a version of the
thing I was writing it's not a great
power all right this guy is I mean
Dragonborn just look at him no got a
tail blue which is very pretty weird
actually yeah yeah yeah you like that
yes sorry yeah it's pretty good
that's most of what you do that's all I
got trying to get your attention
specifically and I'll have it and I've
written it in your food
yeah I've written it somewhere where I
can hold like on my napkin or something
like okay yeah I'm like it showed weird
decorum question mark I'm like I'm not
be rude am i are you saying decorum you
said you showed me decorum I'm like no
no don't worry about it
you need not he's not expecting much
from you it's fine yeah today so hang on
us again so go back to this closed bar
oh my god okay in certain towns and
cities surface world obviously not down
here well yeah yeah uh sometimes if you
have had a few too many jugs of one and
you start dancing on the table which is
fine in many cultures oh yeah sometimes
a surly bartender will tell you grandma
you've had enough to drink and then they
won't serve you anymore yeah well it's
like obviously don't dance on this table
I wouldn't dream of it but a lot of art
in your table do you know what I think
it is I have a theory about this
I think they close the bars because your
tables are made of wood well your this
is the nice table most of the tables
here certainly a table and an inn or pub
it's gonna be made of stone sir this is
a table that can withstand revelry but
I'm not allowed to dance on it
not this one I we have a dancing table I
mean I can we have it there's one oh
yeah yeah oh yeah absolutely every house
I'm just saying that's probably why I
think if stone tables were more common
to be a different situation
maybe you know what that's probably
right there's not anything to do with me
ya know there's too much thing about
it's just I was thinking about as you
were saying this the the water pressure
in the sconces drops again ah and so he
is seated in such a way that there are
pillars just behind him and then in
front and then in front like this
separated by a distance of perhaps 20
feet each in a room that is perhaps a
hundred feet across now you can see as
you were talking to him and he is
holding forth on his profound surface
drinking theories you can see that the
water has slowed down and then it has
stopped in the two sconces behind him
and then from the spigots themselves
reaching out is a green tentacle oh oh
that's not great hmm and it continues to
progress and progress and so it's coming
out on both sides and then once this one
gets a little bit farther this one
recedes and then this side you see
another second tentacle come out and
then extend reach down and then begin to
pull on the floor and from this pillar
from this sconce there is a pop and then
the rest of this creature to put it
basically bursts from this tiny spigot
and then just deposits itself on the
floor and the further the initial
surprise
that gives way to a kind of grim
curiosity it's basic it looks like a
like a like a Thanksgiving gelatin and
then it's so he is continuing he's like
but you know by the same token it could
be that surface spirits are not as
strong as that he's still going I'm
letting him talk instead of being like
you got a weird pet back here man
exactly and so he he his the sound of
his own voice is very pleasing to him
coming back off the marble and then the
gelatin begins to assume a distinct
shape and when the head of this creature
pulls itself up out of the central mass
just a soaking wet curtain of tentacles
falls down out of its face and then off
of its back peels to sticky pairs of
wings and then the hands it's the hands
itself sort of pull out of its own
abdomen and as it does so the gaping
gash in the center of its chest remains
open and inside you can see a starving
frenzied mass of red worm like tentacles
and intestines
I let through him keep talking yeah and
he's like yeah I mean if it could be
that if if good dwarven spirits were
available at more more of your
establishments and then without warning
it turns to this sound and the red
tentacles lash out and snatch him and
then pull him directly up and right into
his stomach where the rest of them begin
to suckle hmm
attached I make this second detected the
sound of his voice
are there other guards in here not in
the dining area you know right no no
we're like walking him and then so he's
pulled in and turned around and Carissa
do you have the ability to exclaim in
your ordinary tongue and ordinary
vocabulary as you see this event and I
would like to encourage you to do so oh
I can actually you can do I find that
it's very surprising oh okay it does
surprise me okay
check please okay wait no so I'm so I'm
we're playing along with your column
yeah and then he gets a developed gets
pulled into the mass mm-hmm and all I
could think is he'd be like oh yes
that's exactly it
let's go we have to go this is what I
was talking about like I like I'm almost
pleased that was my theory was confirmed
and it was everybody's serious and they
eat him but just excited that it
happened I might shock to your my own
voice oh absolutely it just it just
comes unbidden and so he is it's um it's
like imagine that you're looking inside
the glass window of like a front-loading
washer he's just like churning and
rumbling in here and then everyone that
is head comes out he's like no wait and
then it turns back in because the code
is this all advocating for the council
and then it comes back in and then you
think you think that it may be having a
difficult time with the mithril vest you
think that maybe that's not on its diet
and maybe there is a version of gluten
allergy for these terrors Rosie sighs
and she stands up from the table she
goes
alright let's save them
all right I need initiative rolls from
my peoples what I got here on i-95 okay
18 that's very good Rosie more than 18
really yeah what is I going to be 22
yeah alright sorry I'm kidding I'm gonna
tell you guys one of these times it's
gonna happen for me
not today I just got to believe in
myself all right Kath wrist round it's
like I I hold let's see what you got cuz
I know I'm so excited for my voice to
return well yeah just dish it up you
know just just try it out I mean it
maybe just flex it what it'll work
you got anything cool that we haven't
seen you do yet uh we actually do have
something
yum-yum-yum yeah so what i'm gonna do is
i i again it spills out of me ya know
hex go and give it to you but it's just
like hands i do and i'm you open
suggestion i am open to suggestion i
don't know if it's gonna have an effect
in combat we can bring back see big i'll
break necks ebay yeah yeah um yeah I
would love our con handicap sure that I
can stand him it does look like a hearty
feast yeah I was thinking he's a fast
fella - I'm sorry I'll do casual aid of
some kind way down over the door hook oh
he's right he's meeting yeah let's get a
full stomach
so hex on him shame shame how dare you
and then I'm going to try a new thing a
new canned trip from Santa thar a fresh
can't trip a brand new one it's called
told the dead whoa I don't remember how
it works cuz I didn't write down it
spent in this book but it says you so I
wrote notes down so it says it's you
have to the
enemy has to save it's a wisdom saving
throw for it ooh that's pretty good
I see so on a success or if I succeed if
it can't beat it
yes to d8 necrotic if it's been injured
already it takes to d12
I see do you think that munching on the
mithril might have granted it's a nice I
love you I love you Rosie but but no and
I've seen and I imagine cuz I didn't
make a note of it if it succeeds then it
doesn't anything okay well here what is
your spell my dispel D save my Decius
it's 15 god damn kid oh yeah oh yeah no
no I'm totally dead
okay hold it up oh yeah so let's get my
send some eights way those are sixes
yeah get him here we go at the same time
Oh a two and a that's 10 plus hey the
necrotic which I don't it's - yeah it
doesn't go up does it no it doesn't go
up okay so that's 12 no it's just
duration not that's cool no tell me it's
a toll the dead sounds like it could
have some really cool flavor so yeah as
described it's like a ringing sound is
produced but what is it but what is it
for dong I don't we're great power yeah
in like in my drow house yeah yeah what
is his version right mmm okay what is
that resonance try this
I got eeeh this whole time has been a a
serpent hiding here he has not been a
staff I do voke his staff he's just like
a bowtie he's just there yeah he's
present yeah and I I point there like
focus on my target and I crashed the tip
of the staff into the ground in legardie
resonates Oh Krystal and it produces
yeah
Krystal and Bell noise and I sound comes
out like
oh yeah it's definitely a tug of man's
voice giggle dongs dongs plural yeah
it's funnier so there they were already
these these reaching tentacles mmm
beginning to seek out and sniff the air
for more prey and as that wave hits them
they like retract like like the court of
a vacuum cleaner like this next up we
have Rosie bee stinger okay I will do a
I'll give the full barrage on this bad
boy I know I'm gonna target the snakes
in the hopes that it'll get it'll spit
them out steak tartar yep that's me sing
that one if it sounds good but if I do
together okay whoa that's a 26 and
another 26 God and then I'll do two
Marshall Marshall attacks with my flurry
of blows shadow Council Mary Labor's
please Rosie be staggered and a 1414 you
say yeah now the 14 is not hit okay
but you murdered it oh yeah that was
really really great okay and I'm also
doing it needs to do a con save with
disadvantage from my hexie friends and
I'm gonna try that right so you at you
so he his efforts to bring hexie back
yeah we're not rewarded okay wonderful
so we've got a six points of damage and
11 points of damage and another six
points two inch 20 game a three points
damage and stunts Wow
thank you what would he have gotten if
you hadn't if he hadn't maybe had
concept he wouldn't even stunt well he
did it he did safe oh he did say okay
yeah yes okay yes he's not son okay but
he did to get all the damage yeah yeah
that is a heap of damage
Rosie nice work tell me tell me how it
goes because we're about three hits like
what kind of what kind of crashing tiger
shit are we talking about here so
that'll be with the business and not the
party end the business end of the and
and she is getting in there
stabbing like you would if you were if
you were actually trying to like stab a
big rats nests of snakes
she's she's targeting these snakes and
she goes and then when that doesn't do
it and it doesn't spit her out she goes
just for the third strike and she looks
I'm guessing that he didn't spit him out
okay want a dog grass reach down pull
out for mother and then just kind of
like visibly tense up and then I use
produce flame which is just goes along
the blade here is a green flame it's
always green flame I did the thing and I
get to try and make a range spell attack
to attack sweep this way just flaming
blade nice yeah right elaborate like
nice right at the leg ease and I got it
some that take advantage get it yeah cuz
I don't want to miss I don't wanna miss
I don't wanna miss nineteen but let's
see if we can do better oh it and that
would be a 2019 is very good so okay so
then I get to do to d8 damn damage
oh dear I'm gonna talked and it's it's
happens out yeah flames are hot hmm
these are the hot guy hot place ten hops
new you and without my spell has ended
because it no I can't you can't possibly
denier blitz end I understand that
you've got a very large story yeah I
think I know what it's huge sore I think
I'll just swing at his head no no I feel
like I'm still gonna wait I don't know
he's in the tummy is it mid shoe while
you're still eating well oh yeah I did
want to retcon one thing so anyway I
don't want to interrupt your you
lovely description but it's like when a
big baddie is showing up yeah I'd be
like hey hey Clark more anybody cuz he's
in the room oh yeah waiting in the room
so if you're like hey a little help I
don't how long it would take him to get
I don't know the proximity here but when
that's happening no he's sitting in a
chair eating like hey a little help
he's just like seeing down I wouldn't
unsummon him with the difficulty I have
bringing him out I know he's he's he's
outside he just he's not a dinner
ya know I wouldn't imagine in a formal
dinner setting here okay so anyway you
want to bring him into the fray but I'm
gonna swing please hi for the fences
with my sword called toothbrush yeah I
got him on that one Wow
so yeah that hits those 18 plus 6 so 36
all right
that's 1103 damn 14 plus I'll smite him
as well smack a smite on that's I gotta
remember because we're up a level now so
it's gonna be 3d eight hits right yeah
yeah it's attack alone it's based on
it's based on whether or not he got him
right so five six so that's eleven
fifteen fifteen more on top of that what
was the original thirty points total
Lincoln yeah all right that's a tackle
one I get too attached Jesus is Lord
so just do that again yeah second song
soon as a second person is first I'll
take advantage so I make sure I hit I
hit well let's see if I get a twenty
nope all right I hit on that one too
excess 21 I get three roll on the one is
your someone again yeah four so that's
four five six seven I'll do another
smite seven plus five and three 15 15 15
more oh yeah - do you know your right
one
wait that one's for you so total between
the two is 46 okay yeah
do in a pinch Josh if you would be so
kind as to turn on my cauldron lights Oh
No now Clark four bursts in puffs
smashing down the door that comes in
makes that that keening that sharp
keening call as he as he as he wars in
and he roars into your side the two
guards come running in after they say
hey you can't you can't do that and then
as the two guards come in the creature
turns to face them and a just phalanx
assault of jagged intestines reach out
and pull both of them directly into the
belly and when he turns around back
towards you his physical shape that's
very very it's just lumping and
terrifying and you can hear their bones
cracking inside of his guts oh they were
not wearing mithril and you can see and
you can see just a curtain of blood hmm
fall down and you see him rise up to a
fuller more terrifying higher no no no
it's even worse than that guys shadow
Council Mary Labor's please yeah thanks
so much we'll see you again very soon
for Table Talk don't go nowhere
we'll be right here
you