time is the enemy of the past it
threatens the fastest weapon you
wouldn't make it past a second answer
the question
play it brash and reckless to choose a
cautious solution you saw was prudent in
any sepulcher poker to don't become the
putrid it's that well said I pursue in
no mountain too steep for dungeon too
deep to send expendable marks up to the
top of the peak of beneath they see Yugi
they come like sharks to it while I swim
in that money bill like Carl Barks
through it so send your national parks
drew it I'll send him home in a natural
box with the clothes Tyler most of the
parks included
save your breath for a cleric confessor
death is a lesson that life is attending
professor but if you're seeking my
official advice sign on the dotted line
English in the twice hello I am Tycho
Brahe hey penny okay in packs I am also
a mini fest hare would run CEO of
acquisitions incorporated but today I am
Jerry Hawkins and I'm going to run a
game of Dungeons &amp; Dragons for my
friends to my right Cragin bored
narcissist dinar blitz and Ernest yay
for me hey Big Daddy yeah and the shirt
my life you stupid baby
you stupid baby now to the right of my
right repping the natural world walnut
dawn
conserving puppetry to my left not your
grandma's grandma except in those rare
cases where she is your grandma's
grandma rosie beasting to the left of my
left emerging as though from a mist
shroud cthe wrist wrap yay why is this
so part of the same canal yeah dude well
me we're determined we can reveal
exclusively on the c-team that new mommy
is the fifth canal they will know Arg
no this is this joke I like this I like
it's awesome now there's a couple items
that I want to cover before we continue
the first is that we've got giveaways
plenty for people who roll criticals and
also for a short time which is to say a
single time which is to say only this
game we will also accept for teens it's
all natural fully natural okay
naturalized for teens well happy
Valentine's Day show counsel you can
also get incredible treasures like for
example the night wing die set from
level up dice yeah got some more awesome
shit in here at hand
do you guys see these yeah yeah no no no
no this is the so this is an elder would
obviously they do that other cool box
for us but but but look at this no you
have to because because they actually
scale even though they're even though
they're small like you should give it a
toss because they actually feel oh
they're heavy exactly I think still they
still feel good that's a fine wait but
anyway oh you don't have to wait for
this Kickstarter to come to its
inevitable successful conclusion no no
yeah several high rolls a 20 or a 14 I
will just send you one will sign it and
send it to you all right well no no no
there there art listen six or seven
these are all romantic everyone is into
whips if the number is phallic in any
way we'll send you we were all a 69
exactly 21 a 1 and an 8
whoa wait a min yeah that's one option
no let's talk about what your numbers
are now that was 7 when last we saw our
heroes they had made their way to the
Dwarven stronghold in the Underdark
of uilt kazar described on this
program as a kind of clock that you can
live inside it's got the running water
it is it's it is this is a premium desk
this is a premium subterranean
destination for your family that's it
dwarves it's like listen there's
somebody for whom this is a very
exciting combination Airbnb five stars
exactly all caps the review is in all
caps but listen to this response things
aren't 100% great after learning that
they were in line to receive some kind
of mithril pick based on a little-known
bylaw in the rules of Alcazar set down
by their mysterious and largely absent
King our illustrious crew did enter
their Regency Council where they had to
listen to Dwarfs argue for a very long
time indeed they argued so long that
deliberations came to a close and then
they had to be put up indignity of
indignities in Thrym the learner's guest
mansion these are some dark tidings and
and you know cthis was able to assess
early on with his eyes of the contractor
yeah special ability there were issues
with the water pressure yeah yeah you
know I'm not that learning he he
assessed that one upfront right and lo
and behold it was not a garden-variety
stoppage of some kind it was an issue
that is rare but obviously very
troubling which was that a creature had
breached the defenses of the town
through the aqueducts and then burst
forth from what had been only ten
minutes before a beautiful interior
water feature this is a ghastly turn of
affairs I think we can all agree a true
nightmare but it gets worse because the
way that
the stream works now is that when people
sub or put bits toward they are toward
their favoritest characters all of those
count as one bit for me in my cauldron
which you can see down in the bottom and
if it tips it tells me right over here
if it tips then I roll on a table and
every time I have rolled on this table I
have gotten the bane result which means
that negative things occur so in this
case when they were fighting what looks
like a massive Cthulhu vien monstrosity
whose whole belly is open and hungry so
if you thought that you thought that
Cthulhu was bad already this is not your
father's Cthulhu when dinar Blitzen
summoned Clarke more his faithful star
elk reindeer yeah is that accurate yeah
yeah that's the two dwarves that
accompanied this creature were devoured
by the ineffable horror and it cranked
him up it was like creatine I say undid
all the damage we know exactly so it's
goodie so we're talking about a creature
that has been hitting the gym
check his insta I mean he's looking cut
so that is where we find ourselves that
is where we find ourselves today because
we broke last time mid-round we broke
amid around exactly so if I could
friends if I could get a new round of
initiatives you could because any one of
these initiatives could be a twenty or
fourteen or five I would love to take
advantage on this Hey
oh you wanna you wanna ask you I was
appear up you eat it up actually my oh
my - once on before okay so for and we
all in terrible night okay how about you
a Chris 13 okay here we are
and then let's see where this
you know I'm so pleased you don't know
how I suffer back here like I lie back
here very very rarely very very rarely I
do generally speaking my initiative
roles are twos and twos nice today
shadow council may my Labor's please you
I'm gonna deliver a pretty savage
opening round for this blood-soaked
Valentine's Day edition of the c-team
all right so as I described previously I
described that gazing unwittingly of
course into this thing's belly it's like
looking at like the the glass portal in
the front of a front-loading washer
there's just stuff in there and you can
see that Thrym the learner is still
being chewed you know still you know de
let you know he's truly being enjoyed
inside here and it is quite possibly
only his mithril shirt that is keeping
him from being absolutely transformed
into a paste inside here but even now
there's a Clank as shreds of lesser
chain Helms and pauldrons clunk just out
of the open belly of this creature so
let's see who would be best who do it's
like it's like what can I do to get you
into an ineffable horror today not much
turns out well here let's let's see how
it goes we're gonna reach out with our
with ajust a profundity of starving red
intestines I'm gonna try to get you
straight up in that zone already looks
ready
now no see what do you say to a 19 I say
oh no I say oh no ineffable horror I'm
happy by your horror gift oh yeah that's
you all right it's Valentine's Day
it sounds down around on that one there
we go now what I would like you to do is
give me a little strength give me a come
on buddy
well I just listen I I'm trying to I'm
trying to extend the magic here nine no
that's not gonna do it so these things
you see you see these things it's not
even looking at Walnut when this happens
you see them just reach out in a
completely separate angle and without
even noticing just grabs them and just
throws you right in so you are you are
pulled hauled bodily across the floor
directly into this thing's massive
chest cavity no don't appreciate it what
what is that what's that gonna send me
back it starts to set you back
authentically next turn okay so we'll
see how it goes but it has it has an
assortment of these and I'd love to put
them to work so and I inside it oh yeah
oh oh you know you were you were you are
being actively ground against great trim
to learn it you are learning things as
well I about for him to learn it this is
kind of a romantic cup yes I was just
gonna say happy Valentine's Day
obviously to the shadow council ho ho
now on on the acquisitions incorporated
died of course the acquisitions
incorporated single is a one so I am NOT
able to seize any additional prey on
that role its wrist wrap yeah yeah I
mean inside the belly all the meals are
being worn into a single uniform fluid
which must be the highest representation
of of cooperation yeah right in a way
indeed krisstraus what say you
uh-uh well I say that I don't like
what's happening yeah I'm going Rex yeah
I don't like that I was fine when it was
just our friend not friend the learner
allegedly yeah
quote unquote doesn't even know his own
fixtures in his home
what's the when I'm looking at this is
there any way that I can do damage to
this creature without damaging its
contents
absolutely this I mean I can't I need to
know it's all right I need to I need to
take a moment I think to express the
extent to which this creature so the
fact that it was able to push a tendril
through the tiny cracks and and
apertures in these water features it's
not an index of what this thing is
actually physically like because keep in
mind think of something like a like a
like a giant octopus it's like as long
as you can get that beak through the
rest of it can go right and that's
really the situation we're talking about
here this thing tower is well over any
member of the party this is a massive
creature and it is truly like it is the
the blubber around this thing is wet and
slick but but it is also very thick
right and so this is I mean you could
you can attack this without some
creatures are complicated like a cloak
er right you have to worry about what's
happening there
the cloaker it's like the cloaker and
the and the target they're attached to
like they basically go Dutch undamaged
yeah they just split it right down the
middle you walnut is not in danger from
an attack from you here okay
then just swing away this is science
yeah okay what's on the ground do I see
any bits cuz I'm getting ready to lose
some of my own tentacles I mean any
choice meets some chunk scraps from the
the guards that were mulched
oh there's yeah I mean there's there is
still bits of
bits of flesh clinging to the armored
plates you know that ever so recently
clangs to the ground here's what I want
to do you tell me how this is gonna
shake out yes I like what happened when
we were in that in that rotating oh
that's that horrible slang let's need
prison that was spinning around I like
what happened with with my tentacle
friends with your monomolecular what I'd
love to do is find a way to impale this
thing on my own these not necessarily
monomer net molecular the time but so
that I would love to pry it open
oh so we get the contents out yuck
it's got its open now I bet two of us
can get on either side of it and do this
I don't need tentacles for this I'm
saying how can I do it at a distance
with my very special friends you can't
you can now describe for me describe for
me the mechanism that this is attempting
to describe for me the strange machine
you're trying to make out of these guts
I see the yes that's the difference this
time it's actually a construct exact
trying to build okay I am trying to
build something out of this crystalline
right flesh I want to build a I want to
make a essentially like forceps
I want to pry it open my jaws of life I
want to empty it out again autopsy rib
cracker yes that is what I want to do
and if we can if we can ideally I
wouldn't use the points of it but the
loop so I get that the most mechanical
advantage right and if I've got to route
it in that in that meat on the ground
from our from our departed guard friends
then that's how I wanted to play out I
want to get the contents out of here I
wanted to pry this thing of its meal
exactly and that makes perfect sense to
me so hey so what we're talking about
here is a usage of your ultimate ability
right I would I do want a check so that
I can use that to determine the type of
success and your arcane art Kennedy all
right
I got no advantage to take on this this
boy shoot it up oh that's gonna be a non
romantic number a 19 exactly so imagine
that there's you're leveraging some kind
of mystical ratio so between the blood
and flesh that you're altering and
imagine that there's a kind of cosmic
bank you can utilize of additional
structure and so it's a one to ten
something like that and so immediately
that contraption you have devised
solidifies itself reaching out from each
of these sources of living material
piercing straight back and then just
through its natural motion sort of
prying it out like this so there's a
moment where you can see both of them
trim the learned and walnut dong grass
basically exposed until these dancing
tendrils do their best to pull them back
in so that's going to do that's gonna
grant some advantage for people trying
to escape oh I see I see that scenario
but it's also it is also dealt damage to
the creature so this is a I would say
this is a positive result all around I
love both of those things I've damaged
what's up love damage you know I love
helping people I care about rim Thrun
fan number one yeah absolutely the
damage has been decremented good a tune
of ten points oh and thanks my don't
even know so slightly looser in there
you think that when the time rolls back
around to you you'll be able to jump
back in pretty quick next I would like
to have a conversation I saw well I want
to invite you in to the play space Rosie
B singer okay let's talk about your
situation and let's try to create a
memorable moment this
on tiny episode okay um I think what I'd
like to do is use my magic initiate
cleric cleric ability command
hello ho and I speak one word command to
a creature I can see within range must
succeed on a wisdom saving throw or
follow the command on its next term and
the command word that I would like to
speak to this creature is regurgitate
woo from your belly and then as a bonus
section I would like to teleport into
area of shadow within sixty feats but I
get advantage I'm my next melee attack
mm-hmm but delicious a melee attack and
I believe my spell 13 this is pro shit
thank you this is pro shit I'm gonna say
it's like one week one week it Wizards
of the coast shit's gotten real all
right here let's um let's dish it up so
I need to basically I need to do my save
what can I say was it against him wisdom
alright can do that is a sixteen that
does save so I just I I go regurgitate
and it doesn't it just looks at me I
suppose but just even just just by just
even even reaching out with this power
toward this thing's mind it's just it's
like a it's like a
Ice Mountain like it's just it's it's
thought processes are nothing like you
have ever experienced like you're not
even sure you're not even sure if it
would be possible to communicate with it
in this way so so tell me about so let
me let me give you some shadow options
okay then then you tell me which one you
like that alright so obviously these
pillars here just in those side this is
the not the dancing table as well recall
this is the wooden table to the left
this is shattered down I would say there
is a shadow being cast behind it for one
of your stature but Clark more also
kicked the doors open so you could very
easily get one of these positions behind
the creature in the
shadows that dwell there yeah I'll do
that all right do you mind him
high-five walnut dawn grass is it time
to feast a reverse feast yeah exactly a
mega feast I think I want to feast from
with it honey more what's shaping oh no
kind of silly horrible shapes so many
more rock a nut sure that would be good
that would also be good and oh my god
the idea of a giant spider crawling yes
it was very good me throw yeah but I
would like to instead transform into
that big brown bear yeah honey nut which
honey net which has a special thing that
I will reveal to you right now it gets
to attacks always and they always hit
yeah and so this is a giant bear is a
large creature yeah I get it I
understand well no no I think I got
metro line well no no I'm saying I'm
trying to I'm trying to make it so that
make sure that the shadow down so the
shadow council knows the sorts of things
that there or please the servants are
getting up to go ahead so no so we're
just talking about you have basically
like tripled your full volume easily in
the space of a second and I want you to
tell me how these so we do in bite claw
what are we doing um we'll do a bite in
than a claw you gotta tell me about this
okay so after yeah after getting pulled
in and thinking this is not where I want
to die and also not what I want to die
in and just it's really the two things
yes it's like the anger of being bested
by this disgusting thing in this
horrible place just makes her Hulk out
and turn to this bear and just start
gnashing with her with our teeth and
we'll see any purchase with that nope
that's fine it's a - that's okay that's
fine I'm gonna do that I'm also gonna do
the claw and also I'm gonna take
advantage you can you can it has been
granted to you too
ah that's right ah that's worse than a -
for the pun yes it's a one the most
Beth yeah
exactly I'm I am curse uh so I just get
real big and its belly no exactly so you
it off more but- so so you're oh that
weird bear sound right just just whoa
you open your mouth wide just to go at
the alien internal structure of this
creature and then - seizing tendrils
just reach underneath your jaw and below
and just hold it open and then when you
draw your claw back you're gripped and
then pulled farther in to the guts
Dennard blitz in dang it can you roll
above it - I guess that's the I can now
question I was now with it well I guess
your bear form you where's case scenario
if your bear form gets beat up you just
turn exactly right that's all night
right it's pretty sweet yeah I know I
just feel like this makes it a bigger
more likely of hurting you uh and what I
was gonna do I don't know would work now
I Clark more is in the room with me as
well and we have a simpatico - my old
buddy yeah so while they're turning
around in here yeah how you describe
this is a washing machine I'm
envisioning like socks tumbling around
absolutely good hand no there's a hand
there it goes yes they're not like
cinched in place unable to move well no
it's basically like just the muscles of
its digestive process are just like
working them wow this is happening
so it's they're just they're just
getting turned your rock tumbler alright
okay
I want Clark more to Jamie's head in
there for them gonna grab one too I
don't want them to try to I want him to
try to pull them out - that is kick-ass
that so I want basically usually move so
his is a big rack go right here in the
middle here the cat just like because
they do have you ever seen it
they said big shake here and then if he
starts getting pulled in I want to I'll
secure him via hunch
and use it as a rope this military
classic yeah this is we've seen this a
million times
everyone knows when your filthy hands
all in his body yeah your hands all over
me is this the clean version no this
ain't okay if you can roll for Clark
Moore's attack I'd like to know I will
take advantage on this because someone's
got it we have to beat it too well 17
that's real good yeah well again just be
just in case we can reward see see
that's big 14 something for Valentine's
Day hmm it goes so basically this just
sort of this these this other separate
craw here in the front and he just goes
right in basically and it's just held in
place I like to think like cuz we have a
mind link I'm like Jim your head in
there and he's like like a moment of
hesitation yeah
we've workshop lickable things don't
make massive steel oh well shucks shucks
a golly
oh boy else - you know I don't like this
no you guys Clark more clark moores
really business serious majestic beast
imaginary special Beast
no but that's Clark Moore's turn that's
not your turn yeah okay only James's
head in there with the intent of anyone
grabbing on grab on
well they can on their turn now all
right so jointing him back out on my
turn then so now I'm gonna swing on this
thing well it's my friend is in there
he's based on dude well then my did
imagine imagine head imaginary Oh
imagine a scenario where one person
holds a foe while the other hits them I
mean basic yeah he is completely
anchored in place by a set of majestic
celestial horns so do I get some sort of
you are a clever cute boy thank you you
got in that social check AJ yeah yeah
jam a reindeers head into his guts I
don't I get nothing out of that one
alright you confer cool advantage to
your friends right does anyone know
because I don't know
I have smites as spells and I also have
my normal sassy smite can I power this
as a bonus action use thunderous smite
this is a bonus action yet this is like
a pre free attacks might I charge up the
sword with essentially use a bonus
section before or after okay so I could
double theoretically I could pre
thundersnow
I like the idea that's a pre it's like
there's different phases well it is
because I was using this incorrectly
before I thought this was a like the
tack on smites but it's not I mean I
will do that I will use a thunderous but
don't wanna fill this thing full of
electricity you won't everyone's turning
around and there's a bunch of smite
obviously there's a range of smite
products yeah and it's like you can see
it on the back like whatever the product
is it's like that's circled and it's
like smite but then it's like you know
also try acts thunderous smite I got
every flavor here what are you what are
you looking for it let's do wrathful mmm
cool cooler branch I like a cooler Ranch
Cool Ranch smite coming in wrathful
smite and I'm not just so I know that I
hit I'm not going to do any sort of
googoo Venus so one bonus action this
will boost my damage on it
I love land they a fight hit and then
I'm also gonna do a regular old smite on
top of it so shit I meant to take it man
whoopsie whoops alright well I didn't
hit them they're mine yeah but you've
warmed up real good yeah I have all 11
don't you get two attacks thing I get to
do you sure you should check against for
head about that make an advantage then
now I'm gonna advantage okay that was a
joke don't ya funny
exactly here know if you roll it roll it
again and see if it's a 14 in
number number I'll roll right now they
are believers please you yes sir with
sin has shit
that's the Nightwing said from level up
and fighting hex chess mini dice box on
the keychain damn all right we're gonna
start rolling some dice yes okay so
that's a keychain
oh yeah look at this yeah you just have
it oh my god I want I know a team tiny
little size no yeah it's good I just I
don't know I'm just good it's great it's
magnetic eight eight plus this raffle
spike because I hit him yeah as an extra
one be six so four so that's 13 13 14 15
16 and I will attack a divine smite for
an extra 3d8 get it so what do I say
what do we have to wait he's dead right
yeah so nice to get him out of there
Oh another eight eleven thirteen twenty
three nine oh and then because a raffle
raffle smite you must make a wisdom
saving throw or be frightened of me
until the villainous rascal smite yeah I
got in his head I jammed my reindeer
friends tummy and then and then hidden
with a scary sword
what's your 14 game that is a 1 so how
long is he frightened it's a minute it's
a minute duration yeah who lives his eye
he's younger fear yeah
isn't Tyrus to his life now the way I've
advantage what does it take to get an
advantage over this friggin take
advantage of innocent man wouldn't we
all get a like a flanking bonus because
Wallen is inside and we're on any other
wall of this creature on the outside
back tactics impact tech
tactics snack pack dicks
Lunchables alright alright I like I like
what we're seeing here so we got a whole
a disadvantage coming up on this bad guy
rolls so right now there's a whole lot
of horn situated he's can do it's
fantastic
he is continually trying to adjust his
feet to maintain his upright stature
immediately just as a look at
instinctual reaction to the source of
his fear he begins to lash out with his
tentacles but he has this advantage
because of the absolute fear the first
roll was pretty good how was the second
roll this control was a real pile of
shit so it says so they come out and
they don't date like they come out
around you of this they don't find
purchase but you just see him it's like
um like a elephant's trunk like they
just sort of like snuffling around on
your armor alright seventeen they see
what's that what's my am eighteen all
right the the fear was quite effective
against this against this creature it's
a scary sight yeah clearly two thrusts
route Oh take damage for being said it
oh she's just hungry for that thank you
we could have written that off and bark
more protected you with antlers or
something right yeah based on eight
points nothing to me you even care it's
all temporary for you right
Ami's seeking punishment for her
terrible roles I am hoping that this
will like a karmically balance it out in
overall twenty all right what do you
think Chris trout mmm-hmm Emily the
board right here um every says survey
said tentacles something yeah
get stuck inside of and digested
I'm trying to figure out what the dua is
it better to do utility and wait for you
guys to climb out or do I just try to do
as much damage as I can get there
because this would just leave okay well
you guys have got this know what I will
do is try and stop it at the source
endless creatures movement by creating a
hypnotic pattern no go on
this I'm gonna I'm gonna throw up the my
favorite symbol the sign of the earth
you know you know in a shimmering
machinery laser Zeppelin type display
lights and sound an incredible music
experience for all against the dome of
this great house and he's got to beat a
wisdom check can he quite can you da man
so that so then the the ER appears
rounds and then yeah it shames me I feel
a little bit bad and that's the end then
can I question though can i yeah okay
for the podcast listeners it did not I I
know that I'm supposed to take or
usually I do hex first am I allowed to
use it oh shoot it's not a bonus action
oh that's it technically
nobody's about section bonus yeah you
can bring hexie back at any time during
your never I will and I will say I curse
him like I said that that should have
worked
hex you hex for you that's exactly exit
on you yeah in the old ways not even us
not even the spell I'm just saying that
I curse him I love it and that grants a
bonus damage when I'm a disadvantage on
a staff right do you have a stat in mind
or is it it's this is a key feature
apparently everybody's like no it
doesn't make any difference like if I
was to parlay with it yeah
but they say that I I think it's too
cool I'm gonna say it let's do let's
just do strength I mean I know it's low
level but I think it's too cool to to
leave that on the on the table
Rosie be stinger yeah my understanding
is that you're a very dangerous a very
dangerous woman not today
okay so tell me tell me how this thing's
looking he's afraid of dinar
yeah he's a he's a he's afraid of dinar
his friend his mouth tentacles air in
his mouth tentacles are like a angry set
of venetian blinds it is can it is
fairly consistently trying to get off
this bizarre I'm trying to get
dismounted from tonight's erotically
charged episode okay does the c-team
give it the C stands very wrong but I
loved it no it's cirrhotic Odyssey
Raonic like Jesus okay asphyxiation okay
just do all the stuff you listed I'm
gonna do all of it
alright I know you can get like the
different options you like the platter
like you do like the Marshall platter
yeah latter that's it that's it
okay here we go I'm gonna go with two
corner self attacks and I get advantaged
on my first one because I am special
thank you okay so that oh wait a minute
[Applause]
long plonk 14 yes more prizes exactly
more special prizes for the shadow
council merrily wish please you okay so
that's gonna be 21 healthy that is the
second of mine and rules now scrunched
so that's nothing that's sad 15 nope and
that's going to be
in eighteen and so teams okay to those
hit okay and then I am going to so two
successful hits one quarter staff one
melee and on both of those until I
succeed I will attempt to stunning
strike as well okay so if it's gonna be
one day a sport is six points of damage
the other one is my punch hits way
harder than my staff yeah apparently
twelve points of damage so that's
eighteen points of damage and both of
those do duquan saves
oh yeah and exactly up to two and if
either of them succeed let me know and
I'll spend my points appropriately yeah
uh well yeah it's six to cheese a one
and A four so take your pick I guess
yeah so I always spend one and it is
stunned until the and my next turn I
love it stunned means everybody gets
advantage means it means a few things I
would be happy to read to you from
inquiring readers want you know stunned
creatures incapacity hit can't move and
can speak only falteringly although you
know truth be told this feature was not
very talkative before automatically
fails strength and dexterity saving
throws and attack rolls against the
creature have advantage which is the
real meat now if they can't move it can
they just climb out we're not talking
about that
well you you would be able to this is
just a natural operation of its body you
don't have to move around in order to
digest things yeah right maybe you don't
ya know how do you interpret that can't
digest halts know died you alter yeah
that's the whole suggestion grass dude
it's the interesting it is so real in my
house that my son will tell me the K is
silent Wow maybe somebody is regulating
I just want to make sure you know you
got fans
good I'm glad and right now I'm gonna
try and fight and claw my way out of
this
got so much advantage I love it okay so
lutein so we'll the second which is plus
five so definitely got that bite now I'm
doing for the claw that's Jack for real
[Applause]
love is in here wha-wha brand Larry is
an emote for this exact purpose shadow
council my neighbors please you servant
want a grasp
yeah yeah so that would be in nineteen
than that hits right oh yeah you're okay
good
what's next so now we're doing some beer
damage so let's do for the bite first
ah that's six and then let's use a cloth
and that is four that's nine so 15 times
15 total Thanks oh very very healthy
nice bear nice cheese that was yeah very
very savvy so just it's just like you
don't even care what is getting bit
no and cloth inside here now it's just
shreds bites rim yep just like Witcher
knows like underneath the chain Oh crazy
yeah exactly in that zone um that was
one that donk grasped and our blitz in I
understand that you're a marshal of
Paragon well so in that rotation
the bear was going nuts did three grab
one to take the opportunity with a full
round nail two to grab on to Clarke more
would you like that well I was being
taxed for him jamming his head in there
okay it's quite good so he is getting so
both hands around you can just see two
two hands come out around the side of
these massive antlers and you see Clarke
Moore just pull him bodily out and it's
like um imagine if you will a dark pizza
where the size of a slice is being
lifted slowly from the rest and thick
elastic trunks are attaching the two
strata and that's the situation here
it's like it does not want to let him go
but Clarke Moore is not going to let him
have it
okay and it pulls until two or three of
them snap yeah and then Clarke Moore
that's my boy mark Morgan does not have
good manners however he has done what
you asked and he has just deposited him
off to the side well he's safe exactly
we're tuck him in we're slick with
digestive juices
he slides about ten feet yeah across the
marble floor wriggling like anything I
can do born baby yeah this is on the
placenta but the best part about our
Ryan joke I said it starts out and then
if someone doesn't like it then you also
don't seem to like it I was there the
person who told the joke is a completely
separate entity yeah what asshole said
that Jack your own jokes a lot the
report right underneath the seat yeah
all right
ascend this Marshall hierarchy okay so
we've got our friend clear Clark Moore's
clear we got our bear doing work I guess
I wouldn't try to like boost you up
since you're in there but I don't really
have much that I can do to to really
just give it a whack yeah I'm just gonna
get more whack give me the old whack I
would debate doing acid breath but again
you got advantage already assume you
don't need to take it hmm oh and if you
were thinking about user oh oh yeah yeah
that's right think about how that that
saves charges hmm all right like
granting an advantage oh yeah granting
advantage is a real is it's gonna make
sure all that spells I burn are actually
burned all right
thunderous smite 2d6 thunder tell me
more when i when i crack-a-lackin' well
I'm gonna bonus action this on top of
myself this is my my priests smite
flavor this is the cool ranch yeah
exactly and I have advantage yeah well
18 pretty good mm-hmm
sorry so 15 plus 6 oh it's claim it how
much dares to D to be six regulars to D
6 plus 3 and if it's a 1 I get to be
rolling so that's 9 10 11 12
write this down excited for you 12 plus
2 D 6 Thunder damage on top of that way
I need green that's 3 I know 2 3
plus I'm a smite him bring that on why
not 3d it's might as well six that's
what you didn't say it
15 15 plus 15 so 30
that was my first oh my god I am running
out of spells so so so so Clark more has
pulled Thrym to learn it out
he sort of cast him out he hits the
floor he's like spinning away and then
he circles set his hooves just like
straight down in front of him he's like
leaning down and just sounds like a
hunting horn like he is he is he 100%
how's your back in this situation so I
want you to so having having seen 30
points I want you to tell me what 30
points it looks like on the field
against this aberrant monstrosity before
I do my next attack I want to know what
this first part looks like yeah well
upon clearing 3m thorium I was going to
come from threw him out of the
battlefield and then I see Clarke Moore
take a step back and I kind of get the
green light to go ahead I'm gonna just
salute yeah I'm gonna uh I'm gonna take
out tooth brush and that was that was
thunderous smite so I'm gonna gonna take
the sword and give him a little little
kissy sensual massage real quick a
little shiatsu well it's just to get
that crack-a-lackin' energy that's how
that's called an arc it's the you rub
your feet that's how it works
so then momentary pause because I feel
bad swinging on this thing while my
friends in bear form in the middle of it
but ya know are you gonna do I gotta do
me got it I gotta do me you know and
then just full axe handle right down the
middle if I can we don't the bear parts
but you know like it hey so you got a
new train here I got another turn let's
I got one spell left so if this connects
yeah man you're putting it to work my
last spell yeah I might have do I still
have naturally been oh yeah yeah
absolutely
17 and a 1 great I use the 79 out of
those two
my recommendation has your dungeon
master Oh give him a break
take that one seven I can ring rolls too
is to have whatever I'll take seven
eight nine ten we roll up to a five I
can yeah ten twelve nineteen so I'm 19
more we're just 49 points of damage
yeah sorry guys alright that's my whole
self whole body what I am now useless
because I'm out of a spell can't wait
anymore I can't
yeah my attacks are getting gonna let
the clip has been here they're going
down okay whenever about the spouse yeah
a lot more value than that eyes so so
these these just pristine textbook
examples of prowess delivered right into
the guts and flesh of this thing you can
see here in the dining room of trim to
learn it this is you don't know if it's
a hundred percent the case you suspect
that many dining many dwarven dining
rooms of this stature are similarly
adorned we're a non-trivial percentage
of the decor is actual functional
weapons and so you can just hear the
light rustle of the mithril chain as he
pulls himself up still dripping and he
reaches over the mantel of the fireplace
and pulls a massive axe and then he
turns himself toward this tower of the
gelatinous green flesh and then breathe
fresh and then he comes hey Valentine's
Day right right and then
draws his hands behind his head and then
throws an axe with both hands and it
lands firmly in this thing's head so
your orientation changes rapidly buh
so we soon as this thing connects and
sticks this thing just falls back and
then begins to flop and flap and then
you can feel that just the constrictions
internal to this creature eventually
just like birthing you out onto the
stone bear the prestige it definitely
has to be just it's that's like it's
what's expected you have to do it like
you have to present yeah yeah being
polite you say as a bear is it dead is
it dead is it - thoroughly okay I want
you feel it loosened yeah I want to turn
back into myself and immediately just
pick through and see if there's anything
in that in that body your Lewton the
course I'm already messy yeah exactly
it's like you can't get dirtier can I
see if there's anything in it probably
oh yeah I support this sort of thing he
ate two guards what is this what kind of
role is this what oh this this is a this
is a percentile roll from the dungeon
master
can you do it there's gonna be gook
sorting believe it I like the way you
said it did you do you do I get out in
the proper form you bear though no no
the parents oh sorry Irene Irene own it
myself you find yes a lavish crown a
crown Oh a lavish crown
Oh like a like what color like a crown
oh boy that was a good job
it's gonna go right through the cornea
and it's just gonna keep going yeah I
mean who's gonna stir your brain it's
rough
no yeah this is cute you'd you'd you
wonder yeah it's the sort of item that
one finds that immediately leads to
questions as to its prominence sorry I
I'm sorting through there and I just
think here that laid eggs and then I
pull it out and just go drugged I turn
I'm not turn to from Paris and then I'm
like he won't know anything and
interpret Rosie and go ah that missing
king yeah so Rosie is next to Thrym and
she's using the corner of her cloak to
like wipe the digestive fluids off of
them just like oh you're a mess
sweetheart so forth rim yeah yeah he
could obviously you know I'm something
about well well no exactly this is like
you're just like it's like a you're just
peeling it off it's you imagine you're
revealing skins freshest layer I will
imagine right it's a mask if you will
like it obviously it's like it's like a
there's a salicylic component excellent
you know what I mean so he looks oh oh
yeah he looks good million bucks
how does healing him but then I look at
you and I'm like does this does this um
crown here look familiar to you
good luck he looks at he's like what
should it does it should should look
familiar to me I guess not how does this
crown work nice it's nice it's a good
one it's not what you described is
tattered no no okay okay let's wrote
back epic fails to smile yeah
can I do um I'll bring it over to you
and be like can you tell who like
historically would have something like
this sure I can try can I do it I'll do
in his video this really um okay kings
I'll take advantage of this advant osh
company either a 16 or I'm not 16 okay
so you are you are going over this crown
turning it inside out turning it in the
light you don't think it's a dwarven
crown at all do you think that you think
that it would require significant study
with the use of a library okay does it
does its make look elven to me or a
human or if you had if you had to make a
guess you would say that this was an
elven crown okay okay
okay well I tell you that and give it to
the horse person should maybe keep it
yeah
am I the hoards person amid this this
farce that I'm a yucky drow do I still
have the bag on me am I still bound but
don't forget it's a it's a it's a
creature oh yeah I guess that's true I
could just ask it I don't I don't really
have any interest in keeping up the
pretense anymore yeah I'm like you see
what you can do yeah maybe I ok so then
maybe you start to bring it over to me
and I the you know the pretense just to
fall away right
how is through the shakin yeah he's he
goes out onto the onto the regal steps
of this his authentic and not guest
mentioned and he looks over at the guard
house and there is raucous laughter and
merrymaking good job yeah good thing uh
we were here in your main mansion see so
he walks over and you see like visibly
you can see tiny pools with each step
being deposited I think it's yours
dwarfs dwarven biology is distinct in
some ways but they do not cry from their
feet and he goes you see him he walks
over and opens the door quietly closes
the door and then after about five
minutes he opens the door again you can
hear the sound of armored plates being
removed and then you see five dwarves
leave out the front gate and close the
door behind them damn I mean they had to
come in that was well deserved yeah is
this or is this creature something that
I would have had expend of experience
within me in the unders dark sure sure
and I think take a peek I try what would
that be just history but no this has
nothing it's not history I mean this is
this is gonna be this is gonna be no no
this is this is Derby this is dork shit
like this this was gonna be in the
Arcana okay let me try to our cam to
work shit I wanna I'm gonna take that
advantage why not all right thirteen
that bed oh yeah they've been pretty
well invested today so um this is this
creature is an aberration it's not a
there's not a natural creature so it can
be the result of a couple things it can
be the result of experimentation gone
awry it's not organic it's a it's not a
creature it's a creature product yeah we
get exactly like so it can be it can be
the result of an experiment that had
gone awry it can be the result of it may
not be native to this plane may be
wherever it's from this is a good place
for a mouth beyond that it could also be
the result there are there is just a
sort of hostile radiation energy in the
Underdark right that can warp flesh as
well
how much have you told me about the god
of meat amounts let's think about that
know you know pretty much all of it hmm
I don't know that we've ever connected
on the the the star component that's
true oh yeah I don't think we've
connected that stuff on purpose
yeah I think okay second that's true
okay okay this just erm come back oh
yeah absolutely
okay he comes he comes back and then he
is like just from the remaining
fountains he's just splashing water on
his face
servants are bringing him fresh clothes
they bring him two or three weapons he
doesn't know how the nights gonna go
basically like they're bringing him to
bring him tools to succeed in any
scenario can we turn these off she shut
off the main somewhere down - have you
encountered this this before here he
says this is he says I would not
describe this as a normal evening this
household no she threw yeah I'm so
embarrassing I don't know I've returned
to the table I'm sipping yeah and I'm
looking at walnut and I'm looking at
dinner I say I think I remember him
saying something about a representing
our interest to the council yeah yeah
yeah so he goes back and there is
obviously a there several trays of stern
dwarven spirit and he grabs a tumbler
and then sets the tumbler down and then
grabs the bottle instead he takes the
stopper out sets the stopper in a
tumbler and just begins to pace the hall
and he says yes
that is what I said and I have every
intention of doing it the Regency
Council interprets the words of King
myth Barack with a what might be called
an undue legalism some people do their
best to interpret them so long and with
such granularity that they feel no
compulsion to act on the Kings wishes
we're gonna need a sophisticated
rhetoric to break them down well through
him to learn it certainly should have
rhetoric it's the boys it's not a
compliment oh how could it possibly be
not he raises his bottle to you takes a
drink hmm he goes over this there's a
selection of books here as well he is
pulling down he is pulling down volumes
and is clearly engaging in a bit of
legal research mmm he has quite a
library maybe we can find out more about
I want to know about that crown I want
to know who it ate oh yeah maybe I could
take over doing that while you guys are
talking to him but you can't read that's
not something that anyone else knows
what is this canon can she read she has
to be able to read documents but it
would be movie dwarven alright that's
true namely my sesame hieroglyphs thing
like we don't know like how
sophisticated the document see ledger is
I gave me to where you are that's
magical well it's deeply magical yeah
that's all emojis right yeah yeah we did
canonize that acorn she know that she
does think that her name spells dawn
grass yeah and like that's not anyway
but she believes it hard definitely
right
and she'll defend it to her death so
while we're talking to him just tell me
how many are against us there seem to be
a pretty lively debate how many there's
there 16 total there are 16 Regents and
how many are not for giving us this axe
how many do we have to convince he would
say he he counts for a while and he says
how many lives do we have to save 15 I
would say we're gonna have a hard time
with all but you that's my guess like I
said they're there they fetishize this
they fetishize the man's words but they
they do everything they can not to
follow them what would change their mind
yeah welcome how can what can we do I
could then do we have to go to the man
we need to wake up the man yeah cuz
here's his hand on the bottle shakes and
he's like he you're new and so I know
that that seems like he's not asleep
like it isn't like a nap
wasn't like a trance then it's quite
familiar with that for hours and hours
meditating it's something like that he
sleeps for 75 years at a time
and then when he wakes up he does
everything he can do to get the city
back to where it was 75 years ago where
where's this happening well how long ago
was the last time you got up
50:51 it's close enough
wait hang out he's he's like he's like I
don't he's like him honestly that would
be the easiest that would be the easiest
call go wake him up I could no no
what if it could be done without waking
him up I could enter his mind in a in a
in a in a kind way in that of a subject
of royalty not as
Invader and we could get his commands
right from right from the source and
then he could enjoy a continued slumber
I think I speak for everybody when we
all we want to do is get out of here as
fast as we can back to the surface so
there's no scenario in which you become
my vassals and manage the safety of the
household for 24 years
there is a that's not on the table
that's the easiest I'm saying that's
that's my plan a in the fullness of the
many versions of the multiverse I'm sure
there is a possibility where that does
happen but that is not the one we find
that debt honestly that is a comfort to
me grandmother that is obviously
somewhere someone we could use shadows
and tentacles and do a weekend at
bernie's kind of thing it just kind of
puppet him in there turned about for us
hey Clark go I think you're right Clark
all right we can't have tentacles and
shadows go up behind his arms no but
just is just a ghastly yeah sort of
cabaret yeah we approximate what we look
like so he's he says he says dream
surgery there your early surgery and you
could you prepare a document detailing
the mystic process shivers he's like
you're outside the room and you run back
in you're like a stupid I'm sorry sir
yep it's like he's like everything down
to the last syllable must be appropriate
yes
well lucky for you our drow is nothing
it's not appropriate
always at all times said I've clearly
taken a bite of some that creature and
I'm just wiping a little bit just to see
just to see just to taste it to your
your academic ledger in your red taste
not great yes Ben okay sort of salty
don't bite again not exactly salty
enough krisstraus edibles would be under
dark it's just a like boolean process
like no no no don't eat it no no no no
no no no no it's so little tea down here
oh my god
we're and we should have starved to
death all right so what is what is he
proposing it's he his he's proposing
that you become his no guards for not
only thirty years what he has heard the
party okay is that is that you do
fantasy inception yeah I will describe
to you an incredible detail this
practice go on and and and we can make
an airtight document it holds update any
amount of scrutiny oh my god well all my
documents do that but yes sure another
one usual oh so you want the standard oh
yeah you got the lease no but did you're
correct but maybe describing it to these
lay persons yes will be the difficult
component amazing but I'm confident I
can place myself in the minds of even
dwarves well if they're not if they're
gonna negative ten points already but
you started in the hole
you're like a dozen that saving my life
got us roughly even thank you
if they're if they're hemming and hawing
about giving us the pick I can't imagine
them being on board with us invading
their King's room with the words of the
King can't we just act unilaterally you
know to show us where these guys
sleeping we're doing this they will be
made to understand that what we're doing
is going into the King to give more
words and they want that and that's what
they want all right let's do it
you tell me exactly what you're gonna
say dictate to me right and then say
everything he says back and awaken mine
doesn't know its ending there has to be
like tweet level we could - I mean I'd
have to know them and I don't suppose
sending works on some news sleeping they
would wake them up that's usually yeah
it's typically although you lie all the
utilizations I know about for sending
are for woken up people right they
really cover it but I bet I could look
in there and see yeah I imagine that
awaken mind also has the potential of
waking somebody up yeah yeah and that
might be the thing they're afraid of
that's that's the lesser-known awaken
the mind let's just try it what's the
worst that could happen
exactly he'll wake up and then we asked
him about that pick his buddies are not
obeying his words exactly I'm game bro
sleep and get brunch listen whether or
not we get the pick is I mean that's
great and I probably could fit in the
hoards person bag that's a good idea but
if we can leave though is the critical
element to me and to each of you sure
well we're but this is a waste of our
time we should be going
of course back up I'm not here up not in
the Underdark let's figure out how to do
that everybody break this together yeah
find a way out and misson let us in
again see if they'll pick up again
they're mine she take us to where you're
King heads out of here Oh may I actually
attempt that though cuz I don't think
I've done that yet I have not I have not
messaged omen right you you have you
have attempted to do I have in the past
yet I'm saying that
right now the message I want to convey
is like trapped in the Underdark
we're in alcazar how fast can we you get
us out of here who you want to send this
message yeah I am going to send this
message yeah you receive us sending
almost immediately and he says to say
you know you can imagine almost like the
florid script and I mean in your mind
the communication seems to have the
official livery of an acquisitions
incorporated document right right I'm
home
and he says I'm sending help okay he's
not mad that we said that we had to open
then immediately bounce so that's good
the response the response simply says
I'm sending help those three words I
worry about that
yeah that's cryptic well that means we
got to stay here it couldn't be more
clear yeah we're very safe we're very
safe at the moment in this city mm-hmm
don't say that
[Laughter]
Norvin brunch okay all right you guys
for me you guys prepare your document
donar and I are gonna grab some brunch
at night yep
tonight brunch night for a nice brunch
that's the dwarf thing figured you would
know mimosas that sounds okay
we do all that the Underdark believe me
we all we all have our motivations
it's the underbelly me under believe
what a rich story as we exit you go find
brunch you guys can hear would be like I
would love to learn how to do that
wonderful smite move that you do after
your shots it's very nice it's variants
useful it's very useful I would love to
learn how to do so many punches so fast
I can teach you but you'd have to church
oh so rich do you authentically want to
find an all-night dwarven establishment
absolutely yeah scene a joke darling
joke about brunch I'm spilling the part
I have brunch half writing yeah I think
that it is I think that you guys are
working on a document and I think that
they are authentically going to that
it's small
clearly it was once an industrial let's
say that it's called
the journeyman hmm and it's like it's
like all the dining takes place on
tables that have clearly felt the tooth
of Steel hard work the forage back there
is cranking out artisanal deep pastries
yeah see those she snorts she's like
fucking hipsters they have they have
they have discovered a kind of coffee
beer that is designed to do both things
at once and it's it's like drinking a
roller coaster
thanks an accelerant and a depressant
yeah all right yeah get a couple of
those and and while we are drinking I'm
demonstrating with my tiny little fists
on you're a gigantic frame like all the
best places to like punch someone it's
surprising like it's really just like
right up in the butt cheeks no they all
start in a different place but they end
in a zone yeah
I'm explaining smites I'm like you got a
pray to your God oh okay that's that
step the end god mine marvelous
he wouldn't know these people more than
me he goes to a different school what we
broached this a little bit before little
bit yeah yeah we talked about your
copter for a little bit you think that
you think that there might be something
you don't see any reason to believe that
other people aren't drinking the same
thing that you are drinking you see
indeed they seem to be drinking this
sort of like midnight black used engine
oil liquid pretty readily and they seem
okay with it after the first class all
you can think about is like it's like
the equivalent of like a junior high
dance that didn't go well it's like you
it's like 10 minutes in to this drink
you feel like it just just pins you to
the ground like you feel like an insect
in an exhibit it's just like every
you're just going back over all these
social scenarios everyone that everybody
you've chose that you chose exactly the
wrong path at every juncture like just
today just today you can think of like
14 ways you have hurt others and
ultimately made your life worse and it's
like the hangover is in the glass I
tried the command and I use the word
syllables it so what is it so what is
like sorry what is like dinars sorry for
himself hungover I don't know yeah today
we have to go we have to find out how we
need that you know we need this dark
flavor I'll have to think exactly so oh
he's so self-centered wouldn't even like
acknowledge it or not without this not
without this stuff is the lubricant
mm-hmm consider it yes it is so you guys
are gonna be wandering on your way back
while the dumb grass how are things
going with this
how's it coming together you have you
have you it has it been a clean process
or has it been a challenging
interpersonal struggle I want to say
that I want to say that Catrice has made
no effort to to dumb down anything and
it's really frustrating because he says
that you know first you have to
establish that awakened mind is a
communication between two minds yes you
need to establish the presence of a mind
but before you can do that you need to
establish the presence of your own I
don't know if we need to get theoretical
with it maybe they just need to know
that it's like crazy drow magic I'm
willing to start describing it later
down the process but then we need to go
back and tie these proofs up really make
it get to that but let's get to what we
actually want to say to him what do we
want where we want to ask him well they
need to understand that we're going to
speak to their king
in a manner they should choose with that
deference in that tone I don't know what
kind of a mood he'll be in I don't know
he's been communicated with in dreams
before but will be very gentle and
present ourselves yeah I got that you we
spent 30 minutes talking about how
gentle this is and I think it's Jim and
it's gentle it's really well covered yes
and it's incredibly it's a gentle yes
all this is about that and you got it
imagine having a dentistry performed on
your forebrain don't even name yeah I
don't even know if it goes anywhere I
think it's just a lot of explaining
things to the umpteenth degree and right
you it's always gets lost next yeah
these forms are normally like was was
there an ineffable horror check essay
here and not so much multiple yeah this
is a bespoke form this is like a letter
of intent this is a letter of intent Oh
interesting
okay so you get like we spend maybe a
half an hour
on me trying to explain a legend you're
like don't know about that
what if you compose a form that's
original for this purpose it hasn't been
established before and then I and we
both fill it out together
yes oh my god that's great so I get rid
of all this garbage that I've been doing
and I'll make up this form and I'll use
my special my special villain like my
official villain before I was using the
scrap stuff now I'm making an official
form and use my special level to
document see stuff get it all looking
improper and then I just make a series
of checkboxes and blanks and I go okay
so what's the first thing establishing a
link between two minds and we've
established that those minds exists mmm
check I'm just dumbfounded how easy I
know that that check doesn't carry any
weight any any more than any other
symbol but there's just something about
how solids will you row it South kills
all the time at that warm hearth like
interpersonal moment we're gonna bring
this first half of the show to a close
precious shadow council mara leavers
please you we will be right back after
these commercial messages don't go
anywhere hello this is Jerry Hawkins
again remember me we're playing Dungeons
&amp; Dragons only a few sure minutes ago
well now we've returned to play more
digital records now when last we saw our
heroes two of them had managed to get a
hangover after only one drink a potent
dwarven liquor now during this same
period the two good kids were doing
homework and become and basically being
productive members of society
good so you have done this you have it's
a late night at Chez Thrym he is
speaking into the mirror he's trying to
draw himself up to his height he's
clearly practicing his oratory but he is
gonna try to he's gonna try to flex on
the Regency council in an effort to
secure this pick because he helped him a
lot by pulling him out of the guts of a
demon monster mm-hmm it's the least you
can do I mean that's that stuff's I
think that's the recognized
that's the recognized response you know
that's the expectation I think mmm
you're gonna demon and then you're out
of a demon and someone's responsible for
that you you look you you take that into
account
yeah then you go on your conclusion
earlier was that this was just some like
under dark shit yeah I mean just maybe
this place isn't as safe as we thought
okay but yeah it doesn't seem to be like
an it's not an emissary of anything of
this plane yeah that is a good point we
just kind of glossed over that yeah
monster emerge from the fountain and
we're like this is normal let's get
drunk let's go let's get drunk in the
middle of the night so the next morning
Thrym along with a new selection a new
retinue you are all taken with him to
the Regency Council as I said they have
a beautiful door that seems to recall
the great gates that you entered
initially and as you enter back through
this gate the arguments have already
begun in earnest they have not waited
for Thrym the learner
to begin these deliberations where we go
in I clapped threw him on the shoulder
and I go hey good luck in there and I
convey on to him the chopped evil
splendid
he has advantage on his charisma checks
the door is open and it's just it's just
it's all ferrets and rolls it's just a
heap of tiny friends carry us to the
surface
you haven't sounded up yet what have you
to say actually they don't even they all
just like murmur like an agreement peas
and carrots peas and carrots peas
carrots rhubarb rhubarb so you have do
you have a copy of this document Oh
in triplicate okay is there a single
document is there one for each member
oh yeah I would have written it out 16
times so hey have you all um yeah I mean
I have I had four hours of transom and
I'm the rest of it of Scriven Scriven
and transcend sounds like a good banana
yeah yes yeah it's really obvious that
it was up to the last hour so like the
last one that like maybe I had four
Thrym it's like it's not even it's like
everything is trailing off like
everything is slated on the page like
cramming stuff in on the end yeah tiny
at the bottom says I'm sorry but but but
this is three Muscovy right that's okay
he knows he knows how it is and he's
he's reading it and sort of mouthing it
to himself as you guys are walking over
he's nodding his head like trying to
absorb it he's gonna go in there and do
his best so as you as you enter it like
I say they're already hard at work in
their task which appears to be a kind of
eternal like fetishization of the
bureaucratic art form the win for them
is not really having to do much mm-hmm
and so when Thrym gets in he slaps the
table a couple times and there's no
effect he slaps it a couple more times
he's able to get a couple people over
here II Gayle's them with a tale of
heroism says this is these are the
people that our King our noble King
chose for this boom and I've seen
evidence of what they're capable of
last night I put them in the guest
mansion think about that I put them in
the guest mansion still they rose to my
side against a horror and there's a
summer's horror hasn't been seen for a
hundred years
hmm how many people does he have in here
who are paying attention to him yeah
right one right now right now that I
think the horror part kind of gave that
kind of gave the thing a stinger okay
like that's a that's a very exciting bit
to throw in so he's got everybody the
attention is definitely there okay and
he says he says it's in the book this is
the book we're sworn to uphold these are
men and women of Valor and natural
charisma even the drow hmm even the drow
has risen above what we thought was
possible I have it I says as you know
there's much restraint yeah just as soon
as you have your mouth it's all that
just like that like the dead guns of a
warship like all the heads just turn I
did though if the book here it's in
there many copies of it yeah
okay is it out like opens or absolutely
okay
so just to back up the wonders that we
are capable of yeah I'm gonna use
thought mature G and this is not listed
on the card but I'm gonna see if you buy
this it's what all I want to do is a
gust of wind and I want to have the
pages of whatever open book of myth bark
I want to have them just go as soon as
he gets the attention and everybody's
like Oh what is it a horror yeah yeah
whore a horrible whore Oh
hundred years in this and I just like
that's good okay well that's just it no
no there yes they don't they don't
notice it oh no no I'm saying they don't
notice the spell casting is the sound of
a distant Bell we're in like super inner
chambers so there is no wind yeah yeah
oh yeah totally and I like it wind blew
exactly
so as you so you do you deliver this
system oh well you're surprised ooh wow
it's very it's very exciting Thrym says
and that's why I'm recommending that we
call a vote right now let's put this
thing to bed and get back to the task we
were sent here to do and he says all in
favor of granting the boon that the king
himself swore was theirs and he raised
his hand no no don't worry Chanukah and
there's and there's there's no other
hands and one of them says okay we all
see the we all see the drought right
like right like in the Regency council
chamber you see that the drought who
saved through his life well just this
that's what I was told I don't know if
he's been in sourcils in some way do
that's very Thrym I would say that's a
deeply Thrym prospect detects
some mints or slurry you got you got
magic around here he goes oh yeah fucked
up somehow yeah bet so yeah he says he
says we he says we could just give him
but we all remember when the assassins
were sent to steal the water key I
assume that's nobody forgot that there's
only a hundred years ago we weren't here
then what happened okay
it happened right and so its rim through
my just having I guess we'll just give
him the water go get the water key we'll
just give it to him that'd be great so
and then and then he says listen you
guys need to listen to me right now puts
his hands down on the table and behind
this is the table in this chamber
there's a kind of bar relief can be a
bass relief bats relief sounds like a
product for fish yeah it doesn't like a
relief carved in the shape of a bat yeah
exactly and there is very plainly the
symbol of a simple hammer and great
wings sort of unfolding it in a
protective way and you would never in a
million years have imagined it that
there was a seam in this so perfect as
its manufacture but sure enough it
slides open and you can see that it has
the same it's a it's similar to one of
the gates that you came in on it appears
to be sheathed in one of these
mysterious metals that this town is
known for and you see a relatively plain
looking dwarf except for the fact that
in his hand is a mithril pick and it's
not um it's not fancy you know how like
in um in Indiana Jones and the Last
Crusade there's like the cup of a
carpenter yeah like this is clearly a
pick that is for it's like a people's
pick right
it has a there's like a light inlay
silvered metal spiral on the haft but
the pic itself is something you'd use
your entire life so the dwarf has this
he also has upon his head a regal crown
oh and he yawns and stretches his right
arm loosens up his shoulders pushes the
door open a little bit farther walks out
into the Regency Council room sets the
pic before the party on the table and he
looks out upon the council that was
assembled to interpret and then enact
his words and he says I write these
things down for a fucking reason and
then the one who had so recently
elevated his tone and says my king music
no he waves his hand at him walks back
behind the table back into the door is
that close and sin and seal without so
much as a hinge just a perfect motion
like a natural force like maybe this
existed maybe this is the only thing
that existed in time and space and the
rest of the planet just to create it
around this perfect figure and the
entire room is stunned
except for Thrym who is very very
pleased with himself one of the other
Dwarfs says we've had to interpret his
written word now to interpret it can
mean anything why does he write fucking
things down with are the other things
are the things fucking yeah
yeah he's a character I'm looking at
this stack of beautiful forms that I
waited up all night to make and just
immediately start going well
put him out get the red ink out and
start writing void just go back through
there's sixteen times three yes well I
and I'm as disappointed I was really
looking forward to this being conveyed
to them yeah it's very upsetting
yeah three Monday as you're getting down
to the bottom two stream stream is like
don't leave mine just leave mine I won't
i won't i won't legally enact it I just
if I don't have this to remember I'm
gonna forget and I don't want to forget
well it goes like of course and then
just in like the smallest little she
goes here you go with my special
signature on it I think I just figured
out what the learning means well he
forgets stuff and it tosses full of
books
that's sad it's really sad you guys yeah
so they're gonna make fun so he he says
well if our business is concluded yeah
pick yeah how you have it in front of
you great who wants the pick just grip
this hard on the weed teleport up up to
the surface on the rag and let's get out
of here yeah yeah yeah does it fit in
the bag actually I don't know if I want
to put in them but you make I make a
very big show of in front of them being
like our drow is the one who will
collect this royal pick so I shall you
see it's like there's a buzz like breath
stops but like in a bunch of at a bunch
of different points anyone have a bunch
of different throats the people that I
hear gasping they get like I think
daggers cleared out I ran a face yeah
don't you don't you say a fucking word
I lift it up I'm not even like it's
great pick oh good haft
yeah feels right yeah this is a
well-made pick holding that pick this
yeah as you as you as you lift it up off
of this a smooth surface of this table
it's like once that once the back of it
comes up off of it it just strikes it
against the sort of like the bezel and
just such a way it's a it's a tone like
meditation chime mmm do you think do you
think that if you did not touch the tip
like you don't know how long it would go
well done Oh tip toucher I immediately
touch that tip I immediately grasp it -
no nope no no meditating right now hmm
exactly is that upsetting to them Joe's
trying to our Channel know what one of
them does towards Leaguers I'm wondering
if just for safekeeping I want to put it
in in the document or sorry in the I
certainly almost like that is you I
couldn't if I wanted to I don't to put
it in the words person back I don't know
if it will fit all the way and I know we
may need it is it am i what kind of what
kind of play isla Gatti's mouth have can
I add it to him can it be bound to him
in some way just so I don't have to hold
two things
well yeah cos he doesn't have to eat
things right you know what I mean he has
two little guys no but he still hasn't
he still has kind of a parody of a
biological form yeah he still has a
cavity
I just never tested the depth of that
throat happy Valentine's Day why is
there a reason you don't want
I'm concerned that we're gonna need it I
don't think it's like a treasure to like
here we go home office Oh have you ever
tried to get anything back out of it
no I don't think I don't know a transfer
you can you can I know exactly what it
is I mean you can I've never tried
though yeah I put okay I've put all the
coins and what-have-you in there okay so
we know that I've put various items in
yeah I mean do you want to reach in yeah
well I mean if I peer in what am I
seeing
like I say snow so it's it's snuffles
around for gold as we've seen but if you
are trying to get something out of it
you can just you're basically just like
set it down and it's weighted has a good
weight you can open it up like this and
when you do that you see a container
that has multiple places inside of it
yeah so you can place things in there
MARY POPPINS no and there is actually a
note inside the container that on the on
the front on the top of it it says kiss
wrist wrap okay but that in therefore
should know well I read it hungrily yeah
cuz I'm hoping okay when we get out of
here 15 minutes it said it says I had to
negotiate on your behalf for quite some
time as the cursed coins you sent
through your satchel created a
significant amount of trouble for other
branches and then there's a - missus
secretary I say to myself wow it really
really has whoops
like months in that in the bag then yeah
as long as I'm able to recall it or
bring it back yeah yeah absolutely
I mean you couldn't mean you're gonna
close the round a quick peek in there
yeah it's just like object permanence
all right okay all right yeah you can
you can store it in there lovely okay
done and done just my hands off me exams
help exactly so he's three miss is
pretty pleased with himself he's sort of
walking the perimeter appreciating some
of the art on the walls perhaps for the
first time I think things may be
different for him in here in the future
you don't know if it's necessarily a
good thing but he and his retinue he
leads you out of the room and toward the
front gate with his with his his new
soldiers but first he takes you to the
stable we're fully two stables are taken
up with a massive beetle Sam Beale
better be long
Beale upgrade that's better beetle watch
the baby oh yeah waxed yeah yeah this
beetle looks coming but you have the
stripes no there's no stripes
why not natural scarab ribbing
yeah it'll make it go faster so okay as
we approach it and as I like I stopped
everybody alright at least I stopped who
I who's within arm's reach him and I say
like and now if the council is at all
concerned what's going to become of this
pic well I mean we'd be more than happy
to remain here within the city's many
walls and doors until our own conveyance
can can retrieve us that we certainly
wouldn't take beetle from you is they
are very rare in the Underdark I'm LED
timers rare incredibly rare especially
if this this is a fine
I'm drought understand this is a great
bill you want to give us this your head
will stay here and then someone will
come get us he said we're not outside he
says I don't think that it is I can
understand your concern and then
certainly I appreciate it
he says I'm not I don't know exactly
what kinds of reprisals
my co councillors may have in mind but I
would let me absorb the brunt of those
I'm not sure I would stay in the walls
of Alcazar I think he's right you don't
want to go to the surface get out of
hell I don't want to take a Beatle to
the surface I want to that one oh man or
somebody to just make us appear there
it's gonna take weeks of travel didn't
exactly say he was gonna get here in any
timely fashion either no that's true but
I would rather be somewhere where
various persons might not be able to
penetrate I mean listen I may be I'm
outvoted but I it it's fine maybe no one
will catch us on the road as we're
approaching that makes sense it'll speed
things up okay
ready the beer but like if you don't
want to ride the beetle I'll stay I
still have Clark more Ione ever unsummon
Clark morning you can right in front
yeah how far can put you in out of your
range far yeah I I think this until I
and I know exactly how far as far as you
can conceive not possible it's a
challenge is the very idea of running
dad is a plain old elk and I don't think
so he's a star deer that's fine rider be
home ribbed for her pleasure we walked
past it I want to get back to it another
day thing so um so at upon seeing you
hmm because you had provided a you know
a mode of of communication mm-hmm it
hisses at you but you don't think it's
bad
happiness oh it's good like what carrot
does it yeah like it they're happy it's
mouth parts are going nuts son I'm gonna
get up on top right I can't say anything
I'm out we've been there all right
wonderful so I get up on that Beetle and
I pet the part of it behind me you're
like all right let's go go let's get out
of this dwarf place yes get her up it's
moving I wrap my tiny little arms around
you you want to wait so so Clark Morris
working are you just gonna walk on foot
are you gonna take advantage one of
these conveyance no I'm okay I'm on the
beetle but I'm trying to figure out if I
can get under that wing casing yes where
can I hide in or on this I don't think
it would be impossible to get tucked in
there oh but you know what though ah but
now maybe maybe you can maybe you can
remind me or I can look it up myself
right in there get it cause that beetle
but I don't see you you'll be safer
you'd be there a year yeah I think I
still have read some real estate in man
a nice place you got here I think I
still have masks of many faces and I'm
trying for you I don't remember how long
it lasts
yeah you can but well because I'm not
comfortable with that option the bar
whole options yeah
I will disguise myself as a much smaller
beetle oh that's wonderful - sighs
beetle that if you look closely has four
limbs not six it won't let me be a
beetle but it maybe it'll let me be be
Lesk it'll Bailey I can't be a beetle
but what I want to be able to do is be
on the back of this thing and look like
a part of it
beetle barely like maybe that's the
beetles friend you can cast this guy's
self it will without expending a sauce
no small spot okay we get there how long
does she last that's a really clever and
I know it's super if I can have a look
like a beetle oh so I have this spell on
a game that I played last night you can
appear one foot shorter taller right and
you can make yourself still humanoid in
appearance right so you could be a
beetle man just imagine like a fry queen
or something like that
thank you yeah yeah but I can't add
limbs though no so it's like a basic
arrangement of 'ln limbs and if anybody
gets too close to you and tries to like
feel your carapace they know this
Valentine's Day yeah it's awesome far
from being touched right you become dust
no okay so actually so you so you're
gonna you're gonna create a mockery of
life right like it's some sort of a
forgotten conjoined no no do some
fucking Kafka ass yeah and I do end up
akhira I do it when none of you are
looking your we're on the journey and
you somebody says something it looks
back at me and I'm like a bit don't look
at me butyl man I have to recast it in
an hour but you know it's I think it's a
rest have to take off yeah um do you
keep the beard of course
so that beard is around like so
pedda pulp so you're trying to
manufacture fan art at this point like
that's that's the situation there's
gonna be one of your elite skins I don't
think it would surprise any of us it
would a little bit but not really did I
have more we're change dinar for sure
because you guys have spent time yeah in
each other but you and I might be like
within oh no no we're just like okay oh
I didn't reach a good thing you could
reach another level and it did she
sounded listen we just ride this out
it's my own voice and you could think
I'm just gonna ride this out the best I
can as far as you know I came of the
beetle ya know it's like it's that it's
like aftermarket yeah yeah is it we're
gonna Beatles riding a beetle does let
us worry about that so the father did
you ever speak to me no so as as you are
wheeling Herbie and Clark more and
[Music]
whatever this creature is yeah junior
Herbie the younger you're willing up and
the gate men look down with just
pleasure upon you
just like I made five bucks on that bed
yeah and I just I want to make sure that
you know that I have really appreciated
having you you know I've loved it and I
appreciate it
that's great and then I pull out a
business card and I go if you read the
services of acquisitions incorporated
you know how to call us gesticulations
do this yeah this is walnut things that
fancy people do they just set it on the
ground just
I'll come get it put it anywhere she
puts it like next to the wall like
because it up yes so like no one so the
the last of these mini doors a solid
slab of gleaming mithril ten feet long
and three feet deep
covered in incredible work slides down
into the ground it's like a fish ladder
type thing so as the party moves past
that gate the next gate in front goes
down this one pops up behind you and you
hear that voice just a little bit duller
a little bit quieter now says there's a
real it was a real pleasure and this
process goes on like I said before
there's six his occur which is like a
shiny magical metal sheath iron doors
after these other ones in the back and
then just two solid iron doors each one
of them has fewer and fewer dwarves
basically each one of them represents
the strength of the of the gate and by
the end it's just a single face and
you're noticing that the farther out you
get you're leaving the sound and the
bustle of the city of its occur or
alcazar and you are hearing another
sound the closer you get to the outer
gate so it's sort of like crossfading
between this ambient sample yeah which
is wood for lack of a better term would
be like bustling market dot wave right
ten hours is exactly 10 hours on YouTube
and then and then the farther you get
closer out this is something more like
goblin radar me dot waves
lo-fi hiphop Jill farther exactly
soundcloud rappers dot wave you get out
to the edge drops out and when the final
gate drops down you can see a boiling
mass of goblins and hobgoblins some on
beetles some with rickety caravans and
they are excited imagine imagine that
their favorite act has just taken the
stage there the moment you become
visible they are amazed by a new a
youthful energy you might say yes can I
sue you look back up and you can see a
couple hands sort of on the
crenellations and at that when the last
gate opens down you see those hands
disappear you see the the gateman cola
way from this room even louder you can
hear me going you'll be hmm how far away
are they
um maybe let's see from here maybe 200
250 feet okay I want to try something
really quick they're just in a throng
yeah right now are they approaching from
the south like we traveled north to get
to this and they're coming I assume
following us from where we came from so
you have you are leaving the town yeah
and then from the direction that they
came from basically the way I came from
there they can pursue exactly right and
so okay so just behind them
of course is those is the ruined outer
cities right butthole but we have to go
back because you said that they were in
a throng yeah and then in my mind I
heard that's wrong to throw it's wrong
and I was like yeah yes yeah great
www D I was wondering if we wanted to
try and make an escape do you haven't
won a parlay with them well it sounds
like maybe they're a boiling mass so
yeah it's like can you talk to do you
speak boiling mass yeah but I can do
hallucinatory terrain now what is cool I
know I can make terrain resemble some
other sort of terrain and it's against
it intelligence investigation versus my
spell TC and they are not smart
what's your spell to see it's 15 15 so
what would what kind of here are your
gorge Oh like between us and like
between us in that it's cool that like
the ground just looks like it opens up
and it looks like a gorge st. Gorge or a
cave-in or yeah yeah they're like Gord
that's tight yeah gorge cool anyway yes
I would like to test hallucinatory
terrain and see if this works
yum-yum-yum-yum use a lot of fun so let
me roll 300 saves
[Laughter]
yep Samantha's yeah oh don't mind me
it's gonna roll 300 C maybe you can
offer like the goblins as you see
goblins hobgoblins yeah they're animals
yeah exactly yeah sorry promise
yeah what's your spell fav DC uh 15 they
do they do they do quite well so no no
they they fail this part so something so
the this rending crack in the earth
spooks
some of their mounts and so they start
to they charge and then when they get to
this they get to this gorge they imagine
for all their worth that they are
actually falling down an interminable
chasm and so though so the beetle legs
like it's just it's like flipped over
it's like rolling over goblins like
something in VR yeah it's the legs are
just like kicking and pulsing straight
up and then over writing this gorge
I guess the cave roof this is this is
just it's an important piece I should
have emphasized this before I tried to
but I want to make sure that it's
clearly understood it isn't like the
roof of the Underdark is like just
interminably high in some places it's
quite low and over here a lot of the
light for alcazar actually has is from a
bioluminescent lichen that's close
enough on the ceiling to actually be
seen and so in this same space in this
same profile the hallucinatory terrain
shifts and is altered okay
so you can see a what looks to be the
blades and whirling teeth of an Emma's
ear pierce the roof and then go down
even farther and then as it does so it
falls down into this Gorge and then
fills it with lush greenery that comes
around and so you're trying to you don't
know who in this retinue would be
capable of this type of warfare mm-hmm
like you you just learned this yeah
this new fur this is not a goblin right
it's hard to imagine
and then that the iconography itself as
to there's too much knowledge so you are
currently playing around with this space
I would you are welcome to try to
continue to do battle with this
conceptual realm is he doing dueling
hallucination yes awesome
it's really quite having the best time
so someone else is participating in this
I agree
you think you think that you could try
to rest this and put another spin on
another shape oh I see this is like
sorting stone the Wizards the wolf yeah
he's making a new yeah so right now it's
like not baked I see um I don't know I'm
stuck so it's it's basically oh it looks
lush like for a moment like you know
that it's not true because it can't be
true and it looks like this sort of it
looks like the sort of forest that like
imagine you'd seen when it only in a
book so it looks perfect so it's perfect
but the colors are over bright and this
isn't this is an under and under dark
creature who's made this then yeah you
made a hole they filled it with plants
so you have to kill the place so I have
to kill the plants okay so yes then
we'll say the hole becomes a pit of just
boiling lava oh so they're cracks as
these trunks and just like the old
growth that's just like the part of this
natural cycle mm-hmm it's just snapping
over the mouth of this gorge and falling
down and like catching on fire from the
heat even before they hit it and then
that that that magma is just rising up
and lapping out at the edge and it is at
this time that there's almost a
here that here they would call them a
rift down in this space this is this
this would be a geographical feature a
rift can be in the ground but it can
also be in the ceiling and you can see
something like a waterfall of clear hmm
pure water that falls down and then
going down in Georgia and then strikes
the strikes the water there strikes the
lava and the burning remains and then
after a rush of steam there is a like a
glassy jet-black Dyess with chairs
around it what I wonder
don't send Jagan's is the greatest game
of all time yeah so what yeah how are
they go so this has got to be the
ultimate photo their date happened right
it's all in our brain exactly I really
like they already thought they were
falling and dying mmm so there are some
goblins who are having the worst time
food ever and you can see in that sort
of ocean of terrified flesh you can see
that it parts almost like in in a field
you can see that there's almost like a
an orb of space that is moving through
this through this mass through this like
field wherever it goes there's
substantial space granted hmm around on
every side and then when that bubble
appears at the front you can see a
hooded figure with a staff and you can
see even in the glum darkness of the
Underdark
you can see very plainly a chain with a
focus symbol
[Music]
situated on the front and I you you you
can it's a fair distance away but you'd
have every confidence that you know
precisely who this might be the guy from
before can you be more specific
oh yeah there was a period of time where
dinar blitz and leveraged his let's
draconic is force of charismatic power
hmm
and for 10 minutes things were pretty
cool alright suppose as far as you plan
ahead I'm like walnut
he's probably get this beetle out of
here you want to go then he keeps heat
he keeps walking in front and he takes a
seat Oh at one of the chairs I think he
wants to parlay with us uh-huh
I'm gonna go up because I think he was
like a formidable natural and I I want
to go up and take a seat at the the
thing and then after I do it I just look
back pleadingly and everybody else
what's here give me a time later
give me let's see our Constitution say
no no no no wisdom oh I just give me I
just me a check I write a regular yeah
yeah regular old easy now what's the
dangles between our Beatle and this
chair the configuration that's a tie-in
oh yeah that's that is about from here
that is about 200 feet or so okay one
several five maybe woof ah 13 yeah you
you can't get much more than this but
you feel you feel confident that that
wasn't druidic mmm magic
okay you know and as you begin to look
at his Everybody Loves Raymond train but
as you begin to really assess it hmm you
can daunt I'd say you you can you can
determine you can sort of see the path
that that this you know sanctified garb
you can see the connections between that
tradition and other Truett and other
druidic traditions you think it is
customized for their rights and
responsibilities of a druid in a alien
place oh sorry
sit down and I do Dritz they have their
own language but it's only written right
it's written it's written okay
you do love writing yeah does he have
any critic on him I mean it is like like
inscribed or anything like yeah he
doesn't have anything there's no if
there's nothing stitched in or anything
like that and the the hood is still the
hood is still very low you're not you're
not perceiving like active direct threat
but this is clearly a person who this
this is a person who created a parley I
say environment okay okay so then when I
sit down I'll say I'll say what did you
come here to say he says sorry it says
it'd be impossible to tell okay
the creature in the hood says where is
the other one who's the other one you're
the lizard ah yes
I look back and I go dinars no you're
wanted that's not it's it's not anger no
no it's not it's it's not anger that's
fine it's something but it's not anger
would you come over yeah alright yeah
that's fine I mean I'm trailing behind
you hidden in your shadow
yeah concealed and then my back as soon
as he yeah as soon as you sit down I'm
going to slip into the darkness behind a
chair but I'm not gonna
oh yeah exactly like like so convenient
yeah of course yeah I'll walk over I
won't sit down but I'll just kind of
stand there it's rude Oh while you're
done coop so while you've done that and
while you've done that I want to like I
want to close the distance but not
intrude upon the space so I I've got the
does it have rains I want to know no I
know she's been controlling it and she's
been controlled well she's been
controlling it with exactly okay just on
the vibrations on the wing case okay
that I'm going to think about that and
then realize I don't know how to do it
right and rather than like go like this
and then have it charge the scene I just
I just abstain you gonna stay with I
will stay with the beetle okay
the beetle begins to wander over to
shred of illusory foliage I get off the
beetle and and attempts earnestly to
chew it for a long time like longer than
a person would like it tries to chew and
chew
I find so much reflected in this in this
moment and this seemed I liked the idea
then after you get up early does it
you're walking upright like beetle would
walk it no not even like skittering
around like walking over like like we're
between takes yeah can't figure in your
beetle costume yeah yeah cheese's cock I
get here 10 minutes earlier Teamsters
took everything yeah I near the beeline
I just feel self-conscious
right he says no but you're gonna stab
you I was gonna try any time when I
wasn't before now it's not doing
anything
exactly he says it says how did you
learn to do that says you're no mage
you're a lizard that's on two feet I'm a
dragon and it's in the blood baby and I
can do it again so can you get kids so
yeah let's keep it civil he said I'll be
making an app again he says would you
that's up to you but not me so I learned
a lot you have to understand that for my
kind being dominated is very novel hmm
and when it pulls back the hood you can
see a just a chandelier of tentacles
where the mouth would be cresting back
up to a sort of cephalopod mmm head and
their eyes that blink in the dark all
right so this is the same guy dominated
because he said so but there's an under
some bruise or something he has some
kind of illusion yeah I go yeah I mean
nice nice that's good yeah well this has
been great and you know I'm glad we
could catch up
you've gotta be hitting the old dusty
trail he he sort of casts his eyes
around in the darkness of the cavern and
he says there was another I just I'll
the beetle falls away no okay it's not
gonna I don't think I've heard a lot of
stories I don't know I'm not sure if
I've actually encountered any myself but
I don't think this this this guy's was
gonna do anything anyway well does seek
redress recognizes what we were they
think I imagine so diem that I know this
being this type of oh yeah that's it
this is a classic this one goes back
aways in the same way that the the what
you know of the EPA lore involves a kind
of Genesis myth mmm that involves a
perpetual utterly moral war against a
depraved other the drow have a similar
the droughts have a similar relationship
with these creatures yeah now with the
beetle facade shed I hesitantly began
walking toward the table as in the hunch
of a beetle despite myself like like
haha he'd do that like I'll be like no
he's dead
like trying to protect you know instead
we killed him and they walk over you're
alive you an beetle hunched form just
looks like you normally is me I normally
it's just I'm actually I'm hunched out
of like concern a lot of concern but I
don't want to be apart from that party
what is your personal feeling about
elephants
oh I because it doesn't have to be it
doesn't have to be you don't have to
inherit that no and I would truth is
you've been on the surface for a while
I'm fascinated
but I don't know its feelings toward me
it may see a drow and make that
assumption but it seems civil enough and
I'd rather not be caught out exactly
yeah hey Josh could you tip my cauldron
please oh my god so when he when he
looks upon you like you you don't know
how you're supposed to parse this these
expressions like you know you know that
they all must mean something but you
know that these specific crinkles or
it's it's tight here but then it's loose
here like you know that these must have
some kind of analogue to the rest of
them that don't make any sense to you
right but you can at least categorize
them here you don't even know what the
basis is and so I rolled one I've never
rolled assistants on my cauldron yet I
am very excited about what this might
represent know as soon as Rosie sees
this as an ill-effect all this is coming
together she pops out of hiding over the
top of a chair she goes do you know
elder Brian it's just like super rude
I'm sure it's like oh you're from Canada
do you know Kim yeah exactly he says
perhaps and he looks he looks back over
to you and he says he says don't hunch
stand at your full height you have met a
brother today and he reaches into his
satchel and in it is a tiny simple
version of your focus but the symbol
that's held in it is a symbol for the
entity called that which indoors which
we saw in the met but yeah isn't yeah he
did and he he hands it to you and it is
weighing and wants so desperately to be
a part of your focus I stand at most of
my height not the whole thing it's not
you don't get the whole thing yet you
and I you also are seeking no I have
found that's our game haha okay thanks
so much thank you so much
no it's gonna be good no I mean it's
just complaining about let's play again
next week ah thanks so much hey shadow
council that is our game for today but
don't go nowhere because we gotta sign a
bunch of stuff for you and then we're
gonna talk to you about a bunch of other
things and it's gonna be super cool
don't go anywhere I'll see you soon bye
you