time is the enemy of the past and
threatens the fastest women you wouldn't
make it past a second and answer the
question play it brash and reckless to
choose a cautious solution you saw was
prudent enemy sepulcher poker doodle
become the pew tree it's that well said
I pursue in no mountain too steep for
dungeon too deep to send expanded their
marks up to the top of the peak of
beneath they see Yugi they come like
sharks to it while I swim in that money
build like Carl Barks drew it so send
your national parks drew it I'll send
him home in a natural box with the
clothes time for most of the parts
included save your breath for a cleric
confessor death is a lesson that life is
a tenured professor but if you're
seeking my official advice sign on the
dotted line English of the choice mark
Sinclair hello I'm Tycho Brahe hey of
Penny Arcade pax dot-com web online I'm
also a Memphis area drunk CEO of
acquisitions incorporated but today
Jerry
Hogan's I'm here to run a game of
Dungeons &amp; Dragons for my friends to my
right
Dragonborn narcissist dinar blitz and
[Applause]
what they want it's him now to the right
of my right repping the natural world
walnut dawn grass no catching the
thermals oh yeah yeah you know you're
never coming down
nope yeah I mean to my left not your
grandma's grandma except in those rare
cases where she is your grandma's
grandma rosie beasting I was I was
completely engaged at the beginning and
to another some Street magic
he's on my credit card to the left of my
left emerging is though from a mist
shroud the thrist drow
[Music]
they think that it's in front of a live
audience that is not miked that they
just can't hear oh these are the sounds
that we make exactly the sounds we make
quite naturally now gathered friends of
course shadow council mayor leiris
please you when last we saw our heroes
they had recently made the acquaintance
of a incredibly powerful sorcerer named
somebody moral good one good recap Strix
it was strict II realized although I'm
well pleased that you were right there
with the name yeah materialized in a
heap of bloody rags there was a period
of time where there was a whitewater
rafting scenario it ended with some
malevolent crawdads shortly thereafter
you were able to emerge from these icy
waters having traversed a substantial
amount of ground and you are now in the
current continuum east of the city of
gala death where a young Catherine
Straub did grow but in addition just
before the game ran out and Strix
D materialized and went back to her own
game Chris Perkins DC a twitch.tv /d D
Tuesdays Tuesday one day before we so
greedy before we send her back the party
did make contact with a very strange
shop in the Underdark
that is in sort of a hollowed-out
stalagmite and it is operated by one
Laurel
and her entourage of surly dwarven
salesmen / bodyguards where car yeah it
windy legs baby wizard no more elder
wizard coming in with the real
techniques now that is I think
everything you need to know in order to
play Dungeons and Dragons whatsit I'm
ready for it slice that's okay well
exactly the situation is that your
parents went away for a week's vacation
now now they left the keys to the brand
new Porsche ah now the question is
reference now the question is would they
mind whose parents well Smith your
parents Oh No Hayley so so you are you
are correct some last-minute shopping
and indeed a substantial amount of coin
was exchanged to assist your new friend
Strix on her way back to whatever she
was trying to manage before and now you
are here with this bizarre tower that
ambulate surround on a weird kind of
massive skeletal hand and moral is here
and I have every faith that she would
sell you something else
what's she got any impenetrable drow
disguises various sizes verse two let's
let's converse let's bring it up here
everybody to I don't want I don't want
salesperson to hear us okay I want to
hear your rat voice by the way are you
all right oh yeah and it is gonna be
that rat from Charlotte's Web wait so
disguises
again I'm still my mask of minifigures
active know for how much longer maybe
another 20 minutes yeah you are just
cloaked yeah okay and you walnut weasel
and you've turned dinar into a small rat
or regular worthless cute rat very very
cute cute right you ever seen good okay
Kurt I do have yeah purchase sort green
red green are smell and it's contagious
its deadly in drought Oh only drought
can get it okay rats can carry disease
along with me yeah we love disease down
here I listen I'm I'm glad we're looking
for better disguises because I have a
feeling that anybody who's not a drow is
just gonna be slaughtered on sight
there's not gonna be a like what brings
you here type of a thing
gotcha this is not like it's not even a
this is the furthest from a hub for the
Underdark it's a backwater town they
don't get a lot of outsiders if any and
they kill what they don't understand so
I can't but let me let me do the talking
first Oh sounds great
what could possibly go wrong I know
these people it's granted I know they're
the culture front it was like from 300
years ago yeah I can hash of the piano
older that would have been smart is this
running monologue why please talk to
everyone
somebody tell me what to say maybe
that's the best way to know this you ask
them for cheese wait no way you know I
could actually go for some cheese too
we'll find out I quit
alright I'm gonna try and keep this
active if anybody has a good thought on
how I should see if they can disguise us
better just just speak up good okay
we just need this guys yeah yeah you
guys are used to secret Adan his person
or on tasties person or on my person
tasty okay
so tasty is just heaped with any beasts
no how are you situated on you how are
you situated on young tasty I wouldn't
yeah he's little I'll jump on you okay
[Music]
like instinctively just yeah I'm just on
top of your head scratch behind the ear
just like well loving nuzzle yeah so
describe for me how young tasty no
obviously that's why you ng yeah on one
hand oh and then on the other hand it's
just ta s T T young test yeah no there's
a - Yuki it's very small though okay
yeah right over the over the show like I
stole like smash just like drape
yourself languidly over that yeah how
are they gonna react to this goblin
that's a good question DM I don't think
that the jar big fans of goblins I think
the plan was for us to March him in like
he's some kind of prisoner sacrifice
sacrifice it's a sacrifice okay yes he
is tasty this is the thing my disguise I
have to rest and then it only lasts for
an hour so I also will be shopping for
something that lasts longer than that
well this shopping montage could count
as a short rest I think well yeah
they're in the shopping montage is going
to be accompanied by the monkeys I'm a
believer okay just be yourself man as a
priestess whoops just a moment do you
have anything that could help us to
infiltrate Hey
our tics that might be in the city by
affording us with some form of disguise
maybe a potion that would allow us to
look different like a like a costume but
as a beverage invisible also works
that's also great what I just thought of
his invisibility if we could do that she
says she says what was your name again
Apgar Apgar
kelan's Anna Trin praise love praise
whoa praise Him her yet but she at that
the praise loss she's like that's not
that's not required it's how we do what
do you know not for you
you know where you are out here I know
inside the walls it's which part of gala
death are you trying to make an entrance
into lower called earth and specifically
the district of cosmic Verve in this
dish mall that she raises an eyebrow and
she says when were you last there I my
duties take me many places but maybe 270
years ago under 71 years ago she says if
you had made lower gala dearth the more
frequent stop I think that you'd
probably know that what was lower gala
death is no longer even within the city
walls interesting I hadn't read that
zoning report
[Music]
tell me more
she says well many of the houses so this
is this a piece of cultural information
that you're aware of that you can inform
the party of at any time right is that
almost as just as a warning to other
houses there are goodness gracious I'm
sorry no I think the cauldron tipped oh
Jesus look at one our went from two to
seven there were that rat action yeah oh
I'm gonna come to you in a second
cauldron so you you know that just from
a cultural perspective as a warning to
people high houses that collapse hmm
people don't like move back into them
they simply remain empty yeah and when
enough of them when that happens to
enough of them the wall is rebuilt
behind them so essentially those places
are are cast out and this is this is new
information to you yeah you know you you
understand the cultural practice right
but what she is telling you is that this
part of town is not part of town about
how long ago did that happen she looks
over at she looks over at some of her
dwarven assistants and one of them makes
a series of quick hand motions she says
about a hundred years ago hmm
finally happened I'm assuming that the I
mean and it gets worse rattles off the
names of a few houses that he remembers
then house Rosalie those are all have
all been no she said Deanna she says
well II might have
to the worst hmm I mean here's what they
said I mean who knows what it who knows
what the truth of it is what they said
was that the rot in house were loosely
was so deep and so poisonous that none
were to be left unchanged what are you
gonna do those those blue hands can't
trust him squeak-squeak I'm like a
drought kid okay no I suppose i I've
told you many times had you studied
you'd remember that what happens to you
when you're naughty drow and loss gets a
very cross and you get transformed into
something that looks like her why would
she do that if she's mad but but you're
not
not if it's force times very bad yes
agreed sorry grandmother all changed
I understand yes I see
good good here so real good do you have
good thing I see her she really good for
anybody who's not dumb like me yeah
what's your performance skill to thrist
drought it's a four plus four okay
I would like you to role performance and
she is going to roll against it indeed I
took exactly right long - okay right so
that's 16 like try again alright so 16
is gonna be it doesn't he
okay she is perhaps you know after
decades assessing people and what they
can deliver in value
she is not you can tell that her canny
clever mind is already beginning to
dismantle this Apgar situation she says
are you having any special connection to
these houses give me a perception roar
okay okay okay oh that's gonna be a
Levin nope that's terrible only and know
we're all drought no but are we all
really drought I mean really don't we
all connected only only that I've been
informed to root out heresy but indeed
but not so well informed that recent
events going so far back as a hundred
years have made it into your notice I
was only given the look precisely is
your purview what's your sect boy this
is where Chris is at a loss but cuz
risks would go armed with some
absolutely yeah absolutely give me a
history check that's gonna be that's
Jack it's gonna be Jack which it wasn't
uh that's gonna be a sixteen that's
perfectly acceptable your able to fish
you you couldn't if somebody asked you
about it later you wouldn't even know
what it was but you're able to act but
you were able to do you were able to
cannily deflect this faint here the
united church of the holy book lung
which is a spider body part i trust that
that is acceptable she's just absolutely
the does the do agents of the
of that sex still have the deep pockets
they were always said to indeed well we
have business to conclude I am going to
why don't you shop for a little bit and
then I'm going to tip my cauldron it's
like I hand over the money
cauldron tip everything explodes I've
already rolled for what's happened it's
really just a matter so what we're
looking for is either something that can
like increase stealth invisibility or or
shape change because I might want my
young drow Ward to appear as a
full-grown adult maybe she'll learn some
lessons that way I'm also dragging tasty
by the way um roughly but secretly
gently and I'm saying rude things to him
but what I would have what I'm doing
with you is shopping for tasty I'm
dragging here in front of stuff and I'm
like duh and then your squeak is either
like one squeak for now - squeaks for
yes if you think he looked cuter than or
whatever yes absolutely but she says I
have come come time is the enemy
she's like I have raiment enough I'd be
happy to throw that in alongside a few
potions that should do the trick every
valuable as the our dogs have been
burned by holy flame same type of hair
see I'm talking about we just came from
shadow town yeah she's she's she's she
was like brushing through the racks
shaking thing shaking spiders out of
clothes she's like yeah those heretics
she's she's moving around back through
and then behind this rack of clothing
she
pulls her hand aside reaches back and
gets out something like a vile base that
she sets out and she has four potions
that all seem to be the same color and
she sets it out there's a so imagine
that imagine that there is a sort of a
nice show floor at the widest roundest
part of the base inside the stalagmite
but it also has windows for people to
approach and so she sets it out on the
sort of on the bar yeah basically and
she says any one of these if consumed
and obviously timing is important and
tasty drags himself away and just
careens through it's like it's like what
it's like if you're of a kid in Kmart
and it's like there's like low hanging
racks of like dresses and like skirts
and pants he's just going straight
through like if the clothes are flipping
up like this he jumps up like in from
the ground to the bar in one hop and
then he grabs one and pops off the top
and downs oh boy and then you hear him
cry out and he'd like punch his over
like until he becomes just like a dark
sphere and then when he stands up and
turns around it is a stunningly handsome
mostly naked drow male that has that has
that like model that specific kind of
model
it isn't that it's just like you it's
like just glass if you can't find the
person in it and it's it's definitely
tasty and the way that he's yeah it's
like it's like whatever is whatever
what's happening before it's like if we
just extend all the ratios whatever
tasties thing was it just wasn't good
for his size hmm he kneels down and
slides off the bar and the pants just
fall to the ground like this is it's
just like male soft served just pulled
straight out just whip up around in the
cup he has been elevated from tasty to
tasteful he's taste folio and so now now
he's he is he's got a new lease he's
just brushing through the clothes
he's demeanors change no no it's just
he's doing whatever he was doing before
there's still like tasteful little nips
but now they are out of the long ears
but now for some reason in this context
yeah yeah just a nipple chain know for
some reason that Antonio no it's there
the asymmetry of the nips out of the ear
is just is it's magnificent I see now it
looks like the whole thing now it looks
like he got into a fight protecting
someone's virtue yeah like it's a
totally different cast
deny are defined its gross he's like I'm
one gross non dragon for Noah no there
it's all the same yeah it was one squeak
for no - squeaks for yes wait this could
change the dynamic of this whole plan -
to cover the prisoner leeward maybe he's
like a traveler by musicians for potions
so as he as he shifted and twisted you
were deposited on the bar but don't
worry I'm gonna give you an opportunity
as he's brushing through he looks over
at the at the bar and he just places his
hand down as a platform I'm like not
looking and also shielding my eyes a
little ha but I you're protecting his
new dig yeah it's he packing yeah he's
moving wait for him to drown I know
exactly what to do it's eight solid
inches for on a cauldron roll a four is
that deep oh shit Oh - fight it Edward
oh now listen I'm panic I'm paying for a
for a physical transformation not like a
politeness add-on yeah I don't care
about the downstairs or these manners we
just need to change the appearance she's
like these these potions as you see
obviously you know that's not free but
if you're going to lower gala dearth
there may be
a bit of business we can arrange Josh
would you please tip Michael groan that
wasn't a Magic Mike potion though she
says Apgar hates Mondays for lack of a
better term it was my aunt's name she
says if you are going there there are a
substantial part of my business is the
result of items from this place I'm
always looking for new stock hmm I would
be quite willing to refund the entire
cost of this purchase if you were to
bring me back things from the high
houses things you think might have value
on the open market even to collectors
you have to understand there are those
who find a kind of delight in their
collapse hmm I have many collectors from
the surface that surface world
are delighted by these turns of fate
even down here in the Underdark hmm well
as you know the money is of no concern
to the holy book loan indeed indeed I do
enjoy this challenge yes well 300 gold
today I'll throw in the raiment of
course everyone loves raymond simple
easily done 70 yeah she says she says
bring me back which you have and there's
every chance you will completely earn
this back thanks Josh
very good little scientist yeah where
you got it are you still in that kind of
coin in that rat oh yeah well we have
enough potions that kid go back we could
we could we can now drink those push
instead of being animals yes nice okay
so do you do that so I turn yes right
here in front of ya so yes I jump out of
tasties hand and then turn back into
walnut wood jump egg in it and I look at
the person like there's also the extra
piece which is that I mean it's before
your time but there was a period of time
where I mean being the NEMA's ear itself
always was imagined to destroy this
people I'm slightly worried about like
it's for mother gonna bug out is
something gonna go weird and then I'm
just trying to excite look over and I
look at Daenerys a rat and we're really
soaking that up for another I know
seconds I'm like I see you turn back in
yourself and I'm like just stand up as a
rabbit I'm just like good still trying
all right
oh I don't know not working transform
and I'd look at Morel and I go oh no you
know dad there's just a wood elf hanging
out yeah and the Underdark now house
moral react to that he said oh don't
pray she says she seems cool yeah I
don't know she seems cool yeah I'm
sitting here about wall yeah she says
you're far from home
yes where how did I get here anyway
thanks are you are you are you on tasty
as shoulders though no no I
okay I'm sure because that's a great
picture well just really slowly is being
like oh how did I get here grabbing one
of the vials and then uncorks it and
then just start stringing it do I turn
into a hot guy no you shift there is
like a decision point after you drink it
she's like like there's instructions
she's like you know in your mind picture
it picture it picture it picture it okay
there's a period of time where you get a
few different walnuts like imagine that
funkopop had a line of walnut toys
[Laughter]
weird-ass fish that like swim sideways
yeah - two eyes on one side I hate it
it's fine some eyes on my nose it's
great but yes that's the situation okay
so there's a clearly a point like you
are plastic right now it means it means
you means that you have to guide this
process apparently this is what taste he
wanted sorry I'm just the only thing I
have for Fraser right now you're
thinking about the therus right now
you're feeling the weight yeah like the
bone structure is not up to the task
gray in this middle period right you're
pleasuring regulation yes I think I
think I'm great great all right so
almost like imagine imagine a like a
bowl of ice cream it's been left on the
counter and imagine the dog just comes
up and just licks it straight up as soon
as you as soon as you picture this gray
Kath RIS
there is just there's just this pressure
that sort of sculpts you forward into
there's the attractive brow gentleman
that we know is good but gray gray but
gray so sucks
terrible
so there is now a drow garbed in EPA
reggae Leah
yikes
well that's gonna contend with that and
maybe I should just turn to gnar back
into himself well I think about what to
do or I'll go from rat to droughts
squeaking my way over to the file so you
your your clever little pause Scrabble
away quark you stick you stick that rat
face right in tip it up can't get it off
it's just going like this just back and
forth this fluid is slowly going down
into the rat that becomes a sort of
puddle of rap imagine just like a hairy
puddle on the ground or on the surface
of the bar now how do you guide this
process
I am i I was gonna say make a clone and
Chris - because it's like I have to do
is the only drow of reference - I mean
dnarnaud is less about this all this
workings than anyone we could be twins
yeah yeah I do I'm better than her right
different color okay yeah blue and gray
what other kind of color is there what's
a better color
yeah what's another normal drought color
well you don't know but what would be a
better color for Denar okay would you
think gold would be like so it's like it
looks like looks exactly like a thrist
but all copper little with that little
or like shiny I'm at like a dull skin
like a like a skin texture Oh gross no
it's that extra little in our chart the
love child of you two of you finally I
know it's nice to see ya and brilliant
white hair okay what helps nice for a
nurse to drop yes yeah Wow
okay I guess I'll drink it
ah and then I go oh I thank you for that
uh uh is that your first impression Oh
God
Rosie throws the hood back and she's
like it's not yours usually durable it's
a Microsoft if I break it then it's mine
true uh Rosie throws the hood back and
she's like this is probably not a huge
surprise so no yeah yep mortified yeah
and I drink it all right the in process
yeah exactly so there's a there's a
there's a period where you have a sort
of like wax and cast right and honestly
the first thing it calls to mind is the
is the shadow shaping moan there's a
period thats I've was able to
communicate to you where it can be
anything and you know you feel like this
is doing something like that okay then
the thing I think that Rosie would do is
just for variety sake make a like a an
old lady version of cthe wrist
essentially like it's the scheudle she
likes old lady and we're all kissing so
I think without discussion she'd be like
well maybe I should I would like not I
wasn't paying attention to her Thornton
and so she it's exactly cthe RIS - the
beard short hair very old gender swap
age swap okay so this is how our Rangers
this is what we've what we've created on
today's episode of this EP is available
in artists alley at Comic Con come get
it
it was probably a ECC this weekend oh
I'm not I look like well no you're out
please exactly you're the weirdo right
Morrill says I
assume you won't be needing one Apgar no
no I suppose not
because this is who I am just like the
rest of your your elite cadre everyone
appears who they are legitimate 100%
what a strange turn that these potions
would just reveal the regular drought
within their previous disguises I'm
hoping you get dressed by the way
picking out Ramon's that everybody loves
holding it up to you but it's all like
kind of revealing oh yeah okay
yeah yeah exactly exactly like the deep
very the very very deep okay so yes yes
she'll take that but she keeps trying to
adjust it and pull it up where are you
boy Catherine Scerri girl kisses okay
your boy you just look like me but great
okay yeah yes you cover yeah and your
copper yes me I'm just a palette swap
and you looks like girl me this is like
if you choose your character and push be
in a state of oh yeah yeah right
yes well the legendary skin yeah I was
I'm not sure what they will do to me
when we get back in there the point was
for nobody to look like first Chris
think what you should have said
something better damn nerds this is the
Underdark
they don't expect anybody here I was an
outcast there you are all gonna die I'm
gonna die first because I'm the only one
who doesn't look
I'm gonna turn back into me I'm gonna
have blue skin they're gonna see
immediately they're gonna where I'm from
they're gonna slaughter me and we can't
afford to buy another potion because
your friend drank it all
I hope that was all inside yeah like I'm
so I'm so I'm I can't move the small
from my face but the thrist is so mad
that even as he's as he's chastising
everybody he's like some vocalizing it
so you saw is audible
oh you can hear the voice in your mind
but his mouth and neck what I'm actually
like I'm whispering it yeah you can
figure it out it keeps sorry time is of
the essence maybe um so we should just
yeah yeah I mean at least we all look
like drone now so moral so moral is not
dumb and it doesn't even require a
substantial role to recognize this and
she says Apgar may we speak may we so
she walks up because you'll recall that
when the cart when her strange cart
first pulled over you could hear her
coming down multiple sets of stairs and
so she just usually she utilizes her
neck to indicate where the two of you
you should be going and it's over toward
the base of one of these stairs you pass
tasty I'm who has finally settled on a
hat it looks like it's like a Robin Hood
style black felt hat with a looks like a
shining silver feather in it where is ya
know it's like a market and heat he is
yes looking he is looking in a silver
mirror and he likes what he sees
everybody does there's nothing else on
it's just a hat it's like a it's like a
like a bachelorette party
basically is happening in here what now
that we're the same species unlike let's
cover this up let's get some some days
off a skirt a long skirt some kind of
wizard
haven't you done enough take this out on
me
he is completely he is completely it'd
be like maybe this experience may not be
universal
occasionally brothers get dressed up by
their sisters yeah and they put up with
it yeah and that's exactly what's
happening here it's just like there's no
beef yeah it's just like whatever
whatever you want him to try on you can
have a stack of stuff and he'll go
through it so in your minds try to
imagine what the final tasty look is
going to be so that you can present it
just like in a TV show and on three will
save at the same time absolutely right
here straight all right now Josh if you
could tip my cauldron please yes I know
it's it's bunkers ville but I gotta go
no scenario I gotta go here moral says
you are a spectacularly poor actor and
this is precisely the sort of place
where not having your wits about you
will get you killed
I have as many things there is a cost
associated with them but I have many
things available in this tower that may
be of assistance myself included I have
no love for these high houses and I am
prepared to help you but it's going to
require that you stop pretending
Thank You Josh just take it off I'd
remove it the mask of many faces I have
no love for these houses either least of
all my own yeah well then you should be
overjoyed to learn that they barely
exist only there were only two things to
come out of this recent interaction
they're any good
what happened to this goblin she
Orient's her her gaze over toward the
stairs and she said yes that was he he
earned some fans with that display
suddenly that's what he was thinking
about before you drank and learning that
my district had been eliminated from the
city border I got the good thing it
makes it makes our work much easier she
says listen my offer still stands you'll
be able to pay for this quest very
simply by handling these tasks but you
need to be far more open if you want to
get the type of advice you're going to
need hmm where should I be didn't well
if it is truly your desire to penetrate
the ruins of the roughly a state you
need to understand that the family their
servants the children were all
transformed they live there still there
the process drives most mad that my kids
first having been from the society may
not be surprised to learn that no no
it's it's it's but you can always it's
not a hundred percent
there are those who there are those who
undergo it
but every every thread of that
experience is tinged with trauma
understood what surely there are others
that you've employed to do this type of
work for you what advice have you
offered them well my father's for lack
of a better term always provide me with
the utmost protection on our raids of
those dilapidated places she says so if
it's not a PR who is it Chris Ruth Lee
this is Jesus Carissa isn't a name no
it's a that's a sentence it's a mockery
of a name it's it's from Childress the
unbelieving Chris
Chris all right so if you are
authentically from rahu loosely what do
you know about the collapse of that
house I only assume that it happened
after the shame of my departure and
apparently my sister and my mother were
unable to restore the house the house is
integrity so it was the sin of disbelief
that began it was it widespread in your
clan no I hope as I was the only one
except part of our undertaking as a
result of the news that my father may
have also been a heretic in the same way
unbeknownst to me when I made my
discovery that caused me to leave she
says I think that I may be able to
provide additional assistance but
halfway through the word assistance
the cart and indeed this stalagmite are
jerked and twisted off of the off of the
platform it kind of tips and lows
outside the hand this bony forearm that
is lashed to the side of this tower has
begun to sort of reach over to you dinar
this is the hand that's yelling yeah so
it's the site of a horse its massive
okay and it is sort of like using its
hand to sort of turn around and it is
sort of reaching a finger out toward you
okay yeah bad it away are you doing your
bad wait wait what are you doing it
flattens out like just despondent no sad
it just flattens itself out against the
ground and then just sort of drums its
fingers weakly all right now I'm ready
for the tasty or tasteful reveal I'm
gonna need you to okay here's what I've
here is what I've been given this is the
very top says sparkly boy is this like a
almost like a veil cap with a fascinator
definitely okay so he is wearing a veil
cap with a fascinator sparkles orbit his
head hmm
he has are these kissy lips definitely
yeah these lips are ready to kiss
anybody who is into kisses it's they're
primed for that exertion if you will the
arms are fully exposed the arms are bare
nom the veins in the arms shapely arms
the veins are pulsing with the exertion
of just maintaining this level of
masculinity
fourarms oh hi masculine blood yeah
exactly is is doing it's doing its work
now this is the other part that's vital
there is a kind of there's a cool sort
of vest the neck has a nice fold over
from the left to the right oh I see yeah
there is a diamond of cleavage window in
the center from which a tuft of deeply
masculine hair not unlike a bird's nest
does emerge and provide warmth and
comfort there is a second diamond window
below that only a few inches where the
bellybutton may be seen the bellybutton
is exposed fully Wow it is 100% prepared
also for birds for whatever yeah it's
mercy he's a walking a year yes exactly
and the pants there ain't much of them
people when it comes to this situation
Rosi bee stinger walnut della grass
thank you so much that solo sparkly boy
oh okay I saw I saw notes going back and
forth I didn't know if this was a
collabo not unlike they have on
deviantART no I was perfect doing this
perfection anyway so the hand is
flattened and now just the index finger
is over and it's just trying to give
just trying to get your cast a little
blank a little affection I don't like
our horse let alone creepy hand course
so I would be like I would just harrumph
shooing them away yeah I'll just on the
on the bony wrist yeah it just turns
away and then balls up it's sad it's sad
your memory about this better witnessing
you her dance feeling I'm you're the one
who likes the horse I don't like these
things like my horse I don't like that
word
okay fine okay so I see this creepy
hamster I was busy trying to see oh no
no you have to you have to
has come and is harassing copper Chris
wants affection from one day that I
refuse to give it oh yeah yeah it's a
bone hand
ah well anything but only Missy desires
affection is gonna get Rosie's goat so
she'll be like Oh hon don't don't worry
about him hi and she reaches down and
tries to pet it like right along the
spine over the hand like so like the
central carpal yeah yeah wherever you
try to reach down it just tries not to
be yeah all right she says she says I
can get you my card is not unknown near
those places mm-hmm I can get you very
near to there you would have our most
appreciation and I can I can deposit you
near the base of the path that leads up
the the the road itself is no longer in
use of course mm-hmm it's outside the
walls and the creatures that live there
aren't the sort that fix roads are
maintained civilizations let's let's be
underway then yeah we're in your debt
yeah yeah she she says yes I'll make a
note of it and she walks down and then
goes down and whistles and the dwarves
immediately stand up make preparations
start moving things that are outside
into the main floor that whoo-whoo it's
the whistles go whoo now that was for a
listen now
so she morale looks over at the bony
mount and says Galit earth and it
doesn't do anything not feeding this
thing gold yeah yeah what's it eat well
what was it or is this what it always
was well it was part of a dragon that I
secured it ponderous expense and now it
is a recalcitrant son of a bitch dragon
hand she said dragon hand guy like wow I
just got it she says gala dearth gala
dearth gala dearth like this way well
that like you were doing before she
sliced your hand I'll go be the hand
whisperer
so you kneeled you kneel down yeah and
again whisper now one hands ear would be
the first knuckle is the ear of the hand
everyone s I get that cross stitched for
the sofa it's vital so right down onto
this knuckle where there's just a that's
just a parchment thin wisp of tendon
holding all of this together the camera
pulls in close and you can see this you
can see this golden drow say right into
that tender knuckle and it immediately
just jumps up into full vigor digs digs
those fingers in yum and morale is not
pleased to have been
to have been outdone but yeah she's also
a very practical woman
and she's made her peace with it in
seconds um she's nothing I can't do I
tell her the best of everything I try
talking to hands turn it into drink
[Laughter]
humility this is kids risk plus yeah so
here's the here's the situation
the that she says she invites everyone
in and up to the top of this spire which
is where it is how it is driven from
place to place
hmm the sitting room yeah exactly on
query how do I turn this off when the
time comes or how long does it cuz I'm
like I don't you got like smooth skin I
know I'm like it's I'm used to scales
and looks like you just went yeah yeah
caress you everything's like examining
each other thank you she says like my
boy in Oakland the nurse fanart that
already happen yeah
terney he'd uh so yeah Table Talk you
know what I mean she says it should be
long enough for you to get what you need
to get done but it'll turn itself off
well turn it so what do you mean by turn
itself no I've turned off back to my
normal form Iraq she already knows she
says she says this is what I can promise
you you won't always look like this
but you may look like this a little
longer than do you intend yours but the
main the main thing is is what I've sold
will definitely do is was requested of
me so there's no wrongdoing on my part
here we go that's that's value for money
even more appreciation customers always
the best kind of accurate that is anyone
hurt
I am so I haven't oh yeah nice picture
yeah I'm still I'm still stung from
Strix is flame house oh yeah you're a
host
yeah I'm not wanting to hound yeah I'm
sitting on 19 okay marvellous Josh if
you could tip my cold wrong c---berkeley
on oh good no I don't know I don't know
what's happening I'm not gonna I'm not
gonna think about it too hard I'm just
gonna roll this dice okay as I redid and
the result that I got on there was heal
so so there's a foot nail just one stab
right in the cornea so as you're all
brought up to the upper deck deck oh
yeah you you've used you pass through a
sort of middle area that has basically
like seven very simple beds around in a
circle and then the sort of staircase
that goes up through the middle the room
beyond this is not like that they're
places is very pragmatic her own place
near the top must be the finest of
everything that has passed through the
shop every now and then she's made her
own selections from the items you see
and so you can you pick up on it
immediately this is like a this is like
a showroom it's like whoo it's like like
rich and like it's like the rich and
famous
Gallagher yeah just like I might even
recognize some like pieces with like
sculptures from various houses yeah yeah
and there are indeed Rahul flee items
here and they're not they're not being
mistreated in any way this is apparently
the best fate available to not be a
commodity to actually go someplace where
there is an affection paid to them yeah
but you can see knives and she has a set
it's almost it's like on a silver tray
there is a fine set of decanters and she
says everyone should fill their water
skins from that it as near as I can tell
it never runs out thank you so upon
utilizing these healing fluids cthe
wrists yeah over the course of this trip
you'll be able to easily get back to
your HP max anyone else who fills their
water skin with it is basically going to
function like a healing potion thanks
Josh and then you forgot the part where
omen messages me back and is like just
kidding I'm mad at you I turned out fine
that also happen to heal my emotion
honestly that's not one of them but now
that I see that this is something that
now that I see this is something that
people desire no no exactly now that now
that we have now that we've actually
gone through and we've used the calls in
a few times there's no reason you can't
put a request I mean the dice the dice
are gonna be what decides this right
through and they'll never roll in my
favor let's be honest no one to get it I
can do it is about here so I'm gonna add
a couple more here yeah weird yeah don't
ask for shit no so that is that is the
scenario
I want to examine the the these trinkets
absolutely go right ahead
yeah what's the nature of the I mean I'm
surrounded on all sides by them so I
assume they are they randomly placed for
the like true collections where it's
just not about their their like their
beauty but more like this is this house
this is from this oh yeah it's not by
function okay yeah it's not by function
she has done everything she can to
maintain just coherence by house her her
collection seems to include more roughly
blue hand items it could be because
they're easier to get she's been there
several times so I'm seeing like there
were various like social campaigns
during the houses run just try to
rehabilitate or position the house as
you know going concern well know as a
positive thing that the house itself
would have been attempting to psyche
where are we so bad you know
branding no no we're the most pious yeah
there's our piety dish it's negative
commemorative yeah yeah what am I do I
see anything's like from my like that I
would recognize as like what do they
have anything of the children of their
things maybe one that might be my own
there's only a the only thing that you
can see that would probably be for
someone younger is a lookingglass mm-hmm
may I ask may I may I handle them these
where's she is she is she is looking out
there's windows her like almost like a
like a Nautilus style like portals
around the top and she has it opened and
she sort of clicks out the window
she makes different types of noises and
you can feel the contraption sort of
subtly moving down there
without looking back into the room she
says I don't think there's anyone left
to be angry at you then I then I will
pick the the looking-glass up and and
turn it over I don't think it was mine
but I don't remember what my sister
might have owned yeah yeah and I
certainly don't know I never met any
other children from my house I'm gonna
roll for a motion and she I press f to
pay respects just like it kind of goes
on the top of the hair when introduced
up tomorrow
he said thrist at me yeah okay okay yeah
she provided a safe context for that do
you want to be caught up in it let's
assume that I go right ahead
yeah for the purpose for the sake of the
party wanting to know why now we're
riding what is this acceptable yeah
catch us up on our interaction and also
why I've dropped my disguise okay yeah
and I and I explained the name to you as
well there is roughly yeah who's your
real name mm-hm but I hadn't been called
that I've only been called that in a
place that I wanted to leave behind
right so so now we've pieced together
that your name your house your house is
now gone we didn't we didn't have all
the pieces before yes in in game we do
now we understand and you you've
explained to us but but they're all
probably dry ters at this point I would
yeah and I would also add that our house
is a very fresh our house our house was
never high and on the totem pole in
Calder's but it's
it had a lot of problems one of which
being that as far as I know there was
only ever one female ever produced by
our mother and I was not thought of very
highly but they had seemed to have
crawled their way up to some position of
respectability at which point I escaped
and I only assumed that that caused them
as moral said the opinion of the house
to plummet that I would even be able to
escape and you you escaped because so
you were so hated that the whole town
ruined your house and your neighborhood
oh I wasn't hated apparently my father
was also not the most pious loss
adherent which is why he was destroyed
yeah we were our house was hated because
we this goes way back we our complexion
isn't a common drow one and it didn't
help that our house wasn't particularly
religious despite what my mom wanted us
to be seen as so how do I feel about
copper bad probably everybody they don't
like blue and that's close to dark and
charcoal color covers way opposite I do
start shaving do I look like you all
this hair could I get a procession check
from twat yeah you can't my bad
imagine I said bitch the first one it's
time I may be in a dark age that's
20 that's me thank you so you're just
sort of just looking around through this
every now and then you need to stop
tasty from or tasteful from knocking
something over interacting with it like
it's just it's not like he's not used to
being this tall and so he's not he
doesn't really get it in a lot of ways
and he said you've been taught for a
long time I'm not used to being this
tall either yeah but he he's had very
drastic yeah it's been a it's yeah it's
been a rough road some of us have had a
pretty drastic burger for me but yes
you're acknowledging but you started out
you started out more on your game than
tasty which is the key and so tasty is
about to knock over crystal goblet yep
off of a nope so I would love it if you
could catch it oh yeah how do we feel
that ethics athletics could be okay I
prefer acrobatics okay slide a hand okay
acrobatics yeah you really want to
ecstasy okay literally can't afford
womp-womp-womp shadow council merely was
pleasing your servant wallet undress Hey
and so the first boom is actually these
super cool copper d6 set I think of them
as being vaguely dinara themed we will
ship those out to you it's fine but they
were all super good you'll be very very
pleased to own them now you are able to
catch it yes like liquid like nut drop
spills yeah but you'd but you do notice
a you do notice like a like a oily
smudge hmm
around the base of it as you
you pick it up you feel like some of the
texture on it is wrong and you pull your
hand out and this something kind of rubs
off on your fingers can I do in nature
or survival do I know is it organic do I
know what this is texture check texture
yeah absolutely use do you think it's
it's it's some kind of a oil and pigment
it's like a it's like a paint can I
picked up any one he could not be blue
Oh what colors and paint it's dark it's
dark okay
there she yeah she's still like clicking
at the window guiding her weird dragon
hand locomotion mechanism
um and I get the sense that it was just
here or did it come from tasty you don't
know okay it's just something you
noticed cuz you had a great roll and you
also cut it like it's fucking champ well
I'm gonna show I'm gonna show that's
Rosie I go swear uh and I can I sniff it
yeah it was it's not like let's just
just it smells like some kind of a
natural fat some kind of a natural
rendered fat and some kind of pigment in
there okay so there's but we don't see
any paint cans in here or anything you
don't okay Missy yeah I was expected
more from quite than neurotic growl
saying maybe ask moral I tell you I'm
like I got nothing like that's a
question for her probably today can I
see what they're doing
yeah yeah just put your put your heads
together yeah I look over there and I'm
like oh I'm already over there no I know
I have to actively go yes
what is this let me see anything
coverings it's not ours
what is it don't touch anything is what
it is defined as that is the only thing
you need to know about it
what is it is it is it morals color what
color is her skin it is more you mean
like that is this subsoil it's yeah it's
dark it's it's the traditional well yeah
I know it's the traditional like it
would if it makes sense it gets the
right shade of tone it's like a makeup
who's this a whole bucket we're just a
little no it's just a smudge on the
crystal goblet as though someone who is
covered in it maybe took a drink a
minute maybe we should play it cool with
that yeah let's keep that information in
our back pocket it's none of our some of
our business yeah really
so who are we to judge literally yeah us
look right I'll say you were despised
because you're a blue how often did that
happen in the drow community are there
other color variants no I know right
pretty much it I think okay I just want
to make sure I understand this Chris are
you are you doing the tasty fan art yeah
I'm using what case what Kate Drew he's
doing but better I'm gonna try and like
can I bring it to life it's looking real
nice this is a really realm of fantasy
and I just went grounded I support you
and under proven it's in our business it
doesn't belong to us
leave it alone we're in a lot trouble
already
yeah when did I become the sensible one
still not not ever seen you affecting
our quest yeah yeah
so from this from the window to the wall
Wow no no the sweat no no yep my orbs
down stop at my talent here no so the
cauldron yeah so you can see
sort of heavy smoke that is gathered
over the city between the top of the
city and the ceiling that basically the
caverns ceiling of the Underdark
hmm and you've seen this east approach
and you know it well you know it better
than any of the other approaches and the
place where there would have been lights
is completely gutted but you can see
around the edge farther down the main
road as soon as it continues west around
the front of the city itself
which sort of occupies a kind of stone
rise you can see that lights exist sort
of everywhere around it but there's just
this conspicuous void absence directly
and basically directly in front and she
is she is pulling up to and clicking
furiously out the window down at the at
the claw to sort of bring the thing to a
stop but it takes a bit it doesn't
really turn on a dime there's a lot of
just mechanical complexities that make
it difficult oh you know for a animated
hand for the DeLorean we're not fine
parts yeah exactly
dragons I guess but it's a classic
dragon Lorien but the way that it is the
way that it functions is that she stops
and then she is also looking out over
this place as well and she says this is
your stop the closer you've gotten to
the town now there are other carts you
know to the right as she sort of pulled
off there's really there really isn't
traffic going to this mmm
haunted ass forgotten part of this of
this city they've rebuilt the wall
specifically to keep it out
but there is an opportunity to go from
the shadow of this contraption into the
ruin and wreckage of that without
attracting a lot of attention from the
rest of the trade traffic that's begun
to thicken outside the city with my
knowledge of this like D annexing of
districts the reclamation reclamation do
what would the reaction be if they saw
like a torchlight like like movement or
something would the city assume it's
just more scavenging well yes exactly
okay um I mean you know and that's and
that is the to become commodified is the
actual punishment mmm there's no there's
no word in in there's no word to make it
a crime to rob from a dead house yeah if
we keep our lights out it's to avoid
attracting what's living there now not
because I'm worried the city's gonna
descend on us imagine that it's a mine
that's all they think of it as mm-hmm
okay yeah I'm I'm looking out the window
longer than I thought I would I thought
I would be a lot more ready to get this
done with yeah well but I say let's
let's get what we need and be as
stealthy as we possibly can and you've
just shared all of this background
information with us your real name and
yeah that's your house and so this is
all kind of an intense the person that
we thought we knew is not the person
that he is so this is this is all
revelatory and Rosie goes are you sure
are you are you okay are you ready to do
this what I'm feeling will pass its
chemical it's just
the a mechanism that this vessel is it's
a it's a remnant of some evolution that
is okay no I want to watch this show so
bad I want to add to that that is that I
am like it's theirs I'm tearing up in
there yeah it's it's really yes yes and
that is neither a comfort nor negative
to me hand on the shoulder and looking
at his face because I mean they have to
do we're good to do the same thing with
which one you go there you go to me I'm
like no and just give him like a silent
but knowing look yeah brofist no never
no Jerry no multi-row between
attentative friends what do you do to
reassure I say let's go pillage your
family home and I look at morale and I
say keep the hand running yeah and then
from that I'm able to like push down
yeah yeah and then proceed so you're
able to eject yourself from the shadowed
side of her bizarre the Howl's Moving
Castle craziness you know and it is and
you're basically your feet are touching
the ground it's this soft mixture of
like just like loam and spores it's like
slightly spongy and as your
being away from it and you're you're
moving away from the cart expertly you
have done it 100% the best that you
possibly can and that is when the hand
turns and then begins to try to follow
Denar into the city the shadow council
mayor Labor's please you this is the
break this is an incredible opportunity
to drain all of your organs of any
fluids that you don't need right now
come back to us refreshed will be here
momentarily may lemon
so what hello I'm Geoffrey K where K and
this is the C team I'm asking star
heroes emotional moments they had gone
with the assistance of their new friend
Morel coal bluff in her strange
contraption they had been taken directly
to the savaged remains of lower gala
dearth a place where high houses at high
houses had once dwelt but they had
through time treachery in action
collapsed to entropic forces what had
happened just before the break was that
they had stealthily escaped the cart and
then we're going to move into the ruins
of lore gala death when the tower itself
that they had used to get here developed
and then expressed a deep affection for
dinner Blitzen yeah which is now someone
reciprocated yeah it's another I know if
there's a Ragan yeah and it's a so
basically it's like a pet yeah except
the pet is a massive stalagmite um on a
cart yeah it is now while trying to
drive itself into these spun into the
spongy ground of these ruins well this
won't be
draw eyes so we don't want them fine I'm
following us she's doing a lot for us so
no we don't need to pull a record yeah
you got a waiting here boy
we'll be right back movie cheetah we
have to say goodbye to the cheetah and
yeah it's a homeward bound yeah hey I
it's okay I exactly like this is like
beat for beat AI well yeah yeah that's
the that's the spine yeah there's only
one story in Western literature no
everything moving Stanley Kubrick Big
Finish
it's every every story is just a
narration of may I know if anything this
is ice might show I like it I was try to
figure out a way to get see in there
Benton work yeah so it sort of flattens
out a little bit and then it sort of
inches up on his fingers and then it
reaches out yeah and wraps its fingers
around you and just picks you up and
hugs you in midair and just gently sways
you back and forth this is and then and
then sets you down on the ground and
Pat's you a couple times
and then it turns and you see the tower
crawl away oh I want to know what color
dragon know what yeah used to be I have
some affinity there I sure pride more
yeah it's to the bone we shouldn't you
know with her where she got it from yeah
well yeah well we got a redeemer
sidequest right yeah they find her again
oh yeah you can establish that we get
her again she's waiting yeah okay how
much of a town okay who does not have
dark vision is it just you do we have
dark vision because of the potions it
doesn't it doesn't grant it if you if
you don't have it
you're not noticing any it's just facade
right yeah I assume what my stats from
normal is still the same strength I know
okay Rosie will cast our vision on dinar
she's the same height as you know so she
yes I go to duck down cuz I'm shorter
now than I'm used to yeah every time go
through doorways I'm ducking what I
don't have to wait there's a ton of
clearance yeah yeah what is the what is
the layout that we can see like how
close did did we get dropped off so you
are you are a little bit into what would
have been I mean it sort of bumped a
couple times over what you think might
have been an outer wall at one point
mm-hmm
what do I remember of the town because
what I'd love to do is go to some of my
favorite old haunts let's check out see
if the bull is he still a golden boy I
want I want to give us the straightest
possible shot without having like the
minimal amount of navigating the this
ruin a straight line to the house oh do
we have particulars on what she
requested as well um I mean you could
think back to the things that she seemed
to prize most mmm okay as of the types
of things she yeah so the what what
seemed to guide her interests as far as
her her own quarters was concerned was
the sort of the trappings of daily life
okay okay so no it wasn't like like the
Grail like oh no but nobody's but then
but then down below you had a chance to
see the other types of things and
clearly she does trade and other types
of artifacts and as well okay
I assume that once we let's do the
important part first okay it's worth the
money later so you are trying your
goddamnedest to map the place that you
knew on to this shattered substrate
right you're trying to figure out like
you're trying to map streets but the
what would have constituted a street you
is shredded and picked up and spread
hither and yon it's been a long time
walls building since it's more than time
it's it's more than just the passage of
time there is like I said it's these
places are damned
and they reassert it and every day it
gets reasserted that there it is no
longer of the drought I would love to do
an hour can of check and see if I sense
any of my own like like the earth and
its presence in the air well go ahead
and do an hour kind of check let me give
it a try I'll take some yeah some so
business so that's gonna be a 14 rolled
up so yeah Maris please you
your servant Chris drought has offered
to a boon now the second one is of
course the cool Elderwood Academy mini
dice box with the mini dice inside you
would be well-pleased on it we will ship
that out to you soon
now um you don't so you are focusing
your your will and your awareness
through that lets ants do an old an old
favorite I want to I want to get ligado
yeah I want to work him in and lays him
up in the palm of my hand as you know as
though he was a compass needle and then
fixed the the symbol of the ER in my
mind and see if but what which direction
it might drag me you do not find the ER
but you recall the the icon that was
given to you by Carver gall right
outside the city of Alcazar and it is
like a small version like the roadside
gift shop version of your own or focus
mmm and so as you're holding him up
there and focusing deeply lagari has
bent his little head down out of the
staff and he is good at your satchel hmm
good point
old friend I'm gonna I had the ride look
I had the wrong one
fool so yeah I'm gonna hold that one
aloft
so you so you hold that one and it knows
precisely where to go it's just it just
it just goes out in front almost like a
like a sleepwalker
mhm and it just holds itself out in in
front of you with a kind of but with a
momentum and then awareness we all good
to follow my my cool toy yeah your town
yeah is it as the crow flies yeah so
it's like okay yeah that should you see
you still have to it's not turn by turn
no no Lou gaw t it's just all of a
sudden it's like a british woman's voice
turn right no so you are you have this
in your hand and you can even you don't
even need to grip it like you can how
you can hold it like just like around
your ring finger gently and it is so
enthusiastic about the nearness of what
it represents that it will just hang and
tug in midair mmm what we have this we
don't want to be seen
penetrate oh yeah roadie can't see shit
in here so she's just kind of like it's
just like the hand is on that yeah
she's got her hands on walnut Karissa
the shoulders oh yeah pass it up trace
and Plus tend to still throw this
delicious all right so that that thick
cool cloak of shadows descends over the
party so science gone too far
[Laughter]
so you are pulled around sheets of
crumbling wall you're clambering over
what were once houses and shops and
Smith's that that also necessarily
collapsed underneath the Molly oh the
year-to-year fortunes of these high
houses they lost everything as well you
know when they no longer had the
protection of the city so you are being
so you're just you're basically wherever
it's going you're following it right
yeah I'm thankful because this is a
place I've actively tried to forget as
much of it as I can
no trace of it is here and it was good
I'm now that this thing is taking us in
the direction I'm I'm glad I don't have
to probe my mind and see if I remember
anything I don't want to stir anything
more up no but no yeah repress those
memories
that's what's healthy so so you are and
so you this this thought is coursing
through your mind the idea that that a
lot of the painful memories that would
have been attached to a specific turn
more a specific
shop or cul-de-sac it's not possible
like the annihilation has made it
impossible to have that experience and
so you are letting it guide you like a
thousand rulers yes thank you of course
cuz first job everybody that's yeah like
a magic stick like a water magic stick
to Rousey
ya know so you are you are just letting
it guide you just like a stray dog
through this place in that place and it
following its instructions you find
yourself pulled into something like a
dead-end cul-de-sac where you think that
it might have been a square at one point
here racking your brain to to figure out
where it might have been right but at
some point you think I mean just idly in
your mind you think they must have tried
to there must have been a period of time
when the place was collapsing when it
had been cast out where they tried to do
the best they could to reconfigure their
right to reconfigure their space into a
kind of defense ability so this place
that was once an open square is now
shattered fountain where the opposite
road is completely full of rubble to a
height of 30 or 40 feet
it's just shattered building this it's
basically like a bowl and as you look up
and around you can hear you can hear
heavy sharp footfalls in the remains of
these buildings that surround this
square and as you look up you can even
hear that you can even hear the you hear
these heavy Falls which you also hear
the clink and slide of metal plates and
so in looking up into the windows you
can
to see violet eyes blinking in these
spaces and it is then that over this 30
40 foot mass a black wake of dry ders
massive hideous human spider hybrids Oh
driven mad by the process of their
transformation they've begun to come
down and as they do rocks and stones are
following them and a kind of avalanche
that is filling the air with dust
historically speaking in Dungeons and
Dragons this has been the time yes Rosie
Basinger knows exactly what I'm talking
about
this is initiative ladies gentlemen
every conceivable coordinate in between
what I get to go first I never cease
duty this is it I got a 2100 shoot well
20 minus 119 it's a natural 20 and it's
very very good it's so good and they and
they rolled nasty so they are way way
back
awesome I'm really excited about this
some yeah yeah so they are coming in how
many drivers guys know there are four
okay and coming in I do say - okay three
alike do you want us to fight here a run
like are these do you recommend me
members there were yeah oh if they were
whether or not they're family members we
would I would spare them but fight or
wrong so regardless of their family or
not you want us to kill well my
knowledge of the writers is not that
like this is not a parlay scenario this
is not me it's like a wait I was what
you were and let's be friends that's not
the case I could try to figure out we
don't run away I'm saying didn't believe
if you didn't want to know you think
just looking around knowing this type of
terrain mm-hmm you try to imagine a
scenario where you can escape but this
is basically a nest right like the
year-by-year this place has been
converted into it's been terraformed
into what is perfect for dry ders yeah
of anything we need to display of
strength we need to show them that they
leave us alone
this cursors try to recognize any of
these traders faces or just try not to
uh no I want to figure it out I want to
see um would it be enough to what's the
mechanic here to like hold right I don't
want to go first yeah I wanted but I
didn't want to dif different systems
interpret like how you do that in
different ways I the way that I do it is
in it obviously it's so easy with these
things that Clues made me or that pieces
of paper I can put you in here wherever
you want to you can actively choose a
lower one if you want I'm not gonna make
I'm not gonna you rolled here you earned
it but I can give you a shittier one if
that's what you want let's let me use my
turn if it's even necessary to to I want
that I want to discern these dry ders I
want to see what I know of them I'm
looking at there
can I see there they fashioned this
armor do I
recognize faces I don't recognize have
they changed so much that I don't know
it's it would be it would be hard to
tell they have a there generally there's
a you know in a word they're maddened
right like it's milky eyes I think in
some cases maybe one eye that has vision
jaws hung open just active columns of
drool mm-hmm
it it it's approaching each of them and
in some different way but you can
absolutely see regalia of different
houses no ok so it's but as far as I
know they've met a cobbled that together
or maybe there it's still there all in
it it's not clear no okay
in that case I would love would you do
how many of them I kind of catching the
ferry fire um as they're pouring as
they're pouring over yeah we got one
that's gonna be coming out of this
wrecked Warren and then we have three
that are coming directly over yeah they
have Warren G okay it's so you can
easily the maximal usage is gonna be
these three here okay let me go ahead
and and drop that on them all on the
floor absolutely okay now we can see so
ferry fire so you're gonna grant some
advantage we're up against please okay
sounds good I like what I'm seeing here
now what light color do they not like
the most bright lights in general okay
well I can only it's a dim light but I
mean I get to choose the color and big
city as they can't stand them I like I
like blue Thank You blue for my house
yeah yeah take that boy back okay that's
all
I love it blufor fire exactly so tell me
how the party is arrayed here we have
these three coming over the hill coming
down we have one in this building to the
right how is the party situated here is
this like the classic book cover
scenario are you sort of all facing the
darkness and before you find that well
find that drawing because I'm in the
front yeah but then you're also in the
back and the middle right now yeah well
when you say like we have a little mini
conversation before the battle starts
right absolutely
are you cool with me fucking these yeah
and you're like we need a demonstration
of strength and it's like all right I'll
take the one in the middle I won't make
a demonstration of strength
demonstrate yeah all right I don't know
that they could be there I'm gonna say
things to us it's the one in the
building
attacking arrange or anything no no that
you can see okay I mean there are there
there are all numbers they you you think
they kill people here a lot you feel
like it's a really good place to do this
okay so we have advantage on all of them
now you advantage on the three that are
coming down the one that's in the house
is not I guess I'll try to send all of
them the mega beef yeah so that's gonna
be so the three that are raining down
Dragic coming to get us yeah I'll move
toward them uni and due to course of
attacks and to martial arts attacks and
I will add stuns so it's this is this is
that intro like right right when you
come into the restaurant yeah okay yeah
so you're everybody's getting some yep
it's grandma's buffet
yeah actually yeah I should probably do
some uh some gravy man see now it seems
like a really good time yeah you're
gonna serve them up all right forget I
said anything
I always say everybody's tired just then
okay so I will hey can I use to groom
Aziz at the same time but tell me what
you're trying to do the function the
function of it is really gated by two
charges but tell me something rad and we
can discuss it okay now the the grandma
man see the shadow stuff that I make
does now
do any damage but it is it can interact
right you can make something physical
yeah yes so I think what I'd like to do
is try to entangle these three ferry
fired ones with routes of shadow but
then also behind us create an image of a
gigantic black spider - to make I don't
know if these are even intimidated will
because they are so crazy but if there
if there is anything that they're afraid
of it would be the creature that caused
them to suffer this fate so that's gonna
be but try to stop them at the same time
produce approximately what I feel like
love my present herself as mmm-hmm okay
so we have advantage on them you are
basically going to try to hold them in
place as well okay then yeah then what
we'll do is we'll add will add damage if
you hit okay great so that's that's my
turn yeah yeah this is you you drawing
this out now do you utilize any of the
any of the wisdom that you got from
scythe Oh
like decision isn't does it and is it
inflected at all by the new skills
you've learned so he was able to teach
me how to form my staff into something
incredible so probably what that staff
which is female I'm ahead what she does
is she she is the one that that leaves
me to become this giant spider so the
staff of the master it's like yeah and
then vanishes behind me and as it as it
kind of like slides out of my hands it's
growing all the legs and coming coming
to be this like super nasty lots of
noise but it's that thing they do were
they rear up yeah yeah it's gross and
then and then just right on the bulbous
abdomen the staff of the master like a
bright sigil oh yeah right
love it right I like what I'm seeing
here fine delicious use of the product
walnut on grass yeah inheritor of the
mysteries of the EPA
how will you increase joy oh yeah I'm
going to sing this do flaming what is
that house spider there's one of them
house
oh okay I mean I had a fucking thing
going no that's fine
sorry well I guess what whisper
something to her and is gonna drop a big
green flaming sphere a what a green beer
on the three yeah but it's important
that you know that I'm casting this at a
third level so I would damage it be
increased by 1 d6 thang they make a oh
it's a it's a so maybe it'll just link
two of them trying to land it between to
the 5 foot diameter you can catch -
alright - and they need to make
dexterity saving yes they do but you
will not surprise you to learn that
they're real real good they're they're
they're not in a good spot I just want I
just thought it was funny like they're
very very dexterous but there's no
question that they get disadvantage for
that ok hell yeah
Oh wah-wah-wah-wah-wah
shadow council may my Labor's please you
grace saved Ryder out did ya did you
know that oh here but the next one is
that the next one is the one yeah that's
that classic time we're rolling one of
them saves it's just half I mean and
yeah he gets half damnit no and you can
please add whatever add one more die of
whatever you're using for third level or
fur yeah well I don't know oh yeah I'm
just saying because we have advantage
and because she has gripped them yeah
I'm just gonna have you add one Gary
Goodridge yeah
[Music]
so 11 yahooza another one yeah just a
little yeah that's easy because then
that one just takes six so look at that
yeah thanks just 12 divided by 2 right
there no sing around like RC car Oh a
ball oh yes can we ball how long does it
stick around when you move the sphere
you can direct it up over barrier across
Pitts it ignites flammable objects and
shed the bright light and a 20-foot
radius they hate that
oh that's right oh right is very very
good cuz there was a big whore of a buck
that's right is this gonna affect us
being a jump in an attack though is this
in the way at all for us of two of them
yeah of two of them just don't hit those
so we're going to do a dex check the one
that's not hit by that I don't I don't
think that she has designed this in a
way to make it difficult for you to okay
attack them
well I remember her before but I there
was like a ceiling ball that was coming
down there was it was like this yeah
denier blitz in hopefully you can do a
lot of damage because they have a lot
I'm gonna take advantage on everything
forever first before you start is there
any combat use of your alts it's it's
dominating something that can be I mean
I can yell at one of them to do what I
want but it doesn't feel as I can also
kill a bunch of them with my sword and
feels like this true of four enemies if
there was one that was an obvious leader
no there's not one that's like leading
the pack that I could their crazy pants
the one in the house it makes sense yeah
you tap him for management yeah seems
smart I'll just kill the three of them
does win this against it just seems
easier a lot of yeah alright so we
already have advantage on all of them
and they all have disadvantage
no so it's like do I can I even spend
for advantage all right well here's what
happens
oh we all stab with our weapons at the
same time at the same wound and all our
swords and and barbed implements just
get chilled right before does any damage
at all so I'll I will what I'll do is
target the I guess someone that's hurt
the most
I'm gonna come in with a thunderous
smite as a bonus action so if I hit with
a melee attack I'm gonna do extra damage
then melee Mullane Oh melee Mario and
then I'm gonna go after that guy first
I'm also taking great weapon master so
yeah this is no we're rolling for people
to get prizes that's what do you say
yeah it's a 17 yeah that's right and
that's a 10 so 17 17 yes no no we have
natural revenge rolling well I get two
attacks so thank goodness
yeah a little higher than 17 yeah
also flavor-wise I hang looking like a
thrice pull this sword out I just scream
a battle cry as I run in there but it
comes out I like boy so it's like yeah
it's like I need better so that's a 19
okay and that's it was almost like I can
trying that real I like it okay all
right well I didn't with a 17 I don't
take this for granted all right so here
we go now comes the fun big guys
yeah no whammies 10 automatics so it's
10 plus 2d 6 plus 3 that's 9 10 11 12 so
22 plus 2d 6 Thunder damage for the
smite ooh
8 jeez so that's 30 he has
make a strength save or ease push back
ten feet does that kill it no strain
save ya
oh yeah it sucks can I direct connector
direct that ten I can when I'm hitting
him I can pick the direction okay let's
let's say that it's let's say that it's
like that um like that classic samurai
style engagement
yeah that's mostly about positioning so
I wanna my flavor on this is I go in
swing hard and crazy thrown off because
I'm not myself and I'm doing yeah with
the Chris on yeah yeah and then I get my
wits catch him the second time if
they're in a line of three and the two
are the one that got hit I want to hit
this outside guy back into the ball back
into his buddies I want to smack these
guys all Tigers but I want to hit him I
want him back towards that ball with
with that push see I like it yeah yeah
you can choose to ten feet if you want
to I do
so what's he so he hit it I'm gonna
smack him back into that ball so and
then windy want to get all that D on him
that's 46 it was the first time any
creature that ends its turn within five
feet of the sphere so be at the end of
it the end of its turn okay yeah okay
okay so it knows a big heap of spider
yeah there's a spider ball I mean I know
at least knock him in that direction
oh yeah yeah and you on top of him no
how do you you definitely made an
impression on his carapace
so that is dinar blitz ends turn now the
bad guys go
you see tastiest with bad guys so there
is this agent was a bad crap all over
the back you did know there is there
smoking taste follow yeah but there's
this dryer off on the side that is just
sort of observing these events as they
come down and tasty just without
hesitation you
is running up this rubble and then goes
into a lower window in the same
structure and you see him disappear into
the oh the darkness so grave Leroy
Jenkins and all over this thing great
no it's gettin it's gettin jacked kid
let's see I need to roll for my cauldron
now so let's so these Striders these
riders are finding it crazy they begin
to immediately lash out at the closest
most delicious targets mmm
in this case obviously two throws well
well yes another Catherine's right
exactly um so first a cruel a cruel
woman atop this spider body just bid
decked in sliding steel plate just
starts to bring down just a rain of
razor-sharp claws and sword blows oh boy
oh no oh yeah they're having a bad day
okay what's your AC sixteen okay miss
with the longsword sixteen yeah miss
with the second longsword Oh No so so
these so it's just like everywhere you
go there is one of these legs coming
down it is like it is it is you know
that it would be easier if you were
Rosi bee stinger mm-hmm you know that
you'd be able to just dance around this
as it stands you're having to contend
with having like fully twice the target
size these are coming down so that the
sword goes one way the sword goes
another way and you're you're getting
out and Rosie would not have been hit by
this attack so the sword is basicly in a
cross in front and then as you try to
sort of pirouette and turn out of the
way she brings her mouth like her teeth
come down and clamp into your shoulder
hmm in such a way that you you can't you
can't physically pull yourself away from
her got the pouch yo you're gonna get
pout okay don't you don't help me bro
yeah you take one point so it's like the
flesh part of the wound you can feel the
things like the top and bottom of the
things connect inside the meat of your
shoulder and then a second later it
feels like a fire is running through
that wound and then all up and down the
right side of your body begins to spasm
in agony that's nine more points okay
jeez Oh am i poisoned this just poisoned
damage you do not get the poisoned
properties okay no which is good for you
the other two are going after the much
the oddly colored cthe wrists drab your
Dec is massive as I recall 18 yeah so
two sword slices are amiss more misses
it's just swinging madly its jaw just
hanging open sort of swinging slowly
back and forth
and it reaches down and tries to swipe
for a bite as well swinging with the
sword
oh man I got it this all right here that
was a 19 and a 21 womp womp womp Thanks
shout counsel me relievers please you oh
so that one's gonna connect with this
savage bite just right on the side of
your face yeah just like my beautiful
face bites into the chief I'm like no
you are able to secure a hot
eight points of damage uh no okay so I'm
not I guess I'm not poison I can't be
poisoned yeah I can't so does that mean
I don't take the damage right no you
take the poison too much this doesn't
seem that's a regular I'm here to tell
you right now flavor is that whatever
biological immunities you might have
developed in this surface not biological
it's it's divine it's from God oh it's
sweet holy Lord yeah yeah your holy Lord
has no place in the underdog no you guys
dead from the from the window to the
wall arrows whistle out toward dinar ah
it's only a sixteen yeah so just a hail
of like three arrows three separate
black barbed arrows are flung out of
this window just above where tasty
walked in he betrayed me yeah who's
doing that yeah exactly
I don't have bow and arrows now exactly
so in interesting okay Josh if you could
please be so kind as to tip my called
what what is happening oh heck
what is life you did life
no no no I can't even use them this is
like some Gift of the Magi as I had
suggested previously this was this seems
as though it was the it was a urban
space once a place of high society that
had been converted into a defensible
maybe even a last stand situation right
and you can see just up this rubble into
the left there is a flat portion what
was perhaps once maybe the top floor of
a building now the rest of it having
been sheared away it's just a kind of
platform and you can see a ballista
positioned up you know still still
attached hinged ready to operate you
think you think that you may be able to
give you may be able to figure out how
to leverage it and you you utilize this
this moment to tell your allies about it
thank you so much Jeff mmm Oh list
explains at all okay that was pretty
great good night
so Chris first row go for that ballista
no wait let's see I mean it's up to you
I mean you can you have many many
options at your disposal
these things are implacable the lips you
know the terrifying thing about them is
that you know it's not personal
oh yeah see they're not conscious of it
they're just an informant they're just
animals in torment yeah I'm sad for them
I mean that seems like the wrong
reaction to have wouldn't being
slaughtered by them potentially I'm
sighs just feel sorry for you is I'm
just ruined I'm gonna drop some
[Music]
tentacles yeah in this space which kind
the spectacular Oakland this particular
variety are there any other kind yes
oh let's see here so what's the oh I
just I didn't what I had one quick
question so if that guy is hitting me or
did any of them end in the ball still
they couldn't move right so they all
took that ball damage oh yeah oh
absolutely
cuz they ended their turning the ball
damage is 3d sex very nice mm-hmm
this text says you know what here as an
added value terminator I will use these
dice no just music medium dice sound
well so people have to do damage oh no
no no no never gets to see the day these
are mine yeah all these 20s even here um
there are rolling oh god okay no no this
is this is gonna be quite a good gift
for the person who gets them okay this
is way over average okay yeah that's a
healthy supply of damage they're less
healthy but yeah absolutely I was trying
to use it and environmental no love
there's possible there's yeah they're
like that there's just a black smoke
yeah before he drops the tentacular may
I suggest for the pleasure of the diem
that we discussed the possibility of
doing a group combo attack this has been
this has been your fantasy for ages
right yeah you want to try to combine oh
it's the tie because it's to the top of
the round we'll just all burn our turn
yeah dinar yell at us so good that we
get inspired to do these red shadow
beasts with tentacles coming out of yes
yes so I dominate the team yeah into all
alting at the same time yeah yeah or
like a general your yeah your dominate
could probably be used on like the guy
that we can't get to right Lena could to
fire on yeah but but acting is the
general how would he dominated by dinar
but I wish that it were
we all chose to give up our turns so
evil so basically a reign of evil shadow
creatures from which evil tentacles
burst oh I'm not mad at it Q being it
yeah what kind of creatures would well
not summon down here for forest friends
like bats okay okay cool
flying foxes that's phat bombs and you
would give grant them some kind of like
tentacle lashes coming out of their
mouths or their wings or hugs how that
work that squid slime BAFF squid well if
I remember right I mean I don't know
it'd be alive anymore at that point but
we could have them sort of dive bomb
yeah that's what I was thinking yeah so
we get those bats mm-hmm I popped my
coals out of those while they're headed
for OC and I just think the ultimate
yeah I was thinking have the bats dive
in have them drop with the shadow spikes
hitting so they're hitting for damage
and then they impact and die and then as
they die I guess you're designing them
yeah that's how it goes according today
well like yeah as like rather I don't
care about the dry ders but if you if I
see you thinking about those forest
friends I'm like on all the pets to be
rats
well not understand things need to fall
in babbling well so these are under dark
things that walnuts why Amy said okay
yankin you can blame you can blame deny
yeah Rosie will use shadow to like mount
almost like jousting just yeah like
shadow Lance's it'll all be like these
bats are coming in but they have these
sharp shadow Lance's coming out of their
chests thumbtacks yeah exactly so it's
gonna hurt just how is this communicated
in
like how does it work oh no no no this
is all Denard do you need to hear about
like role play flavor oh no no this is
all denial because it's actually the
combo actually comes from you yeah
establishing the domination and then
iterating everyone played like basically
popping all of the alts at the same time
in a specific configuration yeah let's
see it dinar well that's I guess that's
what it would be like I feel generally
sort of thing like I just said he was
the eyes would glow super gold and super
gold yeah just that gold beams emitting
from his head and he would just assess
the situation and then just be like you
make bets
don't tell me what your thought your
eyes are shining and like through it
it's so potent it's kind of piercing the
potion like the the mask I can see the
outline of dinar beneath it oh yeah and
then tonight as they come in if you like
give um shadow armor spikes I'm like no
yeah green lantern little suits of armor
yeah but it's light like like they it's
fine because the you the shadow stuff
that you that you in fold them in yeah
so Brenna got a snack the other night
I'm probably get right back to it it was
like it was they were called chocolate
enrobed strawberries oh yeah right and
so I think that it's like do you in robe
them in shadow
delicious shadow that and its hinge
again it's hinged and perfect all their
wings this is like a peachy right this
is like a peachy and then and then as
they impact turns to you and go
tentacles what are you guys doing
I mean whatever this all works out -
yeah and then what this is gonna have to
be a massive amount of damage yeah and
oh no it's it's it's really you all you
have to be like incredibly pissed at me
hijacked your body's also this last four
hours so oh my god oh the dogs that the
dummy that we had was ten minutes yeah
yeah this is the dominate that you get
from the go if it was at the eighth
level it's eight hours so it it happens
people okay it happen happens like
they're these these flying foxes these
massive war bats are coming straight
down shrieking silently as they get
close like the armor just pops the armor
just like pops and goes free and then
just all this all this spiky shadow
steel it's just piling up on them and
then as they get as they get close that
is when I mean it almost look like
there's a like a Cthulhu vien cast that
as they get close just these it looks
like an evil papaya or something
they just vomited over a dark papaya and
that emerges into midair and then in
midair becomes itself this massive
central star like a sea star surrounded
by lashing jam whips that fall in and
collapse on these already burning
spiders the best ever but these these
things that they have thrown up and then
immediately flown away to safety the
they are just sort of like
writhing in place like they have a
relationship to physicality that is
distinct they can be where they want and
then work and operate so they are they
are taking this place they are taking
this place apart these three foes are
now actively bleeding from all-new from
innumerable wounds they are in an
incredibly bad spot they are going to
reach out and try to touch someone but
something I put something in here and
specifically designed to test you okay
it is a really good thing that you did
what you did
let's put it that way so but this the
shadow substrate that was a part of this
process has now been sort of ground up
and abraded by this bizarre first strike
and so they are using what is left of
their energy womp womp womp womp they're
using what is left of their energy to
leap on you Rosie with that 20 so that's
the that's the longsword they have
disadvantage they're entangled by
shadows we've still yet these
protections are abraded as I suggested
so eight damage from the longsword okay
boy that's the second longsword cruel
and deadly misses other cooed riders
come over for Big Daddy Denar mm-hmm
twelve is not sufficient 13 is not
sufficient 11 is not sufficient so they
are just you can't even tell where that
exactly you can't tell which one of
these is coming at you it's just a it is
just like a single organism this is all
angry legs and swords
got in their own way so they so they
have tried to two of them have tried
unsuccessfully to crush you under six
attacks none of which have connected or
if they do they've only glanced two
shots oh this is nice okay so 7.6 about
7 points of damage you know finds its
mark in a a tiny sliver of space between
your armor crush and then and then once
it once it hits a second later do you
feel just a pulse of fiery pain lid now
from the wound for another three damage
and then you hear you hear a like a
stifled maddened cry from the window and
then you see tasty now come to the
window and he snaps a longbow friends
that is all I have time for it no no
what what what saw a cauldron again here
good God here alright no I got it oh no
this is this is why I have a cauldron
now some of these could be very bad
let's see what did you get
what is that X with that this X is that
good I mean the church what's the good
one we got another tasty
Josh can you tip the cauldron please
yeah I got sorry there is a thin wake of
pebbles that begin to roll down the top
of this mound of wreckage and cresting
this Hill is ad writer whose raiment is
still that of a priestess of wolf oh no
and we will see what she gets up to oh
no game shadow Council
thank you so much gotta be your fucking
it has been a real real good time I hope
you've enjoyed it hope you've enjoyed
these cool lights thank you for letting
me push great thank you for let me push
the buttons too many times really
appreciated hey don't go nowhere
we're gonna go try the facilities and
then we're gonna come back and talk
about the game for a while
don't don't miss it we'll see you soon
you