time is the enemy of the past it
threatens the fastest weapon you
wouldn't make it past a second and
answer the question play it brash and
reckless to choose a cautious solution
you saw was prudent in any sepulcher
poker to don't become the putrid it's
that well said I pursue in no mountain
too steep for dungeon too deep to send
expendable marks up to the top of the
peak of beneath they see Yugi they come
like sharks to it while I swim in that
money bill like Carl Barks through it so
send your National Parks drew it I'll
send him home in a natural box with a
close tie the most of the parts included
save your breath for a cleric confessor
death is a lesson that life is attending
professor but if you're seeking my
official advice sign on the dotted line
and this should the choice was the best
in sync I'll get viruses I don't care
slime lairs Grill was great
hello we don't advocate piracy
I'm Tycho Brahe hey if penny okay
impacts I am also a mini fests hair word
run CEO of acquisitions incorporated but
today Jared K Hawkins I'm here to play a
game Dungeons &amp; Dragons with my friends
at Becca maze on meet the aggressive we
address how she wanna Rudy to my right
Dragonborn narcissist yeah dinar blitz n
yeah to the right of my right wrapping
the natural world walnut dawn grass we
are talking and we'll just I am each
other the sound effect of an eagle
crying
how does what's the anglicisation Inc
that's you what is what is PR car wow
you're tearing this show apart yeah Amy
I talk about anime yeah we know in our
chest to my left not your grandma's
grandma except in those rare cases where
she is your grandma's grandma
rosy bee stinger Oh Oh audience
participation then what and then just
like what
oh whoa here we go segments that's once
a player to the left of my left emerging
as though from a mist shroud cthe RIS
drought now cthe wrist wrap can you
deliver something in a sort of like a
movie trailer
sort of presentation I want I want the
crowd the gathered throng this is for
the podcast indeed this is something
appreciate this richness because this
this is going to be an erotic Lea
charged podcast the one you want to save
this one to local device time is the
enemy the past the threatens it's that
hey you know what here's this is the
problem I encountered at Australia oh I
lost my voice I would go down because
that's how you think of doing it I
better drop my voice down right I don't
have to I just have to use my actual way
drop if I go down don't drop it and then
just give us something that is
calibrated to make this experience
textured and sensual in a person no this
is what I was born to do howdy how are
you enjoying my rotating satin bed it's
not real sad I'm transported try I'm a
woman exhibit rice Wow
there goes my here so you pervert this
is what's going on we've obviously the
launch pad for this show was a truly
erotic look at imagine if you will an
erotic salad bar type
that's I can what my hands no whip well
we'll discuss why the night a glass
people talk to me we're gonna start go
start the game soon
I don't know 100% win that's what it's
good clothes I said we're close to them
that I will yeah is that yeah right
there
it's the yuk-yuk Hut yeah so when last
we saw our heroes they had at long last
with the help of morale cola and her
bizarre stalagmite cart they had
basically gone into the very fringe of
the ruins of lower gallon earth which is
a drought enclave in the city of gala
death where during a process then the
party came to understand was called the
reclamation all of these high houses
were basically left for the Underdark to
ravage and they simply moved the wall of
the city farther in what's more we also
learned that the entirety of kethry
Straub's high house Catherine who we now
know to be Thrissur huth Lee was changed
converted into a type of of maddened not
necessarily just without intellect but
certainly maddened by the process of
being converted into ad writer which is
like a spider centaur I mean feel lack
of a better term it's a spider ass yeah
and then like a person front 100% of
centaurs are hot yeah even the ones that
are horse on top human on the bottom
it's called a minute or how much hold on
a second how much more so Jack how much
force is on top basically the whole
thing and then it's just like one foot
foot tip to taint horse yeah and then
think about that horse and then the one
leg descends into
clavicle and then that's the human body
Anthony it's just there's a whole body
for a leg okay yeah I don't know I feel
like you thought about this too much
so what occurred but as the party began
to adventure through these ruins just
absolutely shattered vision of what must
have been drow finery three centuries
before was that the city itself had
become a battleground in the last days
of its attempt to remain sane and the
party found themselves in what had been
a public square that looked to have been
converted into some kind of last stand
for the gentry of this culture so riders
pressed themselves down onto the party
there was a lot of fighting I would say
there was a truly incredible usage of
the super abilities that combined
everybody's goodies into a single
delectable offering flaky crust
baked throughout and what occurred at
the very very end when the cauldron
tipped again shockingly was that a new
foe sort of crept to the top of this
Ridge just behind the at this point
truly ravaged dried er foes but she
appeared to have some measure of her
intellect intact and what's more she was
robed in the raiment of a priestess of
wolf if he were not a hundred percent
familiar with all of this nerd shit let
me give you the basics loaf is bad bad
news
she is the sort of arachnid divinity
base of them the model matriarch of the
entire drought culture
functionally speaking and she's bad news
so what I'd like to do here now that we
have a new entry in here is I would like
to get a new initiative role from
everybody I would like to take advantage
on my initiative today on your
initiative wouldn't you you're it weird
listen you're a bold individual and I
respect it
damn see that's why 22:22 very very
healthy how about you big dragon boy
seventeen eighteen minus one indeed now
Rosa furred KB stinger the last episode
and saw you last with a 20
I know it was delicious now Christy
Ronnie to me yeah I know well what's
your dick sturdy uh tax less three no oh
yeah you're right
sorry what is your dexterity right very
high plus six sorry if my basis plus
three
here's this best five no one's plus six
yeah okay cool I'll just use that to tie
break on the initiative now let's see
where this gathered brows wrong
Oh whomp whomp here here here no Alyssa
come back here just come back here
verified gonna see it yes okay here
beyond the veil and non-stop look at all
look at his dumb when I look at my own
womp-womp-womp I say we're fighting next
shadow council may my Labor's please you
the person who gets choose in there the
first one is the is the dice box from
eliwood right Alyssa is this correct
yeah I did it I remember there's no
guarantee honestly that's the first one
next up we have this lapis set a full-on
fucking lapis set and and with mystic
pendant that's the next one but what
this means is that they are rolling
real real nice no they're coming I'm
very excited do not eat a slap no no
Kate we have we have to give these away
they're not to eat lap it up thank you
my favorite Steven universe now so sure
at the at the apex of this this ruined
heap of stone essentially like the it's
like if you put a culture into some kind
of an industrial blending apparatus it's
just a heap of failed initiatives at the
apex of this there is the woman that has
has risen to this is gazing down upon
this battlefield that she's only come
into half way and she is looking both at
her ravaged fellows here at the front
but she is also taking in the party and
she is made still by it
she's her eyes are passing from one to
thrist drab to another and in various
unkind well yeah in various modes and
palettes and presentational stratagems
and she says how many times must I kill
you
so yes the very the very first thing she
does is raise her right hand toward the
you know here in this middle dark
portion toward the more distant but
still visible cave ceiling of the
Underdark
and as she does so you can you imagine
for a moment that you see this hideous
dark icon of the Spider Queen herself
and as she does so you can see the
increasingly ragged riders below her you
can see some of these wounds closed and
some of the black occur that had been
flowing so freely begin to cease hmm so
I have to roll a massive heap of d8
don't look back here you monster hmm you
monster child me yes you I will and I
would never you just did but shit did
now that is her faces passive as she
uses this divine magic to knit the
wounds of her fellows next up is walnut
dawn grass so I look at her and then I
see what's happening and I think this
shit's gotta stop this this is garbage
and I point at her and when I point out
our a silvery beam of pale light shines
down on her five-foot radius
I'll find B mundo say what is this
this is Moonbeam Moonbeam at the third
level so you know I get to do 3d10 but
first I would love a con saving throw
from her go ahead try it
I was real
being beat it and can't you say yeah
what'd you get 15 it's 15 shoot at 14
plus 1 all right so so we get to do you
think up numbers reasonable man 13 can
you at least and it's it's half yeah if
she did her safe 13 round it up
delicious no.6 why are you laughing
no I was thinking about something know
what I heard funny Chuck that I heard it
wasn't about this chicken vending
machine and see him at the chicken beam
that we've all know about it's really
important I'll tell it during table time
I would appreciate it if you did not do
that all right
why are you writing so much you like an
apple back there the head to do math
okay it's that's there's some math back
here it's like it's that person anyway
that girl actually missed my whole turn
Rosie beasting yeah okay what you got
so we got three writers and a priestess
out here one of the building has been
presumably tasteful oh no yeah the one
in the building as near as you can tell
has had a tasteful experience tasty it's
it's like a photograph it's it's almost
like a like an under dark it's like the
certainly imagine if you will like a
dark gift shop yeah yeah yeah we imagine
that there's like like tchotchkes and
mementos imagine that there is like an
incredibly strong and attractive drow
yes his hands sort of on the on the sill
of the window yes just looking out not
really at the fight just looking at
amazing yeah the under mysterious the
under winds yeah yeah yeah who knows
whence they come drinking a diet coke
super refreshing I think how many of
these are very fired currently I do not
remember it would have been the the
cluster the three it's the ones out see
the ones I was gonna ask the same thing
about the ball was that stood as they
still in play no cuz I did something
else okay
that was constitutional okay it's
official okay so then I will attack the
ferry fired once absolutely because
they're ready don't have dark vision get
well done
hello I will do two melee attacks on the
one whatever is closest to me and then
distribute my martial arts appropriately
yeah
that's a 25 healthy young 24 good God
Rosie that's always a 1 what so lucky
I'm lucky and I am gonna reroll it Oh 23
oh and a 17 17 is no-go
ok but there's a mess as they say of
damage did you say that I'm also going
to empower my 3 that hit with stunning
strikes so actually I'll just do the
first and the third cuz I'm doing two
quarter staff attacks on the one of them
and then stunning with a punch that the
second so we'll see how this goes and I
am gonna use a d8 this time cuz I know
how to play Dungeons and Dragons so the
first one's gonna take 5 9 5 14 points
of damage honey bunches of oats and be
stunned unless they can do a con save 13
Oviatt healthy that's fine okay and then
the second one will take 8 points of
kick damage right to the right to the
sack web sack right is a bulb and then
also has to do a con saber piece fun
well that's a one ok so that so the
second one is 100% ok so we got two
they're not stunned a third one that is
stunned and not a priestess out there
doing her crazy shit yeah ok you heard
okay
that was Rosie bee stinger
what's the kethry strobe situation so
Katherine is studying this this new
figure can he recognize who this person
might have been oh you think it's the
spitting image of your mother like
there's no like it doesn't take any
labor at all mama not like the labor
that she went through birthing new I'd
highly doubt that no I don't know what
she did during that drugged to the gills
yeah
epidural had an epidural we should draw
eggs yeah I thought pretty sure they do
now born in dungeons from dragons as far
as I know I'm going to wordlessly hex my
my mother looked like mm-hmm Hank sir so
I always wanted you made it this way
it's not my fault
um who's Kate yeah Wow
I'm back here okay Rosie didn't see that
all right I can go behind the veil then
pop my head out again I need some sort
of notification though what is this
Thursday in state council what is the
status of the the three that you so as
far as I know these are all fairy fired
and that's very fair wears off after two
rounds and then one of them is stunned
okay just one and your mom's I'm just
living life she's just enjoying her he's
a bird it's fine well I don't like that
that makes me unhappy she should have
gone the whole way so I think what I'm
gonna do is drop as soon as I find out
what the what the what the radius is I
want to look at hunger of Adar for those
of you on the podcast Catherine is
salting the Player's Handbook which
isn't offering available for purchase
from Wizards of the coast no no it's
baby wizard situation it's like Travis
consulting use uber play King's Quest
six air today gone tomorrow yes of
course exactly what you mean he's a
magic map man I can't do that owls voice
I wish I could be pretty good not at
this point so um tell me how close is
the is mama spider to those other three
she is probably 15 feet behind them
higher up on the ridge perfect okay so
then I will Center hunger of Adar on her
it is a 20-foot radius blackness a
bitter cold so you're gonna get it's my
body my feelings toward my mother who
and she's going to enjoy that uh well in
Freudian we're gonna run them all yeah
yeah okay yeah let's do that
and that's concentration okay all right
understood
so it's very cold the effect it she's
hungry it's a cold zone and it's a
hungry being lashed with milky tentacles
the only milk I would sup this night
look okay any creature that starts at
Stern in the area takes to d6 cold
damage any creature that ends its turn
in the area must succeed on a dexterity
saving throat they're good at that or
take 2d6 acid damage whoa yeah yeah so
you basically like terraform a portion
of the Underdark
into some malevolent alien terrain that
wet space that was an incredibly good
turn you Kate all those fuckers nice
work cuz Eversole is very upset that
she's here okay right
wait can you can you give me 286 Owen
and I'll apply it to these
forgive me these special friends enemies
do we need to worry about that going in
for an attack or any think we do
everyday probably affects Renzi too you
know alright so here's to d6 let's do
this for her and then she gets a hex as
well mhm
here's that yeah what is that uh yeah
see and then the other friends just tq6
you enjoy that nice as a nine who else
if too much anymore 6/10 yo son now roll
like you usually do for me are you right
in there
yeah alright and such was my upset I
didn't pay attention I'm getting
thinking about it it's a sick modest
it's the number of the beast so you take
damage if you start your turn there and
you need to make a deck save or take
another to d6 so it's just cold and acid
yeah it's it's cold when you're not
getting smacked with tentacle yeah but
when you are you're like all thing
goodness this isn't cold
no it's acid it's too hot and it's how
it's the wrong thing to great taste
there's no such thing as comfort it's
certainly not given out by hunger
evanora no no
so dinar blitz in that's the situation
you see before you
yeah is that all of these foes are now
in this sort of like shoulder-height
forest of riding wet tendrils yeah I was
oh that's true it is difficult terrain
that's gonna say yeah cuz I was gonna go
in for some wackadoo but now I guess
I'll use my only ranged attack a hat so
Allah Allah the goblins oh so long ago
if they're in a line and they're
constrained so they can't really so I
can line these guys up pretty good and
then I'll get as close as possible
without getting into the damaged area
mm-hmm
and go what's your range on mm-hmm
five by thirty nice so you know so I can
I don't have to get near it
you might quite well here
so yeah acid bomb a little bit a little
bit a little ya know and see I'm trying
to keep it he's a gentleman today yeah
dialed in miss me with that shit miss me
with that a little nozzle can we say I
have enough control over this to
intentionally miss you
I will adjudicate that after we deal
with the initial damage all enemies hit
on a field say t8 convoy Oh Dex a
fourteen eighty six five nine no they
did not do well nine nine is very good
nine / / oh hang on a second why don't
we why don't we get a dexterity save
from you
I'll take advantage so it on for you if
you're able to succeed on the deck save
yeah I'm gonna say that you are able
that you've seen this fucking
presentation enough times winded up yeah
you see the frills I need oh boy a d6
yeah let's talk about fun makes me
whatever fun I think you drama oh right
so dinar Blitzen you have done your acid
yeah and it's gone quite well nine nine
for Saipan yeah sometime I feel like
we're just get a real quick check and
everybody's get points real quick
15:49 gosh 36 I'm 39 I healed up okay I
think I did looks good then looks good
seems healthy honestly no smell exactly
um don't be Josh would you be so kind as
to tip my call already
now listen you started this shit with
your yum-yum Hut and now I'm going to
taste guys that's the joke yeah grab a
spoon
after fully taking in the this affair
almost almost just casually as though
she is simply taking a piece from a
board and moving it somewhere else a
host of white spiders that you are
confident have never seen the Sun their
abdomens have a kind of polychromatic
sheen on them and they immediately reach
down and this carpet of them slides down
the rubble and begins to contend with
that tendrils and tentacles of the
hunger of Adar actively warring with
them battling with them sinking their
fangs into the tendrils until the
tendrils shudder and lie limp and
ultimately they are able to contend
absolutely with that with that zone of
damage thanks Josh so dang is right
because we're just we're just getting
started here baloney
so yeah
blue crap so all different means you can
choose and you chose Bologna yeah
so all the salami so the drivers are not
even even this being said the drivers
are not in what I would call a great
place right now but with what is left of
these riders they are going to start
swiping at the party so Rosie because
you are available mm-hmm
[Music]
18 Wow that does it okay oh man
it's not good that is a five points of
damage okay and then after after slicing
with the sword when the sword comes back
the the dryer is placed both of its
hands for the second attack oh and it is
not able to do this one this this the
the blade sort of cracks and drags
through the ground and it leans forward
lightning quick to do a bite almost
every night that is a nineteen hit would
that be like that's three points of
damage and then immediately and then
immediately you know this well it's you
and you've learned to brace yourself for
it just a split second after the things
pierce the skin hot fire
they spits hot fire it's a mixtape yes
here's my mixtape you know check out
myself
check out my soundcloud yeah but it's
essentially like underneath all the
sanctified robes it's found this way to
cause pain okay so there's this there's
seven points on top of the oh okay okay
well I'm down to zero now okay
that's why
that's baby won't be the first time I've
done this show now that the other two
turn their attentions toward dinar blitz
in swinging with a one and A two
oh we might be good here at 2219
yeah it's great it's great for you they
had to moot well they had if they're
coming over to me then they had to move
away from you cuz I was at a distance
sure because I hit when was that range
attack oh yeah but they have good move
and I'm gonna say and it's easy for them
to get around here she's clear yeah yeah
yeah yeah it's like if you're dead right
yeah four points from the initial bite
and an additional six from the poison
yeah the last one basically like you're
trying to bear the weight of this
massive creature bears now know that
should hit 18 what yay today yes serious
all right
I was like crap alright a civt nice its
way 10 points of damage
oh okay well better be strong now more
than ever 36 oh yeah you're on the human
decks I'm fix pay now are you he'll just
put this away then
oh you're yelling that's right yeah
exactly if you learn well not done grass
more important don't heal walnut grass
and your health I'm just curious
oh you've been touched I have not been
touched and I cannot be touched and I
cannot be killed
it's the difficult terrain scone right
it is able to go in there and do exactly
it's a battle between tentacles and
spiders and no one won so I look and I
see
Rosi fall to the ground and I yell Oh
grandmother and then when I do
that's my healing word for you tender I
know I'm gonna blow a third-level slot
to do this too so that's um 3d for real
juice that's seven
damn so it's five six seven one seven
fourteen fourteen okay so if if she
heals me while I'm down I'm prone but
I'm yeah okay yeah exactly you're ready
great you're ready to work love it
14 points thank you exactly so that was
that was walnuts turn hey our minds in I
don't need you that's right that was so
that was walnuts turn she reaches out
cries this word out and then you you
basically come to just like the last few
moments of pain from the burning poison
leaving your body it's it's it's pain
leaving the body is that what it is what
is it pain weakness pain there we go
buddy here we go I'm sorry no pain no
gain
yeah so since Pope so next up I don't
know is that a thing listen its body is
Julia Child's what's her name yet pain
chef Lee Jane Andrews no it still each
hats Julie Andrews soul meets body what
thank you anyway
so basically that's that's it like you
are you are you are ready to work and do
you have a reason to be angry basically
yeah yeah so these are these the the
ones that are in front of you that the
phalanx here that's keeping people away
from the priestess is not in good shape
that's one stunned
it was incredibly short okay one of them
just one of the three normal-dry ders I
think them easier to hit what's that
what's the effect yes advantage but you
already had that from very far so they
can't do shit against us yeah they're
not good at Yaddo hit auto imprint
essentially okay yeah they're not good
at if you're stunned you're not good at
certain types of saving throws
yeah okay no to me oh no it's no it's Oh
Rosie's jeez ya know Rosie's punching in
okay but I think she's ready to start
her shift I have to use my move action
to get up god I do that and where are
how close are these pools there yeah
there's there is one right in front of
you and the other two have decided to
turn their attentions to dinar blitz in
um I'm going to I'm going to use grandma
man see they already so they are ferry
fire so we get attack on them we had
advantage on that on attacks on them one
of them is stunned until now at the end
of the string there one stunned but I
think what I want to do is use grandma
Mansi to obscure and engulf this
priestess dry up top
yeah me how tell me you tell me more
because this this could be ballin yeah I
think right especially with the new
things you learned from scythe like this
might be fucking sick yeah so I think
from from where I'm at I I give a thumbs
up to my girl walnut and then with my
other hand I want to throw the staff of
the master while you you leading
appropriately and that is going to I
think what I want is for it to form a
cube around a cube of Darkness mm-hmm
around this dried er and part of that
too is going to hopefully if the bottom
of it would grab her by her eight little
feet and and sort of suck just imprison
her climb into the basis of it a prison
that she can't see out of nor can she
move yeah target people from yeah yeah
pull that off I like all of that okay so
plan the exact like imprisoned in a dark
flan yeah exactly
it devilishly delicious so tell me tell
me about this
details that I need to know about this
cube I mean I can picture that part of
it is there any is there anything about
this that is going to be unique to your
presentation of this prison I think that
this is what's unique about this
particular incarnation is that there are
hints of the night sky in oh in the
depths of the shadow yeah and there's
that's not something that you see in the
Underdark no maybe that's always been
the case with Rosie's shadow but we've
always been outside before so maybe it's
not but the the thick walls of it for
the first time you can you can see space
than the end the sky yeah it's not
comforting darkness for them no no no no
it's terror it's gonna be a agoraphobia
like everything that they ate the
reverse of absolutely so you have you
have captured her in this kind of star
box yes and you can hear a sound that is
not like a voice okay inside of it that
is Rosie because first row you're also
playing Dungeons and Dragons so I see
this happen no I can't target her either
no she's not visible she's in there okay
you and if you were to look at me or you
you see me like staring the place where
she was and I am whispering some
dissonant things I know that if I had it
all queued up and I did I see that cube
form around her and I snap out of it I'm
angry that that is not gonna come to
pass at the time you're okay and might
well be who else's who else has so
you've got somebody near you
yeah yeah absolutely and then there's
two targets over by a dinar Blitzen yeah
I think the one near me is the one has
just become unstuck but it's still very
fired oh I see I see over in the window
Rosie as you seeing your dark song and
manifest this prison tasteful is just
good does spare a wink for taste
shoot bonus action hmm let me go ahead
and try something something new all
right I think I've done already once
let me um target the guy in front of you
and I'm going to whip Lagasse out as a
step slam him on the ground I'm gonna
told the dead no yikes told it did what
does that do is the door he's the dead
ringing it rings Freeview that was like
coffin just told you collect yes
you told them extol the dead and he is
injured is that right oh so he's got a
beat a wisdom of 15 does he can't handle
it seems different he does not in this
case he gets out I lovely if he's
already injured then I roll is quite
injured in an eye roll a TD took off -
deitrick God what if he was not injured
then it's a 2d 8 whoo so this is good
for softening yeah it's gonna get you
almost it's gonna it's gonna really open
the pores really there's just trash roll
oh my God my God hates me he'd got
double one civil 102 on a 2d 12 are you
sure that's not a 7 you know that's all
yes it's a 1 that's a 1 then here's the
other one can you just blow all your
charges well I want to try and figure
out a way to work this in this story ok
yeah yeah yeah it told it dead yeah okay
in my mind I'm with force slamming this
staff into the ground and sending those
reverberations into this foe but yeah
nope oh no I was gonna say like in my
mind it's like pow and now anybody
looking at me though I'm it looks like a
tantrum I'm just going oh
Oh see you wouldn't have wanted your mom
to see that that's like a thrift route
I'm just gonna take that he's gonna do
it like that man I really hoped it was a
seven I guess that because you know
sometimes once again they got that
little tiny look uh no idea live it over
it was 12 every side should add 13 so
that's how you know who throws in a
weird place right now and I don't think
this is at all uncommon yeah yeah
there's somebody mom's here yeah yeah
weird that your game for the first time
and yeah trying to hit that home run
Denard Blitzen
okay so the status of these three bad
are they are they all still very fired
and no one's stunned anymore I'm just
trying to find a weekend no one's done
easiest target no instant and if you
were to look at their status or just can
I get a visual cue when the bleeding one
the other yeah yeah
one of them is actually like pulled the
drop down down to its complicated place
well that's who I go after yeah uh
seeing a teammate go down and come back
go down for a minute would you know
incense Denari be like oh no ah revenge
in the midst of working to a fury or
back up and say okay still sort of mad
yeah you guys here kind of Benjy as well
then Jeschke sorry they're still very
funny just burn advantage there's two of
them on you right now yeah and they are
still glowing okay all right so they'll
see Lee flame I'll go further though
with a weaker one yeah that's it too so
I don't want that that's a ten
so sixteen no yeah so that's not gonna
hit all right an attack number dos
mm-hmm I'll give it the old college try
that's another two that's the number of
the beast hey dad it's a good role but
it's not this for a rule that does
reward the show counsel know it's close
though that's a 19 so you can get going
over I didn't I was gonna great was her
master and I didn't because I was like
sure I had someone so so here we go into
the depths sorry
2d6 +35 get three roll to a one got to
keep that I went down
that's six plus I will then
smite and as well level three let's
fight
level two oh sorry six plus three nine
nothing
yeah 19 I'm not done nine kills the
target no all right then I won't play
yeah I mean but then I get an extra
attack because he died yes do you really
yeah an extra attack my kill someone so
here's so here's so here's that so I
mean tell me about this attack like are
the are the are the sharp nibbly bits
coming into this or this will be because
the first one was a miss the first ones
a miss
so it's blade side yeah miss stop come
back by T sign catch that saw through
and now going after the other blade side
again perfect it's like a dry dirt or so
styler yeah there's like it's friend no
no way it's like it's like a like a
serving platter gross and you know what
let's just go for the beste for it we
will do great weapon master on this it's
a get I only get +1 better he vanish
come on 18 19 19 is right got him let's
just roll again see if I can get that
that double damage of a 20 battle
council 19 again all right close all
right so plus 10 automatically then to
e6 plus three so I'm gonna write all
this down cuz there's a lot of damage up
this guy x2 ones so we'll reroll those
real quick okay it's fine we're all
friends here and that's five you killed
it I think you that burns my bonus
action at that third attack is usually
so go through it a team of spiders wanna
be cool
who wouldn't be cool what's so cool I'm
not saying like I'm talking like just
like a weed whacker with a sword it's
going in a society of laws now so I love
this there's the miss come back with the
sharp bits I want a head slice back
straight off of the reverse two of them
two of them are now on the ground in
multiple pieces
imagine a dark lunchable right
compartmentalised yeah I like to imagine
after I kill the second one there's
pieces of him on the sword and as I'm
killing the other one it's just they're
mixed again yeah oh yeah there's like
the arm of the other one is like inside
man I want to go it's a male long all
right now
Denard Woodson has gone we are back up
to the top and there is one who still
hates rosy be stinger sir they can hate
though exactly both what's the money
pilot but both both hands now say this
hitter can see you know hands now are
both hands now on this blade sir
oh yeah with the two hands it's a
different time eight points yeah what is
your role for a co19 yes no I I felt
confident in that
the next sword slash doesn't work and
the bite just comes down like on the
necklace oh just like and you can you
can you can feel something running over
the necklace and onto the onto your
Raymond nasty venom and you can you can
see what looks like cracks forming in
this sort of infinitely deep stellar
prison at the top of this hill Oh
walnut don't grass there's cracks in the
thing there appear to be cracks forming
in it
yeah imagine like a like a like a glass
crystal or something amazing I would
like to do it my girl who sorry because
that you're reading my mind I would like
to use for shrooms
yeah you have some friends too
under dark fire ants never to go in
through the cracks and eff with that
that lady oh yeah and you know they all
bite at once that's the thing about
firing that's one I'm gonna fill the
prison though yeah that's one thing you
gotta you gotta know is there a way that
I can spend one of my charges and this
is a new thing I'm proposing now to to
juice just a little bit of juice onto
her well here allow me Patterson well
you guys you go next okay so is it
something that you can do on your turn
generally speaking generally speaking
the points get used that way yeah all I
was saying all I was gonna suggest is
since since we have so many of these
charges no yeah yeah wonderful yes we
use what a goose it I just want to goose
it a little bit like just give them a
little shadowy trails come on other
butts or something yeah we're like when
they bite they like shouting venom seal
the cracks
yeah just oh yeah yeah yeah maybe but
maybe when they go in they help they can
like into a kind of hive there are mud
fire ants
what will when your turn rolls around we
will invest ourselves in this control
okay and as it stands now you can see
that like a window a portal has been
like shipped out of the solid shadow and
you can see just a an avalanche of blows
from the legs mm-hmm trying to widen it
and as it does so a river of
bioluminescent ants begin to emerge from
every this this heap maybe a
nest for all you know they're coming
from absolutely everywhere yes until the
box is glowing with them and so they are
pouring straight into the box now okay
sounds like you're putting your leaf oh
yeah yeah more chips and chunks are
flying out from the front of this but
there's no there's no way to get out
because there is an additional wall made
entirely out of incredibly angry ants
but you bite a chip he's very tired and
that's hey OCP stinger yeah
it's your turn okay so you want if you
want to try to work you can you can just
keep you can just keep working I'm just
gonna keep working how do you want to do
I don't have a staff anymore so I may as
well just keep manipulating this shadow
this is very cool I would read this book
thank you like I would read it I would
read half of the second book until I got
tired of it yeah but I wouldn't but that
first one is like very good it's like I
don't know about every chapter is like a
different character it's like I can't
keep track of it but the first book was
good I don't know what you referred to
so I would like to spend however many
charges you adjudicate will be
appropriate I want to to juice the dance
and juices and seal them up inside like
a sim the male person in the sins that
had been annoying whistles and build a
little house around her until she dies
yes or just with a stove in there so
they set themselves on just they like to
swim around in my swimming pool and then
you take the ladder out mix around in
there you take the ladder out of the
swimming pool and they die in a high
anyway on table talk how to kill yours
yeah no it's a hole that's the best one
that's the game race your stupid songs
she whistles it
that's it that's a cool song I'm driven
in a dance song every day know what she
said what she does it's over now
so here's here's what you have here is
what you have done you have taken this
cube of shadow stuff may extrapolated
from this staff you have come to know as
a as a friend and a partner and you are
starting to use that same material to
sort of wrap and fold itself in so it is
becoming the material is coming from the
corners and so now it has become
something like a sphere cool then you
can see that the material is sort of
reaching in from the cracks and there is
there is a incredibly a deeply
terrifying sound issuing forth from that
ring from the bite yeah from the bite
zone Chris job mmm rest how are you
ladies aunt cube we're still gonna rent
me to fight yeah I was later yeah who
else is here who else can I just one sad
Oh someone you sad did it just one sad
aunt out here or one sad writer what
what what are they up to
but they are the ones that hate Rosie
the most okay let's just go ahead and
enjoy throw some Heldrich blast at them
well that's a great laugh that's a good
one it's an alright blast I'm going to
save the best for a blast you operate on
you can mark that off in the book I know
it's written somewhere no got to it can
you believe I came up with it just now
just now can you believe it incredible
it's fresh
are you cool with me like locking your
mom in a star cube and walnut do it disk
ascending fire
you don't know these yeah I'm just like
no only to seem okay all right I feel
good I have you have like the control
group they all are good like these are
all good rest now
and I will take advantage on August
because there's two of them but have to
do it two times that works for
attentionally yeah okay so let's see
yeah right that's that's a healthy I was
20 mm garbage will do 22 and then here
comes the second one 17 whoa he's these
servants so County Serbia we are
Labour's please double that whatever it
is they're dice yeah it's big damage now
for the next president who got the cool
stuff we're talking about that lapis set
from level up it's very cool very cool
you will be well pleased they have a
dramatic weight pleasing to you all
right here's the first blast that's a
what is that that's a seven oh yes and
then for the for the double damage one
here's a Tootsie ten a m-- and eight and
18 twice wait
18:36 no never double this oh you just
leave oh I think they roll in the marine
double it no I shouldn't
yeah yeah the first the first blast the
first blast catches it in the torso the
second in the left side of the neck and
it sort of grass I want him surpri like
in a with authentic surprised at the
wound and then it collapses dinar blitz
in so they get me anywhere except my
neck my one week's mark my blood it got
me in the blood uh well Big Daddy is
under control in the box for the moment
and you're her she's in a box of hell
yeah so I will run over and give you a
little juice in it
what are you thank you I'm at six yeah
I'll give you I'll save some just in
case I don't know it's gonna have to
restless combat but I'll give you 15 of
my pole so generous this guy this why
it's just so fun I'm a giver
I give will you take a short rest well
she we don't know that's your mom yet no
I mean I have a good idea well no I mean
we don't yeah we don't know oh I see
that makes sense yeah are you are you
curious at the you know the the depth of
my fumbling do we have do we have reason
to or exhibiting any sort of like tells
yeah then I would just think it's
another big spider to kill and I
wouldn't want to mess with what seems to
be working so I heal and then I just
wait flex all right yeah yeah which is
the Jim we are back at the we are back
at the top of the initiative
yeah and it is at this point that the
face of this sort of interstellar marble
shatters out the front and completely
cloaked in hideous insects biting
literally every zone emerges emerges
this versus this increasingly Haggard
priestess who with a few whispered words
the insects begin to like release their
mandibles and they begin to fall down
and then she sort of sweeps
her hand in the air and then beckons a
host of insects
mmm different insects shoot I got bug
stuff exactly a bug so these so these
these insects have let go and they begin
to drop and sort of heap up in a pile
mmm she's just leaving a trail of these
glowing insects as she traverses down
and you hear this cloud of insects as a
you feel it as a sound before you are
aware of them in the dark but you can
see their little you can see their eyes
sort of glittering in this zone and it
comes upon you as a wake it is like a
blizzard of biting insects so I need
Constitution saving throws from all
everyone who's near me gets order of
protection you get +3 charisma because
so charismatic I could we got this guy's
Constitution SAT fair though he said
Constitution yeah confusion yeah
Constitution saving her I thought it was
any saving through Oh though it's good
you get my charisma below you know you
just know that your friend is cool help
you boy boy so we all get +3
yes okay oh oh yeah I'm gonna take
advantage cuz I don't wanna get hurt
I'm already Queen 20 say you guys know I
didn't roll 20 but I guess I got a 20
all right I'm in advantage a oh you go
for a guy to me okay
Chimbote it's one advantage that's
precious
yeah
that's just so you guys so you're you
did quite well where else 12 okay
that's not good wow thanks but not it's
not personal it's only been in the last
like week that I realized that when I
roll badly it's not a failure on my part
oh it's a weird feeling wow so bad so
it's a weird feeling
twenty-one points of damage everybody
else takes 1000 you're 21 so so I mean
if it's a point in here but you are
completely surrounded and cloaked by
like biting like vampiric insects in the
bug ya know like just like you would
have to cut your way out of here like
there's you don't see anything but you
can't authentically see your allies it
is an authentic nightmare every wall no
no no this is this is a 40-foot so sure
its massive now we're gonna keep a bugs
no I've already seen that she learned it
from watching you alright my mouth tip
that's the worst part
the it hurts but they're in my mouth
because it gross no it's worse it's how
your being dead so not at least you
don't have to have them I don't know but
you're not to suffer through thank you
for I would like to grope down at like
my my group is a word they use in books
I'm reading a book where they use the
word grow up a lot reach for grab a yes
Lord you know when they say that they're
like his hand perps around in this
pocket yeah I'm sorry um reach for my
blade cast flame blade and start trying
to hack my way out what color it is
green flame he inflate greatly you can
absolutely you can you can move through
them it's just a thick curtain of them
but you can definitely get from place to
place
oh you thought I couldn't see through it
that I had to cut my way out no that's
how it feels but you don't have to
you're fine you're fine
well you painted too deep of a word
picture okay well then never mind it's
difficult terrain because you can still
move No so where are you so we leave
anything yeah okay in that case I'm
gonna transform into a wolf and bite
bite this be
yeah everyone attracts your green flavor
emoji I'm done yeah chat opposite the
opposite
it's the blue water no chicken it's been
a second one okay
I'm gonna try and get my dinner right
now and I'm gonna take advantage do but
I don't need it 23 Oh
22 really no no anything do to do 6 no
pussy 9 okay and now they need to
succeed on a strength saving throw or be
not grown what they get their flat or
she is she is flat good so a pro nice
mmm thank you welcome
so you've walnut done grass of wolf net
thank you
has dragged the prey by its neck down to
the ground and it's currently worrying
it Rosie be singer yeah okay
does save yeah I better talking about a
death scene no okay good now we have to
beat well nothin one two done in one
round
oh no you over the course of three close
yeah
catch your stroke but see maybe I'm
misinterpreting
do you have to do it exactly at zero I
thought if you want exactly to perfect
zero you were you were stable it's when
you went under that you were is what I
thought it was okay but I could be wrong
cuz I'm new and um so I went to exactly
zero points yeah I thought that maybe
your conscience what do you what does
this look of yeah okay I'll look it up
yeah you look it up you keep going
no keep your strap um gosh I'm real mad
at this lady you let out a mommy no
don't
I wish it was like that just on the just
just to this side
Wolf's nut the heavy just the massive
weight of this wolf as briar down and
it's just the like the shrieking sound
of the of the legs scraping against the
rubble yeah this massive weight rolling
around gosh there's so many choices
believe it or not that is my that's the
problem I'm having right now but yeah
it's honestly like but it's cool like
this is like Chris wrist would be like
conscious yeah about it I feel like it's
this is the first time that kotharis is
acting like more rationally yeah like
because my options are we have some kind
of a parlay if it's possible we'll bind
her with my tentacles of a can but I'm
gonna do that I was under the impression
they were to mad chocolate
I imagine like you know we'll find out
aye-aye-aye
how far am i from this this washing and
prone clothes me your ears
I mean here you have enough movement to
be as far as you want to be from this
mess no within striking range close
enough for a dis with with wit yeah
we should cool it so I reach out and I
whisper as you know the loudest whisper
you could to so it is audible to the
group and I say it's just this this
please you this is this what you want
are you not happy now well classic mom
am i right yeah never satisfied you have
the form of your beloved goddess now you
know danger pleased what you just love
being a dreamer but this wish has damage
associated with does have damage but we
have to see if she can beat uh TC 15
wisdom mm-hmm let's see wisdom is
something that she is quite good at but
something about this moment perhaps
keeps her from being fully engaged okay
that's a good idea and I have to
remember I'd remind myself that even if
even if she failed or even if she
succeeds she would still have to take
out damage so she's going to enjoy 5d6
psychic yeah plus 1 d6 a hacker oh yeah
from X should I just see if I can throw
them all out one blue for no one's we
looking at here fine ones sue 1/8 from
that and then one so 8 and then no these
are for yeah okay let's just do that
lets just - psychic course yeah
ok so 11 and then the necro alright that
was a woman so 12 what what a thirsty
whisper that one was we're cutting blade
it's a blue level at my foe and then but
she's prone but she won't she struck
with beautifully no but does does she
cannot flee right because as unimpressed
as you might have been with it
twelve is sufficient to reduce the
targets hit points to below zero so just
at this voice that just this amplified
this mystically amplified voice of her
son just cuts straight through her
consciousness and there is a moment of
sort of glassy eyed reverie and she says
if only I had killed you one more time
the reward would have been mine and she
collapses on the side Josh can you tip
my cauldron please oh you can see part
of her raiment is of course that which
is sanctified by the Spider Queen loaf
but there is an extra portion something
that is not classically a part of that
collection and that is a what looks to
be almost a dragon scale cape imagine
that dragon scales had been pounded out
of mithril and it flows almost like a
liquid of her shoulders and so as she
falls
it sort of spills out this this this
shining mithril cloak spills out and
spreads out behind her you don't
remember that from your childhood you
don't know when she came by it but it is
clearly it marks itself as an item of
tremendous interest Thank You Josh
I ignore it
I'm I go to my knees didn't expect that
it would that I would be able to when I
assumed that I would meet my end here
trying to recover this secret yeah I
could thrust his slumped over over the
body and you know pounds it like pounds
it yeah as if there was as if there's a
the intimation of anger but you can see
that there's not needles just performing
its performative yeah he stands back up
realizes probably everybody's watching
him and yeah should we continue know if
there's dragon scale and then horde be
like whoa I wish is the bomb yeah I have
no interest in hello everybody
did you know her is this you do you I
just stalk off in a direction yeah you
guy go up 25 feet as though I'm
surveying you know the next place we
need to go just ignore yeah well I'll
hold it for you it's right like a
babushka yeah it has no perceivable
weight like these are dragon scales dude
they're awesome you like try to cheer
him up yeah I'm like this is cool loot
man you got the last hit you should get
it I want to walk up to uh cut this um
yeah
you can't we're not an initiative
anymore right she's done okay
so I'm gonna turn back into myself but I
assume my self is still great good dress
yeah I thought it would help I just
stand next to him for a minute and I
think I realize you're not doing
anything yeah I've got the map open but
I'm not looking at it there's no way
yeah yeah
and while I was singing go you good
let's finish what we were came to do
it'll be good
okay be very good okay do you hear you
hear feet start on the uneven rebel
behind you and it's tasty oh and he puts
his hand just on the flat front of your
chest
and he says I am tasty this is are you
tasty it's wrist stoic just a hint of
the voice breaking I am now and a
trembling that liquid but does not does
not spill does not betray it that
somehow is more meaningful yeah
and sees that Casey got him to break and
she's just like yeah okay and she looks
back tonight and goes cool Kate is there
anything on the body of this priestess I
think Rosie would be like looting the
body is there anything that would
indicate her relationship tickets wrists
or any anything that would denote her
station but there is a there is a symbol
that you've seen and you've seen this
symbol many times that's both on a
medallion and on the hilt of a small
dagger
it looks like it's mostly for ritual
purposes it doesn't look like it's
designed for heavy combat okay
it's a very it's a very similar symbol
to the one that was quite well
represented in morals cart now she
seemed to have a particular fascination
for oh yeah the icon I'm a problem with
it being a secret I mean as you're
investigating and I will turn back
around and say she was you silh truth
she was my mother
oh that one time okay Rosie like steps
away she's like so um I shouldn't didn't
have any she didn't need these things I
would argue upon becoming ad writer I
don't think she needs them now either
but no enjoy
dude writers generally in your studies
are they able to communicate like that
that's a good question
like yeah it just the process of the
process of transformation affects people
affects people affects people very
differently okay she that's what you
know she kept some amount of sentience
mm-hmm her former self yeah yeah range I
will and I will share that as she was
dying she said that she said if I had
killed you one more time then the prize
would be mine those were the words yeah
yeah I don't remember having died a
first time so you know what she's
talking about there may be in the throes
of you know whatever dim synapse firing
just upon the edge of death you know had
she learned the Tetra through Nautica
maybe I'd be able to glance down see if
she'd written something yeah but I
assume she's not versed do you have so
much to teach her
so these things that are on her person
that have this symbol which is I guess
the symbol of house roughly yeah these
are these are things that Morrel was
interested in so they do a gesture to
them and say you want to bring these
tomorrow or should we leave them and
then that makes a lot of sense this is a
good a good exchange okay your payment
so I'll take the pendant and the sword
dagger it the symbol on it yes and
present them to you very respectfully
like these these one view uh-huh
see how would how would consist receive
them I think it look what are they way
he would conjure velvet to carry them
just okay yeah velvety appears it's
light enough so just the little hands
underneath the velvet make a little
pouch yeah yeah do you take these with
us deposit them okay that's perfect
you're starting to notice the longer it
hangs on your shoulders dinar you're
starting to notice that along with it's
sort of like strange lightness you think
it might actually be bigger than it
looks when you start to reach your hands
back and sort of like like draw it out
its comically large hmm even too big for
me
no no it'll always full it always fold
itself back in okay um but you think
that you may be able to extend some of
its protection Oh even to another even
to someone else who was close ah you can
probably extend your protection out to
one other person Albert yeah something
to consider something to consider
just keep the tent fabric that's
important anchor
should we say anything yeah
last rites well just guys standing over
the body you have some religious people
here yeah Bon Appetit this is a mother
after all
I suppose in the technical sense yeah
what would walnut want to do
this case being fairly ignorant of the
dynamic between these two with the with
the maternal relationship the important
um just the fact that it was someone's
mother that that's like a thing even
though she's not who she was that that's
a thing to respect
so whether whether whether anyone's
noticing or not Alicia probably didn't
muttering something like muttering words
under her breath but like almost like a
compulsion like she has to do it okay
yeah I don't like make a big show of it
yeah yeah I have no rights that would
please her yeah you know sir exact
probably have done them well this this
battlefield having concluded its story
that party is free to move on according
to the map and according to the device
you have from Carver call that will lead
you inexorably
to an encounter with your past
hey shadow council mayor leavers please
you hate we're gonna go right into the
break but don't go anywhere we're not
done we have a whole other hour so
please stay please stay please please
stay really need you don't go please
thank you we suffer don't we Amy we do
look get to the word sangwich okay
this is Jennifer cave archives something
happened no doubt mystical in nature to
the device maybe it couldn't handle the
emotional realness and that Thrissur
Ruth Lee brought now when last we saw
our heroes they were just setting out
from the battlefield they had so
recently resolved a conflict in there is
now a tiny invisible creature coated in
lustrous velvet holding a few artifacts
from his house mm-hm you are now free to
move about the Underdark I got my my
gift
from from the carbon Gault thank you it
wasn't a goal dekat yeah
no please kike wish I got that one in my
back pocket next um a minute yeah I'm
gonna just start following it again and
I'm saying just let us do part
just heating its counsel yeah absolutely
so you you once again hold it out just
let it let it guide you through this
space and you are moving now from these
shared public spaces and the areas of
industry that supported the large houses
and you're moving now into buildings and
spaces that can't be annihilated in the
same way not by time or even for you
know even with enthusiasm because many
of the high houses and lower Gala death
are made from columns that project from
the ground and then meet a stalactite as
well so these some of these high places
are made from what are more or less
floor-to-ceiling columns hundreds of
feet high in some cases so as you the
higher up you're moving into this space
the more you're seeing the sort of your
the more you're seeing places that you
would truly recognize you know I mean
these also would seem more defensible to
be caps alone there's no wall to break
down this is just the structure no no no
it's a it's exactly right the closer you
get you can see that if it weren't for
lack of trying as my father would have
said the bases themselves are cut with
deep gouges and scratches so whatever
whatever occurred before these houses
truly fell must have been a maniacal
spectacle I'm gonna I'm gonna cough and
take a moment to clear my throat mm-hmm
shadow counsel did he is only having
more lustrous because to me it sounds so
bad because it's turning to become
painful oh so I can only imagine it as
also painful to hear no okay no no quite
the opposite
[Music]
so Catherine while we're largely walking
in silence I imagine I turn to Rosie and
I point out to you some of the
stalactites that I in mind yeah it's
miscible this this pointing one this is
how I knew I was on the right Street and
singing back to my house yeah does the
sisters up there those are the sisters
right yeah just because there are two
stalactites imagine and you can almost
see how they're like that - not just
elect dates but like - cones they are
they're like upside down cones yeah yeah
oh absolutely not
I support that sort of thing 100% I'm
but these no no it's like then let me
spoil the the the moment where it's like
I didn't I didn't ever think that you
would actually need to see them I
thought that if I was to take you there
I would have to drug you in some way and
some like some sort of a lava
hallucinatory oh yeah chemically induced
come here but on a different plane of
some kind or I would just you'd be
drugged I'm just
grab it the best I could sure what are
you drugging me in this fantasy of yours
that's it's effective I'm glad that's
happening this way instead meets you
less expensive so these essentially
these these manor houses are they sick
they look sort of like just piles of
melted candles everywhere and it would
not be hard cthe risk to find your house
in this in this place well let's let's
proceed if I get a whiff of getting
within you know something looks
particularly familiar to me that I'm
just gonna start to like jog up ahead
yeah and just say come on right this is
this is the place absolutely
the the focused pendant that you have is
now not really directing you in any one
direction it's now just sort of like
spinning in place back and forth it like
wind itself up and then wind itself the
other way in the hand so you are you
must be very very close to your
destination because it's it's not
designed to show you your house right
it's designed to show you something
specific and if I mean evidence of
evidence of something or an artifact
connected with Carver galls imprisoned
deity a creature that he calls that
which indoors do you remind me Dan all
right you have a skill does it let you
look for an object a specific thing oh
yes I do I have located object I don't
know what we're looking for I'm actually
kind of surprised that yeah if this
thing indicates my father's study that
he would have done it anywhere near the
house right it seems foolish yeah indeed
what did gets out he does so but the
doing do you know what it look like I
need to know what it looks like well
it's it's this I'm
I can show you this the unity the sigil
okay that Gaul gave me and it would we
would have this symbol on it okay yeah
I've been that that works yeah I just
need to be able to picture in my mind so
I need a picture of it so that's I can
totally do that
yeah is that's the plan I'm gonna do
that oh yeah all right all right go push
push it up against my forehead to absorb
it get like a real good mental picture
yeah this unnecessary all part of it no
this is ah there's a lot of pomp and
circumstance involved with this and then
yeah and it's like I'm great I'm great
I'm gay
yes describe our name and object
familiar everything is sense Direction
thousand feet okay so that's that
basically you're looking for another
instance of that symbol yes here
somewhere absolutely you do you your
awareness expands out and it identifies
higher up in this the structure that
stands before you it identifies an
instance of that symbol nice so you just
kind of roam around like a dog that's
trying to sit down and I'm just like
audibly saying colder colder warmer
colder colder warmer warmer warmer
so the rectal I get there the base the
base of this house the heavy doors that
you remember being made of shining
mithril even the hinges are gone it's
just a it's just like a passageway now
there's no there's no ceremony to it at
all with this just a threshold mmm-hmm
yeah it's just like the there's no items
that I recognize I would imagine it's
just like the topology yeah exactly yeah
it's not like oh that old curtain yeah
it's like not textured it's just the
geometry of this space yeah and so as
you enter you can see the stairway that
leads down
to the larder and the houses the house
with least storage areas down deep in
the basement so that's an availability
there's also stairs that go up to other
regions of the house personal areas as
good sirs and I presumed in our enter
when I hang back with walnut a little
bit and and as soon as they're kind of
out of earshot to to take her hand and
say some mothers are not worth
remembrance or reverence but it does a
great credit that you cared okay
yeah what I remember so what would I
remember the layout of the house would
my father have had I study absolutely
feel like he might not have been
permitted no it's a it's a in your
recollection it was very small almost a
closet it's like a Harry Potter under
the stairs bedroom kind of sneak yeah
like yeah in cave sleeps there works
they're not all that out it's like a
storage basically it was a storage area
that was tolerated for his you know
little experiments okay let me yeah
let's find our way up air and maybe he
didn't do the research there but maybe
there's a clue as to where he did it we
just go up there and
and what's the police term case no no
when like you come home and the
apartments just completely turnover they
were looking for sleeping yeah Danny
there's a specific verb for that crime I
am select tossed yeah that's right so a
salad ransack that's gonna toss the
salad yay you make your way up up a set
of stairs into the floor where people's
individual rooms were you can see the
simple door that led into your sister
Federal's room you can see that her room
has been thoroughly dismantled and the
things that are left in there things
that said that no one wanted or thought
that they could thought would have any
kind of after you know value in any kind
of market mm-hm
afterward but you can see on the floor
sort of poking out almost from the bed
you can see what you think is the cover
of a book with it I give you one of
these like a SWAT team like for the
podcast he's making crazy as maybe the
edited at the end I think it was the
marker I just started doing my little
bit ah wait in the hallway do the
Macarena tiger turn no I don't come here
doesn't matter so I'll stop here and I
will wander in there and and pull this
out yeah you know whatever whatever
scent type memories you would have
associated with it there's not there
isn't any hint of it this is not a place
where people live anymore the book
itself is a book of but are functionally
speaking fairy tales so it's a very
common
there's a very common brow fairytale
about and there's it's retold in many
different ways but it is about girl who
seeks lost wisdom and then is visited by
various incarnations of love and
invariably
these young women succeed so long as
they follow the correct path
occasionally there's a version of it
that involves them being insufficiently
cruel or in the moment of victory not
going for the kill such young women are
punished in stories like these scoop
that up where the other thing I would be
concerned that we're not we're splitting
the party I'm so with Rosie are we
downstairs yeah we're downstairs for you
in the foyer a larger or the because I
guess there's where we first came in yes
yes I want to make sure I know where you
are so humans always you told me to be
the home yeah when I go for the record I
I want to wait in the hallway not
because you tell me to meet in the home
I decided to wait in the hallway much
decided that these two things just lined
up yeah and they worked out great it's
just you're actively I'm racing I was
gonna kill you yeah um I'm - I'm
continuously looking like I'm trying to
tell you something
oh okay but I can't work up to it oh all
right it's just like the body language
is up and they're like I have more to
say about it but every time you do my
expression never changes every time you
light up like you're gonna say something
I have this like very patient smile and
then as soon as you lose lose steam I'm
like okay and then I just keep going
back to poking around the house and as
soon as I hit intake it's exactly the
same every time can we do a perception
check to see if we find any good relics
for me
dude yeah you can yeah absolutely man
the system they're fuckin the Dragons
let's do it none for me thanks that's
very nice you find possibly because no
one wanted it it is not in terrible
shape you find the ledger of house
remotely it's so clear like it said it's
to anyone else it would be authentically
boring but for a level 2 document sir I
got it it's almost certainly it'd be
like reading the rings of a tree oh yeah
then you could assess you could get you
could pull incredible information out of
something like I'm tucked in already
you're you've already you've already
gone in I'm like Rosie look at this
mother tell me what you see rosie has no
idea what she's looking at she's like
what a lot of kissing cousins in this
family well that makes a lot of sense so
there is our boy yeah oh no no it's it's
all good I support you 100% always look
like me right now I'm exactly so the
there is the this is your flipping
through at the very end like the last
the last thing that was entered into the
ledger is for a repaired house banner so
they had sent the house banners
apparently to a family called the
skillful hands of house good dog
and so the rat sent up for restoration
and then there's a symbol of fixed after
it in terms of the price and the price
is just indicated as enough so they were
they did not indicate how much they were
will
to spend simply that mmm they would
spend okay the price was right well just
not if it's nothing after that yeah
so that's dis so at the very end
something had been like they were
restoring their house bannocks mmm
interesting interesting because proceed
and we don't see house manners around
you're welcome to look around would you
like to look around sir please
okay no I'm gonna give you some love for
that yeah shuttle council mayor Labor's
please do your starter Rosie be stinger
has offered you a boon so we gave away
our first two goodies so now it is gift
certificates to the store where you
might find imagine a dark t-shirt some
of our other C team stuff eventually
there may be another shirt you might
like you might want to save your coupon
for next week especially if you remember
the C team and good standing that you're
you're looking you're looking around and
you can see that near the stairs there
is an especially there are especially
deep grooves that can get into these
deeper that seem to be worn okay great
detail roofs near the stairs yes what do
they look like they were made from well
they look like they look like it's
probably they're probably the result of
a crate or a case of some kind
oh and being dragged away from roots
Besant yeah your your suspicion looking
at it is it this is a place where a lot
of stuff moves okay do I see an obvious
entry or exit oh absolutely yeah yeah
these these stairs go straight down oh
this is down oh yeah absolutely
okay I know it says like a nudge walnut
like you see what I see these won't you
pointing to it yeah if you want to take
a break
this from this ledger I have a feeling
there's something going on down here
shudders yes yeah I bet it's a whole
creep flow Ledger's it's gonna be really
exciting that's my number one castle
let's go do it so on your on your way
down foods have been 100 percent
ransacked
there's nothing especially to the naked
eye there's none of the fine wines weird
mushrooms expensive cheese expensive
spider cheese yeah exactly
um but you can aquarium gravel so you
can see that they have a bard and indeed
sort of gate dated enclosure no a gated
enclosure presumably for items of some
value and you can see that the door
itself is ravaged this is no longer a
door in any meaningful sense but there
is still a crate here in the basement
that has some surface damage okay but is
mostly fine and it's still here behind
this locked door tourists and as I
suggested it has a door in quotes so
barely a door for lack of a better term
and inside there you can see but you
think it might be you think it may be of
dwarven make hmm it's just like a solid
firm construction and you think that you
see like the glint just here in the low
light you think you see the glint of
like strange symbols strange writing
that goes all the way around the the lid
of the box okay not in a language that I
recognize no you it may not be a
language at all it's just a set of
symbols that are unsettling even to look
at
but sealed into the top of the box it's
almost like the invoice it's like the
return invoice it's the the match of
what is entered into the ledger and you
notice immediately mm-hmm that it's not
right Oh a discrepancy I go yeah I
immediately start looking at this
discrepancy the box that they sent back
mm-hmm everything else is correct mm-hmm
but it is six pounds lighter six pounds
six pounds None the Richer it's yeah
absolutely yeah how can we pray bard or
yeah Locker sure what's the deal if I
have to what are you gonna do describe
how you describe how you open it like
this is how you ransack a house yeah
like granny show you something I think
I'm gonna do a little bit of a bite I'm
just you know I can't can you actually
I'm gonna do that it's like I could do
it nope I think I need your help
um I actually I am fresh out of wild
shapes so I guess what I will do then is
whisper to my staff and the the end the
very the flat bottom end of it becomes a
like a pry bar yeah yeah yeah so they're
the the staff changes from its its
wooden usual very similar to shape into
a shadowy bar and I crank that bitch out
could I have a dexterity check make with
their acrobatics and I will take
advantage on that too it's gonna be a
twelve no what's the box made of you
take
so as you went to and you're like you
like you flatten it out you think you
think that the hard part is over yeah
right you shaped the stuff of shadow
yeah and as soon as you as soon as it
connects a bolt of lightning leaps from
the box up the shadow rod and basically
strikes you straight through it and you
were knocked across the room against the
bars whoa
yeah you take five points of damage dead
again okay so here's all I can do is I
run over and I go oh my god grandmother
and I reach in my pocket and there's
just a nasty funky good barrier and I
put it in here mouth and I'm moving jaw
and I rub your throat and I look and I'm
like pushing it in there and you get one
HP I'm good I'm fine I wake up I know
but it's like it's too fast like when
she goes she flies like too fast against
the gate and then falls too fast just
like look at all three frames yeah oh my
god yeah uh-oh my grandmother are you
all right
yeah I'm great that thing is electrified
though I go don't worry I'm gonna teach
it a lesson thank you
and then I touch it it's made out of you
had seen a bunch of you'd seen a bunch
of novel metals during your time in hilt
kazar mm-hmm and you think it might have
been one of those there's a bunch of
alloys that are just unique to the doors
of that city and you can't 100% map
which one it is but it's clearly
manufactured from some strange alloys
this is like this is lightning odium
yeah like lightning oh yeah how would
you feel about me trying to mess with
those there's an obvious lock on it well
here yeah yeah go ahead and go ahead
mess with it okay I'm gonna try and do
something shit yo
ah so I want to use heat metal mm-hmm to
heat it so that it is red-hot and
malleable and is that enough stone is
lava not stone is alloys not metal to be
heated and then I want to take for
mother and push her into the lock just
trying to save up a lock I like it there
like Josh could you please tip my
cauldron oh and I died
no no no this is this is actually okay
this is assistance on the so this is
okay don't be scared by the pretty
lights so you you heat up this alloy to
a red-hot here in this corner and then
for mother yeah like a like a like
opening an envelope mm-hmm for mother
just finds this this crack and you open
this you openly the seal whatever mystic
seal is holding this together it's just
a flick of the wrist so you you
basically slide it from one side to the
other and they're in the roof of the box
goes nice amazing thanks Josh so inside
you can see sparkling gems and perfectly
preserved house Ruth League banners I
got a yeah I was just gonna say I make a
bird noise even though we've never lost
a signal ever it's always a different
bird voice yeah ever we do that exactly
what do that nice yeah well anyway I
make a burden mourning death
hey and church trying to go upstairs
okay
I like to think that well your continued
sister's room
and I was just standing
oh hey like a decrepit Halloween to say
great nice house you got here and then
yours and it's just like I'm like
peeling the wallpaper and it's like
waiting and then we just hear like crash
boom and then oh my god did that crate
open and they go yeah and I hear it all
upstairs
I'm just like you got any of my dad's
shirts adventure may continue alright
and I know this room where I'll hear
that bird call alright maybe just prior
to the bird call yeah we're in my dad's
study absolutely so we see very very
small simple a point and simple very
very simply appointed sort of it's all
rough stone deeply chipped whatever you
know whatever weird cobbling hedge magic
shit he was getting into down here and
there are there are things in here that
were apparently not worth stealing as
well there is a very small very simple
knife with a handle of black wood rare
in these parts and as you see it the the
symbol just begins to spin and now sort
of sway in strong counter circles mmm
I'm going to grasp this knife the knife
at its hilt this may be what dinar was
detecting on this knife has as its hilt
a very simple indeed perhaps handmade
carving of the unity icon that
represents that which in doors
dad what you doing in here
it's a it's a like as I said that very
the knife is very it's not ornate it is
incredibly simple like so simply you
wouldn't take it just as a tool almost
any knife would be better you know what
would you've done with it
may I see her may I proceed yeah may I
no no I'm let me try and stead of that
um you dork Hannah I love any and he I
love it I love it
you gonna do a little sense of this
thing yeah let me let me go ahead and
take advantage - hey pretty solid that's
that's a 20 and then a little 21 that's
very good right
so the the weight is about right you're
using your skills as an Arcanist to
assess not just the physical object that
might how is the enchantment but sort of
the mystic echoes of the enchantment
itself and as you turn it if you just
turn it in your hand you the blade
itself is like - dull like it's
comically dull like it's this is
possibly the worst knife of all time not
a knife yeah not a knife and in fact you
think that it's actually - you think
that it's actually two pieces and there
is there might actually be space where
the blade should be there is a void
present there oh I see Oh like like this
is the mounting for a blade it could be
this but it looks to be a blade but the
sharpest part of it is gone mm-hmm I'm
gonna take the
there's any scrap of fabric let me just
run that that void across it okay you
take the scrap and then you hold it like
in the loop so you can try to cut
through it yeah as you do the fabric
disappears hmm good thing in try cut
your hand may say doesn't is an anti
knife I don't know what function this
has hi
okay I'm gonna say at this point we hear
this bird call yeah yeah I'm gonna take
this with me hey don't cut with this
knife it just makes him go away
it hates fabric and his curtains got it
good answer did you take your knife out
and just tell dinar don't cut with this
knife and then take it away from him as
your dad as you were as you are warning
him about it you feel what seems like a
breeze like from the blade of the knife
it feels like a breeze like through a
doorway what I'm gonna take that and I'm
gonna take that blade well look at it
edge on I want to see I want to see that
that anti edge as you as you turn it
ever so slightly
it's like looking it's like turning your
head back and forth looking through a
cracked a narrow slit or something
there's something there's something in
it God there is something inside it hmm
you like cut there
well this is my visit what I'm concerned
with is getting too close to it want to
go down and see what y'all are up to be
very careful with this did it come with
a with a cover your house is it current
no no someone threw it on the ground
maybe somebody is in there yeah bones
are in there yeah your home's gonna be
real careful with it
let's go ahead and descend the stairs
what could go wrong okay yeah we'll come
back to the foyer like I just found my
dad's knife and some shirts where are
you guys
Rosie need some help and we found some
stuff in the basement get down here okay
she's seen how I'm holding Rosie like Oh
wha get down there and see her and a
message what are you kids been up to use
my father's shirt as a tourniquet nice
quick that's your bonus
oh yeah sure bonus I'll I'll give you
the last 59 thank you I pull I'll take
better care of these next time sorry we
explain to y'all what you found
yeah I say I'm like well first off here
are some gems to put in the in the horse
person bag Knight give you those gems
girl I kick it this way and then I go
and then and I start I lift them I'm
like this seems to be House banners of
your house oh yes I remember those yeah
they look well kinda you know I'm gonna
have to draw them later yeah but it's
the most intricate you've ever seen
really really epic no let me do that one
some thought okay but that's what they
look like but they're in really good
shape yeah yeah like they were now down
here in Thanks yeah it's like they're in
a better humidor no I opened the ledger
and I show him I say um well here's the
thing is in the ledger here it's there's
this curious entry and I show show you
that the entry then where it says enough
payment mayo and there's a discrepancy
it's off by six pounds and here they are
fully restored and that was the last
thing that was ever entered into your
family's ledger hmm ruff and how much
does dad's knife way
[Music]
see all that Sherlock wait in other
languages okay I think it's a mystery
and frankly bad bookkeeping that's the
other well this is the worst crime of
all yeah when the Wynwood that one who
is the date on the ledger do I see that
the date oh yeah absolutely yeah it was
about fifty years after you left
oh okay so we were right before the all
the excitement yeah
it was the crate oh it was under buy six
pounds what was that yeah exactly so the
the discrepancy was that the crate that
was returned yeah was six pounds later
okay you know when payments are light
mm-hmm so here's what I want to do gang
I'm gonna Caillou catch you up on it
because I don't want something weird to
happen like it's not the right place
where things are anything weird
I'm gonna preface it with that okay
thank you everyone for coming
I don't want anything weird to happen
hmm but I found this knife it's my dad's
study it's got the unity symbol on it it
it's a bladeless knife which you know it
seems like a convenient as a spoon right
yeah bladeless camping knife it was in
my dad's office there's a picture of
this cat in the cradle and I got this
silver matter little tears all over the
Blarney so but what I want to do is I
want to see if I can look into their eye
maybe I demonstrate with another piece
of fabric that I cut through yeah does
it vanishes again it does I want to peer
into it into that space this see this is
what it
like me metagaming andrs what kids risk
would do because wrist would like what
he would want to do is stick this knife
hilt on something that does not move so
that he can safely bring his face toward
it without it like without accidentally
like reaching the plane right right of
whatever makes that thing disappear but
I suspect that kids risk could also just
take it and and just hack at the air is
he recommended so let me let me just
first try that I'll do it up against one
wall yeah there's a there's a there's a
light just just through the air itself
let me say I do it on the wall okay the
wall is scraped okay mm-hmm it's a
scraper this is probably for stucco or
ya know now I know I will try it against
the air yeah it just whistles a little
bit mmm it's like a hum almost your
first idea that seems very scientific
that he would ask you teen where's the
main break can i see inside of there yes
let me go ahead and like I need to see
what's in this knife it's no weird yeah
let me I'm gonna press it up there you
tell me if I start to look like I'm
going into a knife okay you'll know when
you yep
alright so you're getting closer and lo
searching idea taking note of my
sensations of my face you're good maybe
I've got some like some some scraps that
I'm trying to predict zone like when I
when I get up in there but what I really
want to do is be able to see yeah and
get changed my meeting angle so if you
anyone who is watching cthe wrists hmm
at this moment is seeing that the closer
he gets to it a kind of a beam of
illumination from the blade is
projecting itself on his basically like
at his eye level can he see how are you
actually yeah yeah yeah yeah you're
looking in there well with Locati I
guess right you're blind yeah
chop him up it makes a lot of sense okay
yeah I'll have to change it so that I'm
like Lagasse's forging forward yeah it
is here right okay a mine just blinded
by that light I mean can I see anything
or is it just that white light it's just
it's just a song it's just a white light
I'm going to if you can you tip the
cauldron Josh
wowser me so you can see in this moment
you can see this light casting on his
face like this and then Carissa hand
tightens on the blade and you are
watching this occur no you can see that
your hand is taking the knife turning it
toward your face and then it thrusts it
directly into your eye oh and when this
happens the rest of the party sees the
knife suspended in air and Karissa is
gone ah thanks Josh
no is it stays put yeah it is frozen in
the air the place that you are in is not
a place of shame
it is a well-appointed study it has
racks and racks of books elaborate
instrumentation a well-appointed
Allwood desk Wow
scattered well scattered isn't right it
has a prodigious amount of sophisticated
alchemical tools someone might think
that it was scattered simply because
there's so much equipment but it is all
there it is all there arranged with
purpose
there is a book closed on the desk
itself and the cover of the book says
the book of unity - it's right there is
a glass dome over what looks to be
almost a jewel fixture inside made from
some silvery metal and there is a seed
held inside that sort of bell jar
there's a seed held the way a gem would
be held in a Juna ring there is also a
jar that looks like it might have been
worked on I mean it looks the place is
immaculate
it looks like whoever was working here
was working here yesterday and there is
a jar and in the base of the liquid in
this jar
there is a worm like a polychaete worm
the type of worm that has a hog a shell
and lots of legs right and it is sort of
curled up at the very bottom and as you
come in it begins to ping and nip at the
round portion of the jar well hang on to
that there but there is two pages of the
book of unity for you to enjoy oh thank
you no problem it's my pleasure but
those are the those are the main
takeaways this is this place is here
apparently inside this knife there is a
second life that
existed and it's all contained I mean it
would take a lifetime for you to read
the contents of these shelves Katherine
never comes out is the problem yeah
that's realistically probably that good
I look I look behind me because I want
to see if there's a is there an obvious
exit
yeah yeah there is there is a doorway
and there is just a slight crack through
which a gentle breeze emits gosh okay
here's the seed trembles gently in its
fixture I'm gonna reach out my awakened
mind just take a quick scan and
I asked first i probe at a nice like in
my way I'd say hello friend
it says another one was my father the
first I don't know who your father is
and I don't know who you are
what are you free me and find out but I
don't
so is that is that what you have then
for me is knowledge of your of your self
of your aspect Oh child I have the best
knowledge I have the knowledge that was
forgotten
no you're speaking my language seed it's
like disgusting let me I want to see I
want to live here and just be here this
is what I am and misty step into the
worm near the seed no I want to UM while
I have you know I know what I do
whatever you want I know what I do he
says just a second and he jumps out he
goes through the door pushes through the
door
no so you can i yeah exactly so so if
you push through the door you emerge
from the blade the blade is still in the
air and it falls okay cool so now I'm
standing in front of it oh and the blade
into clatters to the ground
yes and the first thing he says how much
time passed hey how much time passed ten
years yeah
not now Rosie don't he was made curtain
the whole time I knew it
how much time passed yeah he's only been
in there for a couple of moments oh okay
but is it scares 101 yeah I was
wondering if it wasn't held in the air
it was more than just like you and blink
him and it took a moment to fall yeah no
no it seems to hold its position okay
okay so not instant yeah it's my dad's
this is my dad's study knife alright he
went in everyday had no idea it was he
and the knife and his own study he just
he I guess he just stabbed himself in
the face and I'm like you see some
giddiness of course I should have known
why didn't I plunge it in my eyes up
there ridiculous what did you see
a place where I think he he did his
studies it was a room it's contained
within this this is a gateway to it and
all I have to do is punch her my the
orbits of my face did you see any damage
from this no no it did he teleported the
instant it came in contest zero-cost
yeah yeah it's awesome
yeah he's done he's done okay so you you
enter you enter this quiet meditative
place off to the right you can see a
simple but comfortable chair there's us
there's a pipe resting on a small side
table your favorite weed can't wait
empty that pipe out I don't want that
yeah it's bad no I want to can i
percieve does it does it smell like that
perfectly okay this isn't like the rest
of the place like this isn't this is not
there ravaged doom of the house
what is your death smell like he's like
old books and seed under glass and a
pyre head worm I don't know yet Josh can
you tip the colder place somebody wants
to be Rosie's favourite so that's what I
determined thank you
um so as you as you come back you notice
that the glass of the jar is gone Oh
which stir the bell jar the Wormser the
bell jar yes you know the worm is still
writhing and swimming around in a in a
corkscrew pattern in a central column
thanks Josh memory I'm gonna use
awakened mind reach out to the worm are
you anything it's like the equivalent of
like screwing around with your inventory
items in a text parser like I don't put
on it at this it taps its chile's array
or whatever at the glass and what you
can see is that from this angle like
when you when you look at it straight on
it seems to duplicate infinitely
backward so it's it's physicality from
different angles
appears to be distinct Oh strange okay
but you didn't answer my question
no all right I'm gonna turn my attention
back to the seat and I will ask what
what do you grow in seed what nutrients
would serve you the hearts of men
seed it knows what it wants or romantic
did you remove that the jar did you
remind remove your enclosure
you didn't suit me what what is there
anything in this space that does I I am
NOT a the wisdom I seek is not a wisdom
that one finds in books I have a a not
entirely positive opinion of those who
seek wisdom in books to begin with but
not negative either just trying to find
the boundaries it's feeling it out
you're getting to know each other are
you alone
drow oh not frequently no never
frequently so what I'm gonna do is that
that I'm gonna go ahead and scoop up the
book community and I bagged it
yeah and head out of the room hmm
my dad seed girl mousy in there it's
funny don't know in this knife without
bringing a buddy Josh would you please
take my so you you have the knife with
you and you are
warning your friends and erstwhile
allies about what it might contain when
you hear a sound like almost like a
hammer on an anvil whatever this seed is
made of is not is not fibrous wood in
the classic sense it hits the ground
like a cannonball wood and it's it's
weight is too great for its its physical
size and you can see that it begins to
extend slowly on the ground what does
the seed
oh it's pride its way out of the blade
and as it is him that's the one yeah as
it begins to stretch and move out and
grow from the centre of it you see one
one portion of the seed emerge and then
behind it you can see a strong arm
behind it and you can see that that
forms a kind of shield and then with
each passing second the shape of the
seed shifts bit by bit as what stands
before you is a six foot tall wood elf
whose head whose headdress is all sharp
antlers whose blade that you now see is
made from animals an emerald green glass
and the armor itself is a mix of what
looks to be ruff bark and gemstone
and what is your AC well lamppost knife
I get a advantage
oh no it's 15 it's 15 yep she rolled a
15 she owes 43 points of damage to me
yeah cuz I'm some chest head no no
dinner
what is your armor class 18 nope
shadow council may my Labor's please you
kill two people
yeah I'm pretty sure chickie sings I'm
still nice I'm good I'm good and dead
Tbk finally it was coming uh that's our
game what for this week thank you so
much shadow council she uh it's been our
it has been our great pleasure to spend
quality time with you again how much
time do we have for Table Talk fifteen
minutes is enough time to pass out the
love we got it hey you hang out there
we're gonna go do some stuff but we'll
come right back and then we'll talk
about some shit you'll be super cool
you'll love it
see you later
you