time is the enemy of the past it
threatens the fastest weapon you
wouldn't make it past a second and
answer the question
play it brash and reckless to choose a
cautious solution you saw was prudent in
any Sepulcher poker to don't become the
pew tree it's that well said I pursue in
no mountain too steep for dungeon too
deep to send expendable marks up to the
top of the peak of beneath they see Yugi
they come like sharks to it while I swim
in that money build like Carl Barks
through it so send your national parks
drew it I'll send him home in a natural
box with a close tie the most of the
parts included save your breath for a
cleric confessor death is a lesson that
life is attending professor but if just
seeking my official advice sign on the
dotted line and this should the choice I
am Tycho Brahe hey of panicking in past
I'm also well manifest hair were drawn
CEO of acquisitions incorporated but
today I am Jerry Hawkins and I'm running
a game of Dungeons &amp; Dragons for my
friends a truncated set to be sure but
all friends and obviously one love Kate
hopefully your washing along with us
savoring we're gonna do our best for you
to I right Ryan Hartman who the what
just put forward huh do you don't
usually get my wrong to my right know
which one are you ragging warned
arsonist
to the right of my right Michael in
everyone reppin the natural world walnut
dog grass it me yeah her and obviously
you know obviously under these scenarios
typically speaking Kate aka grandmother
night
aka Rosie be stinger correct would
manhandle it an illusory serpent I found
do it in her stead but you know what I
just a tree with respect just put it
back okay you put you put you put it
back on its serpent stand right
you know you speak you spend extra to
the left of my left emerging as though
from a mist shroud just wrist wrap okay
what yeah hey did you did you see that
animated gif thank you um joins from
Inuyasha yeah we're we're here where
it's like all the times you go like this
a coffee robot from the Oh Joe Council
yeah it was just all of those it is it
is so exquisite like I was sitting
enticed and I was drawn in to a realm
you know comprised entirely of Chris
trout's getting my shroud no it was a
real treat
hey when last we saw our heroes there
are sort of a duality present but let me
catch you up if you were not with us
last time
now the c-team broke into activity
groups right basically one group that is
to say one buddy cop movie was operating
on this axis dinar Blitzen and Chris
trout had gone to the local yeah Indian
too many bit three minutes that
were three because because he wanted to
bring we got the mayor oh my exactly so
they went to the local town of shrimp
shrimp is a town that is known for its
gems the fantasy of course was that they
would be able to establish trade perhaps
get some kind of a support maybe trade
for some additional weaponry maybe even
someone to come back with them fried
shrimp and fried shrimp
it's alright everything there is bread
it it doesn't even matter what you mean
the breading sounds like it sounds like
Wisconsin yeah it's the same it's the
same but nice I got him take that
Wisconsin why not be able to no listen
that's honestly way out the stats like
Wisconsin is the most dense home of C
team fandom there is yeah and you're
you're creating problems for me
is what I'm seeing so it comes from a
place of love yeah
since that works for you so but it was
during this time that the
the mayor of the town quiver maybe his
name came from the cool thing you keep
her arrows in or maybe I come you know
maybe it comes from the fact that he is
sort of a vibrating perpetually
vibrating coward that might be it also
in either case Denar forced him to go on
this trip and when they arrived at the
town of shrimp it was mostly on fire
there was a lot of fire and you didn't
see the whole thing it's possible that
some part of it was not burning but you
would have had to look the river was
probably exactly no just a dry bed it
was at this time booth my my cauldron
flipped it was an absolute treat for me
I was able to put Crenn are inside one
of the saddle bags of crisps rest robe
so that is a new situation the last
thing that occurred there was they heard
what sounded like a cry for help from a
young person now back at the ranch
simultaneously as soon as it became
clear that quiver had not been a helpful
person and was in fact quite bad at
knowing how to get around a place that
ostensibly he's quite familiar with they
indicated via mind bullets to the home
team which is to say rosy be stinger and
I was gonna see your true name not my
truth no I have a true that day all
right no no it's crazy walnut and Rosie
broke into Quivers Hut found what seemed
to be pretty robust evidence that he was
passing messages back to Merrick sharp
the leader of the reclamation group a
kind of band consortium that operates in
the summer hills that is where we left
our heroes the very last thing was that
you had an opportunity to talk to a cool
bird and you wanted him to take your
message back right away
and let's see I think I think I actually
have the message that you wrote down for
these people yeah oh yeah we can take it
right away
no he wouldn't think of it he wouldn't
die right away because he's a bird
it says Ms - very dangerous
reinforcements have arrived your men
will never survive await further
instructions Q but this bird was not
into taking it back right away it just
got home just got some seeds that's true
but in the a.m. it has given you its
bird word to whatever extent that's the
word that has value that it's gonna
carry this miss it for you I believe
that all right
you know us bill beak well the
description that that Ryan had was that
it was actually in some kind of S&amp;M gear
and that's an enduring image I have to
say I don't know I don't know if it's
horror or pleasure like I don't know how
to feel about the image I don't know if
the mask has a place for the beak or if
it's designed in such a way as to
incorporate the beak or to enhance the
beach the beach hole for the bank but
then there's a gag in the beach mouth
there's something for everyone
it's a Radio one out are look it's a
range of experiences that's the key
yeah now so the wrist rich tapestry of
life indeed so where do we want to start
our adventure who wants to who wants to
engage with this rich narrative so
you've you've that that birds gone to
bed we're done until morning I already
it maybe you're still sifting those
papers or something as far as us yeah we
hear that cry from the burning town of
shrimp is it echoing all around you here
it seems to be very particular what so
we're watching from the edge of the
woods yes not whales yeah we hear a
whimper I don't think we should get
close I think we should send a scout I
think we should do one of your own are
yeah it's just scent so
Crenn Arielle you know I hope for the
best you gotta grow up sometime
yeah are we doing any more downs this is
what you do yeah come on you over here
oh and we do this news for me yeah I
think we should send one of your your
menagerie as a scallop that makes sense
now which I think I could I can afford
to send out Locati
which one can you part with you've got
so many yeah exactly well I have nice
yeah well hold on a second the problem
is that I don't know that velvet would
be able to be of much use certainly
couldn't carry an injured personality
isn't Felmy busy back at camp make many
Velvets are ya I don't think though it's
the right well the right flee but you
have options for this at least just to
discern what the scenario is
well this could be a trap of some sort
as well it could be bandits still up you
know lingering about the place is on
fire mmm
Logano I could send away because I am
mildly I'm gently sighted at somehow I
got enough ice for both of us yeah yeah
you're rid of the rest uh yeah so um I
relieve legate of his staff form and
coils around my my forest yeah boils
just thick bands look a solenoid yeah
exactly it's a it's like it's like the
fruit by the foot yeah it's for you not
done yeah
and I say the patty there's someone in
trouble don't eat them go find where
they are who they are in their condition
I'm just gonna switch sight with him
what's it what's the range on that would
I be able to comfortably do it from the
distance we are from the from here yeah
he is unique to you and you're you know
you have some kind of an affliction that
has overtaken at least one of your eyes
mm-hmm the bond between you and magadi
is pretty substantial by this point okay
so I release him okay I take I take
possession of his senses and drive him
yeah guide him through those done that
path
okay but you can see as you are it's
like a drone I guess in a certain
respect now you can see as you're
passing through shrimp is clearly a bit
farther along like if this was some kind
of a like a game they would be a level
two or three village so there's there's
more individual housing less communal
housing and as it as it passes through
like whatever whatever force came
through here acted with great swiftness
there's a lot of sorts still in
scabbards hmm
it was clearly very very fast approach
but lagari can can absolutely perceive
the origin of this of this cry ooh yeah
what are we looking at is it in a hiding
in a house yeah absolutely but it's it's
in a house where the roof has partially
caught on fire and as ligado sort of
crosses the threshold there there is
clearly a young person crying beneath
what appears to be a set of of Timbers
or a hastily constructed defensive
structure I see how young is this person
I see here you probably guessed I mean
here how old are you now
Oh huka the wrist was like 300 yeah
exactly
this was this would have been a long
time ago human children don't stay
looking this way for very long right
right um but it's down there in that
range that I suspect cthe wrists Rob
would identify as from five to 20 down
there there's a newborn the soft the
soft area of human development
okay I'm gonna relay that back to you
that there's a there's
there's a very tall newborn trapped
behind some kind of a of a barricade how
do you even lay that to me dice it is
your name
I say is legate moving but you're still
standing there next yeah I'm standing
there for you yeah I don't like it still
I guess so look at what he's seeing
I'm nice you don't know why he just like
is the family I'm just Darius sometimes
he just does weird yeah like that
has been like Dennis been the case right
out yet Kris what are you doing oh sorry
good distraction like none of this has
anything more do let me send I'm gonna
send I know I need to to comfort this
this injured person but maybe the site
of this snake just like this massive
snake with a knife for a tail do you
think maybe that's right yes you're
thinking yeah yeah exactly
with a mouth that is full of more knives
you're saying that maybe this is not the
right demographic okay I'm gonna take
care of a keep ligarius site and i'll
i'll have lagari say hold on helps on
the way we're gonna take real good care
but the face just completely impassive
no no expression that could even
possibly be a horse it's just it's just
the two sets of like slightly scraping
against each other up took the hair clip
yeah I'm gonna have a say like what's
your name just its agency who's it who's
there
we're here to help I brought some
friends of mine we have to go down there
dinner I don't think a guy who can come
free this person is that the case yeah
well yeah why well you can do whatever
you want well while the guy is looking
like I want to assess the state of the
person and the barricade like this is
are they trapped yeah yeah
yeah they say they appear to be yeah
they're on their chest flat against the
ground in this structure they're like I
say it's either like hastily erected to
as a defensive means or as a place to
hide like a little fort gosh so they're
not pinned but they're there of their
own volition it's it's possible oh well
if they chose it I guess all right I
know it's your bed lyonie I'm jello the
kid there you brought this on yourself
goodbye and then before the guy leaves
it reveals its face and then exits yeah
I'm the last thing you see before you
die
no so if this person is trapped she's
reaching her hand out just like out in
front of her dinar do you think you know
can you get Crenn are and quiver back to
town where you want to wait for me here
here's something to do I mean I'm in a
mask of many faces now look like
whatever am Eric Sharpe was wearing I'll
keep my face covered that's the only
that's the Bandit I know yeah yes that I
was familiar with but I don't know if
this victim will be afraid of him I
would think like I want to look like a
bandit in case of bandit sees what I'm
doing that's true
you can misty stepped down there right
can't you body swap with my daddy can't
you gonna see step benders that's true
I forgotten all about that and I still
have misty step you can don't I you can
teleport down there I mean then getting
out is the next now we'll figure it out
afterwards yeah yeah yeah okay so this
is what I will do I will tell me more
I'm gonna miss you step down take the
Gottis place not in disguise yeah well
goes myself you go ask your thrist
around less frightening Oh No maybe
that's some stick find out
yeah I'll do that and then I will
attempt to like ascertain freeze I shot
her out of there
for them out of there sounds great and
then while you're down there if there's
any trouble I will immediately run away
I'll leave you to your car yeah I'm
gonna right away no right away my magic
oh yeah I got big elk we're already on
our way a lot of swords I'll just leave
dump this guy in the river young my
daughter I'm not to come back to the
forest oh yeah I'm not going back to the
town okay I let's let's do it I will
misty step into that slightly on fire
house exactly and it is absolutely
progressing along the fast roof at your
appearance her eyes grow wide and then
you can see you can see that she is
trying to move out from underneath of it
but you can see her brown knit with pain
I'm sorry about how I look but I'm here
to help
let's see what I can what can I do what
can I solve yeah do I think that I would
be able to this beam small enough that I
could lift it or would I be able to its
pre hastily yeah the stuff is pretty
hastily assembled you think oh okay then
let me go and try and just start pulling
it apart how strong is kiss right isn't
that strong here like Nate Anderson I do
have made jam but that's not super
strong either we can look at each other
this may Jenkin looking a bounce yeah
turn Locati into a crowbar let's say
internal I got eNOS I'm certain oh
that's leverage to line that's true
yeah let me do that and with the child
is a fulcrum I will move this is physics
a little one day it's a lesson yeah yeah
let me okay let's return ligardi to
staff form and see if I can get a get a
wedge in and and pry this off of you
exactly there is a at first there is a
shriek as you're beginning to shift the
weight of this beam but then she is able
to pull herself out like elbow over
elbow but she tries to she tries to get
completely up onto her feet and she's
not able to let me see what's going on
where's that where's that injury where
are you hurt yeah it's the left ankle it
seems like she's trying to put pressure
on that okay no no she's not in a
position to explain it you don't think
no no let's not do that
I will pick her up there might still be
explained ER there I have friends at
that top of the hill there might be and
it's about and she's like you do heard
there were so many bandits when did how
long ago were they here so Tony tell me
what tell me how this is happening so I
could I can I can visualize so you are
carrying her like this yeah I don't know
like this in the in front right I
haven't I have not transformed yet I
have changed my appearance yet gotcha
but I want to stand at the I want to
stand at the entrance and kind you know
see if there's any sign of movement well
I explained her like the sisters bandits
about I'd may have to adopt a disguise
she goes to safety oh yeah she says
there's there's there's so many bandits
I mean how many how many friends do you
have I have we have many at a town near
here but it was me I have a very strong
friend and I've been a very strong milk
was made of some stars no oh yeah he'll
have a very cowardly man of no note so
as you are breaking as here breaking the
composition the detailed in indeed with
practical notes that could be of use to
the child so you were looking down into
the town as he has brought her out like
this oh yeah we were yeah we were hiding
on the edge of the woods looking down on
the town yeah yeah you can see in his
arms you can see the shape shift as he
is just communicating this information
you can see the body like twists almost
like a rope like in the middle of his in
the middle of his arms hold still now
yeah I say Darren do you see this Murray
just keeps like a little kid I'll give
him an opportunity to react to it very
well I like the idea that it's happening
in the middle of a big strong man and
there's an elk and that that shape is
like like twisting and almost like a
sound like a nautical rope stretching in
the breeze and you can see that the that
night shift has now entered the nice
shift for you um it's it's now sort of
like a tattered blue robe long arms
clawed fingers abut blue flesh like your
own greasy matted black hair like my own
behind yeah exactly it's really it's
basically like looking into the pup
mirror yeah yeah it said in distress but
no and immediately upon this shift
you're looking down you see the shape
change and she is immediately reaching
an arm up over your neck and trying to
flip you to the ground hmm
so that is initiative City ah welcome
aboard yeah I don't to yell say hey pay
attention you're in trouble yeah you're
being fought drop it
there's an active combat and you're a
participant I think I think if I'm being
like I sailed I wouldn't be like hold on
like trying to assess it while I think
you're welcome no no we're just wait
we're gonna once we enter into
initiative will merely release you we
have got all kinds of cool stuff
oh so look at which cool thing we're
gonna give away first illicit isn't the
ones on top here the rose the delightful
level up set of these sixes let's do
that let's do that so we'll we'll push
that through in the channel obviously
thank you so much for watching the show
so 20 is very high in our blitz yeah
well it's only 19 because then I'm
subtracting sighs oh man
omen has a negative one - so what do you
got his rasp still higher so that is
still higher a number of I know I'll be
a number yeah some B's a number of a
beasts yeah absolutely so dinar blitz in
you are seeing this Wrestlemania as
phenomena unfold before your very eyes
you have a front row seat so alright
pause my turn so we're up here towns
down here yeah how far like how far out
did they get towards us the I think I'm
pretty much outside the door the house
okay so your lights red yeah yeah you're
saying you're seeing you're seeing these
buildings sort of like cracking with
heat and he is sort of he's coming out
of the tiny trail that leads out to the
okay alright so you've gotten a few
steps yeah yeah you're at the edge of
the town it's not gonna fall on his head
no well I'm just trying to assess yeah
you're into sort of a burning another
courtyard but just you're on the edge of
the burning town you know we're still at
the farthest edge can i how far is that
can I get to him enough yeah turn on on
Clark morning yeah
and he do I see any bandits or anything
anywhere right you do not you don't
think so I mean I always see but you're
welcome to help do it yeah you've heard
about this incredible technique 16 it's
not a it's not a 20 but it's not almost
Norway in your and your quick scan you
you feel like you've assessed it
correctly you're not you're not aware of
any subterfuge mmm be rough
yeah all right there's another problem
I burned sending to tell you about the
well you're also being there a show
cleaver at the moment or I know that's
the plot so yeah yeah I got a run down
and save my sweet boy no this is good
so yeah I'll run down I will ride down
on Clark yeah a sword in hand
hey where's this toilet here's what it
is Crenn are in the Bjorn we're riding
Clark more I'll see you see you stir up
sword in my right hand quiver as a
shield and my left hand by the scruff of
his neck facing outwards he's a human
shield in this hand
and I got the sword in the sand and I'm
running down that I'm writing down a
jousting yeah it's exactly that you just
want you just want to know where he is
yeah obviously if listen his character
between like his like a vest on and if
you're up up through the - yeah on the
back yeah I see and you can sit there
comfortably like a kitten like a baby
kitten like this works
yeah so that's yeah it's you know right
up you're gonna write up on this new
this hag yeah that's so the hag and the
cthis are really a you know not yeah
they are they're a single it would take
some real doing it to target her to hard
to target her independently if it's
wrist okay you can just swing and
obviously as you're done you master I
would support that out yeah this Park
more hub Church uh
Clark more as I I think actually has the
DM you get to dictate like what his it
is if you when you find steed stairs an
amount yeah he gets he has all the all
the goodies he's an intelligence of five
he I I think he has more than five but I
gotta get the the book out yes whatever
the the stat kid is for me uh Fred yeah
he's gay I got that right here how do
you do oh that's why I was asking if you
had Jesus dinars attack it's true yeah I
know but I don't want to hit I don't
hurt you
yeah definitely could I wanna I want to
do a uh well I want to do a I don't want
to go swinging in with the sword but I
do when I do a kind of bludgeoning
attack so I'll swing a guy at you bust
as I would a shield just to kind of
knock you both down yeah I was gonna say
gets roll a match yeah now I don't wanna
let go home I don't know he's gonna do
he's a wild card but I'm gonna be able
to use him as a as a in here okay a nice
gonna do a little little bash with him
come in though the way that you might
like drive by and like open a car door
yeah yeah just a knock you both down and
then once you're never going to can
Skinner and I think it's good yeah Mary
died right so what would that be what
kind of just uh I mean it's I don't know
what my own arms yeah exactly
unarmed stuff right now down free for
this just go ahead and give you the role
I know I'll work ethic that was almost
another Twain that is that's kaijus mean
a good out of with your yet yeah yeah I
gotta burn these down anyway you can't
nope no want anybody not on the card so
he so he yelps and it is very
high-pitched um as you attempt to use
him as a glance in a radical
reinterpretation of the jesting art
everything else is pointy yeah no
antlers would have hurt it's quite
reasonable no cath wrist Rob your
initiative allows you to go before
let's see I guess this is just this is
pretty much just straight-up combat well
you can disengage and hop on and we
could run away how does that work I've
never I've never done that but well you
are currently you are not grappled by
this thing it doesn't go yet so you can
just throw her on the ground I guess
just try to just try to get away from
her right yeah I think when you're in
that proximity thought you still had to
distant no either yeah well yeah I mean
but all I would mean if you hadn't
disengaged is that they would have an
attack of opportunity which okay so how
is that all it is all right yeah I mean
okay
well unless unless you take some damage
and then you get to leave yeah
fire town yeah unless this thing is like
actively like gripping me I'm not doing
any helping yeah yeah to keep it watched
it has its own yeah it has its own
intentions here alright then yeah let me
let me dump it oh yeah I'm not helping
at all I just like dark yeah right here
so what I would like you to do is I
would like you to give me an athletics
check Thanks I've already done it it's
garbage don't even worry juice yeah it's
true let's do it
have some safe analysis all right
nightmare that would have been a 5 is it
the minus one okay 14 was that give me
pretty good what depends on now it
depends on how they do they get a
natural 20 womp womp womp womp womp
your servant has granted you a boon l ii
cool thing is this crazypants dice
holder from Elderwood
it's very very it's actually the the
guts of it are the same as the AI mu a
manual if you like those yeah exactly
has real organs inside just press your
dyson to them gently and they'll state
you'll see brand-new GI tract is it just
hangs onto those dice so you're trying
to your treat you're trying to disengage
with this thing so any and it is gets
got a hold of your legs so instead of
well like I was gonna say instead of
disengaging like I better drop it but
instead I piledrive myself
with it something you managed to suplex
your own self right so as you come by
you have you you swung a mirror at them
yeah because I missed a radical a
radical new technique and then you see
you see cthe wrists just try to shed
this parasite yeah um and they and they
end up in a even tighter knot mmm nice
job boys meanwhile I wasted I wasted the
20 on it to go first
meanwhile back at the Beckett promise
wall I know Rozier going because all
advance are dead I'm successfully
defended yeah exactly day one all done
and it's great the night hag like you
can see the lower lip just sort of like
retract from the teeth and then just
through its teeth you can see spittle as
it speaks in the language of the night
despite himself cuz riscos yes finally
okay how many hit points do you have
this is very very important role spell I
have good wrists look I need you in a
second I have 45 45 okay I'm feeling
good I got a I got a hag on me ma I got
a good night's sleep
hang on you all right
more juice okay you fall asleep
what like as you as you're hearing what
a time as you're hearing the words but
I'm a drow did you have do you have
special protection against this if I can
fall sleep let's find out it's a magic
spell well let's see oh I thought elves
elves had an ability to not go to sleep
you think oh well this I'm gonna help
you so much well because that's it's
generated but it's not the most clear I
might have messed that up
say ancestry or Athena it might be
let's find out judges I'm sure chat is
going oh yeah it's no good
I agree that's okay this is part of the
game well I'm just gonna say no here it
is it will be real dandy unless
everybody is opening a book you know a
choice race do it
Twitter earring elf traits mm-hmm
fans history magic can't put you to
sleep and I have advantage on saving
through that being charmed okay so try
it you have but what it does is it goes
out past that to other targets the house
pillar I can't even put a sleep either
okay a paladin was gonna say so but
Crenn are and the dumb quiver can be
flick this thing so crane alright do you
feel Crenn are just settles into the
battle Bjorn just a little little bubble
make it easier yeah that's great exactly
yeah and and and quiver does it just
dead weight goodnight this hanging off
like as you're riding his feet are just
kicking up against the ground I can deal
with this let me get easier to throw
people okay so that is that in so since
quiver is asleep that I can't do any of
those stuff that I do good job Jerry so
did our blitz in certain yeah okay you
still tangled up yeah I'm still rip
still roll around you don't have like a
poking attack well yeah now I can just
oh yeah as I could poke with the sword I
feel like here's the whip zipper any I
sitting on my chest like the old hag
from dreams yeah exactly where that is
that's actually the concept yeah no I
just gasps creature yeah so is she
sitting up or his are we like grappling
but she is she is
you guys are enmeshed to a certain
extent
but she is sort of like down on her
haunch okay and your vertical yeah all
right oh I'm vertical but you're laying
down like this and she's up there down
no it would be easier to get a hold of
this
she's teed up in a golf scenario yeah
okay all right yeah cuz if you were a
little higher oh yeah yeah I'm gonna
pull over this bag polo I'm just gonna
gallop by this time on the right side
where before it was on the left is using
the the mayors of card or this time on
the right I'm just gonna try to - polo
let's see it Yolo polo all right uh take
advantage - goose pretty goose that
that's a - that is wrong on rolling like
gangbusters
you started out do you use the 20 up
front nine plus six fifteen I know it's
just me and my you just whipping her man
windy out today hot it's swim straight
what's up
now I'm gonna pause the initiative after
that turn for a moment to go back to the
town of promise so after you have fixed
that new missive onto its leg you've
allowed it to rest in its cage as you
are turning to leave the hut the Midwife
you can see her sort of silhouetted in
the doorway oh yeah she says what's this
what's this then
and I say treachery of the highest order
agreed explain yourself girl not me
you're mayor mayor of our town who has
been here since its founding and you
have been here since yesterday I said a
useless mayor by your own words and
proof lies here before you he is still a
person of promise and you are a dirty
woman
who fed your whole town not hours ago
you had help from the wild
I called fish for your people now while
I get super indignant she's like
thinking in the back were just like oh I
so don't need this from the likes of you
so rosy doesn't she holds no truck with
this sort of thing of course she's not
about to be dressed down in this way and
she takes a step forward and her the
momentum of it doesn't stop she actually
continues forward and falls into the
Midwife what
so the Midwife reaches her arms
underneath Rosie's arms and sets her
aside and says what have you brought to
this town
she turns over Rosie beasting her and
you can see that the lips themselves are
almost like a golden yellow color and
there's forking veins of colour out from
the lips and you think that her you
think that her throat may be swelling as
well oh okay
so the mid Midwife has got a hand deep
in that pouch she is rummaging around
for the tools of her art okay and she
says I need you to explain yourself much
quicker than you were before and I say I
say I received word from our companions
to check the mayor's household because
something was awry when we arrived we
found he had been contacting the bandits
behind you back she sets her jaw at this
and she reaches a hand up you can see
people are walking back and forth
preparing you know preparing for the
evening
huh
zooming jealous if she snaps for help
someone to come over
and so when notices and begins to walk
over and then false face first in the
middle of the rough path between the two
bunk houses great so there's a blight in
this town wonderful so upon seeing rosy
like this I rush over to her and well
that's like you know and the grandmother
the Midwife is gentle gentle have you
seen this before it's happened it
doesn't happen on its own how does this
happen
it happens because someone intends it to
happen and does a specific sequence of
things what things poison fish oh yeah I
was like is it from the vial we found
earlier she says this is not that this
is gullet and she is she is um she has
taken a knife out mhm and she says you
may not want to look at this oh yeah
this is some Xena Warrior Princess stuff
did this in every episode of Essex she
listened to every episode okay yes yeah
okay
and and so gr you'd are you here for
this uh yeah well it's gonna be very be
very near absolutely so you you have
seen this I mean you are not unfamiliar
with I'll steady l-step yeah you are not
I'm familiar with poisons mm-hmm
and she is able to make a slit in that
swelling and she has a series of small
objects
fashioned to allow air to pass through
and she says I can make it a remedy for
this it's painful but not fatal but it's
it's a 10 hour kettle tell me what you
need
she says I have most of it I'm gonna
need someone to babysit this kettle say
no more
right she says I need you to help me
carry her into my hut and then I need
you to help me carry the rest of these
people into the bunk houses and yes
she's saying this it's just probably
half the town you just seeing people
like couples are walking and then one of
them falls down like this this town
isn't a grip of something okay things
were not good before so I'm gonna go
ahead and enhance my own ability for
strength it's like nice to see some left
ahead Bowl strength yeah so I can get
those guns - nice
absolutely two at a time so you helped
her you helped her with Rosie so
carefully
absolutely you helped her move everyone
out she is she is along with you
arranging them in the lower levels of
these bunks mmm so these homes have been
transformed into a kind of quick triage
center yes after that after after people
are set up and their families are with
them she retreats to her own hut with
you and you you've seen you've seen
systems like this before okay like she
has a she has a meticulously arranged
sequence there's fish drying elisa folk
medicine sit oh yeah this is a 100% CSI
medieval a medieval England situation
going on 100% so she gets the kettle
going and you have an opportunity to
learn from a master I'm ready here we'll
we'll jump back yes to that cthe rib we
got a night hag
over here there's a moment like you can
feel sort of like a tingling like a like
a pin cushion prickle in your like in
your in your fingertips and you you
blink a couple times and feel relaxed
but it's more of a spa treatment than a
mystical sleep system with Sleep Number
yeah zero nice concrete okay but if it's
my turn
yes let's see um I don't know I know I'm
gonna do I'm sure I think it's a quick
before but this isn't me the great that
either and yeah nice to see you
yeah eyes to see you it's not a good fun
but but I'm gonna go ahead and you
apologize to the phone yeah I have it
sorry I don't have anything prepared and
then the eyes have it and then going
straight going straight grace drink
something like that what I want to do is
I want to cast them dancing lights but I
believe she says if this is a drab
classic she's looking into my face I'm
putting I'm putting lights here light
there
and I'm one right here cuz the third eye
Neal gland uh-huh just gonna blind her
with them get that get that glow man
actually have your card uh a card for it
let me see you might to the books to the
book what's more a book heavy episode
yeah like it dancing lights talking
about some tanzanite its concentration
one action tonight's for torch size
lights within range
wolves are hover in the air for the
duration uh I mean it doesn't say here
like if it goes right inside of an
eyeball it will blind down the character
but I'm assuming if it's a night hag she
wanted Troy it
you're trying to your intention when it
bakes make sure I understand your
intention is to inconvenience this night
act yeah I want to put lights really in
her highways yes yeah but nobody likes
it you could surprise me with some Laura
never be like aha so that's rank
this is a combat equivalent of
uninviting Super Bowl party just no no
you don't know it's like unfriending
yeah no no follow block it's equivalent
it's the equivalent of muting a follower
yes that's what it is
she follows still there that's a low
threshold is all I'm saying
yeah no give me those lights right in
there yes all right like it full-on how
about two in one in each eye of hers and
then one in each nostril because I
thought it was funny well I did it I
just need you trying to be creative with
it he's manic swing it I have four and I
don't feel like doing only two no so so
these remind me about the dancing lights
like it's it's just a bright light
that's all it is it's listen ten
thousand candle wine yeah it's a hot
light I've done this before
yeah to to start it to delight and amaze
no not to like not stretch enjoy but as
a distract you don't want to it's like a
flashbulb yes you you basically create
this wreath of light no right in the
yeah right in there there's no fly zone
yeah I'm not making it like a like a
ring light so she couldn't do her makeup
bring that hags do right so you you
manufacture their misery other than
anything else we want to know about
these lights physically you have to roll
against it for it to be like a
distraction or something oh I don't know
did you 5d6 well it's just saying well
that was the other option yeah but I
don't want her to run away I want I feel
like we need to kill it unless it goes
back and tells everybody what's going on
yeah so she get disadvantaged I don't
remember what it is
yeah don't worry Oh if if there are
white space by it
said the term I don't know why I'm
making some up so dragon yeah well it's
a canned trip right I mean I think it's
just a kids with prey it's not the
flight of course yeah I think you're
right it's 46 no don't you try sex
it's 46 damage yeah yeah we're good yeah
yeah she did know you create these
twinkling bulbs I mean it's a full-sized
orb
listen hey don't don't minimize what
I've been able to accomplish there no
she liked her her eye starts to twitch
and she's and she's like she like it
like an insect she's like trying to wave
it away or then going nowhere no they're
not going they're not going anywhere at
all have I'm asked exactly that's right
exactly
it's very very good what she is going to
do instead if she is going to put asleep
yeah today she is going to swipe at you
with this brutal claws I understand yeah
ac is 16 oh then you are hit oh oh did
you ride your plus one
yeah okay yeah don't forget I got
excited about you got you got super cool
rings that I stole from Chris Perkins's
campaign he whose house he uh so this
this catches you just vertically
straight down the the chest for 12
points yeah how close are we on land I'm
still right next to you right I'm
assuming yeah right you stopped there
yeah I'll take it
I can tank my new ability yeah with this
new level I got a divine Allegiance so I
can take the damage instead of willing
party and I can tank it I can't amend it
whatever the number you take I can just
tell
I'll take in 12 or 20 club I have what I
was already it takes 16 that's awesome
this is great this is gonna be a great
opportunity how often can you use it
that's just a power it's just an awesome
until he's dead Alice falls over dead
it's just a thing I do it's like
constantly running like I would see
other when I got the the order of
protection like mmm it's just the thing
so everyone got to get nice and close ya
know get just all sorts of buffs yeah
the buffet
yeah so climb on that yeah so why are
you like a hat yeah in the against the
arm quiver whoo whoa it's a wake after a
turn oh good for him he's just he's
doing it now yeah he's hanging off of
his a tasteful vest didn't our boots a
canter I wish you guys were just
separated and I could just pick you up
pick her up she's just hanging out
that's what I'm gonna do I'm gonna just
get her out I'm gonna break you guys
apart I'm gonna act in tandem with Clark
more I want Clark more to jam his
antlers into her and I'm gonna pull you
off I'm gonna forcefully separate you
two like that probably do it by yourself
huh yeah yeah yeah okay okay okay how
tight of a grip does she have I guess
there's also a president well I mean she
just slashed him you so she's got one of
her hands off at least yeah yeah I I
think especially now that she is
engaging in these melee attacks I think
that you could probably strike that we
can specifically because we can do
tandem attacks me and the steed yeah
this is a way to get some damage on her
separate you guys and I can pull your
right to near feet I'm gonna link you up
on the Clark moon or something nice uh I
roll for that strength well I get do I
got a roll for me and then roll for a
Clark one roll from Clark more first and
we'll figure out the first part cuz
that's a big part of the plan I forgot
to do event you're good yeah fine
fifteen selfie get when you get to my
strength rings don't even worry about it
i i I'll handle that damage on this side
all right how about my my pull mm-hmm
grabbin so evil yeah yeah we want
athletics
okay all right cool I am I'm athletic of
so that's great yeah yeah it's it's
it's gonna be an easy call I'm gonna
juice this one it's feast or famine with
me
these are swords of plowshares here so
show capsule net because we've gone
through our incredible gifts it's it's a
mere gift card but it's like actually a
good time to have a gift card because
all the c-team and acquisitions
incorporated dice boxes stuffed every
stop okay I really I took advantage so
I'm rolling again maybe it's another one
hey if it's another twenty I'm gonna
give it that card that's less so it's a
26 okay so you gain a couple HP I meant
like strengthened by that lift yeah you
fold backwards just fine snaps you get
pulled back
yeah right so so Clark more snorts and
just catches and just guides her to the
ground just like imprisoned her against
the ground and then you just you just
freak you just reach down to just grab
describe this process for me what does a
natural 20 let your friend did I look
like denier knows nothing but next
scruff grabbing big guy over here by the
scruff of his neck you just grabbed you
by the scruff of your neck and just kind
of like but like in a like a pizzeria
like it's just like a loop like a
one-armed like whoop and then you land
perfect perfect ten the Russian judge
gives 9.5 what's his deal don't know
everyone else has got tens across the
board you land safely as just on a
pillow right on old Clark Moore's house
it says somebody who's you know used to
you know the power of flight making me
just go limp yeah like by the time you'd
ripped me and you're pulling me up I'm
like a noodle there's no complaint yeah
laying it over the back wherever your
shoulder yeah um very preppy
sweater right so you're you
yeah exactly just like just the sleeves
so draped on me so you have you're gonna
move there's a time to get out of here
oh yeah I guess I mean we saw the move
because they didn't move cuz we were
right there on the mix yeah
yeah well let's get Adil I need to fight
this thing No
so she's gonna unleash a swipe on one
Clark more yeah that's fine first
fuckity him what can what I swear
to look I swamp
okay I want to apologize - Patrick room
our social media measures because he has
to do he has to check he has making
loving this out $20 is a $20 gives you
that's too much we need to talk
about how much these gives to the Ferger
thing all right anyway so it's $20 for a
natural 20 I mean I guess I can see the
synergy but you know by the same token I
lose money over can we do let's just
reassign credit of 10 yeah exactly
Stickley the same one yeah I mean yeah
any number it's statistically gonna be
the same so usually you have picked you
have picked him straight up off of the
ground slapped him over the back dropped
him a couple times to keep him sharp
just a quick lap and then it and then
it's time to go yes I don't think no
fight this thing let's just move don't
forget coriander we're here for she
could find her way we'll ride back
pasture like come on horse yeah yeah
she's still at the edge of though yeah
so when we run back oh just she'll
follow us I miss yet hopefully Oh we'll
see just we have a gold in her face
yeah just just get this dispassionate
yeah you can see that like just in the
in her sort of copper plates you can
just see the dancing fires of this town
but she is observing dispassionately
so you you basically
you basically pull your way back out the
night hag is fast but not that fast a
night man cometh yeah yeah absolutely so
they so she chases you between these
soft rolling hills you can see in the
moonlight for a while but eventually you
see her just dematerialize like in
mid-stride how good that you guys are
knowing where to go it's gotta wake yeah
he's a wink I mean does he want to does
answer for his crimes
yeah yeah say do you a friend let's go
back to promise unless you'd prefer to
be cut up and eaten right here by me so
that seems like an intimidation check me
gonna intimidate you do it
I'll try roll it sure well yeah it's
true roll dice it's not a bad one but
I've never really used it before all my
goodness what is what happens it's a 1
yeah I'm not gonna take advantage I
won't all right I say tell us which way
to go or I'm gonna or unless you want to
be cut up and eaten right here and then
a little piece of gum that I was trained
just falls on now I'm a little
embarrassed yeah 0 is there a moment
where you consider getting it yeah I
reach for it and it kind of like bounces
off yeah and then it's just in my hair
and I but and I'm like that's right like
try to make it like it so cool stunt but
he doesn't mind as scared as he is for
like it gives some comfort
oh man I'm B I am actually being held by
complete emphasis no I
I want to amp the intimidation on the
back end of that okay because he's not
buying it at all but I want to be like
don't fall for this act he's crazy
my boys crazy he will eat you yeah I've
seen him do it he's already thinking I'm
always gonna do to your eyes and I'm
gonna intimidate here listen please
don't roll any 20s okay I'm I guess it
wasn't a one I'm gonna intimidate
and I'm gonna take the advantage I'm
Lola hi today
all right six minutes all right yeah but
plus six so 22 I guess yeah that's all
right so that's no that's that's that's
quite good there is a there is a a
moment where he grows very still in your
grip
just like it goes from like I don't
believe that - like wait here yes yes
like no that's that's an extra level of
crazy man it's the crazy can't believe
yeah that's the crazy
that's that's what you avoid so he said
he becomes he becomes a kind of physical
compass and then he just raises it if
whenever you need a point between two
points he just goes just half-heartedly
raises up he's a he's seen better days
he's seen better days here exactly so
you guys are on your way back to town
Crenn are has not seen anything she has
been asleep the entire time you didn't
get to see on awesome stuff I didn't
know know if she got to see no night
hags I keep looking down like wow but
that what was that like wake up day
ah so walnut look you have shiest
she has the Midwife who we determined
canonically is named with mid Whitman
it's just Whitman oh sorry it's good oh
no we're we're creating it now for
crowning cannon even as we speak
all right I think I'm just dragon yeah
thank you I mean no um so she has she
has set she has set herself to this task
and you can hear her mumbling something
but you'd have to listen close to hear
it I'd love to go ahead listen
processional
Plus 760 oh that's quite good
uh she says she is actually seeing I'm
sorry for thinking the worst of you but
it's an apology like a blow the human
threshold of audibility my little over
here yeah yeah I just I just I just not
like like far away dogs forgive her uh
yeah I just not matter yeah
safely yeah so she says have you spent
any time over a cauldron uh near one not
over them Jesus she says tell me and
then she is she is grinding things fresh
she is clearly like her body can do this
without any mental effort she just knows
how her body knows how to do it I'd say
I said well where I come from we had
many mothers of medicine uh-huh she says
have you ever seen one of these and she
is she's going through her spice rack
essentially nice um and you can while
away literally as long as you want to
it's literally the most normal shift
like she knows so much about it that she
doesn't know what she doesn't know the
one on one part of the process anymore
oh yeah it's just like she just she what
she just wants to invite you wherever
you are and to just in cash mmm what is
she showing I couldn't be with us she
has all the names for it like all the
names she has for it or wrong gotcha
like it's all yeah exactly it's like
some of them are some of them are body
kingsfoil yeah exactly yeah exactly it's
it's it's straight up yeah it's it's
straight up token earring from end to
end
perfect but um yeah there's there's
always there's always another container
somewhere that she has to sift through
when tell me how things go when you
return of course you need to come
through the river over the fruit of the
woods
well you were already through the woods
actually this is just the river no no I
think juvy we should just ride right up
to the mayor's house we should just
arrive because we know all and a rosier
in there yeah this guy has been nothing
but trouble I want to ride into the
middle of town and just throw them on
the ground and be lying this is the bad
guy J'Accuse yeah yeah your neighbors
aren't on fire and it's this guy's fault
he's working with abandons yeah just
roll back in you you make a big scene
it's pretty late here in this it's
pretty late here in the town and so
there's still some activity just because
people need to have time to themselves
after spending the rest of the time yeah
I mean the whole wealth out of the earth
also half of them falling ill yeah
they're not they don't familiar with
that right that that exact process here
but there's enough people that you think
will be able to hear it but you don't
say make a big public display yeah
exactly yeah it's just like people
people fewer than you would expect start
to appear in the doorways of the bunk
houses yeah it's gonna say I actually do
we know you did you guys relay the
message back to us we just told you to
check but there's being fishy yeah yeah
the door the door to the door to the
mayor's
Hut is still is still oh but we know
he's we know he's fishing and we know he
was intentionally traveling this away
and we know he's well yeah whether or
not he's not trustworthy I'm gonna try
and find Paulette Rosie yeah so I'm and
I had last place I know as mayor's hut
so I'm gonna go there yeah you can do
you want to hang out in the square and
parade this guy or an hour wouldn't want
to publicly shame this guy it's right
over the back of the only bullying him
yeah
but he wouldn't have a reason I'm
operating with knowledge that he
wouldn't have what cuz I forgot they
didn't yeah return the missive that's
true
it wasn't he wouldn't a hundred percent
no so you wouldn't do it it won't be
hard to secure it as you as you enter
the hut you can tell it's been pretty
trafficked just in the in the ground
inside but as soon as as soon as you
come in there this there's a bird in a
cage next to an empty cage and as soon
as you come in with lagari it begins to
you you discover that there is a kind of
coup that is hostile it's it's
surprising at first but you know and for
some reason Lagasse does not like the
bird either hmm that's in a cage you
can't get at it yeah that's no good
anybody this is the opposite of a bird
but I don't want to upset some of these
pets so I'm gonna let stuck Locati away
I'll just say no no yeah if let's say
that he's return to staff form and maybe
that the mouth is moving in a
frightening way no no chill he's still
he's dying yeah he issues a couple more
surgical wrecks to the bird and then
aqueous he's harmless bird he's harmless
is it are you in here who's in here
nobody's here it's just but no no you
are you are completely by yourself
except for this bird although it's been
more reassessed yeah and it's because
you did it once over so the place is had
been turned over all the documents are
collated yeah yeah this place up mess
except for the desk
yeah every day it's in out like there's
new trays our documents are in perfect
order there it is
yeah I don't know if it'll it'll work at
this if I don't have proximity I want to
not run a follow that of that rule mm-hm
I mean I'll reach out and see like wha
Rosie what like looking in other
directions do I see motion
is there any like specific hub not
activity Rosie does not answer my free
dance yeah absolutely I say um I say
this come to the Midwest Hut now yep
agreed
yeah sure it's real jaunty yeah love to
oh and then great she says bring the
mare yeah we have the mayor and he
almost got us cooked and eaten well he's
working with the bandits Sal so well is
it going well there you are you were you
have him in your grip yeah I never let
him go yeah I still got him scruff of
the neck and make your show yeah yeah I
knew it I know right yeah that fits yes
that all lines up yeah I made so I make
my way over to them to that midwife's so
you were just parading around in the
centre of the town in the middle of just
yelling this guy sold you all out make
it a big show of it I'm really mad that
he tried to just take us in the wrong
direction it's actually about being in
canoes removing it could be it's more
they disrespected my time yeah you know
how much my time is worth and I spent it
circle him random trees and also he
killed another town it was responsible
for the death of your of neighbors and
friends over that hill
shits gone to remove it I hope you like
shrimp I have no one here like shrimp I
know you're gonna trade your silver for
now no chance no chance no chance no way
so people are people are coming out
rubbing sleep out of their eyes trying
to parse this I thought on the ground I
could push him I say tell him tell
everyone what you did he says
yeah I tried to put together a deal that
would save this town that's that's
correct mm-hmm
truth uh yeah
I pick him back up Allah he turn truth
but I can him up I'll him up
and get my own quick little backhand
drag it no I grabbed him and I look at
him and I use command and I say confess
and then I throw him back on the ground
yeah that's really really awesome right
yeah he is not able to resist this
compulsion and so it starts out with him
making without with him enunciated a
position that involved yes there were
secret communicates what was the purpose
to create a situation I wasn't telling
them the real information that's like
he's like this isn't it interesting so
these four roll into town and all of a
sudden there's a brand new narrative we
have worked together in this community
for months creating wealth wealth we all
share in and then as the command starts
to take hold the language shifts and you
can tell that even he is surprised by
the depth
it's like liar liar can't stop his own
and breath he says because these four
individuals let's call them true heroes
for lack of a better term and his eyes
are wide but the mouth is continuing to
operate he says yeah did they discover a
plot of mine absolutely have I worked to
undermine this town ever since they came
into contact with me yes did I sell your
lives for silver 100% I love it it's got
the political cadence and he's even he's
doing yeah exactly
you're waiting for the but but I never
come this is come he's like did I did I
introduce a file into the river that
terrified fish absolutely yeah
that's on me when I was on my way out of
town
did I poison the stores of fish that
they had gathered absolutely yes that's
a 100% that's 100% I never ate it
look at me I'm hale and hearty so he got
up I did not speak to a woman in
Flint Michigan who's trying to provide
for a family so so now he is now he is
literally just standing in the middle of
this yeah just standing in the middle of
this simple Town Square just reciting
crime like going back to his school days
it's been bob denied your loan yes out
of spite yes I hear this commotion and
just be like standing in the doorway of
the boats right like absolutely yeah
well I mean yeah I would be like well
you can't even be angry I get mad I'm
happy now I'm like oh well yeah there's
something that we should do we should
change the missive that the bird has and
tell them to attack from the direction
that we're going to fortify tell them to
eat all the fish oh yeah they come come
in they'll offer resistance they all
have prepared a fish banquet where
you're crying in arms go into the cave
but he's the explosives there we will
sign our surrender
okay yeah you don't change that miss
here oh yeah and at the front at the
front gate of the town you can see a
shape beginning to coalesce oh no and
it's okay okay and it's no and as
they as they grow closer to the light
you can see
it is sorta uh uh and she has five
swords with her and two bows um that she
drops off in the middle she has clearly
come into the middle of a like she has
arrived at a moment in this town and she
she drops off all these weapons like a
to pile basically and then looks up to
you dinar I say no you're a karna I know
yeah she reaches up Crenn R and then
Crenn R goes from one bjorn to another
bjorn like the transfer is complete
sleep is maintained yeah yeah never
fighting from the kid I know yeah yeah
you missed a bit but the mayor here
she's just filming it ah the mayor here
well first let's go back a bit me and
that guy big big waves yep I went over
to frame on fire couldn't do anything
about it
she mayor's fault she nods with some
gravity yeah
mayor's fault and then and then I look
over and I see woman in doorway and I go
and that one uncovered this mayor's plot
count one wave just big wave and yeah
and everything the night hag sat on me
while he was doing some kind of
equestrian maneuvers some kind of uh
dressage yes as effective as it was it
was just worse than she says so she
steps forward into the middle of the
square and there's some there is
whispering from those who are still
awake mm-hmm
at this
and she says do you identify yourself in
any particular way in the missives you
send to Mary sharp is there anything
encoded is there anything we need to
know about writing a letter hmm to him
and he doesn't he doesn't say anything
he is still trying to come to grips with
the fact that he just narrated a
documentary about his entire life
literally every bad thing he's ever done
is he I guess he's compelling sighs I'm
sure he it was him so being compelled to
confess would he have to answer that I
guess that's not a confession yeah like
I mean it could be like again like lair
lair where he's just like intimidated I
mean he's just not gonna say it yeah I'm
been intimidated scale laughing right
I've just been the bane of this dude's
existence so I might as well you know
not stop now you gotta give him the big
stuff give him get in there go get get
down off his face or get it dumb off
Clarke more get in his face and then say
his face take it off to the side take
his face yeah period so are we talking
about a dur conic entitlement scenario
no I don't need let me show you here
with the threshold I don't need to
entitle him just to get this bit of info
out I think we can creatively do it I
will just roll to intimidate and I'll be
like I'll just remind him of all the
I've just put him through using him
as a weapon just influencing forcing my
will on him and then I'll just say I had
the lady asked you a question buddy
seventeen goose yeah let's give it after
everything else that has happened his
his reserves are shot and the narrative
he has been telling himself about how
this is going to resolve itself is
definitely showing some cracks in it and
so he said he says
when I when I send a letter to the
reclamation group
it never includes names of any kind and
the first letter the first word always
begins with T hmm no niggaz first word T
I got this
and Saoirse walks up tilts her head to
the side like turns her nose tilts it to
the right and kicks him in the knee and
when he would he collapses forward there
is his head is off before you see the
sword come out oh Jesus and when she
puts it back in mmm
she walks off into the mine was he could
have still been useful oh yeah -
somebody shadow council mayor Lear
Spacey hey we have reached our break
we're going to take full full use of
this break we're really gonna wring it
out and maximize its utility get it done
and then as soon as we're done we'll
come right back and then we'll finish
this game it's gonna be a real thanks so
much for coming
don't go nowhere hello I'm Jared K
Hortons and this is Tess C teams now
when last we saw our heroes the vile
[Music]
blaggard mayor do wealth uncool person
quiver had very very very recently been
decapitated by Saoirse princess of scala
you might recall her that is really the
last thing that happened time will
resume
now oh well that is going to lean in and
to the hut and ask the Midwife may I
have two minutes to fix something in
here
no at the mayor's house hmm sure you can
we need a mayor now hey maybe you could
run like we'll talk about that later and
she's gonna sprint over to the the
mayor's hut in the Midwest you see the
Midwife is actually going out mm-hmm and
she has collected a few strands of the
hair from quivers head and taking it and
stored it and brought it away huh she
has gathered some of those she gathered
some of the the blood from the neck and
put that away
like this is she this is a this is a
moment for her who knows maybe she gets
excited about this sort of thing she's
like we're like standing in the town
circle and you like run out of one
building and then run it with a build up
okay Wally oh yeah so on my way through
I'll say I'll say team meeting at the
mayor say be like yeah it'd get Rosie
out here we're going to see how there's
cool stuff I did I'll say a grandmother
in the town or stricken ill and then I
go no time to talk and then it run into
the mayor set absolutely
throws open the door and her eyes are
darting she's looking for the bird she's
a bird
aha yes you but she doesn't have anymore
she doesn't anymore speak with animals
these with animals and so the the pigeon
or the is cooing like demonstratively
like it's it's ready to carry on the
previous conversation well well it will
take some seed from her pocket and so it
in the in the bird's cage
oh yeah it's it become it very quickly
like within a moment becomes TechFest
so I'll take that time to very gently
and carefully take the old missive out
and she starts to pen a new one on the
stationery tell me more
no name what does it say it says they
will not fortify against the hills you
must attack from the high ground which
is so far I mean that's it
nothing yeah you better so from a higher
plane and her reasoning is because this
is the area that they've chosen to
fortify yeah exactly and now they can't
you know you have the wall and then you
have a trenches all day and now they can
hopefully instead of saying don't come
at all cuz we don't think that that
little think is a helpful note yeah
mouki maybe direct them social will that
up and put it in the pigeons leg and
then she's looking around see if they
were where the guys are you guys so you
it so you have resolved the issue of the
missive attached to the bird okay the
bird gasps marvelous you would you get
there first and if this is acceptable
when I enter I'm saying like what's
wrong with Rosie why is she sick and I'm
and I'm my hands are bloody and I'm
putting a stopper on a while that is
full of blood also I took a head stop at
the mayor's corpse just right just for
just a little quick just for a moment to
hit some of that sweet blood
I was wondering how to do that but then
when the Midwife did it I felt like all
council does not take this one maybe
it's a cool good it's like a drinking
fountain yeah yeah exactly
oh yeah you don't want a situation where
it's like partial merry usage it's not
done it's not done the firehouses waste
not one not an organic one so we need to
show up I'm slightly out of breath they
go grandmother fell
some sort of sickness and I assume it's
from the poison fish mm-hmm but half the
town is ill and we have to stand over
this cauldron for ten hours the Midwife
and I to concoct this cure and then I
say I tell them what I wrote in the
missive and I say we need to fortify and
defend that specific area let's see I
think how long have we been out I think
I would have to reinstate yeah yeah and
since it is definitely time for rest
yeah yeah you need to you need to rest
yeah you go back to the Midwife and she
is she has got a massive paddle
something that might have been like an
oar or something it's a Bruin far inland
like far away from its natural home and
she is she like 12 big stirs and then
she lets us spin and then like chic this
whole ritual here that is that is
involved in it but you think you can
tell that she is flagging a bit okay um
so I'll come in and really bring take
over absolutely so she she has a little
journal and she flips it over and she's
like like I don't need to look at it
anymore but it sort of goes over the
steps that are required in this specific
sequence it would be worth reading over
them in detail okay and I would say that
this exists in a document see continuum
okay Greg is it's about detailed value
so I would like you to make a check okay
hmm
what check document see is a wisdom
skill got it well you're lucky for me ah
Oh Rosie's life yeah whoo 18 almost no
18 plus 4 22
so you assess it it seems like a
negative space thing like the pauses are
just as important as this shirt exactly
so you set it up and so in your in your
mind you sort of make a cadence like you
see her last one and then you step in
for her so what what do you what is your
interaction with her as you oh I'm just
uh watching a master at work
like just in quite reverence so she she
something about her she has know her
midwife's Hut has no bed interesting it
has a central like log pole in the
center of it mm-hmm
and then she just has like a chair okay
she has like I'm just a gently rocking
chair that she sits in and her I scan
her eyes close and then a case she shows
say things like stir stop and as soon as
you were going to do it like she has the
cadence going like right behind you so
you're always doing it at exactly the
right time yeah what's next so it said
time to time to get some rest yeah
before I am i concerned that talking to
you would would interrupted that well
that's the thing like dinar would want
to help a sick friend and being you know
somewhat good and something of a healer
would want to go help but then like just
being like a hulking oath would be in
the way I feel like would be dismissed
out of hand pretty quickly it'd be like
you're more helpful outside of the room
I do need four hours rest otherwise I
won't have anything tomorrow mmm you
gotta get it well I'm saying this over
the thing right I'm assuming you've come
to the height now and you're like at
least looking at Rosie if she's sick
yeah yeah maybe I'm attempting dead to
contact her via awakened mind and I'm
sad I'm not getting anything back in a
tile I just want to see how deep it is
so yeah how far and it is
yeah I'm gonna when will this be done
will it take longer such that would I be
able to take over I don't think I look
good I don't know that she would
coordinated the directions we would have
hours laughter yeah yeah exactly
but before noon this process will be
complete a lot of this had to be started
in the middle of the night mm-hmm and I
take it that it seems like a little work
that's beyond the the the knowing like
the understanding of someone like or an
unseen servant couldn't take over for
this even though mechanically could
perform the task it doesn't know what to
look for and things like that it
wouldn't know how to troubleshoot but it
would be able to do it would be able to
perform all the basic parts of the task
yeah but that would also be a lot a lot
of efforts on a waste if there wasn't
somebody to direct it well couldn't the
Midwife director and the unseen servant
just do would just pay attention to what
she said yeah I gave it a knock that I
would also be really funny yeah okay
let's yeah let's do a Fantasia thing
here yes it's not to say and exactly if
I can hear the soundtrack
yeah me I'm gonna take ten units oh it's
all good these bars
I'm gonna instantiate a an unseen
servant and saying you to listen to
these instructions you're either a stir
to wait maybe you can fill it in yeah on
a dear velvet so I say no velvet cloth
on him though because I don't want any
of that to get on it right so he could
do the work you do the work nude I'm
just like looking for free yeah yeah
where he is and then giving the paddle
and being like okay and Whitman is now
leaning like he does no more rocking
she's now like leaning forward on the
chair and she she's I don't
who is this creature unknown but it does
do what he say within a reason will it
do what I say I can direct it to how
long it will when he stay with that it
will work for an hour and will have to
be reinstated which I could do then you
could then you could sleep and then I'll
take the other yeah yeah well do that
all right she she gets a like a old
lived in warm knit shawl and places it
around his shoulder equivalents so that
it is sort of swaying like a like a
pendulum and a grandfather clock yeah
while it is engaged in this and she is
netting that that is like the piece that
she needed to humanize it and now it's
like a now it's like a little nephew is
over she's giving it instructions but
there's way too much of extra
information right it's like that's it
very good yeah right that's very good
yeah she is
she is definitely she's not thinking
about the time in an hour an hour hands
pour it will be obliterated and cease to
be yeah and and cut wrists will would
tell her but something holds him back to
she needs it more than obviously more
than velvet does yes she is she has
found another shawl and she has put that
on on herself so they're quite the pair
swaying in front of this cauldron now so
you're gonna grab some rest
mm-hmm yeah I need my spells back my
shapes get your shapes back but then as
soon as I'm done with my four hours I'll
take back over nice yeah you you you'll
be you'll be catching just the very end
of it okay
by that time I'll take all the credit
yeah exactly
exactly
so we're now we're now moving into an
early morning phase and of course Crenn
are had no her sleep was not disturbed
in the least she began with a magically
assistant sleep and then just parlayed
that into a solid eight hmm hasn't dinar
did you like sleep in the mid website
like on a bunch of like animal skins
like all curled up in the corner did you
go to the bunkhouse
I think dinar would just be like in the
way I imagined dinar in them in white
house like wanting to help good
intentions but like tail knocking
over oh no it's not like him him who the
swords and the tail yeah I think that's
the whole place this smack and stuff
over is being full volume of the being
told he has to leave feel like you did a
good job but why don't you go to sleep
you did great and then just shown the
door that's really good yeah exactly so
you can see near the hut in a like a
grassy patch you can see Crenn are
playing with a small figurine of a
creature you may have seen they're not
they're not incredibly uncommon but it
would be yes that's it
cat no no it is it has a strange almost
like a pleated like a firm plate over
the top of its head and then the rest of
it underneath it almost looks like a
short squat crocodile but it's mah is
just massive and it has incredibly sharp
claws that they used to dig and burrow
no but it's a like I say it's a it's a
it's not an uncommon monster mm-hmm but
it's definitely not something one season
there in the city and she has a little
figurine it's about the size of a
grapefruit
[Music]
and she is playing a bunch of games with
this figurine that only she seems to
know she's like playing hide and seek
with a physical with an inanimate object
basically so and this is like in the
middle of the town square
no dude in the morning is just it's near
the midwife's hot okay all right so I I
wake up out of the bunkhouse and I come
out and I see that yeah yeah with my hot
bean water yeah
they have it it's ready squeeze yeah I
mean closing what's the what's the
what's the right up on this thing what's
our they understood to be dangerous
this is it's this is a figurine oh
you're not that was like oh they are
real tree playing with this creature and
the gala this no no no this is a
small figurine gotcha
and I said about this nice food right
yeah look over there play with her what
you got there
she says friend and then she holds it up
and from the ground just wow he jumps
right up on the leg and then just like
it begins its assault like that this
creature like there's there can be no
defense against it every every defense
you every defense you try to put up it's
always ready to come yeah edge it's
going for the most tender regions in the
armpit obviously as a favorite yeah I
would play along
no I know pull over on my back and just
yeah I do that perfect what does she do
I don't know should be oh it's it's a
plus she she is tired of it yes I know
they don't get tired of it
no no no goes it goes and then I guess
to break like free because I can see
this will go on for hours
okay well say you think that's a good
toy I can't even bear toy and I kind of
take that away I'm like we're done we're
done with this one now
yeah yeah and I'll give her the shadow
Rubik's Cube oh boy
of wish you have three do you give her
all three or do you ever one just give
her one absolutely there should be
enough for one point exactly
Rubik's kids is a kidney exactly officer
if I'm wondering be smart three I guess
that's that it's additive it's
completely added we gotta bring one to
water too exactly exactly
then I'll sell the other whatever you
want to do with it
she she takes it and then just sits down
but like in one movement just like right
on the right on the ground and then
begins to contend with this object so we
went from it's like giving a kid a like
a that's not a switch or a gameboy yeah
yeah so we go from like these loving
playful wrestling interactions so now
she's like absorbed in this thing and I
just stand up like super self-satisfied
like dad of the year did it again that's
parenting yeah thank you yeah yeah she
is it looks sort of featureless in its
current state
but as she is as she is interacting with
it different parts of it are sliding out
partially from different sides and it's
not a hundred percent clear to you how
its functioning but she is deeply deeply
focused on this hmm
this object and and you can tell she
seems to be gaining sophistication with
it in that in the manner of a child in a
endless-runner IL game and then I see
her doing that and then I get a little
jealous and then I'm like oh wait I want
to connect so then I sit down next to
her and I get one out and I start doing
it too I'm like how are we doing this
is a bonding exercise absolutely do you
want to try two
yeah I'll mess with I'll take one out
and this with it I'll play my game boy
yeah it's gonna be a competitive aspect
yeah so what you want to do with this is
you want to roll a wisdom check with
your plus and then you want to roll in
intelligence check their crap alright so
just this plus my wisdom mm-hmm all
right as a person okay zero six monkey
and then in my unity in check also zero
once someone is show most authentic
parenting experience you can possibly
have in them so you so you got your like
well this is a baby like yeah I
should be able to work with this shadow
sphere and so you sit down you got it
out you're like alright um that her is
this like hers has now come apart into
two pieces and she's found a way to fit
it back together again except now it's a
square and yours is still exactly the
same orb the man gave you in ring
Leonora yeah it's possible that this one
is is defective in some way that's
that's that's one option only explain is
this these orbs have seen a lot of rough
travel and you know I mean expiration
date like there's a lot we don't know
about these works that would explain
your in efficacy that's what I yell yeah
well I'm doing it no one's watching or
cares like this is broken that's broken
I'm not dumb
I'm not dumb this is broken I'm smart
dumb like everyone says yeah so what she
is taking part in different pieces and
then she looks over at you and then she
holds her her little paw out and out
stretches her fingers like this and she
says friend red pencil don't play back
man
kids spoiled yeah I'll give her thing
back okay
she puts it she sets it down in front of
her and then strokes its nose and
it immediately expands into the creature
this figurine is based on like the real
creature now exactly and it just lays
down in front of her while she is
playing with this that's weird
no I got favorite uncle yeah where do
you this jeez
she likes the game way better though
yeah this is so normal
yeah that she is she is not paying
attention to this monster in any way she
is completely focused on this little
shadow object and so that the creature
is just like I say just paws down
stretched out and it's not getting any
love over here and then it just puts its
head like over in front of you and
there's a tongue sort of loss out a
little bit I would be taken aback by all
this but I guess reading this scenario
reading tomorrow would play a low social
cue yeah the social contract dictates
not to kill this thing I guess in front
of her it's just like knife hovering
like and then he would pet him good
thing and then just be like does he have
a name oh yeah
she said she says friend friend
yeah and it's just it's just it comes
out and this tongue is it is very very
large and it is very very wet and
there's a lot of it and it keeps coming
out like an ant eaters tongue do I do I
know what this until you have a lap full
of this tongue do I know what this
creature is called they're called
bullets bullets okay I've seen them
before
yeah yeah they're not they're giving up
do you wouldn't they're not uncommon but
again they're not like so when I do they
would not be an urban creature outside
of janar Scala well when I seen sorsha
and I say what's the deal with the
bullet no I want to
oh my what is it what is that about need
to have a discussion well yeah it's a
family to scope out our daughter yeah
yeah yeah I mean absolutely so you you
are engaging in friendly optimal
parenting serious
okay Thrissur how are you spending this
time once you emerge from your trance
yeah let's see so we've so I took I stay
awake
you slept and I then you trance and I
took back over era right during the
trance I would be thinking about the I
feel like I feel different about these
this these people in this town really in
fact well the fact that I would not
immediately just detonate all the fish
out of the water if that's what they
needed it's like I'm giving that there's
there's deference like let them fish
don't correct the Midwife as far as
velvet being a worthless organism from
who knows where
it does your midpoint that's the only
value that it has and I'm thinking about
the people who have set this town up and
in an attempt to start something new and
how they deserve that chance and I'm
hearing the words and it doesn't sit
right doesn't feel right
I'm we're here too because it's a job
but hey they should they need to have an
opportunity for justice and if I run
across a walnut I think it would start
like I this is the same piece of the
thing so maybe we have our bean water
and I just want to set up what she looks
like when you see her she so in the
night while she was the only one working
on
the thing her thoughts turned to Brahma
and she spent a considerable amount of
time
weeping not into it very carefully not
into it yeah oh but like she's around
sad part grandmother sick and promised
dead and so she just spent the entire
night crying so when you see her her
eyes are like completely puffed up and
she's like what's up you know what that
would be like there would be those
tracks oh yeah through this mirror yes
the clean tracks so it's the opposite
it's the complete opposite of mascara
running yes inverse yes she said she
goes morning what's up it's a beautiful
day I have seeing a start it's hard how
do you how are you
maybe like doesn't know where to put his
hand but it's like when you say that's
me when you said to me it's like it
echoes in my head it's like it's a
beautiful day it's a beautiful day a
beautiful day I go it's a beautiful day
it's a beautiful day it is I like kind
of sitting it for a second I'm like yeah
maybe everything gonna be okay this is
this town is uh they needed our help but
they they deserve a chance to prove
themselves they deserve a chance to to
be more than what they are now and I
can't think of anything more enriching
exciting than that what's wrong with me
what's going on
well like you what is this I don't I'm
not I'm not hot I'm the same temperature
I usually am grave cool oh yeah did
something happen to you last night a lot
of the same sorts of thoughts very very
cheerful distressingly cheerful yeah one
that's like almost like you know now
that you mention it and then she feels
like something weird and it's just like
shrugs it off but she goes no no no what
what's going on with you what's all this
it's just motions to you it's a same old
same old trying to play it off
well maybe keep an eye on it oh
absolutely
and I I realized that I'm standing up
straighter than I usually do and I do I
just catch myself leaving the hut as I
go to produce some more unseen servants
to help other people
hmm catch myself humming stops uh my
throat mm-hmm that's when I turn to see
if you saw her yeah I'm shaking my head
like note met this no no no no no no
that's yeah and I avoid annoy the noid
at all costs he's gonna wreck my meal
no I avoid dinar and Pinar I seem to be
having a sort of a heartwarming moment
and I don't know if I can take anymore
I mean I'm worried I'm gonna start
smiling yeah you give a wide berth I
just yell as you walk away just like and
I'm like this is broken it's not me
mm-hmm whatever
so as you're shouting it Christmas drum
you can see in the Morning Sun you can
see a shadow behind you sort of creep up
behind you in kronar I will then turn
around it's the devil he's been you
again
he's real invented the dragon dragon
he's in every game think about it so he
recruits you this is an incredible way
to play the Dragons I've seen them seen
the videos turmoil into a box it's a
great book I'll expose your bed so you
see there's a rattle of armor as sorsha
sits down on the other side of corner
yeah she said and she's she's looking at
the shadow ball yeah and she's like and
I look at the bullet then go make a face
right back
she reaches she she tossed her and she
says put him away and Curnow reaches
over and pets his nose in the same way
that she pet the figurines knows and
then he just shrinks right back up to
that point in the nose mm-hmm and then
now that he's smaller Koerner picks him
up and puts him on her lap while she
continues to play with this object does
it move when it's in a joyful no no no
it's just like a it's like a ceramic
porcelain yokai figurine yeah so you
would collect yeah that's like a little
me bow yes exactly it's RFID um and she
says do you not like the sword it's a
lovely sword because I I know the
artisans myself
I assure you this I assure you this
weapon will serve you I have been
practicing with it every night have you
I killed a bog witch with it
whatever have you have you these things
that can actually be easily determined
in this yeah it's actually very very
easy I know I'm good at lying yeah yeah
so you do performance all right let's
see it I'm performing this analysis see
right all right get to lie to someone
yes okay that works
all right just in front of your child
all right all right no I love the sword
I killed something with it last night
because I love me so much
19 oh my god did a telephone I read
that's hella fied she brings me well she
really she can she can respond with
insight doing right so yeah plus the
plus three so 22 yep Oh give her
advantage got her so she looks back at
the surgeon she says really oh yeah and
you found you found success in the
engagement yeah that's a good sort thank
you again
but why are you wearing it as the second
sword why didn't it's a place of honor I
said thank you what more do you want for
me it's just getting man inventive
what's the deal with the little monster
figurines what do you want to know where
did it come from that's very odd skull
it's not odd I've never seen it before
that is not the definition of up it is
so there are many things you haven't
seen and they're all odd everything I
don't know is odd and dumb the walls
come up yeah she says it's not uncommon
for okay for children
in the hierarchy of Scala to have pets
such as this this is this is not it's
just not common engine are no is it
dangerous but to foes I def owes it it
has no it cannot harm pranaam okay it
doesn't know how its 3los safe dinars
then yeah placated a bit he's weirded
out by and he's irrationally
overprotective maybe absolutely well she
she she asks there's a pause after that
and she says is it true what they say
about janar that there is Oh a what you
think I was gonna say nothing you know
we know about do don t know about his
race I mean we know there's something
there no she says that there is a a
great dragon that lives in the mountain
above it yes it is very true being of
the royal family have you seen it only
the royal family sees it for us yes
Barr's main less blessed be his name she
says well how often does he receive do
you consult him she gets too excited
yeah but you haven't seen this before
and you know that you know that janar
has a reputation of being somewhat
mysterious and it's a reputation that
Gennari maintain actively yeah and
Dinaric would get the deflective a
little bit i mean it it would answer her
questions yes but i mean they're also
like irregardless of their relation
she's like state secrets regardless of
their relationship yeah state secrets
and things of that nature so you would
he would be kurt in his answers so he
would
like yeah yes she says when can he be
consulted
that's something I'm trying to figure
out you don't know I is that nothing but
is that not the purview of your high
houses it's our only purview so this
information is secret even from you yes
yes listen we'll go with it let's try
another performance check yes this is
what it's like if you're talking to a
person who's really smart uh I'm taking
advantage protect my my secrets have
another point dogs all right so
it's like five from you today
that's three - OH - right one for me
it's all of it the way Oliver no
please no and well no it's very very
good
okay and she says it is said before my
time but it is said that thee the monks
once tended a dragon in our Mountain as
well and eventually it's not clear it's
not known by us but eventually the monks
took over the religious stewardship of
the town and you can see the result they
may have needed a dragon's wisdom if the
dragon managed that town was the dragon
that do you not have a dragon no no
she's and it there's at the pause and
then the know has wait yeah she says
Scala is
in terrible need no the people of Scala
mm-hmm
they need a place to they need a place
to run to do you think that Gennaro
could keep them I am not the person to
ask
so you're not a you're not a generic
Prince I am a Gennari Prince I don't
have that authority
well you don't have that authority but
you but you must know who you speak to
your mother perhaps yeah that'll be a
good place to start
she's like when we have when we have
resolved promise yeah let us discuss
this again we can we can see knowing
what I know about my family and what
they think of outsiders Dragonborn or
not I don't think the odds are good she
nods and she says we'll find a way I
mean we we saw it firsthand in in Scala
like there you guys weren't exactly
happy to see us me when we were there
it's gonna be just like that I
understand even even though the the need
is great the need cannot ameliorate this
[Music]
it's there's a there's a lot of things
going on outside of Gennari you know
can't help everyone that's our town
motto can't help everyone she said right
over the gate right over the closed gate
right all right and she she allows
herself a few more
a few more moments she gives Crenn our
health inducing scritch and says we have
two more days to prepare more df1 yeah
the one then yeah yet adventure all
night yeah that's true mmm she says she
says I think that I can get more weapons
from their scouting parties yeah where
did you get those weapons well
occasionally they are foolish enough to
send people in groups less than six he's
robbed a bunch of people for robbing a
Robert Sarah Wow
oh this skank you took it from them all
right I thought you were just saying
like traveling parties I'm like I mean
yes she's she is mad at the
suggestion yeah that and so she she gets
up and applies a little bit of affection
even to the figurines and walks back in
to the to the center part of the town
the the fluid inside the cauldron walnut
has thickened considerably great there
has been a state change of some kind
inside this cauldron and you think that
you think that it's it's good so it's
going to be ready soon okay um so I've
called the Midwife over to give it a
second glance
absolutely so whenever whenever the the
unseen servant like whenever the shawl
hits the ground she gasps and then she
goes in and picks up the she goes and
picks it up and then at the door she
just says growl okay welcome welcome
running back in she holds the she holds
the shawl up like this
and then when you've instantiate Edyta
she places it down on the creature oh
yeah I would have been since it takes me
10 minutes to ritually summon I've been
doing a 10 minute overlap so there's one
in the wings so I think I want you going
cooking I have one with me ya know it's
like you just trade them out yeah it's
really a matter of putting the shawl on
the visible on the one that's not about
to disintegrate exactly exactly
now how do we want to how do we want to
invest the day's energies c-team
obviously that the main thing that
hasn't been explored yet here is the
mine itself we do need to check out the
mine that's one option also it's become
quite apparent perhaps that the food
stores are not 100% the best I want to
investigate that one do we give a dose
of this cure to brazier so Midwife can
take care it's very it's very very close
like now that's thickened so she'll take
care yeah exactly exactly well she'll
she'll give you she'll give you a
stopper she'll give you a violet stopper
it should be ready in about ten that's
ten minutes ten million yeah so I want
to get the boys together
rub it deep into the scalp yeah and I'll
be like Dinaric this team meeting
hey look it's our chance I gotta go in
minner of her probing come on oh oh oh
coming yes okay I gotta go yeah and once
once you come over I say um okay so
while grandmother is incapacitated we
still need to help this town we
currently have no food again because
it's all been poisoned and that needs to
be destroyed well yes well no that's
interesting
that is I I'm sorry in the dungeon
master I'm supposed to serve
passionately I think that's that is not
on these sheets I'm looking over at Eric
Benson judges will allow it so I look at
denarii and I go now that's interesting
do you think that we can get any of this
into the hands of the bandits we could
do a few ways to use as a police there's
a few things we can do with poison just
yeah I mean well let's we can table talk
our way through these plans we've got oh
no I want to talk to Dan are someone all
right
from the mouths of babes we can send our
we can dress up our boy toy here as a
spy as one of the bandits and send him
with a gift of poison fish with a
shipment yeah yeah that I could send a
rush car we could send a missive telling
them that there are supplies coming and
send them like like via bird yeah soften
the blow be like hey we're Sam I'm
sending you some supplies to help you
strengthen up before the attack yeah we
can't just put it on a cart and send
somewhere we need to know where they are
we can get to figure that out from the
bird though you can just tell them where
it is
yeah oh yeah we can meet them there that
makes sense we're not even just leave it
how'd it feel like hanging job over on
you know whatever Hill there's a pile of
fish I'd love for you it's totally not
poisoned fish hill winky face
that's a nice eggplant emoji and then
coming from the bird they would have
less reason to I mean those are two ways
to get them to believe it and get them
to eat it
we should buy your first try it yeah
yeah we weaponize it making a no bombs
throw it at him just how potent at this
poison the fish bomb exactly right I'm
gonna be aerosolized
yeah well the Midwife said that it was
it was like coming from there guy like
it was like an it happened once they ate
it
yeah yeah so unless you can throw it
into their mouths
this is like launching diseased bodies
like when you're seeing a castle
yes I know it's true hey so we will plan
the rest of that when our beloved
grandmother returns um for now Josh if
you could please tip my called Wow
now more fish Jesus everyone well the
corn is poisoned yeah uh other cereal
grains that's all it's a real show
give me the quinoa um nope so what are
the farm you are looking inside the
merry inviting front window of a small
but increasingly well-known in called
the drownin Cordier you can see is the
scene a young woman with tight curly
blond hair smiling at a young man who
smiles back and scoots away from the
table and as he does so you can see that
the proprietress gives him a glance that
suggests that if he never came back that
would be acceptable
he leaves the drawing courier and finds
his way down an alley along the left
side of the building and there he climbs
a trellis upon which young hop chutes
had begun to grow and when he makes his
way to the roof there is another person
already there and she asks him what have
you discovered
and he says commander the the team you
are you are seeking is not in is not in
red larch currently they have accepted a
job with acquisitions incorporated in
their far away
and she says excellent continue to ply
your trade with the young woman in the
inn and report to me on the regular
schedule and as he climbs down and
leaves the the woman retrieves from
behind her an instrument does this even
work let's see let's see and I gotta
make sure because I'm very nervous
because I don't do this type of it all
the time to open a for you yeah
and she seems to she sits on the roof
and then looks over her shoulder at a
very particular window in the drawing
Quarrier and begins to play let's see I
can do this I'm not completely it
up let's see no I should be able to do
it if I was both at a told you would it
never end well if I was smart I'd have
started with words like him if you were
here maybe the fear would subside if you
were here my darling dear you'd never
get our lie Hugh and I just seemed to
rhyme and times made more
- maybe I'm strong I'm the wrong one
for you let's see I turn a hand you turn
my hand and then I turn another for well
that was dead I can't recall what she
said anymore it's for the rest it was a
test I don't know if I passed the worlds
of power and your fire and we'll meet in
the ass Hugh and I just seem to rhyme
and time has made it more true maybe I'm
strong I'm the wrong one for you
you'd be surprised fat don't try to
apply some clever ruse
[Music]
maybe you're strong and you just never
knew alright Josh thank you hey that is
this week's episode of CT thanks for
rolling through we'll be back next week
with our friend Kate Welch aka rosy bee
stinger don't go nowhere come on back
for a table top we'll see you soon
you