time is the enemy of the past it
threatens the fastest weapon you
wouldn't make it past a second and
answer the question play it brash and
reckless to choose a cautious solution
you saw was prudent in any sepulcher
poker to don't become the putrid it's
that well said I pursue in no mountain
too steep for dungeon too deep to send
expendable marks up to the top of the
peak of beneath they see Yugi they come
like sharks to it while I swim in that
money build like Carl Barks through it
so send your national parks drew it I'll
send him home in a natural box with the
clothes Tyler most of the parts included
save your breath for a cleric confessor
death is a lesson that life is attending
professor but if you're seeking my
official advice sign on the dotted line
English of the choice oh yeah I am Tycho
Brahe of Penny Arcade packs I am also a
manifest hair weird run CEO of
acquisitions incorporated but today
Jerry Hawkins appeared to run a game of
Dungeons &amp; Dragons for my friends to my
right dragon for narcissists dinar blitz
in wasn't right oh do it do you want a
moment to collect yourself yeah do you
want to try to do a 2.0 this there's no
post it's actually just ok thank you so
much for your dedicated assistance to
the right of my right repping the
natural world no the dog truck
have fun Wow you know what hey to the
left to the left to the left my left
should've put a ring on it you must not
know about me um to my left not your
grandma's grandma except in those rare
cases where she is your grandma's
grandma
Rosie beasting apparently this means
something in baseball someone sent me a
gift saying I didn't know he was a bee
stinger there's a dude going like this
Oh secrets hold on on a bat or like just
on them fucking ghost bat so this is
ground I know baseball I have heard one
want to see that I read about it either
baseball no that's bacon nope or the
left of my left emerging yes they're
from a mist shroud wow that's crazy
yes I just incorporated had have a CFO
or a CTO are you are you looking for
position yeah I was thinking about
applying for it you or Rosie Rosie
obviously nice you can't spell
cartographer without CTO that's my
application I hope you like it
is that at the top like gold leaf like
embossed er like yeah are you selling
bevel and emboss I'm selling it it's
rich for cheap suggestion box the only
question that I have is how long have
you been sitting on it literally a half
of a second right now when when last we
saw our heroes after a semi eventful
journey to the town of promise in the
sombre Hills one of many small villages
that is a part of an incredible boom
and precious metals and the jams out in
that zone you finally did arrive and
when you did you came into contact with
sorsha and Crenn arm of course on the
job
Maeve Perry as the thrust turns out not
a real person I'm always playing crazy
tricks like this great yappin today yeah
get ready one other thing that you just
accept is true a lot y'all ain't even
know when you arrive there there was
some a bit of dark news a bit yeah a bit
of darkness the engine News News but
have you ever seen news yeah yeah
exactly like news but they were out of
the chicken and so anybody who had
ordered the chicken for dinner they had
to order either as a beef for the fish
that's the kind of situation also
bronsted so CNB in the moment I think
that it was just it's just the two of
you that went over to yeah yeah there
might there might be some audible
wailing yeah I don't think it's a secret
yeah so but that is the that is a
scenario gifts were exchanged
there was a very fine indeed enchanted
generous Ord offered by Sasha to dinar
but dinar doesn't like it cuz he's a
brat it's not good enough for him does
he princeling that's dinar
I can't remember we've talked about it
before does he have any toys hanging out
waiting for crew to give to Crenn arm
make sure you know I want to see that no
yeah oh no they're definitely toys but
that is the that is the scene we set
before us the town of promise relatively
small as I suggested really to sort of
bunk houses side-by-side a central
corridor goes through the town proper
there is a hut for the Midwife that you
met as you came in before there is a
mayor mayor quiver but it really seems
like the Midwife kind of runs things
here and you see you see the folk of
this small town emerging late from the
mine and getting the town ready for some
rest but you can see that they're even
even in the in the dying light you can
see that there are some attempts at
making some defensive structures at the
east and south of the town but either
due to damage could be the system forces
tamping down their efforts to do it
these defenses are not in a great place
you and we establish it there they have
a sound what a great deal of stuff
indeed now that is that is something
that we did identify last time they do
have stone as a building material for
the use of the of the party I'm curious
if anybody has anything else they would
like to do tonight before they take
advantage of the rustic yet complete
amenities of these bunk houses let's
assume a lot of time has passed we're
talking about a situation where the
water level of the river has risen yeah
okay this is the story ya know so uh no
I just mean that so well it's not like
sobbing right this second but she
probably has to fill out a form about
this oh this is the best is it Jerry
yeah so I think she'd be filling out a
form but it's like every time she goes
to write stuff and she's gets choked up
so it's like you can do the defenses and
stuff but I think she's just like really
really making a meal a tryna its Rosie
how many more like is she like taking
the quill and being like okay what how
do I feel this nice like I would I have
to do it it has to be me on the on the
on the page yeah in the margin yeah
you hear that telltale scribble this
gray of the document sir nib and it says
would you like help well you're trying
to fill out a death form right yes
like too big underlines it three times
you can see that the page sort of
shimmers and line by line it's it
resolves into a blank sheet and then it
is filled out
immaculee the form that you were trying
to use and then the leftmost sheet just
asks you a series of questions and the
this agent is offering to fill out the
form if you can offer the information
okay yes you know well that's upset when
she can't do her own documents oh yeah
okay so there's a few questions
it says my name of deceased it's just
like from Oulu BA I feel I feel like
this is me but I also feel like it's the
right thing to do
location of death oh that was in um
janar know without it was yeah yeah
scholar she has dragon place it's filled
out in both common and Dragonborn mm-hmm
tough stable looking alphabet
it also says relationship to deceased
well this says co-worker oh it's I could
not be more pleased over on the left it
says I can take it from here from our
own records
so on Ilan's is that and she you know
puts it all back together he gets it all
nice and dry can see bag and then it's
just like alright why are we let's let's
get let's get to business
let's business take your mind off of
take her mind off of it of course um
rosy Burgess chorus and asks you you one
time we were camping and I slipped this
like this you had a sort of a security
system that you set up outside oh yes
should we do something like that I'm I
think that's a good idea I don't have
that one anymore
I'm just good and forgot that that
particular spell cuz their children the
child spell and we can do better than
that visit of this town it was better we
only sleep for hours
mmm-hmm suddenly transfer ours per night
we do much can take a watch what is the
like I assume the townspeople are also
interested in in security is they're all
as they're a watch sorted there is but
the watch I mean and you had you had
seen it as you entered like the weapon
racks are decorative at best yeah and
the weapons that are that are on them
are just accessories really appropriate
for cosplay only I got to get the pink
bow on there so their piece fell better
sell that cosplay we can do something
with the stone I can use stone shape on
it yes I was wondering you guys don't
you
how many until the attack three more
days or indeed okay to the as per the
brief from mave there are three days of
preparation left but as I said it's it's
it's it's late now
yeah there's it may be that things make
a little bit more sense in that in the
morning mm-hmm rest Rosie will proffer
to you a flask that has been secret
Adhan her person somehow somewhere come
on drinks with that hi yeah it's rough
she chokes on it immediately take it
it's like you're it's like you you know
that you want it you know that you need
this medicine right now sure but you
have to build up a tolerance
she unplug her nose you're gonna sleep
great tonight not deep enough hey can I
get a perception role from you
Rosie be singers nineteen that's quite
good so as you are offering this bit of
comfort to walnut Don grass it's common
it's common for you almost at a
subliminal level just a sort of orient
yourself that's what makes you such a
good cartographer and so your eyes flit
up very quickly to the home word star
just to just you know situate yourself
in the galaxy of concepts and as near as
you can tell there are two stars missing
from it oh so they're my my red one had
been yeah the red the red one is now
occupying a different position in the
constellation okay and the two stars
that were above it are now gone okay so
the home red star is
a constellation from which a star was
eaten sorry missing possible yeah who
can say and the red one has a was not
the one that was eaten no indeed where
the red one was there is no nothing
and then deeper down into the structure
of the constellation itself there is an
another star and then the red star has
taken up a place centrally in them okay
there's some kind of a there's something
occurring says there are more stars than
before no same amount to say it's the
same amount but they seem to be winked
out okay the the fact that this
constellation has suddenly become mobile
is something that Rosie's been dealing
with for a while so it doesn't freak her
out but she does draw the paper
parchment out and document the change
the Delta between these two changes and
she's gonna run a casket rest probably
hmm oh
currently yeah okay as well I think we
can time I think if you're outside with
me are you yeah that's I think that's
fair to say cuz I was uh I'm in
strolling around the town maybe I'll
share this idea with you I know that I'm
just I'm walking the perimeter just
walking the perimeter and then coming
back I know that
I mean I'm of anybody loath to do this
but this town is flawed in a lot of ways
that towns here are and that it should
have been built in the mind yeah it
should have been underground now we have
to defend these buildings when and now
what's in there is just stone what are
they gonna do this town is healing their
this I mean what we're going to do is
try and build mine around it and that's
a lot of work okay so I think we just
don't put everybody deep in the ground
to keep them safe six feet under deeper
than that if you can if we can get it
got three days well it's the only way to
save them
[Laughter]
and I tell you about what's happening
with my constellation once you stop with
this yeah I asked you if you've ever
heard of anything like this and in your
in your reading cuz I haven't have I
I don't know I'm gonna do a kind of a
check would it be it wouldn't we are can
this will be history I think that yeah
if we're talking about it yeah I think
that the difference here is between
astrology and astronomy right yeah I
just want to know if stars have changed
and anything I recollect I will take
advantage so that's a 17 Alyssa can you
give me a theory I forgot my laptop just
some buffs and background here Jerry
forgets his laptop every show but
usually remembers that he forgot his
laptop it really really is but it's like
but it's like Alyssa's back and I
celebrate that yeah
really back I'm taking your hands just
like this Chris yeah who got a 17 he did
it's not it is rare but it is not
unheard of it's you can you can think of
a couple different examples generally
speaking people explain that away
because usually they've mapped the the
powers that they imagine govern their
lives onto those stars so they usually
contextualize it in that way but there's
many stars in such a short period of
time is this is unheard of well we've
never I mean as far as I as far as I can
recall we haven't dealt with any entity
that it let's say the best dream is now
we haven't dealt with an entity that
seemed to be directly related to living
among and consuming if not stars than
maybe just deities of other types and we
did happen to
liberate one recently and and patristic
will confide and Rosie like this this
god of mounds is so simple and it's
machination that we free 'god the stars
change it's like pulling a lever that's
i think wonder one point not only that
but I think we can track the movements
of all of those things that we're
interested in by the change of the
constellation and I feel bad for it yeah
because it's with one of very few gods
that I've actually had access to and
there's so little to learn are you sure
it's a god
I'm not when was the last time you spent
time in a God stomach and left multiple
times we're able to come back literally
never yeah so what makes you think it is
because of what it cuz of what it said
and I believe that nice very nice yeah
basically Wow essentially yes okay but
it it's eating the other gods it
certainly is able to contain them that's
impressive
yeah so whatever mechanism that is is
pretty pretty good that's some kind of
petty mundane power seeking God Eater
yeah okay maybe is going to on the road
to godhood yes she's a great hope Crosby
movies check it out 1943 Rosie
sometimes other gods speak to me I don't
remember the last time that's happened
but it does happen
yeah okay so then what we'll do is Rosie
will unfurl a parchment and make it
essentially what is a new map of this
constellation and to to
consult with you and try to track based
on the movements of the stars we will
now start to take notes about God
activities and see if there's any
correlation we'll start to do science we
can we do it
hate so is that something that you could
do in real life
yeah okay the two of you throws knew
right now no no like the pink well yeah
no we have other stuff we know what if I
need something from Melissa no no the
main takeaway is that if you create this
we will leverage it as a game aid in the
future and we can also share it with the
love - okay okay so like I say I mean
the it's it's now getting quite dark
except for a central fire we get is
nighttime well I'm just now it's the
super toaster night nice dark night no
it's nighttime yeah sleep dogs I'm gonna
take first watch even though we have
three days just because we did steal
were loot that had a bunch of special
stuff in it today that's right oh yeah
you gotta be feeling good about that
he's got all those cool documents how
the loot just makes me sad oh that was
gonna be a gift
hey what doesn't make you like
everything's gonna anyway so I take up
station near the entrance to town and
[Laughter]
Katie crying all night okay
I think Christmas is like I was like I
know I know that she's upset and that's
and I don't want that for her but as
long as we can hear the crying we know
she's okay
at least do you know that sure it's all
clear through parenting as well as you
hear those crickets now
exactly
well good bed because that you took four
swatches I wanted to work on this
bouquet then I was trying to see it
seeping in dual wield two great swords
both by one hand how you think can I do
you think that here's what's up
do you think that wielding two great
swords would be very challenging but you
think that you could wear them both if
you wanted to that's what if you did a
lot of push-ups yeah
the average Dragonborn me then I think
there's nothing I can't do oh my god
will you please try to wield them in
combat oh this is actually a good
question so you are out there on first
watch hmm I want to understand like the
mechanism of trance right because it's
supposed to be that kind of EDM house
but is there a lot of base is there
there's a lot of pacifiers usually in
this trap where there's they drop so it
depends it depends on the at different
points in the game they have described
it in different ways for a while it was
also called reverie something for you
more fun than so reverie is it's a
restful process where you can relive and
explore memories mmm I was only its
derive rest in that way we could
essentially like how of depending on how
aware of the environment
somebody is while tranced then that's
just to people who are on some kind of
watch if not you know the traditional
yeah I learned about rats yeah so this
is in in the context of me being a baby
lizard Indy to the coast so hashtag big
lizard
that's a job but that's a long one that
in addition to revisiting old memories
and trance elves are considered to be
souls that are reborn over and over
again and so they forget their past
lives when they're young and they're not
supposed to tell adults about them they
can talk to other baby else about it but
that hashtag baby a hashtag maybe I'll
um but that as they grow older they
start to trance and remember those
memories again and that's considered to
be like the old age and and like a
really cool coming coming of age part of
being an elf look forward to that
sometimes when you trance yeah you got
you got some of that cool shit to look
forward to um but yeah we should we're
wrong don't get that because it's like a
blessing of coral on oh I see I wasn't
gonna say that
I don't think it's risk would go for
that it would just be like no anguish
that's just this is a hallucination of
some kind that doesn't work for me this
is meat and I don't anything I'm seeing
from earlier is invented exactly so now
that now that we know no right I'm
trying to figure out yeah we can we can
figure out we can figure it out right
now I want to use trance this is the
origins in dragons I get my for yeah but
that I'm able to provide some kind of
support standing watch that's all I want
well I don't I don't yeah I mean the
only component you can my understanding
is that you have awareness but but
because not profound what we just worked
out though if I I'm gonna spend any of
my brain power while asleep it's gonna
be on working out the constellation and
how the movements of what's been assumed
it's gonna be simmer no it's gonna be
some Sherlock I mean like the Benedict
Cumberbatch one right yeah the one where
I'm just like punching slow and then
quickly you are essentially asleep
dreaming up stars yeah that's right put
them together but don't wake and holding
watch so you're trained to multitask
you're like well like good like when I
listen to books on tape and I'm driving
into where it's like I'm going to sleep
I'm absorbing erm I'm getting
to work I'm hearing a story yeah this is
marvelous yeah this is great stuff so
you're you're four hours pass hold on
what is what does well not see where she
trances Oh probably kid memories from
her growth oh yeah because you're so
young yeah right we focused on that
stuff that's probably taking up a lot of
mental space that's that explains to why
it stays so fresh to like every day you
wake up from this trance it's like it
just happened I know there's only four
hours to but feels like an eternity yeah
but it's like it's it feel like an
eternity but it's still not long enough
it's a it's a curse that you can only
transfer hours yeah
[Music]
so where are you seated this is the
thing I want addressed I didn't want to
like get into a bed I wanted to be your
stuff not next to you because that's
silly
lighting you can be like you know where
the stone piles yeah let's say that
that's where I've just you sit on your
still out in the dark and I'm like
there's a comfort to it this is the good
part the rocks with a good there's a lot
to interrupt you there's a lot to
diminish your joy while you're trying to
make these you know astronomical
calculations in every dimension there's
some night bird you know trilling it's
beautiful song and how close is it how
close is it my work is important yes
what I mean is when I dissonant whisper
the nightingale I got a song
counter song and so it's like every now
and then you'll see them that's your eye
yeah blending off of the gently moving
river you hear like the splash of the
occasional leaping fish it's it's hell
on earth that's intolerable I'm trying
to work understand you Frank trance
you're like shut up bird where was I oh
stars but it goes without
I mean it's eerie you know that at some
level this town and you and you have met
some of those who would harm it you know
that at some level this place must be
being watched or there's certainly a
kind of Armageddon clock that's running
out for it but this is a beautiful quiet
night enough for for this kind of work I
could use Rosie's input but really yeah
did you take the first shift and then
yeah so as this as the Sun starts to
rise men residual will shuffle out from
wherever late isn't Sun rising where we
have dinner okay
absolutely yeah we went through the main
just two bunk houses also okay so she's
got her shawl kind of like draped around
blanket style and she hands you a cup of
something hot but not particularly
flavorful the fact is is that you are
actually when you get up and you don't
you know you don't stay you don't sleep
long in the bed you are actually offered
a cup of something hot um and intensely
flavorful and black nice home
the mid
life steps in everyone calls her midwife
literally haven't I literally haven't I
bet I have it down here as the name so
don't even
Rosie asks her name's midwife they call
you Midwest but what is your name
[Music]
[Laughter]
no I I have it written on here it's got
the W and the Y yeah right I mean it's
like a yeah no no no I got it she says
my name is what I do but she offers and
she says that it is from a beam that
grows on the hill over the mine
whew that's a strong brew yeah I take a
set it's intense nice okay bold alright
cuz I asked her for another cup of
Colombia I'll bring us a very good I'll
bring out two cuz rest you know you have
a yeah they have a massive pot of it a
communal pot XY over the fire
absolutely there's a little bit of like
even at the bottom it's like silt it's a
it's thick it's two seas and they stand
for coffee I was hoping to there were
Birds this you know what if the if the
bandits get this town you know they're
gonna have to contend with those noisy
birds I only need four hours and I am
upset this helps but yeah not enough
rocks I know what's going on this is
like a forest the Midwife
she she has enabled this encounter but
she would like to
she has soar show with her and she liked
to have a meeting with you specifically
oh okay so the group of you
she basically decides that giving all
this information to one of you to
distribute is the best way to do it and
so sorsha identifies the tactical
situation that the town is in which is
that they have built walls in the past
and that they have been they have
collapsed
for various reasons unseasonable routes
would sprout inside stone walls the
midwife doesn't the Midwife says that
the town is cursed and it seems like she
doesn't take the word lightly and you
think there's probably a lot of curses
that she could handle but she doesn't
understand the source of it so the town
is almost completely out of food here at
the end of this siege because it's
almost impossible to get out and no one
from the town has been able to get any
fish out of the river the tools that
they have been using down in the mine
and to build the walls have the metals
of them been brittle and broken in the
work and the entire wall that protected
the southern part of the town
so there's imagine there's a imagine a
dark plain south there's more something
like a grass field it isn't attached to
the road proper but the wall that they
had south of the town is mostly just
charred stumps at this point okay and
they had that between the town in the
field or did they did it they did that
was sort of like the bulwark against the
against any problems from this
so she says you may be able to get
something out of this river it was
always so good to us before well I have
someone I can ask about that for sure
what do you guys have for food anything
do you have dry goods of any comments
she says the difficulty is that we're
hemmed in here mm-hmm
there is a place that we used to go for
help a nearby town we would trade our
silver for their gyms it may be that
when night falls a group could try to
contact that village in return you can't
eat gems you can't eat gems but our
understanding is that they've done quite
well in trade I see okay
okay what's the name of this town uh
fruit I'm sorry I was thinking about
something I heard earlier okay well I
want to see one of those travel posters
for free just a pile of shrimp so they
don't have any these towns are are
pretty young you think that your
assessment is that agriculture probably
would succeed here but in the early part
of the in the early part of the boom
they were able to get whatever they
needed just by training so they haven't
I'm not like so there's no seedlings I
can link help along no it's a very very
young it's a very very young place other
than the other than the shrubs that seem
to grow naturally on that hill there
aren't a lot of food crops around here
well sounds like there's some kind of
natural born curse so Rosie's first
thought would be to consult walnut and
see if she can either determine the
source of this curse if there are there
are plants that are destroying the wall
from the inside things like that seems
like right in your wheelhouse also maybe
you can turn into a fish and talk the
other fish into letting themselves be it
is it is but also that's the best part
it's like if you don't know how
something works yeah you just talk to
somebody who is like an expert and
you've got like a great idea
you're like well you you can turn any
animals right it's your thing this is
like very limited knowledge thing you
can talk to the fish maybe you could
turn into a bear and let us carve off a
little bit yeah when you get down to
zero HP just turn to yourself again yeah
that's that's mechanically sound
something warm for a second that's
amazing
[Laughter]
so well that's like really like just
blanking despondent but willing to like
I quit any of this so she's like okay
bring me the water source okay
where is the river the river so in your
mind the northern to the north of the
town is the hill with the shrubs okay
that mine is carved directly into the
side of it
South burn down walls right to the east
there are some sort of half height walls
the sort of walls you might find in a
Gears of War type situation okay yeah
exactly
there's gonna be a shootout here yeah
almost certainly and that is where the
road proper actually sort of comes all
the way up to the town on the west
basically the western border of the town
mm-hmm that it basically stops at the
river okay borders the time okay okay so
it's close yeah oh yeah absolutely I
mean that's that's the in do you were
there last night so Rosie you say take
me to the water source
Rosie leads you like eight feet this is
very serious about it it's like I'll
take you
so I want to do oh my god how do I have
no +2 nature I know right weird so yeah
for some reason nature is intelligent I
know isn't that weird
I think I should do wisly I think it's
wizzy listen can you talk to them yeah
okay
what about survival now I'm gonna take I
feel like this would be a nature Jay
maybe the dam can help you with that um
I'll take advantage oh yeah I don't want
to just determine see if I know anything
funky going on with this very funky 911
can I tell if there's anything wrong
so tell me describe for me that because
these roles are shamefully low Wow rude
be because they are soon exactly but
describe for me the process and then I
can weave so long I'll go down to the
water get down on her weave she's
looking at she's looking at the the
water she's gonna stick her hand in it
taste it she's getting down Fox Mulder's
down yeah yeah yes nice
Scully sir yes absolutely so you taste
it and there's you it immediately can
tell that fish peed in it no no it's
been that this that this pond like very
close to the to the town has absolutely
been adulterated it's been a dull to
rated adulterated okay can I tell Haley
can I try can I try again to see if I
can get to the source yeah absolutely so
tell me what tell me what types of
skills like now that you know that you
know that it's been the someone is
actively trying to mess with it yes so
tell me how you'll try to find it so how
about this one survival like if I know
if it's been like something's been put
in the water that's right mmm its rivers
tryna marriage are you looking for the
juice yeah attend to you she said do sit
real quick
so you just you just just trudging until
the water is like up like to your
midsection yes then you just turn around
you look at Rosie and you go mmm so do I
think that this is a problem that
natural plant life around it could solve
or is this like there's like a source
you you think it's too focused you think
there's actually something here okay all
right
can I do detect magic that's very
interesting
yes of course you can okay so I know the
presence of magic within 30 feet do I
sense anything yeah absolutely it's you
know it's you know it's yeah I can see
the aura and determinants cool so you
can see you can sort of see just a sort
of like gentle pulse somewhere near the
middle of the river itself so you go out
until the water is just up past your
nose in the middle of this river and if
you look down into the water you can see
a vial whose stopper has been removed
I'm gonna grab that I'm gonna grab it
and lift it out of the water and bring
it back to shore the oil I take it out
you grab it from the silt yeah and you
pull it out you can see something coming
out of it and trailing it and then when
you get it out of the water it is
vomit-inducing
and I would love to have a constitution
save as a result for Bowman rolling like
garbage day whoo yep 11 okay so it's
just like you you throw up but in your
mouth oh that's nice
Wow did I transfer you
doesn't come out oh that's good my full
cheeks
oh no no like I'm like a like a trumpet
player yeah like you're on beat or yes
yes good okay
do I smell it as soon as it comes on the
breeze like this nice spring breeze that
has been giving you these wildflowers
from over the river is now giving you
something like like like baking liver
it's like when you eat one of those
Bertie Botts every flavor beans do you
think it's gonna be tutti frutti but
it's vomit instead it's just like that
Rosie's not into it
um but and I think like as a reaction to
this horrifying smell she's she's just
like it's early still and she's just she
can't no it doesn't help it on strong
ones I'm like stomping up there's no
sound loudly dry heaving no teeth oh
yeah you you think some natural do you
think the natural action of the river
will probably push that stuff down and
sin it out pretty quickly
okay that's great the vials still appear
to have substance in it yeah does it
have goo yeah it has a it's probably
maybe 33% make it corn oh yeah of course
if it was violent can you can you can
you morph into like tail I'm gonna take
it uh over to two threats and I'm gonna
go when you make of this Oh what is
going on with this town no I already
have a drink magically okay sorry I'm
silence
it looks like you're showing it off as a
little prize on a game show someone
sabotaged the river let me see what I
know somebody poisoned the waterhole
smells really country all over again
hmm it's beyond even what I would want
it blending it's a blended beaver
commended beavers well no country that's
from our country it's wild it's good so
I don't think there's anything that I
would that would help me determine this
archive well yeah I mean that's it as I
can see whether or not it has any
magical property but it seems like it's
just like a fish you're like god this
smells like shit Carissa
what is it you don't want me it's in a
river first one first then one rule you
put this in a river that's a bad time
that's not a great Arkana even for me I
guess that one is actually a 13 so just
to see whether or not there's any magic
element to this herb is just done yeah
you don't think that it's I mean it was
probably created with you know it's
really created by someone with talent
but you don't think that it's mystical
in nature you think it's just fucking
gross and there was no sign of a cork
how did you get to the middle of the
river cork elemental
occupied can I you can yes she is almost
always occupied as you see but you can
absolutely
you can absolutely track her down okay
yeah I think I'm gonna try to find her
she seems like the most likely don't
walk around yeah stink just like walking
through town yeah yeah but like it's
just everybody well not never bad
double stinky difference because it they
might not have met you last night
they might how it is yeah Rosie's got
that flask of stuff that she fed you
last night
she's using that as like a smelling
phoenicians Thanks
okay we're gonna go find the Midwife
follow me so we call the Midwife
yeah anyway also in Netflix nice okay so
your hands this
like shit - I got stinking it's a real
condition we find we find her yeah she
is in she is in her small hut teaching
several children the letters that they
will need to know hey yeah the classics
she's starting with an ass sorry about
your beat then you go right to cue gotta
have the qx5 yeah Niner so yeah there
you go
they're triumphs they're doing their
best okay
scratching on the ground some of these
are not letters that's great we can talk
about public education in this town
later midwife we have a situation here
she might have smelled us coming kids
kids are getting behind the Midwife and
like hiding from this smell yeah I tried
that didn't work there it is what's that
this is in the river
I'm gonna take my hand off only you can
smell it's like hmm just a lot
[Laughter]
you make one Constitution check and now
you're just huffing she she she asks for
it her response is not extreme she dips
her finger in Rosie throws up hmm we
found this we're in the middle of the
river right where your fish aren't she
looks around in her kit and she's able
to find us she has to try several
stoppers until she finds the the one
that will fit
she puts it together and sets it up and
then walks out to the river itself and
dreams exactly she walks out until she
is waiting about halfway through and
says I don't know how I missed this so
I'll wait out there with her be like
this is where it was it was right right
right up there I said just that didn't
fall from a tree girl I know someone put
it there she just sits down in the river
it's just like the bubbles yeah it's
just like up to it up to her shoulders
she's like I'm getting old
yeah you usually that's a good thing in
the Midwife this is reverse I mean not
specifically I'm like trainee either
burden this is somewhat of an area of
expertise for me natural things I go
here this this will make you feel better
I don't want to use force right just
summon up some I don't know whatever the
fancy version of coho salmon is like the
tender rich pull them out of the river
and feed people yeah after that charming
display I thought they were just gonna
dance
oh no yeah I want to have them if
they'll come through the river analysis
it's moved off exactly it's a whatever
like even even the sort of reek that was
here before like this river is cleansing
this town the way that I call fish this
is important is I stick my head halfway
underwater and then just you just say to
the fish oh yeah I just say the word in
druidic or whatever I'll just say fish I
sing the song in the fish
[Laughter]
you get down you whisper the fish call
yeah and as soon as you do it like a
gleaming salmon Oh too much just leaps
right over your head there does when I
go see Fisher back
y'all gonna eat I did it what a great
what a great day she's just like they're
just like going on both sides of her
under the water and she's like we have a
lot of we have a lot to accomplish here
but would you be willing to get a few
and catch a few of these and get them
out yeah BAM I want to see I want to see
what did art Denar are you up yeah I
guess the stink do you come back to the
fireese at the fire pit good hot bean
water bean water
yeah who knows what that by what the
effect of the caffeine is on the
Dragonborn biology put some sleep in a
fire
yeah I just I feel like dinar would be
an excellent I guess I'm thinking of
like a bear standing in a river fishing
like I feel like a dinar standing in a
river would catch a lot of fish oh he
could like sashimi all of them yeah sure
just a rich rich slice
what about whip could you whip him out
of the water oh yeah yeah yeah well she
should get the floss out yes so she she
stands up drippin wet waddles out of the
River and to a stand where the the the
wooden stands that had the the weapons
laid against them they were in bad shape
and also the weapons that were on them
were weapons in quotation marks right
the fishing rods are in excellent repair
hmm of course they are in immaculate
that's a shame because we don't need oh
I will enable wit fishing if that's what
we want to do I think one is like
sharpening a stick I think this is
something that she knows how to do and
like a fishing rod would only get she'd
be like what is this tangled in it like
a cat like 1 or 2 it's like mmm yeah
you're mummified after one or two whips
you can use whatever implement whatever
instrument you would like sharpen sir
but no like a ice fishing just like
whack him on the head well I'm a low
point for this show oh yeah
oh she's ready to go she's looking she
has a nautical pass yeah I'm Chris Chris
but you are welcomed to this fish fest
as well Stravaganza yeah well again yeah
and you can do anything
I'm too included like there's there's
literally no rules just right this is
like the Outback Steakhouse a fishing me
of livers I mean the so what occurred to
me was since we have some time to prep I
ask it's a good idea first you seem like
you're ready for business
yeah I'm like I could probably square
out like a whole region of fish trap him
in hunger of Adar get him get them fresh
act fresh-caught between those milky
tentacles and we could just probably
just pick them out like like fish in a
barrel
[Laughter]
yeah swords to plowshares okay probably
what do you want to need swords well
here you can do what you want to prepare
your I'm asking prepare your ritual do
we need that many or yeah okay there's
no I mean let me let me read up on it
make sure it's not like tentacles will
obliterate any fish yeah they might yeah
they may not like it but here
so one by one so so no so this is how it
functions so well he the rest of the
party is out securing these tender
beauties cthe ris is on the riverbank
studying a grimoire of some kind like
i'm looking up like hunger aphid are in
the index and then the fishing other
uses for well here's good news how wide
is this river the river itself is 30
feet long
okay that's pretty feet across I can
it's not it's more than three feet long
not only can i reap the you know this
aquatic bounty with hunger of Adar in a
20-foot radius by opening a gateway to
the darkness between stars but any
anything that starts its turn in that
zone is gonna take a 2d6 cold damage
keep them fresh for you so here's what
i'll do i'll i'll drop it in there
keep those fish fresh and cold and this
is the Milky tentacles right yes they
don't
right away though at first it's a sphere
of blackness of bitter cold and then
that once the Gateway is open the
tentacles emerge because if a creature
ends a turn then you're gonna take that
milk damage technically it's 2d6 acid
fishing dukkha thrist
fishing this is this is what I want I
wanted on iOS yup crystal is fishing mhm
we're looking at what's the best Dacula
fishing that's all I get stretch what my
leaky what's the best place for the for
the fish to like is there any Eddie's
over there I need to avoid cuz I want to
all come right through here and then I'm
going to release these these beasts but
then I'm going to dispel them right away
so we get that that freshness sealed in
but then we'll have to just sweep them
up as they are carried down those so
you're just gonna freeze the fish you're
gonna make them chilly
I don't know that they'll freeze but so
a lot of them will die gonna be slowed
I'm sure that boom slowed yeah
well it's 2 6 damage how much fish up
maybe this looks larger fish yeah listen
you blood them right in the river blood
them this sense like you you'd know how
to do this do we need more hands should
we get something what you don't gonna
want to get us some Nets yeah absolutely
yeah we should recruit some children
children you'll want to see this come
she's got all the towns folk kids with
me coming this is gonna be great
thinking we're gonna go fishing you miss
it yeah they're all done well here well
you're well you're preparing kiss kiss
yeah I will show dinar how to show these
children how to fish okay so if you can
grab your D 20s out of there also I will
have Clark Mar with me
when I woke up nice yeah you said that
ten minutes ago
no Jamie if you would please lift up
your character sheet and scoot over your
book you'll see there's a piece of tape
there is did you make a mini game yes
exactly
tell you what okay now the very first
part of doing it is to roll a survival
check so grab a d20 no roll and
according Eddie you can take advantage
if you want should we actually use my
smaller one because I mess up a specific
place for nothing I can move them in a
moment at a moment's notice
all right that's at five would you like
to take a yes okay that's a 3-week all
right what that means it's all in and
rail that means that you get a single
cast and it's at a d4 level you want to
roll much better than that between this
tape and that tape mm-hmm
you will flick with your middle finger
and then any die that you hit is a fish
that you can collect hang on oh the
number on the top it represents the
amount of food value that you brought to
town is a food value is roughly akin to
morale for a city for a for a village
like promise that has really been under
heel for such a long time okay so it
doesn't matter what number this is no
that doesn't matter at all but if you
can get as many of these fish as you can
hit you can take okay what you just
explained to us I explained to the
children yes exactly it's like this kids
it's like this listen up you should live
fish make people happy very nice boy so
boy so how does it work so how do you
tell them it's like because there was
clearly a couple different fish here
yeah one one of them for women one of
them tugs at the shining cloak bulwark
and says find that one because he
is the largest and most nutrient he's
got a lot of vitamins in him and you
need to eat your vitamins all right now
would you like to show him how it's done
walnut yeah all right you're gonna need
to start survival with a survival check
and you want more than three or five you
got it that's an 18 okay but that gives
you to die you get a d8 in 84
good I have no control over my physical
self charmed by this well here you
haven't seen nothing yet
what's this the old wicked finger oh no
no terrain you're not gonna upstage me
yep oh that counts I know oh you got you
grabbed a tender for value fish she
stumbles when she first no the first one
is like caught in the bank yeah oops
mega tugs now would before before you
set up your your evil fish catching
engine you guys want to do a little cast
they'll reel and rod over here yeah all
right yeah I'm getting ready I'm
realizing I really I don't have enough
pickled octopus tentacle yeah I might be
able to do it with this much I know
right it's not a big part of the game
it's not here so you should start with
your survival check yeah yeah and what
you can take advantage in okay I will do
that because my survival is not great so
it's gonna be either 14 or an 8 okay 14
grants you ad for thank you
their jump in a day mmm yeah you summon
a lot nice no honestly it is chickies
like us yeah I see four tumbled gently
off the table
no nowhere close to them guys just it's
just lost in the folds of your cloak it
looks it looks like you're feeling it
looks like your arraignment is being
haunted by a tiny ghost the line here
now you obviously you have an evil
mystical spell but would you would you
like to at least try the game here so go
ahead and throw the dice and obviously
survival oh I'll uh I'll enjoy a
advantage juicy management and now the
tender fish over here Oh looking good
I'm vittles was scary isn't it totally
they give it a good one though from
there yeah yeah here we go don't be like
me try my best
you're you're both eyes on it goes right
over this is a situation where it's like
you catch a small fish and then another
fish just bites on and then comes along
for the ride holman exactly so that is
that is a that's a that's a healthy
amount now do you want to I mean you're
hauling out some plump some plump
product do you want to activate your
truly nightmarish fish threshing engine
well I think that I think that I see the
town is having probably having some fun
with it
oh it's definitely like a fishing derby
like people are definitely coming out of
the mine to watch for a little bit yeah
and then head back down this could be
the last thing I do
I was gonna say that like he has enough
social understanding that like maybe
they need to do it and enjoy it rather
than me pulverized their River with an
alien pod let them enjoy fishing that's
true yeah Wow and then when they're done
with the fun getting a chance to look
away it's this wholesome down by the
river a good time and there's just like
there's just like a like a black light
pouring out of my mouth and then I close
my mouth and just maybe I'll let them
enjoy it for a little bit
I have been wondering if hunting that
would make an appearance I'm getting
bear snakes nice tried dress get more
fish than Denari I like this is the
first thing that has been able to truly
distract me from my grief okay yeah I
get dinner like a side I like alright so
right right around you is just the water
is just displaced in this massive splash
children seem more okay with this than
grown-ups mm-hmm I see a person
transform into a massive bear exactly
the Midwife
claps and laughs and and it was just
just like pushing people toward the
river like oh don't don't be so
superstitious are you down with some
fish you want to get those fish
well-well already can Clarke Moore do
anything can an elk rail good at fishing
yeah yeah there's another one didn't
make any funds there isn't yeah there's
no reason exactly up his old head in
there so Clarke Morris survival is
six holy good for him still roll friend
mm-hmm take out that posh happen 24 my
friends this is stressed there's a
special rule actually if you get a twin
so it's gonna be worth doing 18 it's
very good 18 now there is his bites
Clark it's good serious get dangerous
alright so you want to hit the back oh
yeah fish wine
I don't know cuz I'm trying to hit the
doobly oh yeah absolutely so it's a time
for there's a time for that precious
it's not honey-nut to get in there
alright so give me the d20 yeah let's
see how many noobs we get on this ultra
chunks really we're looking for the sick
flavor okay 21 is 3 holy crap you're
like I'm just glad to know there's one
coming now I'm excited
ordinarily I'd be upset about like
loading it up like that but it's pretty
good you're like I'm gonna take all
these think of a really good next
Wednesday I'm gonna drop this claim your
singing is so so sure what are you doing
Dana the hook once did again yeah you
caught too close to the Sun three fish I
did that's good very very good
now is there more more over here more
love oh yeah you don't get it yeah oh
yeah no yeah embarrass that's right well
now it's like it's like an us versus Ben
thing so she's got him she's got a
Russian side
can she how
like are they still like unsustainable
no no the town the town is okay with
this because no one has been able to get
anything out of this and they haven't
been able to go anywhere to resolve the
problem either like this is this is the
best thing that has ever happened to
this town so yeah by all means
roll that d20 well and give me the
flavor your kind of fish with the forces
of shadow so I think maybe a little okay
so you describe for me that the
parameters of your shadow net whatever
it is what I would like to do is to
create a dam in the river looks like a
wall of shadow so that rather than going
downstream they're all just like pooling
up and they're not moving too much so
like it gets easier it's easier for me
to get them absolutely here so it'll be
some support so here's what I want to do
you ready yeah watch this so first of
all you're gonna use graham and Mansi
Yeah right
mm-hmm this is how I would adjudicate
that fuckin sweet all right I'll take
advantage on this survival check why
don't you
I shall do it it's a twelve or a ten
twelve I guess so is there any survival
just lost you okay so twelve total huh
get sick with it thanks now but these
are these are a high-value fish these
are high asset value fish no don't
overshoot the box okay got it in the box
that leaf listen it was in the box he
does not overshoot the box but you still
get he gets the big fish though right I
think that that's fair
well I was gonna say explained so what
just happened was you create
like a Corral yes shadow yeah and then
but didn't cast the line and it didn't
bring anything that's right yes so the
shadow Corral for these fish you see an
operation well you need is a what you
need is a heap of rolls and you can come
out of this like a fucking champion this
is a tier V champ you need that like
20-plus but I mean this doesn't with
some like egging on I say yeah all right
I think all right I'll do it that way
cuz this is the perfect time destroy
these fish that's are you gonna
annihilate the fish well yes it would
well yeah yeah so now I could do my
garden like okay it's it's I'm charmed
by all this and people standing on the
edge and like casting their lines in and
like hahaha okay everybody out adults
win a cult swim swim like tentacular
spectacular yeah that's what I'm gonna
do forget hunger padorin don't like so
describe it describe it for me see how
many of these we get we're gonna what
we're gonna enjoy is just spearing them
from anywhere I can beneath what I love
to have happen just these two come up
like shafts and yeah piers fish and then
coming and pluck them like from a tree
come children send the kids out to do
that let's see yeah what's so but what's
required for it to succeed still in our
connection well that that's that's only
if you want to Arkana check that is a
that's an artifact of season one sure
that's if you want to create something
substantial and continuous with crystal
oh you wanted to fuck up a bunch of fish
is not in our Canon rule okay my friend
yeah if I can drop those there and
murder fish and will they remain
contained absolutely here
here you are my friend there's no bomb
in the water it's important then
nobody's what are these these are curly
tentacles so I have generated a base
fish value I see and now you can get as
many extra fish as you can get with your
home from your four dice okay all right
let's see what I can do on the answer
fish that is all over fish it's so long
and thanks for all the fish okay there's
layered smile on the banks like people
like fishings like father and son and
all that and then this guy is like
blasting for shallow water over here
more so give me the chorus dialogue I
can use to flavor this this experience
so thank you get everybody out of the
water and then there's got to be a piece
of dialogue right there has to be a my
do I like I like for the for the
children what comes the children are our
future
yes our grades natural resource and it
does like fishing hole like that shadow
Corral is now like has collected losing
Chum it's destroyed so so and they're
tall well no no yeah and they need to go
and that saw hedge is carving yeah yes
so it's like it starts after your
exhortation to the children it starts
with a sound that is like a hot tub
being turned
there's a bubbling and churning intense
possibly geothermal heat has begun to
savage the riverbed and then coming up
like a crown of wicked thorns you see
this tiny amethyst flower bloom but it
is only the top of a massive crystalline
fractal tree that is completely covered
in the deck Garland's of fish and then
as it reaches its full height it begins
to dance and shriek in the son of Fisher
Fisher flying everywhere on both sides
of the river hey they said they wanted
fish yeah how are the kids taking it
they they they are unhappy they have not
been delighted by their by this new God
you've asked them to worship you have to
worship it it's just here to feed us
it's just here to take care of us
reverence is enough eventually the cold
river water and the gram and man see it
just sort of snaps and then the water
carries this this evil bloody gem trees
lattice it's way down the river they're
shrimping gods if it's so good to us
lately and then just monster coral reef
comes in no and just rolls like a
tumbleweed through the town like
screeching and shinned and you know
shrieking as it does so
it's only yeah exactly so that is in
terms of raw in terms of raw value that
is more than I wanted you to get hmm
that was in fact a superior result and
what that means is that you can ask the
townspeople to do one more thing for you
today
mm-hmm when it comes to defending the
town itself so this task has taken up a
lot of today the rest of today the very
first day of your capacity to manage
this stuff we need to figure out what
types of fortifications in the town
proper in what way can sorta and the
Midwife direct the city direct direct
the village to produce defensive results
kind of pilots he they have so much
stone yeah we need to fortify walls and
then create some sort of defense on the
hill that's the strongest point of
attack yep
yeah cuz they have the high ground no hi
Graham bad you don't want the high
ground just hiding the mines what I'm
saying low ground good idea that's
really how about we like so one thing
that I will offer to do also it's like
the rodent work of building a wall I'm
gonna generate a bunch of Velvets to do
that multiple moments I just don't
usually do it oh cool
I don't have enough cloths for all of
them but yeah that's amazing I can spit
out and expedite some of that well
feeding the town was one of the main
goals
I mean sources been here a while and is
something we feel general asked her know
like what else needs to be done
absolutely that we've actually reached
the midpoint of the show when we come
back we'll talk with Sasha and see where
she thinks the resources would be best
chef's council mayor let's please you
will be back right away hello I'm Jerri
hilarious no one heard it I'm Geoffrey
Games and this is Tess see teams when
last we saw our heroes they had recently
concluded the most eldritch fishing
derby of all time it culminated in
terror but also in pounds and pounds of
healthy protein the town itself was
bolstered by this positive outcome and
indeed they are ready to be directed for
day ones defensive shoring up of the
town is there any piece of information
that I can offer that will help you come
to good stable satisfactory defensive
conclusions that's no surprise at all
well Rosie doesn't have anything as cool
as what walnut can do for instance sure
so look why don't we start with your
idea and then we can go around talk
about what we're gonna do for
fortification okay yours is a good one
so um I can use stone shape is it not
stole it's so not stone is it yes that's
the mess my ruling okay okay good I'm
sitting in the snow machine seat so
thanks sure so I can do five cubic feet
of stone shaping and so my deal was to
go along the wall and just fuse very
small parts of a wall just a bolster
just to bolster it yeah so it's like we
can pile it up and then I'm not going to
shape it into a perfectly smooth wall
I'm just gonna kind of yeah so this is
gonna be hard exactly what's strong you
can't just be kicked over yeah battering
exactly and so it sounds to me like
you'd like to leverage the stone
resources that promise had heaped up
yeah as much as they can do for one day
and we will do more another day exactly
where do you want to
use that resource would you like to use
it to the south would you like to use it
toward the east where the the road
proper enters I saw they there they are
all especially after the miracles
performed this afternoon between them
and between the relationships they built
up with sorta they are ready to get to
work so we want to attack from the hill
right we want to get them in the town
and we're gonna attack from the high
ground is that which we said we
definitely want to defend against them
attacking us for that yeah that's true
we don't want them so on the hill coming
down so then we want to fortify that
section first
oh that's fairly notice the top of the
hill the north tell me tell me how you
want to do that um that's the tree I
think we would want to do maybe two two
walls one one up close and that a small
half fight one out in the field just
like break them you know ya know - well
I was gonna ask how many stones there
are yeah because two walls is definitely
with a layer in between learning that
you can move and fortify and then
retreat back to the second point if you
need yeah don't you just dig a big pit
there um be like yeah we're gonna over
this easy wall and then it's fall home
fill it with tentacles mm-hmm yeah it's
your solution everything leaves we
benefit from being in that mine they're
gonna will also benefit from them dying
in a different mind the shallow mind
that we make it's win-win
i I just know that they're gonna have a
lot of archers so I want to plan for
that contingency and so you're talking
about something like a trench yeah
between two walls and that is situated
up on the hill no I mean before the hell
yeah two walls for sure I don't know if
that we could do a trench there but if
there's if there's a spot you do a
charge there didn't they could fire
they're ready to they're ready to work
can do a trench in front of the wall
trench wall wall right now right now the
material that you have ready to work and
ready to go
is a massive heap of stone fish yeah
yeah exactly I don't know about the fish
wall as a defensive rampart to fill the
trench of the fish confuse them so that
should go in the trench yeah
stench right away no it got bad right
away I already I know I've done wrong
and I'm gonna make a donation yeah some
kind that's typically what's done in the
u.s. trench fund yeah you are
okay there are there's a town here
there's Hills here and you are building
walls before the hills or on top of them
because if we're building here it can
probably still fire into that
okay so then we yeah we can do it on the
hill yeah I think that's probably the
right the right move okay ups on top of
the hill proper yeah yeah that also
gives us a good place to defend
ourselves while we watch for their
approach because the theory is that
they'll be coming for and then we'll
retreat you the other wall yeah yes
gotcha so you're gonna create a sort of
almost like a crown style like
crenellations at the top of this hill to
thin fine walls with a dug trench in the
center yes
okay got me I like that it's gonna take
some of the day and summit tomorrow but
you will get exactly what you want out
of that process now the Midwife did
suggest that under cover of night it
might be possible to go to frim and face
and try to secure additional help from
another town that no doubt will
eventually suffer the same fate if they
don't mm-hmm metal start doing their
trade
they've got gems they do that silver
I was thinking I mean they said that
they've been bringing it like there what
the weapons that we have are really
crummy yeah get a trade somebody that
going yeah yeah that makes sense to me
who's our charisma boy is that you
mm-hmm yep if you didn't have another
plan no I definitely wanted to go to
that town there something I was thinking
also I just had a question what's on the
other side of the river on that's on me
so those are the summer hills basically
like from at any point in the summer
hills you just look out and it looks
almost exactly the same so there is just
rolling hills no kind of as far as you
can see across the other side there's a
few stumps there might have been a
logging operation there you could do
that that's where they got the wood for
this like for the bunk houses that they
have but there's no cover like it is
naked I don't give them such a fish
slapping if they go in that river don't
worry oh shit oh yeah can you imagine I
can it would be a sound like a sawmill
[Music]
you did wanna go you already wanted to
go Frank yeah did you have another like
agenda there no the agenda was to get
weapons for the town okay you're gonna
take the cart people to fight to towns
folk I'll try
could you who else is going you are
pretty I just go by myself entitled I
mean I would leave I mean I would leave
them or my velvets to fortify I also
realized that like off of the the
fishing expedition
another idea comes to me so I've been
who would I into it I entrust this to me
it's actually say no you need to know
promise ring I'll mention it offhand to
dinara just to test the
even though you're probably not the one
did Chris should talk to about it so
I've been I've been doing some research
in my father's knife and we could hollow
out a trench and trick them into falling
into it or we could turn that trench
into a literal hell because I've learned
how to summon a greater demon with place
one in there and just let it grind up
the you know the attackers know it's
like a like they would they would it's
almost like a little taste of
punishments to come and in the afterlife
just dig that pit ever since we died
you've been really weird you feel
something wet
intensely so on your left elbow and you
hear a sound a suckling sound oh no I
look at my left elbow you think that the
pouch is trying to nurse I'm trying to
get know it is insistent drop my elbow
down nurse him elbow down in there
alright he's been good to me he lets go
and he is sort of like snorkeling his
way like up to your wrist in your hand
oh so like I'm yeah he's just like I'm
now down in this exactly is my I'm bent
or is it straight well no he's he's let
go of this okay so you know he's traced
going nuts on the on the knuckle in the
finger zone wait am i misunderstanding
who's been lunch on me this is your this
is your courts person okay yeah so
that's a big ask
I didn't imagine it to be bigger than
about like that but if it's like oh yeah
he's kind of it it can accommodate yeah
you're like talking to me about thing
boy it's never done this before
being and it's salivating like it's just
ready to it's it's got something it's
got something in there and it wants to
offer up oh go ahead get some I was
expecting when it has something to offer
I was expecting more like a hairball a
cat sound than a it's eating yeah yeah
okay so let's see it it summons up the
the best part of its will and spits out
something on the ground in front of you
wet a little look at it so there is a
little it looks almost like a like a
marble pouch or like a dice bag oh yeah
with a tiny rolled piece of parchment in
the top that's been cinched oh sure
let's let's read that be contacting me
at this it says these are gifts from
Strix is party use them with care and
inside the pouch are two golden rings
okay then there's no instruction on
their use no no thank you I forgot the
rest of it may I may I
that was when I was in my guys as omen
right I did manage to steal a few items
for my team went out was it was it a
theft but not as hot as promise ring but
there's no pepper
there's a like a ring situation with
that party so they'll proceed with
caution I don't know yeah witness
doesn't know that no it's really just
like excited about these rings what's
the letters thing from Strix is party
to assist us exactly you get use a
potion manage them see if I can discern
yeah I mean if you are talking and this
all happens well try the arc an
advantage work for me before
[Laughter]
keep running because I might be able to
that's a reward oh that's delish this is
this is a stock standard there is
anything especially if they did much
more than this it would require a lot
more sophisticated process you have
every faith especially with that that
this is that they're simply rings of
protection anybody might do something
else also but that would require a lot
more assessment and analysis okay
potentially even research it's very
natural I see can I history him same
history why not it's your day we need
and I want to role want to energizes you
can't oh that's a nineteen plus three
that's very nice do I get any more yeah
absolutely
they have markings on them that you
don't recognize and it's important you
don't recognize them because this isn't
like oh I haven't seen that before
mmm-hmm you don't think you don't think
that anyone has seen this before
this is not this is not a
this is not a Ferren artifact this is
from you you have a sense that there are
other places having spent some time in
one this is not these are not of the
realms beyond comprehension
I look at it and I can't even discern a
letter yeah am i able to rule it doesn't
match it doesn't actually that doesn't
match any like anything that would have
a language to it it doesn't match any
language that you have ever seen oh it
doesn't matter if it has a language yeah
yeah exactly
exactly I'm trying to think of how I
would try to communicate it emojis
what's close yeah yeah exactly
it's cloaked in so much you think that
to understand it correctly would require
the barriers cultural not linguistic
yeah it'd be like a psyche ematic it's
fitting to me idiomatic it is it is this
is a cultural artifact in addition to
its mystic payload
this looks like a little poop and
there's an eggplant exactly what does it
mean hot shadow council just like how
long first needs one yep yeah 1600 yeah
I already have 14 that's true my old
junk fine Olympics delicious as soon as
you do it Rosie pronounces you Sarah
Mary twice and he's just for giggles and
I got the Rings are definitely paired I
mean this much you can tell this is what
they call a friendship ring
very very this is friendship yeah this
is a friendship ring I better not be
open during a protection that's what I
mean right yeah exactly
no does anybody who all is gonna go on
denars field trip you know let's go to
frame and the way you sell it yeah maybe
yeah maybe I'll go with you
trying to think about the reason why
cats risk would would go yeah yeah but
like what's the value added there for
dinar your natural showmanship or your
you're fascinated by the idea of a time
imprint but it's just too stupid yeah
maybe third company even trying to
assess it eight hours ago
hey huge bloody crystal tree very good
at catching fish yeah maybe that's why
it's like I didn't mean to convince we
can come up with something you'd look
like a townsperson go in the crowd okay
a lot all right
unless one my dinner I'm go with you boy
trip just a boy later all right
we have to sleep right get drunk freely
it's not it's not yet under cover of
night but it's not it is not far away
even on foot you guys I'm gonna pass
that trace my put that round coriander
okay could all go a long night yeah this
is our song elf ears can hear yes she's
just like it's beautiful thank you
Rosie's playing by the way is
the jam and song from alive man he's
going to train the villagers to fight
barehanded just in case the weapon thing
doesn't work out that's great she's
gonna teach them all martial arts nice
it's like they like the free like the
free class you get mm-hmm yep yep ladies
self-defense classes throwing straight
straight straight eyes neck eyes I
suspect it would be as very effective as
a training montage scene that's gonna
happen somewhere in here okay here you
you get it propped up and you get it
ready to go yeah now are you boys ready
for your adventure as we've been told
this this is we plan to be back quickly
this is not that far away or no the
shaking overnight thing no this is
definitely not overnight okay should
just be a few hours don't need to pack a
bag yeah say we need to pack anything
yeah I gotta say last goodbyes the car
know what I'm saying it's not oh well
fingers crossed yeah so if we've now
have passed without trace last time
stuff yeah if we know the way I'm no
photographer I don't know where I say
that way yeah okay so once we get there
what's the what's the goal
do we we have proof of where we're from
we know what they have to offer they've
done that business before we want them
to fight for us oh are you guys taking
silver well yeah that's that is this
saying so first we're gonna have to load
up on silver I mean I assume the town is
not gonna be remissed like they'll let
us know silver I don't know I mean fact
matter is they can't trade it for
anything
like right now they're sitting on a
worthless mine all right yeah so we take
that how do they have any carts that are
larger than our cart ours our cart the
largest vehicle they have this largest
vehicle in town yeah no generally
speaking what happens is the carts come
to the towns okay to withdraw the
resource um do we need more should we
grab any townsfolk or anything is it
enough for I'm just thinking of like
volume
weight-wise forgive me bringing back a
bunch of weapons doing in able bodies to
help carry it I mean the first thing
that came to mind was figuring out what
the mayor's deal is cuz he doesn't seem
like much of a mayor it might be asleep
at this I'll bring him with us to vouch
for us I I don't know if he has any kind
of power at all that's true did it but
maybe this is the only place in which he
has power he doesn't seem to have any
other control again be he's a diplomat
maybe he could be helpful that's very
good for us to be like the power
structure here is that yeah this mayor
must come with us yeah it's not we're
unvetted he'd be able to speak on our
backs true he would be able to speak on
her Mary couldn't hurt loose those
wheels would they other town know who he
is
I asked well you're someone you can talk
to talk to anybody you want yeah alright
I asked the Midwife she's been helpful
and seems to know yeah absolutely
she has made a sleeping draught that's
helping the younger ones get rest this I
know that tussin yeah this is a these
are these are very difficult times even
for grownups may the angel sing you
asleep
[Laughter]
what do you what do you have well we we
make our I am assuming this this plan
that we're talking through the whole
town never the whole group is a part of
this plan like hey we're gonna go to
shrimp yeah we're gonna go get some
shrimp we're gonna get some weapons and
we're maybe gonna try to convince some
fighters to come with us yeah is there
anything we need to know about that is
there anyone here who has the
relationships with the folks in frim
with rip she says most of us do I mean
we've never had a specific rule about
who can go over and trade like we're
we're on great terms with them is there
is there value in bringing the mayor
he's not doing anything right now she's
like if you could take him out of here
that would be
so helpful addition by subtraction yeah
that's the ideal case friend yeah she
says something his value being him hmm
definitely take him we can't find he's
missing but he's he's me snuck away when
there's work to be done she says please
take him what's his name
I say alright let's go over to his house
and get him yeah yeah yeah yes he has a
baby in the mine she has a Hut he's
always thinking he he has a Hut that is
slightly smaller than the midwife's hut
but is still distinct from the mass
houses and you can see sort of in a in
the candlelight you can see a shadow
flickering back and forth through the
slats of the door Frank who is it your
your new visitors here to to lend aid
and succor to this to this pitiful town
yeah we haven't asked you here you hear
something strike the floor took a little
leather plate or something like that and
then he comes over and opens the door
and says ah
you yes don't summon any more amethyst
trees well I'm around ha ha I wish I had
more control it was a tragedy he said oh
I'm just turning in for the night oh
that's a shame it seems like there's a
lot to do and time is it actually how
late at night is this it's it's getting
it's probably in spring hours it's
probably about 9:00 no lion
and still he's justhe's dork close to
somebody else is like training yeah
everyone's out still doing stuff yeah uh
we would go to France
yeah see if we frim get some additional
aid how how did he how do you intend to
what's the plan
Oh travel there and show them our our
silver and see if we can convince them
to fight if we defeat these bandits it
would help them as well
and you being a the mayor of this town
I'm seems like you would be a good envoy
it's it's really an an honorific it's
not it's not I mean there was a vote I
did win it
hey I push past and I go good cop time
over and then I just kind of push him
harsh let me go put your clothes on
you're coming with us
yeah I step into his little boy and he
go get dressed put pants on you're
coming with us
there's you can see his knees he has
there's paper and quills laid out in
here and in this town that is a
relatively uncommon sight that appears
to be his focus literacy so he slips on
what looks like in the dark of the hut
which is my novel coming out and he
slips on his own bracer like a piece of
archers armor on the on the table
[Music]
whoever we're burning daylight
and when I watch people dig I get very
tired and you can sleep in the car
alright okay but it's in and out like
this no time you go to primp they start
bringing out the trays Fred shrimp we
could be on the row on the road already
if all this yammering
let's go ya know take something off his
desk like this is mine now
[Laughter]
exactly now so you can it's basically
you would get there you cross the river
and then there is a path that you can
take entirely between hills
that is absolutely away from the main
thoroughfares that about carts travel
and our Kent card would be able to
handle it oh definitely not
this would be something you'd be going
on foot on foot oh well that's all well
and good but then we can't you can any
weapons you can do do you want to do you
want to try to go the cart route
I think we're when I got half a carton
you're gonna polish up this product with
the mysticism yes and we've got the orb
like we've got an orb the stealth warble
within the car to raise a chaplain yes
yeah yeah you have all kinds of you have
all kinds of tools that you can use to
do it I'm distinct it's it's it's it's
rough road well I mean if we're the goal
the ultimate goal is absolutely stated
number one is weapons right are we gonna
get them back take a horse and we have
time I think if they didn't bring him
tonight at least get the deal
sealed yeah yeah yeah Dick Clark Morin
and a great top of the cart
yeah I guess we could ride Clark more
and coriander yeah I think about how
many like swords he could carry in his
bill oh that's right
weapon rack yeah we do be sorry okay all
right yeah then we don't need the cart
right then so you so you guys are able
to I mean that the heads are up high
Clark Morris is able to handle it just
fine and coriander just plows like a
submarine just plows straight across the
water and gate is completely stable I
dunno about the color I'm just letting
you know
ELISA I got that I got like my mind on
the cauldron and the color in my mind
well when when I'm hitching her from the
wagon and I hate feeding her but
recognizing that this is asking extra of
her yeah I will also give her a couple
gold coins beforehand
Oh yo if you add that character growth
what's that cold that ice cold tongue
yeah just laps up those coins I just
yikes I just don't
angrily insult her this time yeah I
squinch so you you come out you're able
to wind through this place and it's like
is it a trick that turns out it turns
out that it is a good thing probably in
toto
to have a local guide hmm but this is
taking longer than they said it would he
is on the mayor on this one is often he
is he often has suggestions about other
ways to go ways that are shorter and as
as the night has gone on he says it
might be better if we just went back
this asshole leading us in the wrong
direction
he says it's hiding late how does this
jibe with what Rosie said earlier like
cuz it seemed like her on a a line to
that or is it just no this is not
getting this is not correct it can't
possibly be the same
world hello you guys drive the cart one
time huh all right well one way if we're
sniffing that he's messing with us we
say are you are you intentionally lady
goes a long way
why we could all be killed out here why
would I spend any more time out here
than I was possibly has to I can't his
own a truth yeah and I asked him again
absolutely do you know the way to that
we're supposed to go I'm a liar
yes you're going to take us in the
correct direction now I don't want to at
all but you're going to I'm going on
choke you and leave you out here I'm
going to do everything I can to slow
this down show us the direction you
don't want to go in it's the wrong way
for you
wait we offered you can ask him the
right way yeah he's under a truth spell
yes to lying around about I'm gonna say
is like which way do we go
like you like we want to go to France is
this the right way to go No
is that the right way to go No is that
the right way to go okay the truth
earlier he can be killed out here ten
minutes so ten minutes I keep checking
like a reason to go there right there so
you're you're back on your friend with
beasts you're moving in the direction
and then like I said at night especially
the somber hills are incredible
some would say even optimal opportunity
to be lost simply because you're
surrounded at all times by these hills
that take over the horizon and there's
always another one between the other
hills but going on the path that he
reluctantly offered you think that you
can see frim or a town at any rate yeah
in the distance and even at this time of
night there their central fire is still
going it's a press-on until we can write
get hungry sir
oh what'd ya know why he wanted to slay
guys now right why are you afraid so
you're the mayor of an incredible like a
booming town yes agreed
I'd liked it to remain so mm-hmm
I'm the mayor of a town for the next two
days that was before we arrived you may
be mayor of this town for five six days
no we added a solid week probably more
your impeach Frank covenants clerk more
lifts up his nose and is catching
something on that on the increasingly
chilly breeze still that's not a true
sign I say away as a boy friend are you
afraid of fried shrimp do you fear
shrimp oh it's true
so as you the closer you get to the town
the more you realize that the fire is
not contained to the center of town no
all right to the ground
Oh fried fried shrimp so we should get
my girl I should stop at the edge
actually and what spell do you have that
can scout right oh my god of stuff yeah
say you can have some so this place is I
mean there are there visible bodies
strewn about geez the central the
central area of this camp Josh can you
get my cauldron please thank you oh come
on um Chris Chris you hear a giggle
from coriander settlement video I don't
thing to do alright I'm gonna I'm gonna
ten I was very attached knit round I'm
not yet I'm not obsessed let's see
what's going on you pop it open and you
see a little glint off of the scales in
the moonlight oh no and she says yeah
you hit you you hear her cheer and then
laugh from the oh geez and then she
pulls the burlap right back over and she
could be like yeah I scooped her up over
here little one
I would the mayors right there frozen at
the moment he's like you brought a child
he brought her let me good cup this one
I'm an idiot sorry I should have checked
the bags because my instinct was like
all right we're gonna have to save who
we can or gonna have to like potentially
avoid kind of like now well can't bring
him no we can't it out I mean fight you
don't have one of those cool ashes or
the baby bjorn the traditional yeah my
battle bjorn is in my bag exactly so
before additional yeah sorry i would be
ran up okay you're like here we go
before well mean you also here bulwark
so you have your Warren Beatty's you
have your ear your cool shiny keep your
baby chicken that you can rap that's
true between them your Nenana I can
protect him pretty well is that what
you're calling the bulwarks is she yes
his cloak okay
I'd rat I've put that I put Crenn are in
the Bjorn proper wrap that cloak then
put the mayor in front touch him so
we're all like this little like
suggesting that all on I can extra
shield yeah yeah happily so okay I'll
have to transfer on to Clark more at
that I get the perception rolls from
from tois good perception Oh Zack my
best reward oh yeah you want to yes
ominous we both got four that's ominous
but daddy's rolling again this I'll
juice you know chase it yeah any doubles
much a so what is that
that's seventeen alright so in the
chorus of sounds so the wind whipping
through the flames of the town I'm doing
that Grinch yeah exactly you hear
something like a who just to maintain
the metaphor okay what is but in this
case what is it sound literally sound
like it sounds like a young girl no was
it like a little kid this doing see
where it's coming from you didn't think
you can only hear it right now on in
this chorus of sounds you have assessed
this you have found this note in it
there's somebody's are still alive maybe
these are sneaky themes you got a you
got a bad cop this for me what did he
know about this why didn't he want to
come tonight was the mayor know it's
true yeah start shaking him I said did
you know this was gonna happen but
listen it's been happening to a lot of
towns it's not a crazy thing to think
trying to have stopped it for having in
your town yeah you want this to happen
here town well we should be there
instead I point him at the fire I'm like
this is what we're gonna hear to stop we
could have got here earlier and stop
this now he says you can't stop it did
guns boy you know how I can stop
whatever I want shake them some water we
can we can find that out yeah what did I
grab off his desk
well yeah number one that but then like
this seems like so what do we see any
movement in the town we're too far away
all we know is that there's burning and
by you don't see and a sound oh you
don't see movement you just hear okay
you hear a basically a whimper prolonged
cry from right but I mean we're not
seeing like like looting and bandits
like going yeah hehe
no no no you this this is this whatever
happened here happened already
okay way I say we maintain our distance
so he can't hear us I'm gonna send a
message okay to Walnut now and I mean I
can message you that and so I do concoct
a a message to you interrupt whatever
you're doing it's in your mental message
every night and I just say go in the
mayor's Hut what was he working on hope
everything's fine okay
how's the ring fit well work on it I'm
Indian when I get this message all right
I start I grab Rosie and I go we got a
situation that we need to take care of
nice let's just message me and there's
and I get in real close and I go
something's fishy with the mayor oh boy
all right let's go check it out yeah
so we set out for his head it's like two
buddy cop shows
so I'm dude simultaneously one of them
more progressive you know like season
two yeah no no this is the reboot so
yeah absolutely so his dory is still a
jar chopped because he was physically
dragged out of his hide right here so we
go in and I see these rosy and I see at
the same time as look down under I'm
like oh yeah see all these documents and
I said no like you're sticking a dog on
it yeah just like yeah yeah you know no
I see all these documents I get to work
what do i what do I see what do you see
with your with your eating it's a ten
you know that you know documents
I know documents that was for fun and
flavor I think was a good advantage
because she's a document sir it's true
yeah I get advantage on those rolls
naturally because on the documents I
know you I will give you advantage on
this role for being a level two document
sir thank you well there is a seventeen
there's nothing yeah I'm sorry it's all
burned down to seventeen it's blank
it's very very good no no there is he
goes through a lot of paper
yeah what's he doing I don't know uh do
you just you right now you were just
parting the mystic mail okay so I want
to see what he was most recently working
on which I can deduce by that's where
the quill was last laid yeah yeah
exactly what do I see well the one of
the major things that you see is that
there are two he has two cages in his
Hut so on top of the table here is the
lowest level and then there's a shelf
over it
there are two cages just above with
little doors in the front point to this
chromatic that does it look familiar me
what I guess would be in there it looks
like something you'd keep a pet in okay
the pet is nowhere to be found
you don't see it does it in the door
small small pet yeah okay
bird doesn't go shopping yeah definitely
in the base yeah downy yeah cast-off
feathers okay this bird that shitty bird
that was keeping Chris awake don't worry
there are a couple of the brick up
there's like a couple used ink pots and
a couple spare ink pots it's a he does a
high volume I like everything I go eat
that bird can I'll keep an eye out for
it for a second so um what do I see
behind you you can hear something
enter oh come on
what smell is this sound like small
birds don't like a tiny harmless
parakeet a little budgie I turn around I
look at what's coming in it's a tiny
it's a pigeon
oh is it really yeah oh I look at the
pity I speak with it yeah it has a it
has a tiny leather strap on its left leg
the guy yeah it's a kinky a Superman no
it's Eddie it's empty umm I look at this
pigeon and I go hello where were you I
know you speak with animals
so I look at that mega hello where were
you Rosie says at spigen oh and then I
go
[Laughter]
it's just up up yes high up up - we're
near the near these the soft white hmm
then down down two men I say Marik sharp
he stepped on my leg men do that and
it's like it's a it's coming up and it's
a while it while it's cooling at you
it's just given the boot a good Peck oh
yeah I take some birdseed out of my
pocket guaranteed you have it
and I'm sprinkling it down and I say um
I say did the man have a box with
strings on it a string box
yes well he had a wooden nest with him
a wooden nest round round good did I I
think he will made this year I said I
say no eggs inside I I say I say lots of
men so many he says five but you have
never heard a bird use a number higher
than five right Oh
prayer I believe it swings out and I
believe that this I believe this bird
has been the mayor has been treating
with the bandits oh no that's not good
is there any way we can send this bird
with the message to the bandits that
would cause them to not come oh right it
in in Marik's ink and on his letterhead
whatever we got here dude dude this this
is this is good this is this is getting
you going right this weird this is what
you're after this way you want from a
D&amp;D camp yes yes so we could do some
some document forgery which I'm sure you
guys don't have any of the stuff okay
yeah no no I meant I don't have the
stationery oh we have that here he's
good look at all this crap I said that
we won didn't the mayor stuff oh yeah
okay so I'm saying let's let's send it
yeah so I see I see we're on different
differently now I'm with you okay it's
very different possibilities right yes
yeah exactly exactly
well since the mayor's not here let's do
it let's let's do the thing okay so I'm
sitting at the desk I'm like I'm like I
want to like ghost this yeah Rizzy what
do i what should we do okay so you when
it goes to you and I was like all right
but very good no I made my hand
grandmother uh it says M s yes the - yes
uh dangerous reinforcements have arrived
then I read very dangerous very
impersonal yeah good good good good
punch it up yes um yes doesn't your men
we'll never survive mm-hmm
await further instructions
mm-hmm and then sign it cute mayor his
first name yeah and then see if your
friend will take that back I find this
little seal I do that no I make it up
all plainy
and I'm like Oh tiny documents this is
like when you get the Hello Kitty
station oh no those channels on YouTube
they do the tiny food yes yes yes yes
honey cake this tiny documentary so I go
to the pigeon and I I
I say may I sure it's ends on one foot
and then just all right very gently
attach the document I say um go back to
those men know why far tomorrow yes okay
first thing yes up up and then down and
then down and then five and then five
and five and five and five five five
just shakes this little pigeon head
shout council mayor Labor's please you
we have reached the end of another round
of the c-team thanks so much for coming
along hey don't go nowhere we're gonna
go and utilize the facilities and then
immediately we will return for Table
Talk I honestly can't wait we'll see you
soon
you