previously on Tessie teams historically
she has come back from these excursions
of hers unscathed she's just come back
with a bundle of other people's weapons
this time she has those weapons they're
lodged in flesh bring the sword up close
right to my face and I whisper a small
prayer to VARs maelys when the blade is
set up on the shoulder and you sweep it
across in the wake of it there is a
brilliant gleaming copper wing sorry
hello I'm look I need a I'm looking for
a greater demon I greet you warlock I am
the great
and she wants to go like Velociraptor
self through the grass like head and all
this looks scary
oh yes movement happening around her and
just go straight for the nuts you feel a
blade intersect your back but when I
smell that blood even though it's my own
[Music]
product just freshly dead matter
time is the enemy the pastor threatens
the fastest weapon you wouldn't make it
past a second and answer the question
play it brash and reckless to choose a
cautious solution you saw was prudent in
any sepulcher poker toodle become the
pew tree it's that well said I pursue in
no mountain too steep for dungeon too
deep to send expendable marks up to the
top of the peak of beneath they see Yugi
they come like sharks to it while I swim
in that money build like Carl Barks drew
it so send your National Parks drew it
I'll send him home in a natural box with
the close tie the most of the parts
included save your breath for a cleric
confessor death is a lesson that life is
attended professor but if you're seeking
my official advice sign on the dotted
line English of the choice huh I am
Tycho Brahe hey dude he did that on
purpose I know perfectly well what he
did that was no real shame listen this
is what we're fucking hear from this guy
you ready for this don't shame me on
account of my shameful acts Wow
you deserved it you had the one you're
doing the thing I said not to do it so
cool okay first of all was me was an
apology sounds like what I'm gonna text
yep I'm a Bluetooth oesophagus and
that's why you hear it from there
listen this is Tycho Brahe hey of
packing packs I'm also a minute us
Heriberto and CEO of acquisitions
incorporated but today I'm Jerry Hawkins
I'm gonna run a game of Dungeons &amp;
Dragons for my friends with my array
Dragonborn narcissist and our blitz in
that's fine I like clapping to the right
of my right repping the natural world
it's walnut dog grass across the fucking
cross now to my left not your grandma's
grandma except for those rare cases in
which she is your grandma's grandma
Rosie be star I'll check this out
squeeze it okay
that's auto-erotic right there yeah that
is it yeah auto-erotic asphyxiation oh
okay yeah
this one this one time is no this is a
first whoa no no no they were they were
pure and wholesome yeah they were they
were family associations to the left
hand my left family the chicks together
emerging as though from a mist shroud
cuff wrist now hey Kenneth throne when
last we saw our heroes they were being
filleted by Merrick sharp and his roving
gang which is known as the reclamation
project what indeed they are an
organization whose purpose it's a stupid
name is to tell it to Mary sure knock
his purpose is to bring out all the
goods from these mines which are
definitely not burial sites that's the
thing that's the thing you should know
first you should take that with you
okay there's no evidence from the teeth
or a deception check for me it was very
good counsel may my labor please you
your servant Jared K whore camps is that
for Julie now the very first delight
that we have out here now you suggested
that these were called deep and Richard
eyes these are the elders face and they
come in this pouch and they're from the
show I'll show you what's so Eldridge
about these muhfuckas yeah oh my god
listen I'm the winner it is I who won
but in any case shadow council mare Lyra
species as always think use my question
the show that's what you get when you
fuck with me
yep you heard now I get to be Santa
Claus exactly have you learned your
lesson no idiot Whitney
and rich stones back in this mystical
pouch now that that is we were in the
middle of a fight this is a fight that
involves a thoroughly wolfy walnut dog
grass hoo ha woof now ok thoroughly
wolfed for another hot second till I
bleed out exactly there's also basically
roving horse warriors there is a
assortment of evil sons of bitches
not better not the horse people along
with our own crew and of course Marik
sharp himself who has quite a repertoire
and his bag of tricks is still 60 to 70%
full well there is a giant demon named
grave of men that was some it hasn't a
shadow you know a kind of shadow textile
yeah definitely weird
definitely bad every round we find out
if he decides that he wants to attack
the party too
you know that's something fun there's
something fun that could thrist thought
would be great so far he's been a good
friend to me
gentleman stalwart Manion ally ever had
how long until he'd be summons just I
was natural causes he's ran through an
hour ok he's hanging hmm he's hanging we
will fight this oh no it's just it
really is just a matter of time I'm glad
well what is yeah yeah yeah is um is
proficiency impressive in Dungeons and
Dragons and you know rolling sling yeah
what angle dates
that's fast yeah I'm Jaden Smith now
what yeah right no Chris did you send me
a picture
I did okay just yet yeah what is that
picture of you guys is that a picture of
you you know hey I need some pictures of
the initiative track it's a picture of
kind of crackers but display it upon my
penis there we go oh yes we are off 100%
established cthe wrist Rob's turn I
think it wrapped up last time yeah yeah
Rosie Beast injure yes this is the
situation that you see around you you
can see a few a few eyes glinting in the
open mouth of the cave and you can see
you can see other members of the town
trying to push people back in and keep
them deeper in okay you are absolutely
ass deep in foes right now
how many horse voice right now the horse
boy
give their first album yeah right now
you can see eight horse boys okay
how many neon horse boys how many none
worse place therefore none horrible
who's that hit by America just me and
Rosie yeah so far but don't worry okay I
took some damage from something but wait
what it so there was there's four guys
hanging out he I shot through four and
ended them oh but there's still four yes
a an additional four plus eight horsemen
yes they're circling back around we're
doomed
yeah listen uh maybe there's things you
don't know and we have maybe there's
things you don't know okay well that's
right you and I are cursed with
disadvantage on attack roles or on
poisoned yes yeah at a cross okay I'm
Aaron why did you eat poison before this
battle it's dumped oh yeah yeah you
never think it's gonna happen to you
okay so Merrick is still in melee
distance from where I am I have wolf nut
indeed at Merck Sharp Bisharp and a
bunch of a bunch of people whose heads
have been split open by long rods of
amethyst crystal yes excellent love that
group of men indeed a women looking down
okay listen with enthusiasm black saliva
kissing as it hits the grassy plain tell
me the situation of your your amethyst
sharks and tentacles well because they
are I didn't use the skill to retain a
structure exactly you use it as an
attack so I assume that they are not in
great shape they're dissipating they're
okay limp finished done okay okay
flaccid flaccid Newell like looking in
the fridge hungry tired it's 1:30
nope it's bullshit yeah let's see it I'm
gonna i'd like to use grandma man see ya
tell me more
I would like to use grandma Mansi in a
way that is a protective shield of some
kind
for wolf night like something that I
don't even know if it's in corporeal
substance like Hedgehog spikes yeah but
but I don't think I can make my shadow a
solid right that's his thing well it
depends okay then you will recall that
you can absolutely make solid things
right but it would it does require the
use of your staff yes it's like it's
this is a calculation that only Rosie
could make in these seconds great Green
Lantern ring kind of yeah okay so then I
do like this what what I'd like is for
spikes to erupt out of olive wolf nuts
and wounds to prevent further damage to
them hey okay I want to be ready any
like amethyst we can do this is an IP
concern obviously and I we're all
signatories
we will read the contract right yeah
it's not it's not intended to shit it's
actually just something that I want to
grow out of you so now you're this
horrifying like displacer beast style
critter which will hopefully add some
defense to you but certainly will
relieve me of my staff with the master
se so what is your current AC as wolf
nut um 1515 kid I was 14 that was not
correct it was 14 but I get a plus 1
because of my ring okay yeah yes you say
thanks Chris Perkins Wow now so I'm fine
with this okay I support this sort of
thing entirely
so you thought you're talking about
thank you you thinking about wounds
manifesting a kind of almost like an
obsidian like a glinting of City and
time structure blood around it doesn't
but I think that what Rosie would do is
try to target the wounds to try to stop
the bleeding from getting worse that's
in my head I know that's not
mechanically how dandy works okay that's
that's what she would do is to try to
use them as almost like a shadow bandage
yeah but really those are the softest
parts right ones that part that needs
the most protection yes yeah yeah but
but I also think that this is I think
it's a PR aspect to this too yeah I
think that that's really scary
yes yes who the fuck are we fighting I
think is the very first thing I would
think as a Hinch person and I think that
Rosie looks to approval first to group
of men she's like yeah I don't know that
he's turned away from Merrick Sharpton
to consider you know I'm sure happy no
but maybe he feels a little better about
knowing all that this weird shadow
stuff's going on yeah exactly yeah so I
would come so yeah I want you to do yes
yes comfort we're gonna say there's a
cat damn it we're gonna seems like I can
say that there's a protective aha
clotting effect
I'm the cold of this shadow yeah I'm
gonna give you eight hit points
but yeah but your your AC right now is
currently currently 19 Wow hot shit
Jerry so so that's what's going on but
this is but this this is it's very but
it's very very difficult for walnut to
move under these circumstances right now
you basically created a kind of Walt
like Wolf's humidor like this is
something that if you were if you were
if you were a sort of an upmarket
connoisseur of wolves yeah and you're
like I don't want my walls to suffer
damage from heat
UV radio it's like a wolf gig bag yeah X
but it's the hard shell yeah it's it's
so easy you put it right over the plane
you get out there you get it from like
the big and tall section and it's like
oh my wolf good to go okay that's what
yes it is cold and there is a you think
it's there is a whisper of some kind you
can't make out the language and the only
thing you can really see inside of it is
grave of men sort of floating above and
around the fight he is a parent through
it he you wouldn't he's got kids you
observe him as a chop you observe him as
a sort of does a density mmm-hmm through
this through this shield but it's spiky
it would be very very difficult and
dangerous to gain access to the wolf
under this under these auspices rosy be
stinger yeah you've done a great job
thanks hey the nerve let's in so are you
it's Clark more it is three more than
that it is also a sourcing so this is a
kind of war platform housing exclusively
again we're talking about an upmarket
wolf solution this is something that
you'd only see in the finer houses
literally every person on this magic elk
is royalty like this is there's this is
this of one out of a hundred like and
they're individually numbered
it's the thing you dream of is I'm
growing up uh so you're fighting mm-hmm
you're fighting you're fighting Marik as
well I mean I'm in the demons family
that's where I'm yeah if you brought the
demon over Damon right so you're all
engaged with him right so I'll go on add
duty then okay if there's a bunch of
horse boys I'll go after those horse
boys yeah let's get uh some spec to eat
too dad okay and you got your your pack
ticks yeah usually so you see your your
toothbrushes is at their ready you wait
toothbrush yeah that's the sequel and
sorsha is basically just wherever your
sword is not she is ready on the other
side so I want to cut down some of these
some of these horse boys I think he's
horse gentlemen yeah now last turn you
did stop 20 feet away so you could if
Clark more attacks it's my extra seven
damage mm-hmm yeah I mean this is you
you had tried to cram this week an elk
yeah yeah you had actively tried to
create a situation oh there's gonna be
like a cue ball for attacks oh my god
cuz there's gonna be Clark more it's
gonna be me twice and then there's gonna
be sorcerer who does how many times she
gets sued and who knows yeah she's got
like three four times right eight times
oh nice so you should be able to kill a
horse or two we're going down to the
Dover down just going straight for the
horse Yeah right the glue factory boys
tonight so I guess I will just forget
them yeah what'd you say like let me
what am I looking at on their proximity
here well here so basically they're sort
of there they know exactly how to work
together you can see they're moving in
in pretty clear formations mm-hmm
you suspected works quite well against
small towns but they are they are all
over here in front of you when they're
preparing their own charges and
activities okay but so this is this is
your opportunity to make an impression
all right yeah your first thing I want
to go
right into the to the mix I'm gonna get
right up in there take out toothbrush
okay and use an alt
snicker-snack your new out to go white
we're here let's do it to the new oh
let's do that after Clark more oh yeah
give a lot more hands okay after he gets
his impact yeah then we'll do then we'll
just devolve the attacks done okay
Dwight rain roll you've been rolling
historically for Clinton absolutely so
tell me tell me about this Clark more
entity so what is the nice relationship
with Clark warm they're connected
telepathically I know that yeah they and
Clark or has an IQ of 6mm so he's you
can carry on yeah you can all eunuch
eight with this creature you can
understand other people talking yeah
like if I were to like summon him as a
spy and have him walk around the corner
you could hear what people are saying
and report back doesn't way that the
optimal scenario for him is get a pair
of pants just put him on the front yes
true the one where you know it's all
four and then it stops at the middle oh
really
that's how he wears I don't agree why
yeah but he's so stubborn so what I want
to know before I throw the dice is what
is his relationship with it if you're
gonna tell him to attack how does that
go oh he he obeys 100% oh I don't mean
rule wise oh okay I'm talking about me I
think about dinner blitz in yeah oh you
want to do what's this what's this
particular attack looks like yeah
exactly
like if you see if he's gonna say if
he's gonna direct him what is that like
like what is that relationship like um
well I'll be honest I was going to
initially last game go after Merrick
yeah now I've I had an idea for how this
was gonna go so I I was toying with the
idea of dismounting but I don't think I
well I think then I will stay on he's
gonna wear yeah and I think what he
would what he would want to work in
conjunction with Clark Morrison's they
have a perfect alignment in in a battle
and
able to like double-team perfectly
Clark's more would go hello yeah
snowplow wait oh just get underneath
while donor is planning a swing high
thanks yeah and maybe if he can get
those horns down low kick them up
they're a little more defenseless if
they're midair whoo
this is great yeah exactly
very nice right I've been doing Clark
more has done quite well so you you
orient him toward the target and he just
breaks out it's like instant instant max
speed kicking off of the soil and the
horse is the horse quails in front of
Hobart what come on Jerry consistency
please one image yeah yeah I mean a
picture here I'm getting all over the
place and he charges directly at and the
horse lowers its head and Clark sport
Clark Morris horns okay strike the
person and they go off of the horse and
perhaps eight to ten feet off nice it's
just like it's like it stuffs at a
second and the back in the back legs
kick up and you can feel you can feel
sources chest on your back as the back
part of it lifts up it's not it's people
have no bodies it's just okay it's gonna
come to terms come to terms so so so now
you know you were actually in front of
this horse and two other the two other
targets in front of you all right
we're all preparing their terrible horse
ah is it a mean horse don't bite me I
don't think so I mean if you or jigsaw
you'd have this horse trapped in a
warehouse yeah like trying to teach him
a lesson about the beauty of life yeah
what you do but it would be a really but
you'd be teaching it to them in a really
weird way they couldn't survive right
yeah it's it's a weird school like I
would say it's a it's a strange school
you lived your whole life by not being
sawed in half
now tribe try this take a man Wow yeah
hot take a hot sausage every so often
Chris likes to remind us what we would
be doing if we were jigsaw
yeah so all right the guys off course
he's knocked off and there are two more
targets here above okay
can I get them in one it's wide yeah the
arc of okay in terms of like a var
smalis strike yes that arc is the arc is
wide all right then I will do such thing
yeah the official sound that makes his
snicker-snack yeah I'm taking that for
my son the Jabberwock take that yeah see
look here he rolled I mean literally
never done that in almost two years of
the show you rolled those like would you
not you're not on a team okay I know
we're not a team my adversaries yeah I
got out plead ignorance I didn't know
you weren't allowed to for two years no
one ever told me I can't screens all
over the place you know screen doors
always tell other uses of Google of
words you know they're all here they're
all there like mine oh wait we're
surrounded by TV screen and a meeting
so the that gleaming arc basically just
shaves off the top half of these these
opponents and they
stayed the rest of them takes a
leisurely amount of time to realize that
it really not a part of this anymore
and they're deposited on the ground all
right so that's my first attack yeah who
else is left by all means I mean are
there any that's three hoarse voice yeah
that's that's this this horse boy
section all right where's that fun
where's that fourth course boy way the
right there's eight horse points this
this group of three is here and this is
this is more or less where you're at
okay where are the other ones I haven't
made a move yet I haven't moved Clark
Lana Clarkson Clark more moved from here
but your move
I'm pretty sure you're moving Clark
Boris move I don't think you get to Mike
he gets to attack ride Clark more
wherever you want and then get off and
then go the rest of the way it's like it
feels like I should be able to do it all
right where are they in relation to me
so these three over here are near Marik
sharp here okay
right I would allow you to get off of
this horse and try to attack Mary sharp
I want to attack these other horse boys
no some guys like a challenge not me I
easy mode every cheat code I could put
in there's no gay there's no gameshark
on this one the rest of them are they
had they have their own arcs and
movements okay and they're all far far
away yeah they are they had yeah well
they would like to do something very
similar what you have done already
I can't do the ranged attacks throw
something at them but if they're all too
far away
sorry dummy they're all so far away you
could what did you throw acid out of my
mouth
there nothing nothing arrange for that
what about this guy who's right here you
just throw up on Merrick sharp he's he's
cooking us right I know I know but I if
you're all engaged I didn't wanna hit
anyone any counter attacks can't camera
who's gonna punch my acid back I mean I
guess I could shoot know what the acid
beam that's like I'm running low on AoE
attacks then and I'm the only one who
really has
but alright alright if I'm close enough
datum I'll shoot a very concentrated as
much possible thing at yeah tell you
more about this attack and the damage
Davis I knock down all those horse boys
in fantastic impressive fashion and then
I decided all manage so should I go on
in
anything anybody heard faces yeah
it becomes very tight I get this way
when I'm nervous
she is catching some part of it it's
like the sound is making her want to
throw up like sorry I spit in your mouth
also her hand is over her mouth and
she's waving that you to stop uh no stop
I'm just full of the thrill of battle
and I feel like coming so then I got a
point in some way oh yeah Merrick sharp
and I let loose five by thirty beam you
just let loose your big old beam yeah
just a jet of it yeah I just point it
right out of trying to delay see me cry
you feel good strong pass uh-huh
on the back I need some ginger ale Dec
save him 14 even talking about damage on
this 3d6 he has uncanny dodge think oh I
have 12 so he takes half he would take 6
missed but he looks silly yeah whose
egos more hurt yeah yeah yeah he's very
embarrassed and it dissolves a hole in
his pants no Aziz under a yeah it's the
box with the hearts on yeah but this
this thick rich jet imagine imagine it
dark syrup imagine like just 3 cans of
soup yeah in a trough and then frozen
and then shall an arrow yeah the
remainder of this is just has struck the
shadow prison and it's just sort of like
washing up and they're like laughing
back down around the edges of this dome
and then I'm just giving you guys thumbs
up like I'm doing good
I'm helping me do any of us have to take
this Splash Damage oh yeah oh shit
alright so who do you want rolling
dextral I need you to roll index roll
this this rinsed this rose okay but it's
just it's just the rosy toe okay will
you so that's a 612 too but I also have
uncanny dodge good for you sorry yeah me
too so yeah yeah yeah I have it on
failure so I failed that same so I think
you need it's not so bad no it's fine
soup yeah it's rich so you see but you
there's a an intense
sent cthis yeah and you're welcome to
your welcome to perceive that in any way
you can I'm very familiar with it and
it's and it's a current and it's it's
sharp and it's Senate and it like wakes
me up I feel energized and I haven't
been Adama rolls oh it's like smelling
salts yeah I mean at this point we've
been together so long we putting out so
on like yeah this this is like a good
memory just yes my friend yeah I think
this narrative really supports a
mechanic yeah yeah I love it yeah so you
win the Dragons just just just get yours
oh thanks everyone because a lot of fun
that's a series wrap you hear that you
can hear the weight of sources armor
condense as she slides off of Clark or
and approaches Mary sharp know she's
gonna yeah yeah that her sword is a long
wicked thing with a little tooth curve
at the end and Merrick sharp says Maeve
a pleasure a pleasure I hoped it would
end like this I knew that it would kill
you at some point but this is very
convenient for me this sounds really
cool with him dripping with the vomit oh
yeah yeah he's just he's just like
adjusting himself inside this soaked
garment but she does not find that sort
of thing amusing
she actually misses twice oh he rattled
her does that bar looks like I I hate
Merrick sharp-toothed so I don't win to
win okay every every place her sword is
he isn't and he's able to he is able to
he's able to find gruesome purchase just
in just on one
side and then it was similar to he'd
specializes in using the hoof blades of
the loop just a guide behavior yeah so
he'll strike and then he'll use it
basically like eyes just a pot to shift
and move people's angles that is
sourcing us well not good okay so I have
disadvantage you do i I have packed
tactics which normally gives me
advantage so I'm back to nothing so I
would like to take advantage
Oh would you to bite this POS mark sharp
yeah let's see you yes it's attended by
[Music]
absolutely no you have you have come in
so this as as you're moving the weight
of this shell this is very Pokemon yeah
at this point is moving around you and
as you turn over it's allowing you to
get your snout out there and put it
sharp on this boy so tell me more thanks
grandma I'll tell you a second something
I bite him right in the leg and he has
to do his DC 13 strength saving through
are you from or be proud or become a
prawn mm-hmm no 17 is rock-solid he is
able to close he's able to get out of
there he just shakes you off just with a
cuff a cuff from the top of the loot
just right on the head just to get off
bring yeah so it is now it is now the
hour the dark hour
that's signified by this
all the boys yeah all the boys all the
time so the first thing that the first
thing that Merrick sharp does after he
after he just cuffs wolf nut and sends
her away is you can hear him whispering
something and as he does he seems to
shimmer in front of you as you can you
can see while this while this shadow
protection of the grandmothers is
closing back up you can see that there
appears to be three or maybe four of him
what if you know you know perfectly well
what's happening it's it's unpleasant
great it's unpleasant so and they as
they look down and he turns and they all
turn slightly different and he's just
he's just preparing the three of them
appear to be preparing themselves for
the next phase of this fight that is his
action for this round and this is this
is when the rest of the the rest of the
crowd starts to move in so you are still
a top Clark more mm-hmm and I'm yeah
you're over here this fight is the rest
of the of your clan is sort of fighting
over here but you were you were there
having engaged with this and a group of
people of these Warriors are now moving
in a charging line directly at the back
of you to are able to get past your
defenses but they can't roll very well
so there are they only able to deliver
five points of damage from two but I
need a strength athletics check from you
to stay up on top of this precious
mystical I would say that's what you're
good at
but you always roll terribly on strength
really high on intelligence it's novel
isn't it yeah from here on I only have a
couple treasures just like I kind of I
guess I gotta save Oh me huh I might
have to altogether twelve okay so the
first one giant just pushes you off
enough and the second one of these
Spears is able to push you off of Clark
more and onto the ground you can land in
a cool anime way yeah or you can land in
a way that you can use to inspire youth
angrily in a future round I will say I
never anticipated being knocked off so I
fall off in the oh fish is like yeah
just full flail a good and then and then
it's only Clark more its quick thinking
any leg whips his head around and kind
of I kind of catches me with his antlers
instead let me land on my feet
yeah he just like kind of hits me on the
rebound size of land up right it's a
boom it's a bro
there are so there are two more horse
enthusiasts yes sir
dressage exactly yeah they are writing
Rama's well they they have identified
Rosie a weaponless Rosie as a delicious
morsel okay and they are setting their
charge for Rosie and from the from the
bunkhouse
you see ridha emerge sort of in the
middle place between you and them
ah and as she does she have such
sharpened a long sharpened spear to set
against these foes and as they begin
their charge she lifts it up in front of
them and leans the leans to stick back
into the soil and do you see something
incredibly strange she as she sets it
back the horse that comes into contact
with the sphere as it does so seems to
evaporate into a kind of mist and when
it looks little bit it has the rod and
she looks back and she says it's not
real and as she says that the horsemen
that is following along jabs her cruelly
with a spear oh that one's real that one
is real yeah he pins her directly to the
ground and then retrieves a sword oh my
god from the sheath let's see there are
four other young men who want to be a
part of this no situation Oh
womp womp womp womp ah no counsel
merrily rustici does it be my lady
if you want me to kill pcs this is a
great role for you what surprises is
like a blood is exactly the prize is a
new show different characters not every
character I kill you get to read okay um
I don't have a fine name for that
it just looks weak so the first one is
like goblin stone of anything Vice p.m.
listen this one this one swings cruelly
at yuca therus oh and that ends up being
12 points that's a real deal okay so he
was it the others the others inspired by
this by this soft target look at this
taffy boy yeah exactly
they're they're all drank it to copy all
derisive leagues yeah yeah
taffy boy taffy boy there was there was
an intimidation before there's a lot
about cthe wrist that seems off-putting
but that that cruel strike showed them
that that Chris could die like anyone
else
soft indeed so that is another four
points yeah WOM WOM come on Lord but you
can't even look at it
you've won wha want a real torn it's the
first real one thank you
sadly my Labor's going Patrick who's
gonna be really mad at me because he has
to choose the winners and everything
yeah very inconvenient every time you
get a price think about that yeah we're
not even halfway through the show Jerry
I know I know right oh no 1818 pussy Oh
cuz this is minus one now yeah yeah you
know you're unconscious he's happy
Oh No now gray would meant I'm sure
doesn't have to listen to a dead person
I'm incontinently first yeah you know
you don't have your concentration
anymore yeah
I got him now does he dissipate or is he
out of control now
oh no he when I lose my concentration he
remains for like 1d6 rounds he is
absolutely not really far though he
feels that let that whatever tether snap
and he's just good to go he's good to
roll hold on I got a look at him yeah
I'll tell ya it's Hollow you know so
you're down but that's great news
because the last one is great news they
miss Rosie so Rosie's fine yeah stop
concentrate on spell before reaches full
duration an uncontrolled demon doesn't
disappear for one be round if it still
has it Wendy what's 1d6 I'm sorry three
rounds of who I am now
so this what this is what we'll do for
grave of men I know that you will choose
the right targets for grave of men while
you are playing grave of men for these
three rounds yeah I know that I know
that because of who you are I know that
you will you will honor this compact I
have made with you
cthe wrist robe through honor our
covenant you will honor our coven even
in death know the ability to heal a
person yes yeah
no grave of minta crystalline so grave
of men let me let me describe very
briefly the the scenario you see below
it is it is much as you've seen but much
as you've seen in the black temples of
secret shadow tiny tables upon which
hundreds of writhing creatures just do
battle with one another copulate and you
know these are all happening some true
place but there's a kind of McCobb
entertainment in it this looks just like
those places except now
you can just reach down and pluck one
which one is of greatest interest
exactly first let me let let grave of
men also say that is that as that tether
slips and he looks down and says as
invoker is now unconscious the fool as
it always is well I am free in the world
of men hmm I will feast so so so let me
let me describe very briefly for you to
grave of men the platter that even now
is stumbling and clattering around below
you some of these beasts are riding atop
other beasts some of them are old and
frail very very soon you have but to
close your hand to possess them there
are some who have endeavored mightily
against the forces that surround them
but it is a doom clock has been went
there's only a they only have a brief
time on this stage any one of them any
one of them would be a morsel the the
weak one does not interest me this
strong one oh this delicious a treat
there's a delicious fellow and you and
the thing that would be most delicious
about it is how surprised he would be at
his own but that would be a second meal
it would be a that would be the second
meal but if I may know but how how how
savory would it be if I could destroy
this beautiful celestial thing that he
is befriended oh let's I set my
Oh indeed upon this this this idiot
animals assent like a forest now this is
some bullshit that he's not attacking
any of us we mean why wouldn't you
attack us like a beautiful celestial I
could do whatever I want I'm doing it
year it's it's it's Clarke more first I
want to to remove hope then look at this
this this beacon of light among you is
nothing out maybe there's a some sort of
deep-rooted admiration of someone else
who did stuff with shadows and the thing
man that's covered in shadow yeah this
is my own shadow Eastover yeah I see
tears we got some celestial bees no and
I am I am the cradle maker oh yes he's
not coming after me oh yeah and there's
some sport he's not going after Merrick
right now either there's some fun to be
had and watching you guys fight it out I
enjoyed that and I just kept those
spoils after all right yeah I'm gonna
I'm gonna charge down on all right well
you're engaged in combat he's trying to
break away
well yeah everyone gets a attack of
opportunity if they want right punch him
in the back as he's running away yeah
where am I at destroy because you seem
to indicate that I'm just like kind of
like circling and getting no great grave
of men is just floating above mmm cuz I
thought he was still kind of tied up
with Merrick uh no at this point he is
he is washing the fight and he can
select okay no yeah I'm all for that
select hang else yeah you're getting a
next big boy that's now agree with men
says first a grave of venison my belly
be rendered I mean hit points is that
thing on 266 you do that I'd say I
didn't one tech enjoy nice yeah alright
now I'm gonna let me see here let me
claw at this guy
where's his attacks here they win they
were in the monster main they were right
it was just a clause hmm to the book now
we're playing Dungeons &amp; Dragons hmm
and shadow demons and you have your
Clark war sets no we'll just use a
badger stance Stan 15:18 4242 now get
ready yeah I'll track him instead
yeah can you know 1586 TSE I have no
time for this
my attacks will be sought out by a
lesser being I have a grave to maintain
and care for it's very specific we have
a very specific playing town these are a
devil okay a lot of devil unless shadow
demon I know thank you
what's the range on that guy well he can
fly thirty five thirty feet okay yeah so
like I'm normal
yeah pretty regular guy okay he does
have a shitload of damage resistances
and immunities including slashing damage
from non-magic objects right and this is
and I got three rounds of fun three
rounds of delight two rounds so yeah
let's let's kill this elk first I'm
gonna slash Adam with my sweetest of
claws and that's gonna be what +5 to hit
oh yeah what's the AC here we go
mmm so it doesn't hit he's uh grave of
men is taken aback yeah
so if he's coming in and we're right
next to each other
do I get an attack of opportunity no no
attack of opportunity if he leaves yeah
yeah I'm engaged with your with your
animal oh but I could oh no wait that's
I can move through things though that's
pretty cool that's pretty scary it'll
scare you I bet that's really and your
turn inside of it yeah it takes damage
yes see oh I say you take damage my it
takes damage I just enjoy being inside
all right no that is cthe risk drab
slash grave of men Stern tag team rosy
bee stinger yeah what's going on with
what's going uh I got no weapon it's got
problems crustose I okay so I see great
with men going after Clarke this
beautiful creature and Chris is out he
is out America's still menacing us
indeed more than one Merrick oh can I do
any kind of like perception or insight
or something to try to determine which
me which America is the real one you can
definitely try to attack them okay oh
that's no problem I'll just do that then
because I have like four attacks so beat
how many merits that are therefore there
appear to be three but they're
constantly moving in and out okay all
right well then it is challenging I
don't have my staff so it's all hands
yeah so it's all hands on deck yeah so
I'm gonna actually take a running leap
and jump on to Wolf nut and then go
flying toward these illusions that's a
strike so wherever you want to be the
shadow allows it okay
so then I'll do a bunch of attacks on
the instant trying to figure out who's
the real one okay all right and our
strikes are all +6 and I remember you
have that disadvantage
Oh Megan
alright one last two weeks champ Council
clearly was PC whatever panoply what a
ride
exactly now so that's the 21 well indeed
indeed so the way that it works is there
is a dice mechanic know that I use with
mirror image okay that allows me to
place it and get rid of it so you're
able to destroy one of the images but
that so it's a key
you strike like straight through one and
then the very next attack is like just a
perfect like
all her plexus strike and he doesn't
expect it at all he thought that he had
this under control okay I would like to
also juice it gross yeah I was I'm going
to add a key point stunning strike on
that and needs to succeed on a DC 13 con
save he does okay I still have three
more attacks you interested in this
oh yeah please please ship it but but
give me the damage on the on that big in
just so can keep track of the one d6 oh
yeah well that's only six points of
damage that's fine I love that and then
I want to just do this for all of these
rules that one's gonna be nope nothing
that's a nine okay so that's one counter
there's a bomb and way huh and a
nineteen so there's another bomb a bomb
what yes I do
all right yeah cheer for that one you're
like hey like undersold it yeah so you
you come in contact white was a solar
plexus he is taking it back okay
for a second yeah and and then the next
your next attack on him missus yep and
he returns with nine points of damage
oof okay he's got reactions it's fast
it's just it is is like the best
sparring partners you engage with on the
mountain what are you at 17 so each of
these moths are gonna hit four double
right no cuz I'm reeling with
disadvantage by the way am I supposed to
be saving against my death how does that
work do next next time when we come back
around okay yeah because you're not
tethered to anybody anymore
oh you mean yeah the guy we don't care
about it yeah yeah fuck that guy and
he's sort of twenty this is gonna be a
at a twenty four okay that one connects
with a image okay
and that destroyed exactly so there is
only one of them there's only one of him
left ok so then I'm gonna go with my
little foot straight form it's just
gonna be a 15 no but at least we know
which one's real exactly so at that
missed strike he responds with a savage
11 thanks God okay stop you're done yeah
I'm doing shit yeah all right what
dinner stopped to heal or would you be
like get away from Clark why are you
still yeah like that
Dennard blitz enter it is you're sure
alright so grave a man came in swung in
yeah he's parson missed something but
that's I think that he was surprised by
yeah I think yeah I mean he's still
looking at Clark more but whoa I mean he
chooses a different target every time as
he still he can okay I mean that he's
here he's here for two more rounds
you're right you don't have a lot time
me and Clark more being in simpatico
would be I'd be saying like hey Clark
want to get away yeah okay and then I
would jump on clark moores back and then
right away Harper might get but he can
take it uh so you're gonna have him run
away toward you
yeah but you believe that you basically
drink right with it right yeah do you
think you're gonna jump on there right
away
yeah I'm gonna let him like Clark more
get clear and then jump on him and then
right away okay
so if you would be so kind as to attack
Denar blitzen's faithful steed yeah
that's seventeen mm-hmm he had a 15 so
that hits Clark or young now for that
sweetmeat I didn't have advantage on
that rule I had to d6 + 3 oh and it's
psychic damage 8 8 you like it
ok so for him it's just like the hand
pass through right yeah like it's just
like sort of wind chimes there's
something in there okay alright I get on
Clark more yeah once he can
60 and your speed of 30 thank you Bob
they don't keep up
you just greatest grab the grab the horn
get up yeah one arm mount yeah I just
get that fly the British are coming
just three so the fights happening here
this engagement was here 30 feet away
there are other boys and stuff on the
other side
no one's close right what's this whole
battlefield look like where's the
where's the open ground back north there
was no one coming from the north where I
came from right exactly okay that's the
farthest away from everyone
yeah buy a lot decent yeah all right I'm
gonna channel divinity with my guy and
I'm gonna use champion challenge so
anyone in everyone
I choose within range let's make a
wisdom save on a fail they can't move
more than 30 feet away from me so it's
like it's like a compelled duel to a
crowd to every so I'm gonna come bail do
all the battlefield I'm gonna run away
and just kite them via choir that's my
game so they have to do it wisdom save I
didn't write down what the wisdom sieve
is against I guess it's just my spell
yeah yeah so 14 so it's against graver
man it's a it's against the remaining
boys it's against Marist sharp yeah and
clones and all of them
yeah so what's the range yeah 30 feet
yeah I think it's all and they can't
read 130 feet away so it's it's
definitely American the grave and at
least a couple of the boys it's a wisdom
save against your spell DC yeah against
14 healthy all right here's gonna say so
horse boy 1 I'll let him do those he's
good horse boy to know of course my
screen know they're coming yeah exactly
the on foots Minh
they are there okay dang Wow guys yes
here this is the important one right
Marik sharp right for hey got it
chase me chase me mare excuse me yeah
great man
Tim chase me grave of men chase me
coming this is awesome
I'm Sebastian yeah so you so you and I
just get just close enough Phineas
little fingertips and I go what nope so
you have you now have functionally
speaking mystically compelled groupies
that are follow you around specifically
in terms of two special horse boys and
mara sharp and also add a shadow demon
two more turns right over man
yes you have no choice but to follow me
so they have to follow you but they are
they compelled to fight you uh no it's
just they can't move white knight they
can't they can't get more than 30 feet
away from me what's the duration I
didn't write it down so long as I want
these are just your groupies for life
yeah it's got to be concentration based
oh yeah I got to imagine that yeah we
can handle this
we can handle this we have it we have a
widget champions champions challenge
shavings guy champion challenge it's one
is my channel divinity for the oath of
the crown yeah okay which was new shit
well let's see if yeah that's the thing
it's not in the book except I'm one of
the other books it was a oh yeah okay
that bins chili yeah so you were
champion chili challenge so you were you
I've learned exactly now it is walnut
done grass okay um so to the group I can
keep I mean I've got this really good AC
and I can keep fighting but if I drop it
I can cure women's oh the Chris yeah so
then you consider yeah does anyone have
any feelings about that well no okay
if you know if you heal him then
theoretically we've got the demon back
under control I don't think what I go
okay concentration is broken I'm not
good I can't get him back he can kite
him for two never those great times we
had I don't know it ends by the way Ryan
if the creature you are endo the
creature if you are incapacitated or
died or if the creature is moved more
than 30 feet away from you
all of its non volition okay so if
they're forced away yeah so if like yeah
one of you are in attack it knock it
back in it you could you literally run
forever with these boys
so I can like it follows these guys it's
just just a little bit of farther kind
of tired and you're just snacking yeah
right thing on that horse bar it's like
you're good for hours yeah okay um so I
think upon seeing her breasts go down
Rosie okay well it would and especially
if Marik's gonna move away see dinner
kind of take control of the battlefield
here would transform back into her nut
farm which would give you back your
staff your staff yeah and do cure wounds
on kiss that's really nice so get you do
those Wow
and then I assume that I have to add the
minus one okay
oh yeah yeah when you when you start
when you heal back up you start there
okay okay there's their deficit
delightful yeah there was a deficit
previous versions there's that's like
one of the things they goof with let me
I repeat it though it was it look if
she's like she like sort of fucked up on
top of the wolf night I bounced off of
it yeah okay
you're off now yeah yes sure so
immediately swirling her fur and stuff
like that and I go
my hands and I'm like yeah it's like
[Laughter]
lose concentration and if you tax you
San free yeah oh so all right so Csokas
wrist rob is back up on it so from a
demon exactly hole whose nearest though
because there are unaffected by Europe
absolutely a couple Oh everyone on foot
yeah yeah the foot does guys the foots
Minh yeah the foots Minh are ready to
play and then one horsey ton of attack
of opportunities when those guys moved
away from us true true that's what I
thought was gonna happen
yeah I thought that too I thought that
too that's why I did it it could happen
hey Kevin McKidd still happen because I
love it interesting yeah it's crazy so
so so they have now walnut dong grass
yeah
grandmother night yeah and cthe wrist
route are together with again a whole
new was an incredible new group of
backup performers then the nice
mmmm-hmmm
and they have an opinion on you and it's
a negative opinion if they if they could
give you less than one star they would
god yeah I'm kind I would like to reply
to their comments they came in their
resume yeah you know or anything I'm
sorry about experience exactly they
strike out they lash out at rosy be
stinger mm-hmm the first is able to
connect four five oh yeah okay I rolled
a no it was very high okay there's your
AC twenty-three okay well maybe no it's
not
and then when hit point y'all I know
what slow but also this druid is a
problem as well drew it oh there's a one
[Music]
it's just like they're intimidated right
away it's like already this person was a
dog very recently and that what does it
mean like that's weird one
I think horse yeah exactly so I think
dogs should vote nothing in the rulebook
no specifically states a sphere just
whispers by your ear so it blows your
hair up up and away
that is the beggar so let's talk about
let's talk about this challenge so your
idea so you have pulled out over here
they need to keep up with you yes and so
your movement is such that they can't
see but you're trying to keep a very
speech writing to do a very specific
thing is which is maintain them within a
radius that is far enough so that they
can't reach you but not so far that they
are outside the the full range of it
yeah does that hard that's kind of
kiting yeah yeah exactly this is why
plan yeah so they're going to they're
going to try to chase you around as long
as they
yeah yeah until my my team is free and
clear yeah just trying to I'm sure well
I'm trying to hang my most classic
taking pins pulling all the aggro and
then I'm running away if you and if you
want to bring them back through here so
we can get another pass I wonder if it
doesn't say specifically on here but I
wonder if like compelled duel if they
are it's a I'm assuming this follows
compelled dual rule is a negative if I
were to attack someone that isn't the
target or if anyone else were to attack
the target so when I do compel duel I'd
say hey me and you let's go and if
anyone else comes in and attacks them it
breaks the spell right or if I say that
and then turn in hit someone else that
breaks the spell but as long as we keep
this eye contact you know on that season
but the horses have access to you real
sci-fi horse yeah exactly
I'm saying ours the two horses the rest
of yeah but they just started I started
more than sixty away from them and even
if they have the same speed they didn't
start next to me right so they couldn't
get to me in one that's true what are
they gonna do like go negative carry the
next turn I think they could get next
turn they could they could this is only
because I have to keep the slow guys in
range
okay so horses would then try to imagine
a ridiculous kind of circus carnival
music playing here's something to think
about though knowing that gravamen is
only 30 feet is his feed and he's only
around for another well I guess he's got
to live around left you don't have to
worry about him that long no if you drag
him 60 feet away he wouldn't make it
back I'm super worried about him what's
just what is he by the way is he a Fae
or fees in Sagittarius well that's why
we don't get themed
yeah okay well yeah he's only here for a
minute
having a peloton right if something is a
fiend or a celestial she gets crazy I
know and I'm like I know I'm really
afraid I mean I'm going to use these
little Paris okay so they are they are
all trying to get a piece of this and
Merritt sharp is just cursing at the top
of his lungs my trips on foot rides yeah
that is it Chris trout
tell me more come just over it over all
of it
all right way yeah what's in what's in
front of me but you are looking at 40
yeah yeah four nice boys and a special
horse how's the horse doing plump Hale
not hurt Joel McHale oh but we got a lot
of dead bodies around us right
oh there's no shortage gonna bring it
right up out of the ground
oh yeah oh why wouldn't I yeah how many
of these guys can I Lance with some of
these these uh corpses here on the gray
these juicy ones
yeah I would say that the I would say
that the four special boys the flinty
introductory offer yeah I think they
could be convinced to die balance with
some easy let's go with that and I think
to start ya know yeah as a starter right
okay we're here so so we cheddar bacon
bomb
so the plating obviously vital it in the
higher-end series there is plenty of
meat around here to manipulate your it
sounds to me like you're trying to
leverage some tentacular spectacular oh
yeah but I want I want literature young
man I want you to tell me about this and
then you'll get the results you crave
but I want what I want as well daddy
yeah I have to get mine mm-hmm how can I
flavor this this is what I mean
nice flavor this cuz this is what I'm
talking about so I also assume that
these four guys or not or or maybe no
yes they're no they're in a good
okay I'd love to see if you look see if
you'll indulge this hmm and this
construct doesn't have to last any
longer than that duration of a
tentacular spectacular yeah this is the
imagery but this is the imagery there is
I'm I'm inspired by having seen dinar
and sorsha on the back of Clark more
yeah
wielding their blades as they as they
swing their way through the field so to
honor them know as it omage to them I
will invoke tentacular spectacular okay
on one or two of the bodies that lay and
the two corpses they are together
they're immediately knit through with
with means yes meshed together
lines and then they will rise up on four
legs of sorts that do not bend so they
just sort of Teeter and then this object
will just leap forward at the four foot
men and will extend to more to either
side to just sort of cleave through and
we can have a single horn on the front
too if you want if you like that I don't
know if you've seen them have you seen
the movie splinter you seen that movie
no does this happen in that movie
no but there's imagery that this horror
film you'll be familiar with talking
about well what this time you see should
did you see him chug cuz it's just a
good movie nothing to do with this
critters so pacing homeward bound yeah
phase two picking the city so this this
evil machine that you have made out of
razor sharp crystal and corpses just
based on some fundamental physics a
second it's like an evil child's toy
yeah like if you know those frogs like
oh wait the doll you know that when you
press up on the base and it collapses
yeah but when you let go of it it does
wait yeah that's what it does out of the
ground being exactly so Chris has got a
delight so everyone who's engaged with
them know cemeteries by the way hits the
ground
oh no it's awful it's for Hitler Crabbe
horseshit and this is just like some
kind of nice yeah so this this
contraption leaps your your friends see
this thing coming and they see that the
building delight and it just leaps over
catches them and then lands and then
begins the slow process of incorporating
this new material recursively
interactively into this central core
yeah can I can I flip for you can this
so Boston Dynamics you lose a little
hopping dog robot imagine one imagine
that little one like just running
absurdly and then landing on a person
and then just continue to ride with like
knives this is what I'm afraid of
I know how yeah that's a good one yeah
so so they are out yeah I'll be real
surprised if this last horse guy feels
like this is a good time investment I've
know and as that's happening there's
less delight on my face more pride and I
wanted I'm wondering if dinars you know
he doesn't see it's for him that was why
I'm very far away just that was right
Rosie beasting tell me more okay there's
a special horse all your own how does it
look the horse seems like he knows
what's going on yeah the person on top
of the horse okay also knows what's
going on and it doesn't like it
alright then I want to make eye contact
with the guy on the horse and try to
intimidate him
yeah I see I feel like I feel like you
might get advantage on this yeah these
are fucking annex I want to get
extremely like serious and sober for a
moment and be like yeah 21 bet it is
what else do you want to say that's
literally it
yeah yeah yeah immediate snap good south
just right through the grass and this
grass is not having any of it every foot
every inch of this grass is doing
everything it can so he makes a break
for it and he's like he's basically like
running through four foot deep meatloaf
the rest of the way depending on how
long you watch I mean it's very shameful
he wants to get away fast and he did
everything he could and he's looking
back sometimes and then he gets off the
horse and then he starts to wade through
it to me and now they're both yeah just
a couple are tack
they're both contending I mean no no
they doubled up on this yeah I like that
[Laughter]
[Applause]
no Donner Blitzen so you've got all
kinds of fun over here and you can see
have and you can see some coming up
behind almost like a sheepdog nice and
get him so your ears casually really
want to get them kiting this crew yeah
around and then like just on the other
side like creating this sort of like
equi distant point on the outer edge of
the circle is sorsa
so how will you utilize your train
to create Megiddo so they're there now
coming around the circumference with me
yeah the horse is gonna catch me in a
turn Tolu yeah
suddenly one all right so I got two of
those plus gravy men plus merica are
chasing me and Marik and gravy men can't
catch me the horse boys will catch me
next turn he's 30 he's 30 so he can't
catch me and then by the time he gets
there he's only got one more turn and
he's done so but but he but he's can
still attack people right no he can't he
has to attack me
oh is that true yeah you got compelled
oh you gotta you're compelled to come
after this challenge it's not the same
no or champion challenge yeah yeah they
don't want to attack you they just have
to keep coming after ya they have to
stay within 30 feet of you oh okay good
deal with them yeah makes it good so he
could swing on them I guess that's okay
well the only one he could swing on
really would be Marik because the horses
will be a little further out like I
would not want to I'm trying to keep
everyone safe Denari and pound-foolish
in mode trying to keep everyone sitting
it's such a weird twist for the he's not
he doesn't I did any doesn't was sore
she is she's cute hurt I'm not gonna
bring this this Quadra storm yeah so I'm
gonna veer away from her still keeping
the the radius correct and just keep
this pretty pretty pretty neutral
I'll Denard will pull out a little
bottle of holy water and wait the cork
off and just sprinkle some holy water
just splash it just the pulse points
yeah yeah and just be like hey bars may
Allah praise His name bless this mess
baby like a silvery glow on his skin and
then also on Clark more skin cuz any
buffs Denard owes to himself also
carrying on - Clark more yes so then
he's now blessed so if he has to make a
saving throw or
whenever a target makes the tackle or
saving throw before the spell ends I get
plus t4 so just in case when things
inevitably gets sticky a minute ten
rounds yeah my concentration but that's
fine because the other one is that comes
national you know cool we gucci you did
it yeah yeah so you're you're dialing
this shit in yeah yeah i could see a
shadow council nearly misses you
we got a pause we're gonna take a break
in the middle of the thing we got a five
it's fine it's fine
some of us help us no but we're gonna
come back and then we're gonna resolve
all this stuff you'll see you'll see
some sorts
don't go anywhere we're right back
I killed the fly no we killed one of the
Flies there's another fight listen you
guys don't have to think about this so
even word applies hello welcome back to
testy teams I'm your host here for Kay
Hawkins um
when last we saw our heroes Denar blitz
in was applying a sensual holy blessing
to himself into his special celestial
elf elites oh yeah it soothes well it
protects you just layer exactly right
skids was holy layer that is dinar
blitzen's turn but as we discussed we
think that grave of men did not get
because well I get like we don't get a
whole lot of time left with gravy mints
we want to make sure that we execute
gravamen know the maximum level here
grave of man who feels it coming maybe
make it feel like coming in the air of
the night whoa Lord grave a man is is
infuriated that at this point all he's
tasted is horse there's an actual one
man and my grave of horse no no what are
they gonna say in the Shadow Realm so
he's so he like so many others in this
group are being lured toward you by your
spell seductive voice right it wasn't
even a spell
hey guys the challenge of champion was
inside them I spell I can't resist him I
have to I have to listen
it leaves a one slot open for you - it's
possible nice it's a burn one so he is
going to just lash out wildly at anybody
that's close to him is and is that who's
who's running beside him he could get
access to I know there's like two or
Scott especially yeah he'd get access to
a special horse guy no thank you
not for me to work you there's a guy on
the horse
well yeah you might you may go for it
I'm saying like that's a situation I
mean right now right now those are the
those are the delights we have pretty
much everybody else is hosed okay yeah
let me see what I can do about about
going oh you know what he's gonna try
something here something brand-new
something cute oh wait a man you told me
that it was he was great a man that
takes the damage if he stops in a place
coinciding with a who knows he has a
bunch of hit points yeah you know
grammatically this makes sense to me the
demon can move through other creatures
and objects as if they were difficulty
right it takes it takes five one day ten
horse damage if it ends its turn yeah
it's yeah but it can finish true yeah
and he's got a lot of hit points I'm not
worried about that I just would love to
do damage to a creature yeah by being
excited but since that's not the case
you should it and then try clutch from
the inside hmm
that's now you're talking no that's
crazy I can start the reactor yeah let
me see she's just gonna slash out toward
these these horses these men on the
horses
yeah so whatever the were the closest
one yeah exactly go for it yeah I got
indicated right here here we go
this kid this could be very good for ya
nice work pal womp womp womp even listen
no but it's on brand isn't that for a
shadow demon yeah to grant a boon to the
shadow council that's not professional
courtesy you know Patrick if you would
please be so kind as some reward our
viewers I'm on this most special of days
three from cheering
yes this is nut balls anyway so please
please please let the dice begin so is
this like the the hottest fullest damage
yeah how does it work okay
well if I haven't managed on the
integral yoga mosh so oh not great
someone in it too
that's a little better plus 314 roots oh
that's very good enough to I mean not
great that feels a little bit like feels
a little bit like Elvis blast if I'm
honest
awesome demon yell yeah so derisive Lee
great demon so hoping that he's like
updating the guys warp stuff that he
actually is oh so demon who nobody but
grave of men has had an opportunity just
to explore this whole new world this
whole new space that exists inside these
creatures different from the horse but
not that different
yeah disappointingly similar right you
could be upset at the name grave of men
at all like um maybe I don't want to be
agreement that's not enough myself for
10,000 years time for a change but grave
of win change then marry you see the
shadow demon in the mirror just raised
in black fire um no that is our special
yeah bang grave or missed or missed one
no it's walnut exactly no it's that nut
so I side of the Year thank you yeah
yeah but it's like this day no it is all
politics so I see Merrick running away
and my wounds are still fresh from where
oh yeah lately absolutely it's gonna be
sore yeah and I go oh no you don't and I
cast Moonbeam which has a range of a
hundred and twenty feet and I cast it at
the third level so I get an extra d-10
boom and it lasts for ten rounds God and
he can do a con say right now I guess at
fifteen if he wants to he doesn't get it
fantastic so he takes full damage eight
like magic like it's the better way to
go with this motherfucker yes that's a
good end for Merrick is running after a
an elk and just being cooked I just I
like moving beans I love it you like the
only thing the only extra piece that I
want to know is because it really is I
mean they attacked in the night it's
dark yeah so then this is incredible
yeah yeah the classes of like a phobia
is a game the clouds move away from the
moon and I like somewhere I hear a wolf
howl and I'm like yeah and I just like
summing down that silvery light and it
just cooks oh yeah he is he is
completely seared like he's doing
everything can like that beam finds him
and he just he gets out of it at maximum
speed like rolls his way out of it to
the side and then kids up and Steinke
starts continuing after next turn I
think this speed of movement I got him
[Laughter]
I love this fucking game so much exactly
um and now it's our turn Marik it's true
it's true Marik sharp raises a hand
after he gets out he's patted off his
clothes there's still a kind of silvery
wisp coming off of his his garb and he
reaches up a hand and snaps and one of
the horsemen
picks him up and the other one who's
running directly towards you so he was
going to give you a a brutal hit wait so
the one he's on no no the other one this
is this is the other one I was gonna
resolve him first 12 points hmm see
these are these are long Spears and even
right out of that even right at the edge
that he's able to find he's able to find
some hidden place in the armor that he
can twist this thing in be molested do
anything there it's like good again
saving throw when I do attack it'll also
give me a little more interesting yeah
1.d4 on this is a classic it was way
back good for flavor also um I gotta
give you props on that Merrick Merrick
sharp has been picked up on this horse
and this horse begins to charge at full
speed and he jumps from this horse and
attempts to grapple you on top of Clark
or palmas face No so just like super
badass jumping on Oh No
just like hanging on the side yeah just
like basically that gets up on his
flunkies back leaps off and then just
short you can like see the moon you see
the light of the moon like sly
along the strings and there's in the
cruel face and it's just - yeah you have
to go on the ground instead that's
that's where you actually get to go for
real doesn't you take damage for rolling
along the ground but he would but he's
actually super super good at exactly
this sort of thing so Finnegan roads
getting damaged
did he heal what hey no he became King
he's the patron saint of bullshit I'm in
a cameo yeah Chris job alright see this
this Moonbeam yeah there's a moonbeam
there is a one special horse over there
as I recall see where am i what am i
sitting on here I didn't know what I
could do at this distance how far away
are we yeah yes oh there they are
running out in the sort of central
courtyard of promise itself so at this
point you're probably like crest like
going around one of the bunk houses or
something like that sort of pulling them
around oh yeah I mean well he was in the
center yeah so then I took it to the
circumference it's kind of going around
the battlefield so you guys could just
see me each time you get a new pose Hey
as you see him Simon thumbs up this yes
sparkling thumbs up alright well am I
able to like use mine and turns in your
range speed of 30 feet well let's see
what the range of what is the range of
toll the dead cuz I'd love to do that I
want to see that dead let me see
60 feet is what it says yeah so let's
let's pull his dead I'm gonna told that
Merrick told the dad yeah enjoy a chance
wisdom so he's got a same against mine
15 who's do it reg oh god no no I didn't
do it alright and he is hurt so he's
gonna take 2 to 12 oh he's nice yeah
very nice silly me I want no wait I've
burned up my spells I don't have any
right now to be 12 is what I want oh
yeah it's you never almost never get to
roll d12 - oh God
Oh nein nein Oh 20 of damage cool you
and there its new product if it makes a
difference if you like think about it
it's hand falls off okay no it's
this is awful tell me about Tony heals
up tell me what goes on with totally
dead let's see I can get
I've got lagari I said it's it's time to
pay the toll
old friend and he turns snaps into staff
form and I slam him on the ground then
they have rings it's Ray's Ray's without
heat scream of the dead and then and it
goes and he's and he's like distracted
by that that sailing voice and then he
was told yes yeah I don't like a bunch
of bones well yeah just fire this guy
yeah yeah if he's as he is Arnold he's
big his feet and he's holding his head
sort of in this courtyard starting like
swaying a bit as he as he gets back up
he's buffeted by invisible attacks Jimmy
Buffett attacks rosy be stodgy point of
order real quick yes so we don't skip it
again is this also because it's your
turn at this great Batman's last turn
this is it last thing is oh I don't
think he goes with me anymore no his
last term will come when it's the bow
after me okay okay okay well do tell cuz
this is where he went last time so just
doing it okay I know that'll be his
it'll be his his finale yeah
fan-favorite character graves man yeah
been a big help
beat up on agreed no no Sarah McLachlan
like black and white it's like the
pictures of coming across like he's at
cafe 2018 darns and dragons so hard
where is I'm very hurt
you are very hurt I need I needed it's
so funny I was talking to Jeremy
Crawford
oh yeah just name-drop yeah well no no
II no no it's funny it's funny for a
specific reason cuz I was like I bet
people everybody's playing fucking
Dungeons &amp; Dragons wrong right wrong
right yeah and he's like yeah and I'm
like things like but this is not
important like every table is different
and I'm like okay and then also um and
that was like what's the thing what's
everybody doing it's really oh yeah this
would be good what's the worst
uh-huh perception rules why because you
have passive perception we just sort of
know if you can pick up on things right
way more fun to roll it's more and in
that spirit would you please roll
perception I guess I'll take advantage
on it cuz I don't know what the shit's
going on what a 15 yeah you know what
let's go for the scene with the 16
during the course of this fight you've
always sort of cast an eye a
grandmotherly eye toward the opening of
the mind and you can see barreling out
at full speed a barrel you can see that
kronar has determined that this is the
opera
this is the time where she can inflict
maximum damage on the foe no nor okay so
she's just running toward Marik she's
running right out in the middle of the
fight
so she's Mama's they're dinars they're
how everybody's Marik sharp damned
Johnny horsemen how far away from me is
she right now she's probably from here
she's probably feet that's perfect love
it she's running fast look of steely
determination that's great or platinum
determination I use shadow step which
takes me sixty feet and I will tackle
that little not important oh you will
try yeah I will
don't try have you ever tried to catch a
little kid yeah you know perfectly well
your kids have been in my house I'm
extremely dexterous well so are they so
let's get we're talking about some
acrobatics probably yeah why not
let's see you don't take advantage on
that to my team okay well here let's see
what her role is Jesus you get 20 the
best yeah no you're right you were able
to get her oh it's like it's like you
you you go down and then she's out this
way yeah and then it's like no okay
exactly yeah you have that you have that
grim are mystic third grandmother that
you use to snatch her she's grappled
exactly and she throws something out
behind you but you have her grab like
this you don't see what it is
Dennard what sin do I see what just
happened right right now I mean you're
on the other side of the fear look at
you have like this sort of like Ringling
Brothers thing going yeah so Merrick
Mary Sharpe to horsey well that's
there's two horse he once really hurt
right exactly and there's also that was
like and there's also great with men who
will for you he's doing
back to the future looking at hand thank
you so the only one that can is in
strike able distance to me was that
horse that he tried to ride on last time
yeah yeah you you could you have an
opportunity here to to have that any of
these any of these well I don't want to
double back well I guess it really
doesn't matter cuz this is my back my
freaking horse exactly at this point
everything is is enmeshed um well I
still want to make sure I'm far enough
away from Gregor men so maybe I don't
double back all the way yeah just take
out this horse boy if they're closest to
me um so yeah alright that's all with
you I'll swing on that guy I'll pull out
toothbrush toothbrush yeah and I'll
swing on the blade have it that's a 9
plus 6 15 oh that is exactly right okay
that's a good feeling to d6 plus tree
slashing they're both ones thankfully
with the rollers ah hey oh nice 7 0 to
10 10 slashing how's he feeling as
though he's falling apart
alright well tack on us might yeah just
to really let him know what how I what I
think of him
where's my d8 yep yeah where's the other
one now I guess I'll just roll this one
3 times it works on a 3 D 8 that's a 2
plus I want to get there no wait it
doesn't count on this mites that's a 3
plus a 5 so another 8 okay
dead the the smite knocks him straight
off and this horse breaks off and then
runs through the river okay good
and out into the summer hills all right
that's attack one detect wood there's
another horse there's another horse if I
were to take this horse out of the
equation then can meirin get to me that
would be very difficult for him to do so
c'est impossible if you love America
nothing guy ever never that rough yeah
alright I'll take out the other horse
yeah
yeah like well let's fucking I'll take
I'll take advantage and then I'll use a
great weapon so I'm only rolling this
one with a plus one nineteen plus want
to be a twenty my friend yeah I'll take
the 20
so that means create weapon master
great webbing that I don't know if I'm a
great master I mean I'm almost pretty
good consider good weapon yeah yeah ten
plus ten no 20 plus 3 is 23 uh so why
should i smite him is he dead
he's yeah if he's dead then I get
another attack you're right on top of
there how long you're here so basically
so so this yeah this is like it's like
in I got 31 oh yeah that's the sword is
in to the extent that you have to like
pull it off yeah of him he collapses off
this horse is not so loyal that it's
gonna stay on the field okay
it runs away Marik sees it run off into
the distance
can I get him Eric I don't know okay
Marik hasn't already done America I
don't like if I hit this guy he's gonna
counter hit me all I have you tell me if
you miss and magic is the stuff that
seems to be working again only if you
miss and not I don't know magic easy
things she everything's like attack plus
boost for me yeah me a lotta AC a lot of
hit points it's just right if he reacts
you you might not get it as long as you
don't talk shit is that the axis yeah
all right
uh I'll take advantage and but I'm not
gonna do a great left master I want to
make sure I get maximum that's a 316
okay plus six
so now when you got on I was 20 to 60
plus 622 yeah okay is he dead not get
him he's a lot no wait he has a lot of
AC but I was doing okay just for your
dork needs is because true into this
type of shit no I was doing the
calculation for the shield spell oh
sorry
GD 6 + 3 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 and then I'll
definitely smite him oh boy right 3 D 8
yum 8 mmm nice 1600 plus the ones
17 17 plus what did I say my initial
thing was like fucking 25 or something
yeah I was eight right is it dad so I
think 25 time right there yeah oh it's
it's okay no okay oh so you Rosie B
singer you turn your head back to see
what she what Crenn are is contributed
to this battle and you can see that it's
a tiny shadow toy and then it sort of
hits the ground bounces and then rolls
until it's at Marek's feet and then you
can feel as much as hear through your
arm the shadow singing begins it's sort
of sprouts and hatches at his feet and
then begins to grip and sees his limbs
like from the knees down so you tell me
that I think when you roll like 40 or
more damage you can tell me what happens
I think that's what you earn so she
she's holding him in place the shadow
toy that you know you brought from
Wrangler Norris is holding him in place
absolutely alright I'll say that Denar
Saul because he was the kiting strategy
works there's
and stop something that's not working
but then when he saw Crennel enter in
the field that's when he turned double
backs and that's when he goes into
overprotective dad mode and takes down
the the horsemen and then he goes after
Marik as he sees the shadow stuff
getting to him spill yeah and he just
fully whips it around his head like this
to come down on one big overhand strike
whew I think I'm trying to think you
know he would sauce it he doesn't hate
this guy I mean let's be real
he's been the bane of this dude's
existence first time we met I mean he
took over his brain and just made him
give up his war loot this time I took
him over and tighted him around when he
couldn't fight anyway I've just been
like the counter to everything he wants
to do so it's like sorry but it's how it
ends and then just like aim right for
the old coconut yeah yeah and split it
in half
no I then yeah exactly one half goes
inside cake yeah and then and then
dinner eats the cake brains all over it
I'm in charge now I American and all the
remaining soldiers follow I made a
mistake
[Laughter]
is great what I'm saying is that he
can't just have the whole thing right
you can't just have the whole thing so
he brain everyone in yeah absolutely so
yeah that's what happens we all get a
little smarter we all get +1 and wisdom
re-sprout or not no no no we get don't
remember what it was like waste exactly
all right hate what so what I really
know he's he's host so Josh who if you
would please be so kind
no from the grave
so the yeah exactly exactly as you are
sweeping the sword around and getting
ready to bring it down you can hear
hundreds of hooves do riding in from the
east of town and as they and you can see
America looks over and sees them and as
they are beginning to enter the town and
you bring this sword down they all begin
to sort of unspool into mist and blow
away in this evening breeze like as soon
as they cross the threshold of the town
this entire battalion of reinforcements
begin to burst and spray and just blow
away like dust priest son thanks Josh
so so that is that is that is the
scenario Locati is sort of straining
against your grip I've never been or
protective parent so I just I will
release him what is it boy so is it so
he slithers over to Merrick sharp and
crawls his way up and then just begins
to examine Merrick sharp what would like
exactly just a rally market exactly like
assessing him on and so this information
is available to you as well
yeah you can tell that there's something
similar here
so that there's an overlap spiritually
between Marik sharp to an extent and
what you saw of prints shimmer scale hmm
there is a they're both they were both
cloaked in a in a presence in a kind of
like at ARA manipulation and that it's
sort of like it's like draining out even
as you watch it like the actual
fingerprint like the real purpose of it
now that is draining away did cthe ris
was he aware of the origin of that
influence who is sure scale it was the
result of tema right and the team on
cult do I feel that it's that there is
control or that it's bad control that
control is receding from this now
useless right thing god Wow
disgusting here and so it's a so he
spends with Sun so he's actually sort of
held up by this by this toy in this
gruesome manner here in this courtyard
it's that same toy but you press on the
bottom is just the length over here at
the courtyard yeah by the party what
does that wait we still have gravy men
hanging around right yeah we say so no
let's let's give grieving minis out you
give him a quick little quick Kuakini
attack me yes I'm right there in our
yeah yeah and it's so didn't ours there
but he's doing this to twist is near the
body or is that just cuz the guy wanted
over he can just see through the Gottis
okay so cuz this is not there okay yeah
so then yeah the grave of men will will
see that Merrick another worthy foe
Falls he didn't get an offer he might of
yeah and he just
screams and now he's gonna lash out at
you it's like if I lost the touch say
what's your deal beyond words at the
point trying to wallow in my own
crackling that's what I have that
connects nobody honest evening for rain
or anything yeah no it's no no straight
up eight inches straight dude no please
wall well hurt by an apartment nothing
on no I have a good I had a good idea
it's called 2:156 so that's five damage
it's just like a little like grave of
men begins to at that starts to pour
like as though the material of the
shadow is now becoming liquid and it's
starting to like pour down like like
black gray ice there dry ice fog and
cthis says well that grave of potential
oh my god he's not mad as just
disappointed the corner just slink
ticking himself
I wasted a spell slam for you Amy Perry
right yeah anything so people are
beginning to filter out yeah the combat
music has ended yeah exactly so people
are beginning to filter out of the out
of the cavern did sorsha is the Saoirse
is speaking with Crenn are in very very
serious tones that's the salient piece
of data you can derive from this
situation
so an oncoming second wave disappeared
but there are there any bodies over they
all did they all disappear you killed
them about half of the about half of the
people you slew are there not there but
there are some that exactly lootable
loot Garrick I'm right next to Mary so I
want a loot marriage for sure but just
when I start digging through pockets I'm
a noble warrior king let's see what's in
here
absolutely I mean they have not this may
be a surprise to you but they have not
brought the lion's share of their
treasure with them on this raid but he's
got a war Lee oh no no I was just gonna
say but grab that and give everyone the
truth is that this war is exquisite make
now this is this is the real one this is
well it's unlike his other one his other
one was wasn't war loot obviously of
incredible manufacture but also had
place for a storage document secret
compartments much more like a business
yeah exactly
it's much more like the spy model right
this is to kill people model hey hold on
loot case you got it froz be seeing
everybody yeah so this is not like this
is a sleek instrument like a very very
very compact very solid very stable like
you aren't you aren't certain what would
it is and for you that's pod Wow guys
what do you don't get hasn't caught it
is that odd Green all but you can see it
you can see the the hinging and
mechanisms like you can get a sense
you've had your hands on a war loot
before you know I'm saying and this one
this one is no different you can you can
see the springs and mechanisms you would
use to tuck away all of this
and make it seem like a common traveling
instrument alright so I do that if the
state is no longer unsafe to hold now
and then I just walk out to cut there
son I'm just unceremoniously start
reaching for his creepy little horns
person bag to shove the loot in yeah I'm
just like a two-person job
yeah what else do I get out of Eric's
yes from in aggregate all told this
entire crew you end up with about 200
pieces of silver filled that's like
almost a quarter of what we're gonna get
for this stupid job hmm that's great
that's pretty good wait hold on Sam is
that just you're gonna oh wait no you
said the crew yeah unless you're
personally like stay away yeah well
that's the thing every time I lose
something I keep it for myself it's your
character she's loaded with stuff oh
yeah I'm won gold in the residency but
you need it you need it for he's loyal
to the national gambling minigames yeah
like that's why you have to any a rich
rich boy you know so there they are
going out he's got this trust one time
there they are basically like gathering
the bodies getting the useful yeah well
they're gathering that they're gathering
the Juggalos Derek obviously you know
the C team is down with it there's the
great no link oh no we're not I want to
make sure everybody knows I'm not down
at the clam
when Rosie scared off that last like
intimidated LS guys like guys like ICP
shit yeah
yeah I'm terrified yeah exactly so
they're collecting that they're clicking
that leather straps weapons hatchets
life yeah well that goner but basically
they're creating the preconditions for a
defensive strategy that doesn't involve
kind strangers mm-hmm the next go-round
I hope we all learned a lesson here
who's in charge of this town at this
point right now it's pretty clear that
with MIT is directing most of this she
is she has a big pot of strong bean
juice with some custom it sounds like
some aftermarket additions have entered
the pot hmm
I check on Rita yeah you can where's
where she is she's still pinned to the
ground to the ground
there's no there's no spear oh okay
it's a ghostly yeah yeah so she is but
she is unconscious on the ground okay um
I would have run over to her and I'll
use the healing question I have and turn
up or down throat yeah it's cat medicine
yeah yeah exactly it's a pillar yeah
like a good grape flavor oh no no no
this is yeah this is it's for kids
yeah it's not good yeah
a feud a few drops then she's very
quickly coughing up the lion's share of
your expensive healing potion okay ah
great mm-hmm as long as she's she's a
week um she's just she's just rubbing
her chest where she expected to have a
massive is there a wound no no no wound
at all okay um some fucking fight huh
she tries to speak and it has to Koff a
few times yeah
you know I would not have guessed it
based on our previous interaction but
you have valor you are not bad for a
stranger I'll take it
I also have one hit point immediately
fall asleep
Saoirse approaches you dinar and says
that she thinks that most of those dice
eating brains okay there's still any
brain sex no this is canonical now yeah
exactly
she get word we're gonna build this into
Dragon foreign culture these brains
those two dicks it's fine it's a fucking
weird bear yeah yeah yeah you're right
this is the old this is the ultimate Oh
see it's the ultimate ooh what'd you say
[Laughter]
reclamation the reclamation project was
behind most of the subjugation in
December Hills she says oh this is gonna
be a very after tonight this is gonna be
a very different place after the victory
celebration to me yeah the guy killed
the bad guy she says with preneur so
yeah a literal baby yeah she follows her
daddy's footsteps well yeah she's a
brave warrior I'm super proud I don't
think it as an insult
you're not a baby I'm not a baby she's a
baby she's my baby big strong baby I
asked her
so what do you where are you going next
were you doing she says you up for the D
stands for Dragonborn born mentions men
missions oh I love how faithful you are
as Ryan to this are all so far off she
says I'm going to form a small militia
using some of these weapons once we can
find their main cash and the rest of
their supplies I think that the
assembler hills needs to take a more
direct hand in its own survival I'll
stay on long enough to do that
and after that I need to find out where
all this money was going
you're the only one who knows about the
sumac connection right I think at this
point yeah but I mean I wouldn't I
wouldn't have reason to hide it though
so Oh and Lodi did we did not find an
amulet on Marik no no yeah oh yeah like
that yeah exactly
exactly that's that is excellent
Dungeons &amp; Dragons II I said for you and
Everson I have no reason to hide that
bad information
yeah yeah cool see you next have a fun
summer
stay cool she reaches she reaches down
whoa yeah
yes you made a cupping motion she's
trying to get to our cop you're nuts
what all right I misunderstood that's
fine classic Dragonborn throw yeah it's
just like fine to you as well she
reaches down gets Granero on the
shoulder and then begins to help with
mid you can see that she's talking to
she's talking to groups of people yeah
for a different type of security I would
not take that away hey good game
there's no threats it's just much I give
it to you
and you here for one HP okay guys see
this just debacle yeah brand that brings
all the rubbing off they go
come here grandma hey yeah let me fix
you
she kind of like it's kind of cute she
kind of like waddles real slow yeah
she's like help help
and just like up headed link fully
engulfed by the Drake your hands and
just give you I don't know well I don't
think we're getting another combat I
will give you the rest maybe a 3300 25
keep five just in case I don't know
that's good we still got a little more
time okay
you have a moment finally to examine the
cart and coriander and you see that
coriander is in her
rest configuration right lockdown
lockdown but there are five bandits what
around her on the ground
oh they tried to Jack coriander know
exactly the 80s Batman movies you can
see you can see a couple stairs you can
see that there's a couple scuffs and
Nick's no on coriander but but it's
clear who got the worst of it out here
stuff's next Craig's my girl certain
thickness are buffing those scuffs out
right away
buff the scuff stuff in those Scouts
that I'm soothing because I'm doing like
clicking and whispering and horse shit
to her you know and to eat two hundred
silver yeah oh yeah
well-deserved come on yeah did you ever
give oh no I was gonna do that
I just feet as a funny moment yeah no I
mean I really time yeah say oh yes by
the way ever I have gifts for everyone
mother here's your grandmother here's a
beautiful silver rope Chris yes tooth oh
it's a big old weird tooth did you know
you have to like pull I thought I heard
on the tooth Oh need to pull real like
oh it wants to be with you now wants to
be with there know our little friends
friend of milk and oh my god
forgot about anything is just with me
the whole time just a little baby oh
yeah have fun down there bud like it's
harder than you would have to fight a
baby
Oh God it is okay has he grown at all in
your pouch sure is he still a baby
he's he is perception he's fully grown
like in terms of like his ratios
same voltage like if you have if you
grow like down in the bag like you you
grow back sighs yeah oh yeah give you
just a bicuspid just a weirdo just
sizing your head Giants - yeah okay I
knew I'd like it now you got that I
named Leggett it's weird you know weird
the other tooth and one for you one for
each weirdo I know you get a molar oh
yeah I will I turn it over and I'm like
I will turn this into a great drinking
cup Oh molar and pestle dang I was gonna
call you the wrong name like that's how
delighted I was
he was gonna call you
Denarius just so proud of himself he's
just on top of the world
oh yeah I did good I'm a good good boy
you got everybody presents everyone
presents then full of rain that kid who
can hold her own in a fight yeah yeah
the sure and go up that's why I said do
I coriander begins to decouple and
expand you can see the rich green SAP
stretching underneath the underneath of
plates and as she as she achieves her
final form
she has a few stomps for these for these
brigands um I tell her your body count
is actually higher than mine really well
I'm surprised too but I gotta give it to
you yeah that great tongue is out okay
no how many of this you do now ten now
No
see you all right yeah I'm just so I'm
just gonna one at a time we're feeding
that gold you danced lining in the slide
get that horse
when you get it when you get to ten
coins oh when you get you get the ten
gold coins you you feel that she is
giving you some kind of discount and
exactly yeah and then after that you
just get a few good licks okay on your
face with this with this cold dry tongue
I had a demon before earlier are you
telling Cory oh yeah sort of like while
she's eating just to make conversation
can this be that could the wrist has
seen Rosie do it so much yes please
see what he still be proud of it cuz he
didn't
I made it I mean I did like okay hold
your horse at the end makes it even if I
had made it a little better great game
this was that not a great demon piece of
garbage
this time there's this group of men
didn't even kill one guy not even one
guy even grabbed up man a few stomps
some spirited raises of the head it's
very much like talking to a person isn't
this great right if you boil out all of
the like all of the eccentricities and
details
it's exactly like exactly the same
pledge gone don't need it exactly indeed
those complexities are they don't serve
to leaven the experience if anything
they're their own roadblocks to past
Andy yeah I just go oh I don't need
anybody today
done have an introvert the rest of the
day I hide in my nice working promise
guys thanks good job done what do you
ah if we leave promise I would want to
deny would say goodbye to her Nora oh
yeah I already think we would rest the
night and then leave in the morning
yeah let's you can do it everyone let's
take a long rest that a long rest
yeah you did dude I'm curious though
moan about baby oak and like I would
want to ask like mine to mind just like
you're still in the bag what's the
what's the play what what what's your
how do you gestate and then once that is
done you're gonna stand you gonna hang
out exactly like what's yeah it's the
life cycle right after demi god I don't
know
I've read some stuff he says he says is
that actually Josh let's do this another
way Wow Josh will you oh I don't even
have to answer the specifics you only
turn the stream I think so billion go
into the mode asks a real question and
I'll give you the real answer okay then
you've been in there this whole time
watch the play Shirley you're gonna grow
into a full size and he says well this
fear and I think you'll agree with me
it's a reasonable one is that as a baby
I would not be able to contribute much
to a pitched sorceress melee course I'm
an got we own the or we have one accord
on that I've seen stranger things but
yeah I agree yeah seems like he's he
says it is the I don't have complete
knowledge of things outside the pouch
yeah this is sort of where I'm at right
now is that what a TV stands for yeah
yeah you know me out of the pouch he
says he says is the battle concluded oh
I think so at least as far as there's
this small town that we were staying and
just promised I don't know if you heard
that word yeah battle seems to be
concluded promised its
they're making it for something that's I
wouldn't have said it out loud but
luckily we have no need that we other
thing he says well if if all the swords
and spells are quite over you feel the
flap of the bag lift up come over the
back and then out from this bag a fully
grown oak tree strong American in the
middle of the city like an adult naked
man I look at oak and then I just go
denied council mayor Labor's please you
we'll catch up with you next week but
we'll also catch up with you on a much
shorter timeline at Table Talk
immediately after this will be a short
break we'll do tabletop it'll be a lot
of fun don't go nowhere
we'll see you soon
you