previously on Tessie teams it's actually
just something that I want to grow out
of you so now you're this horrifying
like displacer V style
critter oh no he when I lose my
concentration he remains for like six
rounds yeah absolutely
I'm sure well I'm trying to hang one of
the most classic taking pins pulling all
the aggro and then I'm running away all
right cradles head in my hands but
really quietly the two corpses they are
together they're immediately knit
through with with minions yes
mesh together lines and then they will
rise up on four legs of sorts that do
not bend so they just sort of Teeter
he just fully whips it around his head
like this
to come down on one big overhand strike
boom sorry buddies good sound ends and
then just like aim right for the old
coconut 1/2 goes on inside cake dinner
eats the cake out from this bag a fully
grown oak trees emerges look at oak and
then I just go the past address the
fastest wedding you wouldn't make it
past a second as the question
play it brash and reckless to choose a
cautious solution you saw it was prudent
in any Sepulcher poker to don't become
the putrid it's that well said I pursue
in no mountain too steep for dungeon too
deep to send expendable marks up to the
top of the peak of beneath they see Yugi
they come like sharks to it while I swim
in that line even like Carl Barks
through it so send your National Parks
drew it I'll send him home in a natural
box with a close title most of the parts
included
save your breath for a cleric confessor
death is a lesson and life is attending
professor but if just seeking my
official advice sign on the dotted line
English of the choice well I'm Tycho
Brahe hey of Kenya Kate impacts I am
also on manifest hair weird run see you
of acquisitions incorporated but today
I'm Sheriff or QR codes and I'm here to
bring a game of Dungeons &amp; Dragons for
my friends and I'll Gus the body that
includes such favorites
let's Dragonborn narcissist in our blitz
in I can perform a magic trick it's a
name oh we're haunted AF how did I make
that noise on my mouth moving to to the
right of my right reppin the natural
world walnut dog grass out in the
energized no doubt yeah by ancient
magics to my left
Tamila recently returned from a world
tour not your grandma's grandma except
in those rare cases where she is your
grandma's grandma Rosie oh yeah exactly
you're like you're trying to get out of
a shake wait that's the question nice do
you work for
there's an interrogation I'm gonna take
a walk to the left of my left
you're emerging as though from a mist
shroud its cuff wrist round
rollercoaster
we're all on the right we're all on the
ride together now when last we saw
heroes they had recently indeed very
recently put together a plan a
comprehensive plan to protect the newly
enacted mining town of promise they were
able to annihilate a suite of invaders
some of which were not technically real
but they were led by Merrick sharp and
his reclamation group a nefarious crew
designed primarily to extract wealth
from the summer hills and channel it
toward functionally speaking cult cells
that had begun to erupt
all throughout the desperate valley a
direct result of the collapse of Scala
now to the most recent thing that
occurred the most recent I'm very the
bitter end of the stream last week
indeed you need is that a fully grown
fully naked oak tree strike was decanted
from Denard Watson's body baby bag
glistening fired from the nerve
Woodsen's ouch once
oh yeah right do you write a speech yeah
I want to know walnuts reaction
immediately okay I've been preparing for
this all week
I draw my sword real deal just
immediately right I love this this is
this is the game that I want to run
hold on alone it's the situation that
want to be a part of I need I need a
little more setup than that so he so he
he crawls out of the bag yeah yeah yeah
baby
he dumps himself out and then he sort of
stands no oh no come on
yes no cuz I know much slimy bag no
Issei it's like how how bad do you want
it to be that way and I wouldn't I can
consider hooking it up I mean this is
this is our game how moist do you want
it because I can take that slider a new
wallet recognize them immediately
we just skipping over are you its cannon
deny as a slimy slimy bag
no it's slimy Oh got in with the slime
that is his choice this has been rolling
around it
his hair is his hair is matted with
thick slime redolent of fruits he looks
he looks he looks like he is in like a
casting call for enemy heroes okay what
is he swinging an expression his face is
he proud like what does he look like he
doesn't he seems to be fine with
whatever is happening right now
he has precisely zero yes precisely zero
negative body image and with good reason
because it is magnificent yeah nice tip
to toe absolutely lower except for the
places where you do want a little no of
course you don't
you're not supposed to but none of these
things are even like a more or pass yeah
listen there's a there's a there's a lot
to enjoy oh my god my bag was so heavy
yeah it's a hair of and our dragons pack
a lot of weight from this especially
from the back oh yeah
get a nice ready I had been conversing
with him briefly when he just decided to
turn into a full-grown human and then
walnut yeah I just hear that sword
unsheathed
I guess yeah
that's what's confusing he was a baby
and he's like I don't want to be a baby
aim lamp huh I assume there's gonna be
like this gestation baby it's like I'm
done being a baby do you wanna have a
microphone I guess I gotta have a
microphone for this show yeah
grandmother did we really do a mic check
I invite you I welcome you to our game
of Dungeons and Dragons
I present I love to be here guys I love
it be present with us yeah so I pull my
sword and I say um John do this the easy
way or the hard way he says can I get
more information I say you can either
come with me or I can kill you where you
stand
I don't I don't think that it a hundred
percent works that way but I know that
during previous interactions we've had
things were said and I think that we
both regret our actions
I don't what kind of thing well in the
in the fullness of time I think you'll
look back on some of these interactions
and say could I have done that
differently
yes you're really just full of talk
today ah listen I still have a job to do
and that job was to deal with you so you
can come back with me or I can take you
back in pieces and then we have a number
of full-grown him doesn't even based on
what we've seen so far it seems like
he's a good night now
yeah where do where did we leave this
within in regards to like our contract
with him refresh my memory cuz I don't
remember
we had a job to obtain yeah
and then he disappeared as we were
crossing the threshold and I meant to
get him and then he died so the contract
still stands that we have to return him
I would say was never avoided and I
would say there is a very reasonable
idea that the c-team has a current
contract to secure folk true strike as a
drink I was gonna say docu man see here
it come why are we even arguing strike
says walnut yes I assent to your demands
[Music]
I think that it would be more convenient
for me to arrive in a single piece then
it would be to arrive in chunks of
various sizes and certainly I have had
enough of dinars bag it's not clean
there are concerns there are burn there
are very real concerns she goes all
right fine we're gonna talk later
we should talk we never saw you never
topic well if you thought I was gonna
help you with that paperwork now you're
wrong Oh muss it all up when I get the
pages all crinkly
you know hell no and there is a there is
and you can see in this this tableau in
front of you
that includes this gleaming
precision-engineered
example of masculinity you can see also
a driving machine Ekans you can see
walling out of dinars bag like a like a
tongue almost a couple crinkled corners
bent down over the edge of the bag kept
on his document a price so you kept the
slime baby yolk yum the papers keep it
fresh got sealing that freshness you get
that burp you know when you sue it in
you think child in there you don't 20
Guinea hindsight's yeah here in this
cool reflective atmosphere yeah we can
look back and say best decision yeah
maybe who knows like this is for this is
for history to decide not a say they
have been in engels to such an extent
yeah
then they look like a single page I go
um
I look at the bag and I make it grab for
them man I just start cleaning them but
never like really like I starting to oak
like every couple of seconds yeah yeah
do you do you while you're cleaning them
do you want a taste of the the content
like are you are you taking them are you
just peeling them of hearts or like
onion skin yeah or are you getting a
glance ah
that's some of the product well I know
that I can't fill it out but I mean I
would take a look okay the very the
front and the top says welcome to this
is all while cleaning maintaining your
vision on the front it says welcome to
form DC to inaugural the decision is
rank to examination it must be filled
out in full
my decision is to rank one no outside
assistance should be necessary we invite
you to settle in dip your quill and
prepare yourself to take the SATs dude
yeah good time wise just looking at them
like yeah they do that Wild West in
there yeah I'm gonna use if you'll
permit me prestidigitation to to clean
the page restore no I love it if it's
accept yes just wear pages if I should
say here this is incredible make some
noise that's the sound makes it dirty
yeah it's oiling to having a really
difficult time because listen beef on my
character sheet is written horny grandma
no it says enemies : oak tree straight
me too yeah together I saw I was sworn a
vow but good lord you you can sense to
your left with mid approaches and the
two of you just share a moment with lip
it says it's a friend of yours sadly not
even close now what are the opposite
that's great news for me all yours babe
move like I mean an introduction but I
think I'll grease the wheels as they say
it does seem like the right thing to do
oh I'm gonna have to wash my knickers
out in the river alright jeez I don't
know you that well but
for you how many we're all clothes are
washed lift made a deal with Ned may you
have a long and happy life together you
marry them
Wow Jesus yeah I'm a ship captain I'm
banging ok don't like you but with mid
says I have the only private Hut in town
she does no no no what is it ok look
you're playing both NPCs yeah ok
use your hands looks back ok
he looks back over his shoulder toward
coriander in the cart and says we can
leave any time he says that to me yeah
great oh no I think we're here for a
while I think we're comfortable oh no
you gotta do things sorry I was just
going to enjoy my understanding is I
mean there's often a time limit you know
as pertains and I having been a part of
acquisitions incorporated myself
certainly in a decision is to role he
would understand of course Gennaro heavy
heavy heavy lies the crown and so forth
but obviously even if it's not stated
explicitly there's a there is a time an
optimal time for trimming in the
document the person we can go I'm so
done listening to you talk on for real
now the last time we tried to complete
this quest this slippery slippery little
devil vanished a snake it if you want to
go yeah roto-rooter to make sure you
don't get another acorn on anything see
that I would find pleasurable that's a
happy compromise yeah everybody get
something like you know Oh consent to do
a cavity search on the way home
document uh yeah I I guess Prezi Oh a
scope that like how can we make sure
that you're not gonna just disappear
when we get back to the DNC I assume my
word is not oh no it wasn't last time
doesn't know shit see ya my best friends
and you broke your promise
yeah he's heartbroken he seizes I have
no pockets you have nature's pocket
anything and there's - madam I want to
assure you that I'm not keeping any
seeds or contraband you can't smell her
without you are ass grand over in the
middle of town square you start to sing
you just play elbow-deep they've got
small arms not as quite as bad as a fan
for my shadow speculum you want you want
to use here there's gotta be a better
way
chatter staff we can just not take him
in to the DNC we'll just have him
outside okay okay yeah let's do that
not long great really up oaks ass well I
still a guy in there he doesn't care
yeah but he's a demigod if you want to
leave now you could so I don't even know
why you messed around with the Acorn to
begin with did you say that out loud
yeah I did yeah I said it what do you
mean that's funny he spoke to me briefly
we had a conversation as a baby he's not
killable who didn't know about this
Rosie did you know my I didn't know
about this but nothing surprises me
anymore tried to tell you but I didn't
all right
go home he's uh he's walking back the
you would describe the gait as tight
like he's trying to hide something
nuts clenching magic metered
and wif m''d it's just it's it's like
it's being recorded in her mind like
every frame like 120 cut like slo-mo
camera like Antichrist you see
Antichrist it's like the beginning of
Antichrist okay great there's a lot
going on yeah okay well should be like
what it's left to do here I want to say
goodbye to swooshing oh yeah yeah and
crying I like her do you want a moment
to that and then maybe weak will conduct
oke there Richard him sure do you want
to officially mark this job is completed
doing it like contractually did I do the
paperwork back at the DNC usually okay
right yes there's a table available you
know how it works absolutely so you're
gonna seek well yeah I guess is everyone
to welcome back to the car yeah so as
you're walking back to the cart you can
see there's a few horses riding of the
East Road and they meet Whitman out in
front of the town and you think it's a
you think it might be a delegation from
another now from another small village
brought out in the hills you don't see
me freebies mm-hmm champion so she's
going off to meet them yeah basically
that the horses are coming up and she's
like alright okay who's with me is doing
this yeah okay all right that's fine I
don't do her thing looking for sourcing
granola okay you poke around a bit and
you can see sorta has Crenn are like
picked up it's like carry her in front
of her carrying her out of the cave and
she sets her down and then Crenn r is
trying to run back into the cave and
you're not sure how long this has been
going on but you think it's it's
it's a process when she used the the
shadow ball
yes what happened to it afterwards
there's one more so she as we recall she
has a system of singing you know that
can collapse it back yeah so currently
there's two out and you have one more
with you three of them total but she can
she can sing them back into it okay it
wasn't like broken or anything no no D
here in the last one it needed to be
replaced or something no no she she
seems able to look up look just like a
snowball almost just like we packed them
back in mhm okay then uh I'll go over
there to them and get down on one knee
and just and give Crenn re a little hug
yeah she's it's there's a lot of there's
a lot of nips just little kisses around
the on the on the cheek up on the year
huh and I'll say I'll see you again
little one and thank you for the sword
say to both of them yeah thank you for
the sword yeah sorry sir sir sir she
folds her arms and then not so how are
you how are you wearing these where is
the sword I think they're both on Osiris
back okay so they're they're both double
they're both present yeah yeah she she
definitely she recognizes this yeah I
used it in combat
absolutely so and uh she says when we
were finished in the sombre Hills we
will return to read large on our way
south sounds good
so there is there is an interesting
there is an interesting note okay so
this is in the language that you both
speak whenever is the cure your speaking
she
tends not to use common so before she
has there's a linguistic mechanism that
describes the rank it's all built into
the language it's a suffix and every
time before this time she's used the
imperial suffix which is sort of like
ruler to it subject and this time she
has chosen something that establishes
that you were both of rank understand
bank or linguistics this mana show for
you so but she she she gives you the she
gives you the nod mm-hmm and then calls
Crenn are back to her and gets her set
back up yeah it looks like she's getting
ready to ride okay I'll go back to the
cart she hops back in the Bjorn all
right now Rosie B singer yeah how does
this journey go how does this journey go
back to redline
mm-hmm I think that we all need some
rest so whoever's chillin just like I
think it's a pretty chill ride I hope
it's a chill ride oke no one searches
Ochs
anal cavity but no no one Hey no I know
that
but no one doesn't searches no one but
oke rides up front
Oh Rosie just buck a snake ever puts on
any clothes Rosie's like are you sure
you don't want to put on some pants you
are a demigod
maybe Kandra pant leg and he's like no
for I could I could not be separate from
the wind itself or some elf shit
whatever he says it's great it's nice in
the middle in the middle of this story
as you are enunciated it and waving it
around he says
okk true strike does dawn a pair of
breeches aha dusty now I believe I'm
gonna tell them the story true strike
let me just shut it down so you you roll
back in and at the at the moment the
cart is nestled securely in the bubble
the soap bubble disappears and you are
nestled right there back at home at the
drawn and courtier which you have not
had much of an opportunity to spend time
at for quite a while after your
adventures indeed below the surface
having returned and it almost
immediately had to rush back out
you are absurd oh it's a nice place we
don't need to get inside of anybody ever
again
I took a took ghostly gaze I can I'm not
gonna probe him with my eyes instead of
my hands you see this right at the
threshold like it occurs to me right is
worried about to walk in like wait am i
where yeah I can put this to rest easily
going layer by layer cars all my
concentration you don't then some it's
just you're like maybe you want to go in
no way to stay here okay something
happens your eyes are really red on that
crotch though don't they yeah no stone
unturned if there's anything cancer it'd
be whatever whatever whatever condition
had made the alterations to
your left eye that process is now
complete on the right side as well how
you choose how you choose to present
yourself under these circumstances or
that's a that's a separate matter but
you are perfectly you are perfectly able
to see with this this multi-phase human
system I yeah but of course to cthe risk
I doubt it's anything strange I think
it's just another it might be novel for
a few moments it's like getting older
like yet gray hair looks like you need
bifocals it's like yeah sometimes you
need a cluster of gem eyes you know no
okay
is it a compound eye like a fly or
spider or is it just like individual
little gemstones sucking in their own
side imagine like a so like a spider
doesn't have a compound eye it does have
like eight discreet eyes but imagine
something like that but just like
asymmetrically set in the face close
like nittany yeah so is it kinda like a
little geodes even out okay there's a
little little like a faceted trait to
them I like do it when I'm looking
through him do it notice anything
different other than like a person's
physiology
given his his God his his status I mean
there may be there may be some other
there may be some other mechanism by
which you can assess him but on this
plane he appears to have most of the
stuff you'd expect all the things you've
seen splayed out in various diagrams
right yeah all seem to be present there
I miss I think this is the first time I
used it so it's neat to see these
diagrams like hmm no leakage other yeah
sense he's he's clean
we got an ocular Pat can we yeah give
him a blanket from the back so he
doesn't create a health code violation
when we walk in yes
okay I do that but grudgingly I give him
a blanket oh yeah cut yourself
we're it like a horse blanket yeah like
rough yeah
like unforgiving in grit horse blanket
like sandpaper yeah yeah as he puts it
on to I'm like I had sex on that thing
it's yeah he's trying to he's trying to
shift it he's like I can tell oh my god
yeah it just it just it just it's
hanging it's just hanging off and it's
so firm and there's not a lot of comfort
good and so yeah yeah tell me tell me
tell me what happens next your home
let's go ahead as we get him to the
threshold you ready to catch him
I got imagine like the four of us would
just be like yeah call a hand on a
shoulder I like for like goes we go -
yes all right so we all have hands on
his body
yeah - raw skin yeah yeah - hunch he can
we're just certain shuffling into like
surrounding him and Sharaf yards and
just like prisoner we got a prisoner
like eating there's a naked man was like
a freaking horse blanket prisoner
incoming look away enjoy your meals
profit snaps her fingers a couple times
and points upstairs like that's where we
will take him so yes you will
yeah sorry for the show everybody
yes we're all very sorry well there's
not a private entrance to be upstairs
how many people yeah how many people are
there how many people how many meals to
be ruined real for crowd yeah there's
many what time of day is it this is
about 1:30 thank you
so they chronological yeah we're all
doing this he's facing forward I'm
facing him face to face moving backwards
it's like smiling at him get up so badiy
but smiling little fuzzy all right this
is okay my tails just hitting wheels
knocking over drinks no X jumps over the
tail as it swings through don't get that
you start on that thing
all right let's take him up to that
common area and put him in put him in
that room the smell of profit is clearly
hard at work anytime she's not bringing
something out she's making sure that a
pot of strawberry jam does not scold I
know you want to see my room and wall
not gonna swim in the common room I see
yeah cool cool stuff I'm into this
central room that is completely lockable
has no exterior windows it does however
have a massive trophy full of an
ever-changing mixture of potion that's
yeah yeah I'm dragging that into my room
yeah carving a line in the woods yes yes
big Harvard trench it stays you're
hearing this this this drag and scratch
and then in the distance in the kitchen
you can hear Hey and school we've got
mending nicely yeah I put that in my
room and then I lock my room up nice and
I'm like under no circumstances none are
you to go in my room
he says I mean I've been in that room
before when they were the b-team there
yeah and he was hooking up with whoever
used to be in that room who was it and
you know no I just um well I immediately
goes to getting that like to get mad and
like say something stupid to him and
then she gets sad instead no maybe he's
just in there saying this you just close
the door yeah yeah Rosie quietly writes
in there his paper she looks at out she
slaps it on walnuts door it says no Oaks
allowed
I'll teach him Ochs alas oh do you have
a lot of great open reactions here music
this is a great opportunity just like
ambivalence emoji yes doesn't matter me
do we like tie him up what's the plan um
gotta be magical handcuffs should know
Mina bringin a break I mean a shadow
prison I would just I would just
outright ask him not but I have reason
to trust him but like you seem you seem
amenable and coming along and I right in
assuming that you could escape at any
time that you wanted I think I could do
a very good job of it I have reached a
point I think where I need to answer for
some of the things that I've done I've
run from them for a while and I think
they're in a position to overcome me now
so hmm I'm are you working on the
paperwork or for that I write in my my
ledger hoping that the secretary in sees
this what are you right um all right we
have acquired Oh true strike please send
have you no yes please send a collection
team posthaste
understood well expect them from what
are deep within the week and walnut
right the week like she goes all the way
to the end of the page flips the page
the best part of me like how the
secretary would have to chase you from
page to page
yes no no no it's there any responses
are not response to this is a week it
may not be a full week does that satisfy
you just how high do you want me to push
this one that says well it rates we're
dealing with a demi-god escalate it as
high as possible
understood he's a D word get you places
you get him in that massive hottie like
that you get like that rap about like a
garden hose just put it right there and
then just get it boy yeah he's these I
know yeah do you come back out as I say
it's yeah conversation and it could be
any length you want
it's free place I need your choice are
you bound by certain he sits down in the
corner and then just puts the blanket in
front of him and leans back and closes
designer I take it to mean that you like
to sleep so you decide to communicate
with him telepathically yes fair enough
just keep him there maybe we don't need
to talk about I mean it's up to you
really do you feel comfortable he turn
himself in he seems to want to answer
for something each
send to stay here of his own volition or
do you wanna stick with the hurtin on
him I don't trust him but he also seems
to have come on his own accord and I
don't know what he would have to gain
from try ass this far just
inconveniencing you which has
historically been very exciting for him
you're right we should tie him up let me
float something else out to you and
you're welcome to say no which is maybe
a great idea but I suspected at this
point we have more to worry about from
hemdan from me and I am wearing a power
transfer necklace that you could use to
render him unconscious oh my god okay Oh
your kinky relationship is all this is
okay we've got to talk about that on
table talk whatever that is so I know
Rosie looks it cuz there's two kind of
like gives me side eye and she's like
this is exactly what a very clever
warlock would say if he was about to
pull some shit on us I think
yeah no way I'm doing problems I think
that I have I have enough charges that I
can create and restore a shadow prison
or shadow manacles or whatever sexy
shadow bindings we're gonna do yeah yeah
in your shadow fuck room for the next
week
yeah I was gonna say we don't it doesn't
have to be that he's like behind bars
but it's like a house arrest
yeah scenario okay just tell me and tell
me more about this design me okay
so it's it
say it's pretty beefy and it is going to
manacle his well turned ankle to the
chair that he has sat down upon to
trance and he's in the common room so
like he has breathing a run of the place
yep he can air has access yes yeah but
he he is going to be shackled to that
chair I will not suffer him to walk
around this place because god only knows
what two feet can get him so he's gonna
stay in his chair yeah and that's gonna
be what happens until that that shadow
power dissolves it's torture cuz he's in
the common room so I can just sit and
talk - oh absolutely interrogated if I
could it's about his wiener right it's
good but like but it could be
simultaneous yeah like he's gonna be
like I'm not gonna go in there but I we
use this and then listen I got these
great guards different you'll see do you
know about these cards don't worry I'm
gonna walk you through the whole thing
which salads I think where your room was
my room thank did you see the thing one
floorboards loose that's weird
yeah are you talking to him I'm
certainly kidding
I finally went to sleep as he faked
sleeping let me I don't know that
doesn't mean that you're not in there
talking to him I I thought he was I
thought he was disengaging from everyone
else Jesus I just wanna make sure I
respect oak tree strike I wasn't gonna
push the is just like like feels like a
betrayal of our friendship but we should
tie him up I don't wanna believe God all
right so he's tied up do we we saw most
of a day yeah thank you oh my gosh
absolutely you got time galore yeah what
okay you are you are at your home and
there are no jobs in in the box normally
are we rested it's time to do me rest in
the car yes finally
finally I'm gonna be Trevor so let's
throw the whole chair with oak right in
the cart janar you do have homework to
do
I think wish them and I say as long as
they don't go back in the bag go
I got my fantasy steamer I had to see
steamer now dinar has to complete those
without anyone else to help right it's
true like you can't even be there to to
tell them that you spelled something huh
it says you shouldn't need help fair
enough
correct so explore the space tell me
tell me what you tell me how you begin
so where are you gonna undertake this
effort tonight is gonna do it in the
common room wall Oh bye-bye near Oak
absolutely that's cheating
why having a higher level decision in
the room with you while you do it
that's true talk to you yes Matt it
doesn't say anyway the rules that a dog
can't play football
we got an earbud we got an earbud in the
in the corner so you use you'd settle
down at the chair to flip down type
Bureau style desk you scooch puts on
like comically small glasses Oh like a
little no but dude they it's like they
wouldn't even go up here like they have
to go like down by the side absolutely
and and okay as he as he sees as he sees
you getting ready I mean he sees the
sheaf of papers and he says thank you
maybe I just enjoy having this enjoy
this there's a lot of this all I can say
like a solid 45 minutes of prep without
so there we're doing work just like
everything my ink pot pretty full every
excuse not to do it
I'm gonna do this collated or anything
they're just like there's some wrong
documents in here there's like miss
colored pages important stuff this way
you've managed to develop a sweat gland
yeah sweat between the scales in the
intervening period
well that's doing that thing that cats
do with like they well closer youth
let's eat you see part of the process I
just want to see him get started I know
if I it's like a parent with their kid
and homework it's just like if he gets
started I never probably doing the work
not the issue is not the issue here so
concise we'll look at the sight of all
this it's like everything well in in
okay I take the that that my father's
research nice so I could spend some time
in that in that pocket dimensions of
study can I come in I don't know
I got you probably can but I don't use
that me too good story okay well let's
see I could stab you with it yeah and
then it's just gonna hang in the air
yeah and then I could just drive my face
and do it where it's floating in the air
and maybe I'll also be like okay can you
not grab it once it's hangin cuz when I
grab it I don't know actually we've
never tried I thought I just sat where
it was like fixed you can offer just to
stab them no see this this is definitely
getting back into this Power Exchange
thing so basically
is that something you want to try yeah
but scientifically interesting yeah
absolutely
shot described described with that
describe what that process looks like I
mean I I really like all of you but I
would have a hard time if you tried to
put a knife into my eye
uh I have no trouble with doing it
yourself to myself I'm trouble of doing
it anybody especially knowing that this
knife is not a one that leaves a wound
it seems scary but it's fine
what only works on your family you just
stab me in the eye and I die hmm yeah
we'll see so because this has never
tested this we should know occurs to me
if I was to stab myself with it and it
lingers in the air is could somebody
like use this as a ladder
what's the load-bearing component of
this thing floating in the air it's
substantial really yeah is it but is it
like match my weight or some other you
think pull up on it yeah all right look
I don't know how deep the knife has to
go in I like to put it in the whole way
every time but after I go in if you just
want to like a little cut yeah sure
afraid does it hurt when you put it in
there I don't know that I'd notice if it
does or hey okay maybe prior slide I
don't know
all right is there no just good the
opposite of first great okay great one
it only feels cold okay yeah let's go to
the doctor can you like so you're taller
than me would you mind kneeling before
yeah I get down yeah to a height where
you can choose I even go a little bit
lower so you could select if you wanted
to go in your guts or yeah yeah and then
I just go ahead and plunge it in okay
and I assume I'm gone you vanished
instantly yeah and then my end in this
space okay and then at that moment you
can see almost just a flash like from
the tip of the blade to the hilt huh as
Chris wrist disappears okay
okay Rosie lines up her the middle of
her forehead with this blade and she
says to walnut very chipper she's like
here I go
and then JIT like sort of gently pushes
into the tip of the blade yeah yeah it's
as soon as as soon as you commit to it
you don't know what would happen if you
didn't decide yeah but as soon as you
commit to it you are in another place
like so fast that you have to catch
yourself okay and then behind you you
can see that there is a door that is
open just a crack and the light in this
crack mirrors the light that is on the
edge of the blade ah okay but this is
massive like this is a this room this is
a substantial a substantial volume of
space and it is utterly stacked with
books alchemical apparatus and it and
from a home interior decorating
perspective it is very much of a piece
with what you saw when you were in the
family mansion mm-hmm I see and I think
you can tell to like the difference
between however my father left it and my
own studying techniques where it's like
this is very well it's still organized
and clearly he had a project here he was
working on but then where the thrist has
taken over it's just just Dax and it's
very cluttered and yeah discarded I was
ring on something over you it's it's
like it's like when you see a it's like
a some kind of a fungal rot has taken
root like in a branch or a trunk like it
looks like it looks like the room is
contracted and illness on this side it
is bleeding books
it's fatal cool
what what what what brings you to my
knife um
I think just curiosity and also I didn't
totally believe you yes I think it's
fair I don't know I really don't I was
not expecting literally exactly what she
said which is really cool these all your
dad's books I think so and so what Chris
has been doing and what I want to
continue to do is like figure out where
the crossover is between this community
god this symbol and his and the earth
yeah and if like I'm compiling as much
material as I can to try and see how
they relate you want to try to create a
kind of table look at like a divine
table of elements almost yeah I would
want to know how they that relationships
and because there is a station chef your
vines what to project maybe you're right
absolutely
mm-hmm I support this project when I
represent I think this is the kind of
situation where Rosie would settle down
some books that she picks out that are
probably all astronomy related and she's
quietly sitting in a chair it's too big
for her and Kathryn says every 30
fucking seconds Catorce is like oh I
just also found this like oh and did you
know I actually read this earlier but
it's yeah I said I don't know if you
look at me I don't know if it's to you
those two it's to know about it yeah
yeah she's learning what it's like when
kids were studies loud it's not like a
library it's it's a it's a nigga
libraries it humming mm-hmm well there
there there are books that focus on
astronomy but they it's odd I mean so
the astronomy texts that you're familiar
with describe a star-filled sky from a
fixed location and these books
describe stars as being in a kind of
ocean a place of depth not just not just
the points of light that you can
reference based on their ratios to one
another but existing in a kind of sea go
body you can traverse exactly hmm
exactly so the diagrams are very very
different as a result interesting do I
have any point of reference when viewing
these diagrams of being able to say like
so this is the point from which I was
always taught about the sky but I see it
now in a different almost like going
from 2d to 3d
absolutely yeah yeah so we've been using
history as I recall yeah for cartography
there's a couple of reasons I like that
one it's it based and I think that a lot
of these types of transforms are
actually going to be fundamentally
mathematical okay in nature and Rosie's
very clever so I think that it's a it's
a good mix okay but absolutely so you're
gonna try to mine these yeah for a
different type of information I don't
take advantage - this seems important oh
it's nineteen plus real word its back
this far so I'll take the 23 Alex yeah
- got 23 for your first row me Alice
absolutely so it was always true like
you've always had - it'd be like if you
learned a language late in life you're
never gonna if they were gonna be direct
even your knowledge of the sky over that
Forgotten Realms
is there's always like a little catch
you always have to sort of fix the
perspective from what you were taught
and your basic knowledge your
fundamental astronomy knowledge is from
another perspective in this ocean hmm
mm-hmm it is not like you're always
doing a simple calculation now it's
painless mm-hmm it's like oh it's a
Billy Oh tech yeah it's a library but
there's always that catch your your
knowledge is not from this fixed
hmm okay so there isn't but it happened
so early the shift happened so early
that its instincts you will know
interesting so what I'm discovering is
that the knowledge that I have of the
stars in the Forgotten Realms is not my
native knowledge correct and it's bit so
you're so intimate with it that until
you had seen it in this diagram
expressed in this cold mathematical way
you wouldn't have picked up that
distinction okay the cold ways are the
best ways I don't think she would share
that just yet with you that doesn't
sound like Rosie does it no that sounds
like something that she would be very
that's it that's a pretty huge
revelation are there any other memories
that are coming up with that that are
associated with that yeah absolutely
let's see oh yeah would be a fun movie a
fun way to do it
that's why don't you give me religion mm
oh my gosh okay I'll take a kayo so you
manage again because I'm dreadful at
religion come on okay sixteen much
better tell me exactly at sixteen tell
me exactly what you're trying to figure
out okay so if my perspective one time
you want a memory yeah like that would
be something that I would I would think
that would trigger oh no I know exactly
what the memory is okay
I know exactly what memory is it there
is a as you as you're as you're looking
at this these diagrams in this book if
the light is very exciting as you're
looking at the diagram in this book and
it's almost for a moment the diagram
also
to take on a kind of depth like almost
that you can reach into okay and there
is like a moment a flash where you're
looking up at your father is so tall so
tall in comparison to you and he is he
has to let you take the tiller hmm and
this feels important because moment is
is buried somewhere special somewhere
safe and as you look off to the left
just right off the right off the port
bow you can see massive ship immense in
length trailing a kind of rainbow dust
in its wake and you are both situated
not in an ocean but in this star sea
does this memory feel genuine to me it
doesn't it seems like some it seems real
okay but this is but you've been invited
into a bizarre
intellectual you and my dad yeah I mean
yeah but that's it you you you can feel
it in your scalp like you don't think
this is pretend and you don't think
you're inheriting it from this context
you think that this is absolute okay and
true what's going on over on the
side-table tanara are you ready to get
to werner has been looking like he is
working and it hasn't done anything in
like an hour
and he's just like shuffling through the
papers and to an outsider it looks like
he was doing something he's kind of like
got a concentrating look on his face but
he's not really well that's gonna come
over and be like
please please do your paperwork like
walnuts sees underneath the very top
sheet the second sheet is like is the
letter that he got from earlier and he
hasn't been rereading that over and over
like a maybe like hiding it a little bit
Oh instead of working this is I can't I
can't write for you maybe I could help
you get write for me I can't understand
right for you we saw what happened last
time I try to write for you it didn't
work when if I not gonna ghost do this
either the pencil and then you just have
maybe we could do that I could try it
yeah you really don't want to do your
own paperwork he's just kind of like
distracted yeah well it goes okay all
right let's try it
so what we had like a name field right
something easy no the name field is no
describe the ghost part okay yeah give
me the whole thing and she's got like a
massive dragon board yeah right claw so
much hands so she takes my little quill
in it puts one hand over his hand and
that feels weirdly intimate so she puts
both hands over it so she can like do
like a planchette like this yeah it
becomes a divinatory act yeah
and so she uses that to try and write
down Blitzen in the name field she
spelled his name wrong and he just now
someone else is doing it for him so he
just checks out the game from the start
it was like when Rosie taught him to
cook and he got mad cuz like now I'm
doing for myself it's like someone's
doing it for me leave your body
a quick load can happen yeah exactly so
his bulk is there and it is substantial
especially against the tiny wooden chair
and the little fold-out desk and the
hand that you're guiding just becomes a
little more slack and then there's just
a rumble through the snout like so I'm
assuming this information I need from
him so I keep having to wake him up you
know what though what you can you can
read it and see okay all right what do I
have to what's the first thing that I
say welcome to form DC to another oh
right right right the very first
question is a multiple-choice question
okay what's it say it says I am and the
first choice is handsome and the second
choice is strong you know one that looks
at deny just drooling yeah she checks
strong really fast
I am confident or respected she says
confident yeah I am skilled or
intelligent skilled she looks for a
third option writing in another body it
goes on like this for several pages then
know that she always picks the least
complimentary mm-hmm oh if when it's
possible when possible when it's
possible so as I said I mean it goes
that just this sort of like Cosmo tear
like Facebook quiz like one Jedi are you
types yeah it goes on for a while
and then you flip one more page and the
next page is completely talk to bottom
indecipherable oh man
you think that it is I mean it's it's
not adrylek you would know mm-hmm
intrinsically like you would you you you
just you look at those symbols and just
know what they mean but isn't even like
a language right oh this is not that you
think it could be some kind of either
ancient or mystical script I say the
symbols themselves seem to resent
somehow being written on a page so I
shake dinar look at this yeah would you
get up and look at this I decide I don't
want to toast Danny looks as papers do I
win the test I go I can't read this last
page can you read it all right all right
I'll save the day again can you read it
all I can read esque
oh there's degrees of reading do you
have Doug funnie fan art on the back of
your character sheets no I was just
doodling okay okay yeah yeah that's kind
of big all right so I read it is it
enjoyed Connick no oh can I read it
no this is clearly this is not this is
not a language that you know hmm and it
may not be a language at all but it is
it seems mystical in origin and there's
places to fill stuff out yeah yeah it
looks it looks like the other documents
oh but it's just another script is is
incomprehensible it's not gibberish like
it's merely regular and routine no it's
a you see of schooner and que Eden Ramos
is thing oh my god he's enchanted he's
begone demon was there
for anything it didn't you missed you
missed a lot you missed a lot of chances
there early on what did you do why isn't
done yet dude hey go I did as much as I
could I can't read this can listen it
wrestled my hand oh sorry
we do have someone that's probably
filled this paperwork out before and
then around and I would not condone
cheating but maybe we consider it under
the circumstances tutoring um do we know
this is Ryan talking do we know what his
was he okay
yeah I told you that well he just said
yeah he just wings it yeah that's how we
communicate he and I Hannah she's
friends didn't infer the girl the
decision estate so yeah Dan I would ask
him yet in the corner yeah
just say what's this page you did this
what does this page mean it these
documents get made 13 the test is never
gonna be the same it's based on the team
the decision works with well then it has
to be something that somebody can read
and it said you shouldn't need any help
so it should be something that you can
read what level decision is did you make
it to best friend yeah this is a
language doesn't look like anything I've
seen before I'm stumped yeah you know
who could help us is knife boy over
there I just look at the knife hangin
it's just like it's just perched there
precariously like he went to avoid you
walk by it to leave like you have to be
careful about this knife yeah it's groin
level right now so together
this knifes are floating don't come over
I say could this could read this hope so
oh yeah cuz he can read anything right
mm-hmm
he can read anything but this is made
for you whenever it takes to not have to
do it myself I think got a solution yes
like I like this ultimate decision is
I'm deciding that someone else to do for
me
delegation should be part of this am i
right okay I'm just wondering what if we
well I was like really trying to figure
out a way to like solve this document
puzzle but then is also just like I get
nothing out of this one that goes up to
the knife and stabs our hand with it
doesn't work you put your hand like
really bad oh man I used I used one of
my oh I can do you need help no I don't
need help I'm perfectly capable of
dealing with this on my own I certainly
don't need the likes of you okay and I
use care once is doing this yeah it's
this is just a normal wound it just
doesn't it doesn't want to intersect so
then I look back it wave my hand in this
face like no holes for this yeah rehan
go check it out I guess you just got to
wait until they come out then we're
gonna save yourself young
face I absolutely not would she do that
in no world that sense brave because you
hear what you hear a you hear a cry
outside like from the crack of the door
your well but like I know I'll come out
of the knife okay this place without
Karissa's noise like which before had
made reading so difficult this becomes a
this becomes a kind of oppressive
mausoleum yeah but you know it's haunted
as fuck you just know like you know in
your heart you know that it is ghost
Ville races okay sing this song does it
feel like his dad you it would require
uh while Rosie is by herself she is
going to snatch this book up secret it
on her first where cuz can't see her
theft mmm
I don't have any like speak with dead or
anything but I guess with him gone I
think she probably believes in that kind
of shit um yeah it's it's all gonna come
down to her personal experience when you
know that a ghost is real ghosts are
impressive indeed yeah thank you up sure
big deal mmm I guess she would she would
speak she'd be like is is there anyone
here it just echoes okay cool just
checking it echoes a couple times and
then it echoes again but the quality
and texture of the voice changes until
it's like a whisper whispering what I
said or is it yes no it starts out like
an echo and then it's something else
does it seem malevolent thoroughly hello
geez
mocking well what you said ah somewhere
in the distance of the room you think
you think it's a book something heavy
thuds okay can I do a like a perception
or investigation or something to see
yeah you can so you can perceive
whatever you like okay I'm gonna try it
huge it's a 1900 yes 19 that's quite
good thank you thank you
hey listen you did a good job kid you're
doing all right yeah I mean you did a
great job great job great job
Terry's googling something scary
scariest ghost afraid to find out I
don't think the whole way - jump scared
yeah so you're just trying to find the
source of it yeah yeah it is it's deep
deep in the racks of the books okay and
it's just a sudden book it's a it's a
thud of some kind okay uh I afraid no
books I am a little afraid of books but
I uh I'm gonna use intimidation this
time and I'm gonna be like listen I've
been on this I think this realm for like
a hundred and twenty years - 20 long
story you can't frighten me you fucking
Sorcerer's waves back there
I'm gonna use intimidation echo I'm old
and I don't care you can see a shape but
you're just you're trying to intimidate
the literal darkness yeah you can see a
shape like a silhouette approaching you
in the in the dim light between these
these shelves that seem to stretch out
farther than you can truly see like you
know you're not sure how vast this
library is but it is not this this is
not the the edited version
this ain't the clean version that's
right um Rosie she's like okay well she
pushes herself out of her chair she's
got her staff she leans on it she's like
just come on you you're you're menacing
me I get it
let's we just skip to the encounter here
it's it's fine attack the darkness I
will exactly the closer you get to the
doorway which is where the true light
that people work in this place in the
individual becomes more and more clear
and eventually she comes to the point
where the light catches up with her full
height and it is moral coalesce she says
you're four feet tall I know two foot
eleven and a half actually good you're
not going to intimidate me that way I
wouldn't have thought I would have had
to what are you doing here I don't even
know why you tried and you're dropping
so somehow it was spooky this is not
your father's library and I think it's
strange that you're here I was an
honored guest of cathuria Stroh and he
just stepped out for a second and he
lets you in he did well Tara Lee why
would I be he's my she's my dear friend
I don't see him here
he's a just outside what's under your
road there oh I gotta buy me dinner
first
[Laughter]
he goes she comes out into the left wait
and then begins to undo some of the
damage that cthe wrists rob has done in
the library I think just you you think
over enough over a long enough period of
time the two of them will redo the
entire library everything will be
exactly on the opposite side it may take
several hundred years but they will
eventually turn this entire place um
Rosie will glance toward the crack in
the door and back it moral and say is
this your father's library yes okay
so just doing some simple math in my
head you and Carissa are related what
did you think was happening hey listen
there's a hole like you not being the
same color and the color being the his
whole situation and I feel like we did
some straight-up
checks with our dice to determine this
not successful sure um so yeah this
comes as a little bit of a surprise to
Rosie
Kate thinks this is quite predictable
but Rosie's uh no Perez is like just
doesn't have any living relatives that
we're aware of so this is very exciting
this is huge am i sensing this
malevolence from her specifically no you
think this place has something
okay um do you can I ask her does she
have that same sort of sense of
foreboding being here
what did describe describe what you're
so I kind of look around everything she
says I'm sorry I uh I was talking shit
to you I really thought you were some
kind of evil ghost because it feels like
an evil ghost lives here do you feel
that what you don't feel it in what way
I mean just like sit with it for a
second you're gonna feel like a ghost
once I bite your throat out
right I'm me wrong just me I'm not
getting a ghost thing mm-hmm okay okay
it's probably because I don't belong
here
and I'm not your dad's kid well although
I may be his grandmother oh yeah just
just there's every possibility now
certainly it would surprise me but um
Rosie will actually attempt to help
Morrel with the chaos and say does Chris
know you're here
I try not to be here when he's here I
feel like you two would have a lot to
talk about
I feel like our conversations would
become very complicated very quickly
yeah you've apparently had conversations
with Chris before uh I don't know I
think you should reconsider that listen
listen okay
at that time when the time is right we
have a neutral meeting place do I need
to keep this secret for you that's my
preference you promise you won't hurt
him I promise wow she really made a meal
out on that one for a while
all right well Rosie believes her no the
two of you make as quick a work as you
can of these meticulously laid out books
of Chris's and you see her she turns
back wants to look at you gives you a
nod
and she disappears into the other side
and then you can see deep in the library
yeah I want to kind of follow her you
can see another green another green
flash mmm okay she's got her own
passageway it's true
it's weird our break are we oh yeah
listen oh sorry I got I got super
distracted you know we were having a
super good time hey shout Council Mayor
Lee receives you
we're gonna go to our break and then
we're gonna come back and have more fun
so those nowhere yeah hello I'm Geoffrey
K Hawkins and this is Tessy teams hey so
when the last we saw our heroes some of
them were hanging out with mysterious
droughts inside of a mental knife but
the other drought that was in the metal
knife has emerged at the request of
walnut dog grass documents her rank two
of acquisitions incorporated now we know
it Josie wait mm-hmm yes what I'm aware
I'm an great time in the knife by the
way why it in there it's nice to have
somebody in there I tried to get in the
knife it doesn't work if you use your
hand no you guys you have to plunge it
in that's an S just can't be an accident
so you don't discover the knife the
study by accident you have to jam it
right into the socket no thank you
see your eyes at this point - do you
coming out just full creepy Highness
yeah I think yeah I think so
I like I'm not just thinking when I come
back out oh yeah like I enter the door
and I have to click just my road
blindfold on yeah for to up to this
point I have for the most part they're
fascinating I'm furious
but fascinated I get it - faceted -
furious what yes so anyway we should do
this in the night for right now feels
really ah there was a time in a place
for the knife
lovely go in later you need to do my
homework for me
yes I've decided they give to do my own
work for me
you keep reeling it in realize this
everything is like decided I've decided
you have to read this I do what I want
all the time yes sir I'll do it for you
so am i oh yeah it's it's tsk well no
it's just famous like there's no there's
no labor involved in it do I recognize
that all the script indeed it's simply a
it's like a magical form of notation but
here it's not being used to contain a
spell it's being used simply as a cipher
but it would be a cipher that couldn't
be read unless you were trained in
specific skills interesting interesting
what a puzzle there is a there is a as
presented there is a blank at the bottom
of the sheet that is awaiting a answer
okay and you can write in the same
hidden script if you'd like so you
should know for podcast listeners and I
had smiling I have if this is smiling
because he you know what he has fun he
has a good time he's always smiling but
happy but I have given sweep I have
given kethry strobe what it says and
I've given to him on a piece of paper
and he is the only one who knows what it
says but it's up to him what he does
with that information oh my what a what
I'm looking at is though it's there it's
full of clever questions that I'm
wondering if you'll be able to answer
them I'm kind of him I'm like wow this
is a pretty pretty important test for
you to take so it's like I got a lot
more respect for you given these these
uh these kinds of things a lot of work
goes into being a decision is yeah more
this is a job but do I recognize what
the script is at all or it's just oh
absolutely
so it's the same thing it's the same
notation you would use to construe
to scroll like you used you would use it
as a magical form of notation but here
it's not imbued with any force it's
simply being used as a cipher okay yeah
hey drow tell me what the hell is on
this paper
no worries Haman are on now here's
another question as I'm looking at it
what's the temperature like in the
hemming and hawing yeah and like a
one-to-one ratio yeah yeah not even say
either yeah it's it's it's krisstraus
new it's a new album from Chris droughts
hem slash ha let's keep it take a second
it's like a double LP so no but my
question is we know that down here
there's one question yes indeed indeed
matter on there to make it look like yes
it's it looks like it is a very
elaborate multiple choice thingamajig
but there really is just a primary field
at the bottom right that is clearly
where the answer is supposed to be laid
my leaky I could I can understand why
you wouldn't be able to read this this
script but don't worry I will dictate it
to denars so you can answer it
appropriately meanwhile Denar what
languages do you speak
that's one of the questions on here
uh-oh
well common draconic and celestial
mm-hmm okay
it's good to know it's important that
you don't speak elvish so I turn to you
here's where this is in common here's
where some of the some of these
characters would have thrown you off and
now in elvish who sent this because it
says hoards person cthe wrist drought
prince dinar Blitzen is rash petulant
and arrogant at
positions incorporated we have available
several decisions of erudition and
even-tempered
considered german goad Ranger of the
spine who sought his lost words person
for two weeks while hunted by dark
dreams do you request another decisions
now back in common and so some of the
characters are slanted this way I see
and then an Elvish no that's great
are we considering this who sent this
why would they say this they refer to
him as Prince so who's at the home
office
what I haven't would I have any idea who
could have added this well you know that
the home office has information on every
like robust information on every member
of the party because every member of the
party applied for a trench right of the
license so in this case this is this is
not secret knowledge yeah no this is
almost certainly the work of the anta T
walnut it's called the secretary n' okay
so nice whom you also know that i say it
came from head office i didn't think it
was that bad i go well he does keep
things from us we know that ah yes just
talk about a friendly smile oh okay
shifts yeah underneath a blanket and he
is she still appears to be asleep but
there is a very clear smile sleeping
over his face
oh my go in elvish I say is this part of
the test who's written to me hmm
turn to dinars what's your favorite
language to speak and put that one right
on this line what I read it to like the
first five words of Mike what's your
favorite language I don't know
I why would they put this in this code
yeah this is weird
that's a weird question the other on Ted
you get a level three test is this a
level three that he's gonna become level
three it's a little - that's amazing
okay I won't get denying asking okay
tonight part in common in common yeah I
say Ansari starts in elvish yes don't
college great I go there's a
satisfaction survey that's a part of
this um how happy are you with your
current team be honest yeah it says it
does be honest and the forms will know
if you're not honest this is for me
I go okay all right well I won't look
but you you write it down how satisfied
you are right here big old six out of
ten and then back into elvish well what
do you think you take it or leave it
I agree think about it and go like five
oh yeah then he's like yeah I'm just so
indecisive any chance we can audition we
can ask them think about that yeah so
and the grammar is wrong I'll correct it
and so that I'm in the same script I
write on it sorry please contact me
directly appreciate that yeah you know
like this page probably isn't even
important the next page looks to be some
kind of
chart some kind of a navigational chart
like that astronomy shortly he would use
to navigate the Seas for example just
purely as a suggestion and but it has it
has marked in several locations by
certain stars there are fields that need
to be filled in it's completely blank
I go dress would you go and retrieve
Rosie and bring her back so that she can
help us with these forms I look sorry I
go we are gonna get these diamonds going
for me here isn't it
[Laughter]
Carissa is like I'm kind of pissed off
at that because why would I be asked to
do the decision is job for him in firing
himself you know I mean like it's not up
to me whether or not we need one
certainly not but I will I'll be back
and I'll come on back in I still have
the book but I still tucked it yeah when
I try to act casual you ready to get to
the end zone Mike I got to do that like
a weird lean on a desk wow so you're
buying a lamp to hide your yeah your
whole body yeah we have uh dinars
filling out his little twos yeah star
chart huh yeah you might want to look at
and and also and also I was entreated by
the document in code whether or not we
want to get rid of dinar like no not
like I mean I don't know that's one way
but I think they just meant let it go
Wow so he's not a pip what they asked me
this directly and I and I and I recount
it to you but with special note to the
that number one this was written to me
and also that it's giving me someone to
consider a ranger of the spine who
sought his his lost hoards person for
two weeks while haunted by dark dreams
why would this confer any truck with me
I don't K is he good or not does that
mean it just means they have a shitty
horse purse they do they need a new one
it sounds like this is a guy who would
come after you if you were in trouble do
you think - nor would I do about and I
certainly wouldn't you know this guy
couldn't find him after two weeks give
up yeah you know get another one yeah
idiot I don't want that that's the
dedication a little bit too far he's
like I would find him that day or no all
right you need to come out and assist
with his train where's my mess I'll deal
with that later it's okay this time
though we'll both exit the night okay
and then you exit and the knife sort of
hovers in the air a moment and then
begins to fall yeah I'll grab it up okay
and return to it its sheath yeah sounds
like you had quite the test so far yeah
welcome to my homework yeah glad you
could make it I'm happy to help really
puts our little grandma glasses nice oh
yeah okay so you're peeking through
these lenses at a slice of the night sky
but it doesn't there's no check even
required like it's it's either comically
it's just it's comically wrong oh okay
um comment
[Music]
so it's it's it's simply not correct and
the only purpose the stars seem to have
for being in this configuration is that
the space between them it is there's
language around the edges of these
constellations okay just all the blank
space is actually the letters are warped
and shifted that they can be read fairly
easily oh okay so for your users I
really mean like a puzzle on the table I
like Denny's for kids really he's the
worst
Oh No some of these configurations yeah
okay mmm interesting interesting
very interesting you know this this
chart does make a lot of sense to me and
one thing that I know is what languages
I speak so that's a lot of send
something to me what you got I do speak
elvish so I'm like like jeez I don't
know what's going on with this test but
I mean being like a little too like like
like familial like in a kind way like
how cuz I'm like cause this poor kid I'm
so sorry
it's like our yeah it's like yeah it's
just this test ah oh my brain so Charlie
wasn't here for the first part she looks
at the three of you and she says no wish
to see speak elvish gladly he starts it
oh yeah I do not deciding there
speaking I get it okay here's what this
says cartographer Rosie bee stinger
eternal child dinar Blitzen chose a
gaudy
ostentatious cart but he could have
chosen something more tasteful and I'll
steer Wow
as a result the cart is recognized on
site by more than 12 criminal
organizations the level of peril
generated by this decision is not known
at this time at acquisitions
incorporated we have several available
decision s consider lawn Firenze a
duelist unmatched in war and inflation
will in love yeah do you request another
decision estas him what he thought of
the team and he only gave it a six out
of ten if that helps you're just Lau and
don't revise that number even one time
well he went down to five and then up to
seven so kind of a wash what's an every
now I look down what is it that still in
seven okay okay start with the seven all
right I don't know I give him a 7 out of
10 - so let's use really fair I mean do
we deserve more than a seven
to be honest no each of us he's he's
what we deserve
he's the torture that we do like Elvis
okay maybe we owe it to him to just ask
he wants to stay with the team yes
however given this pattern I'd say we
have one more interesting thanks to go
[Music]
Rosie takes the chart page and she's
like let me study this I'm gonna get
back to you
is there another webpage ah what this
this page much as the previous one does
require a response in the lower right
okay what are you right I just wrote
I'm contacting me directly oh well talk
on it later uh yes sir no I mean I would
I will want to inquire why are they
doing it this way in in this the same
kind of constellation star chart
iteration anyway she writes we deserve
him blatantly connected the next page
has a place for the document sirs seal
mm-hmm and there is a piece of text that
says in a thousand words or more this
document requires the approval of this
decision Asst for the team it requires a
level to seal and direct advocacy on the
part of the documents in common mm-hmm
I go we got the softballs great
you got the open it I hate the open
ended question got the essay question
so you have to write an essay and I have
to approve it no they said the doctor
answered this page this page is
exclusively for the documentary it's
like it's like that final page of a
legal document yeah um so you have to
write an essay about how great dinars
you're not required to actually write a
thousand that's not working it right no
I assumed I would just give you a little
flowery speech so I look at the these
two and one more time in elvish I say um
I say this is our last chance what do
you say I've made myself painfully clear
clear I need more information I think
we're doing pretty good as is I want to
know why they're they're taking this
roundabout way clearly this is part of
the test we are the decision ists now we
have to put our faith in our decision us
okay but I still stand by my answer they
know if I wrote anything other than I
don't know maybe I look at sooner and I
go all right well I have to write a
considerable amount on your behalf I
want to know something if we were all in
trouble
what would you do you've all been in
trouble a lot okay but what if we die
alien truck killed a lot of stuff kill
everything what if you had to choose
between your team and let's say oak I'd
like to think as part of the team oh my
god oak says this you got it we gotta be
strategic here you got to be strategic
here the whole team are just saying to
the team I mean I think three to one the
whole team what kind of choice like
gonna be hit by a train the trains
impressive indeed
our trains profess my opinion is rapidly
changing all right and I go um I go all
right listen I'm just looking for you to
give me any answer to to entrust you as
a member of this team I killed that boss
you did kill that boss killed a couple
bosses I feel like I don't remember
yeah yeah we couldn't jump that number
up and from one day several so the essay
that I write is extremely begrudging and
it is like the opposite of a compliment
sandwich it is an insult sandwich every
good thing I say about him I say two bad
things I on either side so I say like
he's brash he is strong he's reckless he
chose he has led us into peril plenty of
times with his with his recklessness but
he is very good with a sword like just
keeps going back to like she clearly
respects his skill as like the multiple
choice also revealed that that she
clearly respects his skill in battle but
like anything else absolutely not yeah
so she goes on does that and then he's a
pretty good stepdad oh I do write about
that a coda there is about his parenting
well I mean a thousand words no no I
chose a thousand words are more with
walnut in my home I do say that he's
brave and he seems to be brave and then
the last thing I'll say about him is
that he has grown tremendously and shown
great potential even if he hasn't lived
up to his own potential yet this is like
a third grade report card hurts kind of
teachers like you have a lot of
potential you just apply yourself I do
say that if he would but only apply
would that he reaches his true potential
deny it like no idea how close he came
and I mean just just like complaining
like this is so long it's so dumb is
there a page for oak you wanna get in on
this yeah yeah
yeah and I'll say okay as Rosie said I
suppose we deserve em no thanks
there is a place of course for the
documents for seal she to be applied
hesitate yeah like she like a wax Jambu
seal
yeah so she sit there with the stamp
like waiting and waiting and waiting and
looking up at Rosie and good dress and
res like getting a little I ready a
little extra flame does that wax can
cold when you stamp it below the stamp
in the lower right hand corner is a like
a small arrow pointing to the right okay
flip the page this is a different
document than you have seen okay it is
an application for a wild card license
signed by Denard Blitzen of the ginger
Enclave oh hey dinar look at this we
could be just as cool if not cooler then
team Bellerophon we could have a wild
card license you can give that test
[Music]
doesn't mean yeah I guess just because
they have it we know it's so cool I
don't think we can be as cool as them
but this is pretty cool so you fill it
out yeah see and so are you like engage
so every other to lose video scare but
this was like oh yeah be like them
that's cool
maybe then opal want to be on this team
think of it like that yeah shakes head
vigorously yes there is a gentle knock
on the door to the central room you see
aa special air and she says tonight am i
interrupting and I think she sees this
blanketed man over here she sees this
desk open everyone's standing around she
says I don't I don't want to be it's
nothing I can come back I have to I mean
you could stand around a naked man - we
were just helping him with his homework
her face becomes a singularity at this
suggestion and she says I I really only
if I could have a moment of your time
mr. travel yes she says how where Oh God
she says away from the away from the him
if we could sure devilishly blunt wields
a knife I am just the place just liquid
dying over and over certainly if were I
guess we I'm good on that there's no
other thing that I need to help with the
grammar of the document I don't
okay yeah we drop it this is the last
page Sam a level two or just says we
have a wild card license it said well is
it unclear yeah it's looking good Oh
maybe that's what it takes that's really
funny okay so yeah especially this she
look she seems trouble then she's not
she's a little nervous
hmm
she's all nervous okay well then let's
I'll say yeah sure we can we may speak
do you prefer to do it mind to mind away
from the vibrating membranes did all
these beings possess she says no I think
you I think we could I think we could
talk on the long road and if I could
just have a moment to just on Bunbury
myself oh I understand that I
I have many burdens and I just pack them
into a ball just but it's still a fun
store fun okay yeah so she says yes yes
then let's let yes so we'll follow
alright we'll go out and if it's it is
afternoon I will Don my Sun Hat
absolutely so you're looking great
you're angry should have like a like a
sunglasses TV to add to it cuz it's a
Sun Hat plus point but you it's gonna be
it's gonna be like some kind of piece of
alchemical gear it's gonna be some like
steampunk yeah that makes some kind of
Doug dual lens type thing where you got
the different you know I mean in this
realm so yeah customers will ask
auspicious well we're walking is it too
much just the eyes and the Hat did you
have that no told is not on she she
doesn't seem disturbed by it okay
there's a good time yeah no no she she
says I like that and she she makes sure
that it is adjusted for maximum pull
critique oh yeah like though that the
rakish mhm
tilt yeah absolutely as you were as you
were walking out she's she's still quiet
as you leave the front door profit is
back she has now begun to draw out
ladles of jam to store and you know you
know you can just feel it you can feel
it arriving in the in the same way that
Phil Collins would detect something in
the air of the night mmm
even here in this this afternoon coming
back you know that last stones day is
near mmm you know that she is prepping
hardcore for the return the triumphant
return of the cornerstone yeah maybe
this this time she's gonna be in town
it's gonna happen
so as you I see as you walk out your
boot steps on a piece of paper that is
in sort of a wagon rut in the ground
it's a it's a strange it's like a it's a
little woodcut print almost and you can
see there's an old man like sitting up
in a coffin and it's full of the text of
the very bottom says bury me with my
cornerstones and the coffin itself is
just stuffed with cornerstones and this
ancient decrepit man is there dwelling
within a messaging yeah inside that
inside the wood auspicious as you begin
to walk out you make that that right
turn out on to the long road you can see
well vers boys working hard out in the
yard wagons coming in for repair leaving
some leaving directly south down to
water deep perhaps an auspicious says
when i was when i was the property of
that creature
I had another life that wasn't mine but
I had glimpses of what this other
auspicious did but I have never been in
love and I've never kissed anyone and I
don't know what to do right yeah yeah
she said she says pouty lips she says
that you know Denar that like I can't I
don't know if it's a beak I can't I
don't I don't see how he could provide
me with any useful information on this I
I don't I think that walnut is already
in love with someone and Rosie I'm not
sure what she knows about this sort of
thing it's not me it's a special only
and she says here she says the your
hundreds of years old I mean you must
have many conquests in this was terrible
reader than this creature of the mouth
yes but largely non romantic food you
know jesting things I try to remember if
Catherine would have would remember a
first kiss or would it have happened
after he has already shut all that down
and just decided yeah it's not that
important yes this is just the sort of
thing we're trying to figure out right
now hmm
because I imagine that's exactly wolf
Lee
I would say let's see and yet because
this is aware that auspicious is trying
to get this sensitive information how
old is she but she is like her brother
omen
she is a half-elf and she is you would
guess it's difficult with that race to
peg it exactly but you think that she
may be about 37 38 mm-hmm so I mean
because it was I just asked was just
being how old are you just this is 38 I
haven't got a problem she said I didn't
live most of it I understand that I I
too spent my childhood in a life of
someone else's making and I didn't go
down the road you are interested in no
no no I I find these these mortal things
useful certainly but only in that they
allow us to exist on this plane and
extract knowledge from it hmm do you
understand
let's see how how would he approach it
um well she says she says I I've met
someone but I have so many misgivings
and I don't I don't know if I have them
because you would say because my
apparatus was faulty I don't know if you
I don't know if I just can't tell
I don't know if I know enough about it
where you and I do who do have a an
intersection not of the mouth but of of
experience is that we'll stumble in the
dark and that is our function
you can't shy from these questions you
have to answer them are they worth it to
you to answer they can be terrifying
this is good she reaches up and puts her
left hand around your neck and tries to
encounter you in a kiss way see what
concerns a reaction would be well first
of all would be to stop it but what
would be the polite thing it would be
exactly we stumble in the dark and we
have no idea what we're doing but you
just gotta get back on that horse
and figure something else out she says
yes horses yes and she was not with a
hole she looks down yes a horse yeah
doesn't have to be with a horse but I
don't know she she sees a she is
desperately trying to not have a
conversation anymore at this point oh
wait she is she is she's looked down and
there's another dirty piece of paper
that sort of crumpled up in the and
she's like deciding that that is what
her universe is gonna be about right now
and not this she's gonna focus on this
down here Catherine will say this will
break that awkward silence and this will
remove some of this thing of what you
think
it's this this woodcut shows a child
whose face and hands are covered in muck
and then there's a savaged cornerstone
on a plate in front of them and then the
text below says mom I broke it like
family so I try to reroute in fact I
just just says that let me reroute who
is this person that you've met that just
opened up these curiosities there's a
there's a pause while she tries to get
this mental tract this mental car back
on the track and she says I think he's I
think he's only in town for a round last
stones day I think he's he's just here
to to work for the time being but I
don't know it's just something about him
a handsome handsome boy capable man so
you know like gee I ain't neva yeah
exactly
freezin you've now made the right turn
at the other portion of the long road
and are now coming back around the sort
of Halfmoon curve that comes back to
that comes back to the drawing courtier
off to your left you can see Rosie's
lighthouse the orphanage that she
operates full to bursting with youths
you can see a just a couple buildings
away you can see a very strange very
strange construction it seems to be a
house built around a tree or maybe the
tree was there to begin with
and the house itself has sort of lifted
up and grown with the tree so now it's
several
feet off the ground and there is a kind
of staircase that goes up to it but the
windows themselves are either boarded
broken or a tangle of filthy fabric
sounds like a real estate upper yeah
exactly
as your as you continue farther down Oh
Josh thank you very much it's good today
as as you're walking down toward the
drawn-in quarter you can see you see
another piece of paper that you you'd
sort of cling to like a buoy in this
bizarre social scenario you've been
introduced to and it just has a
dilapidated soaked mush of a corner
stone and on top it just says still and
there's a question mark over it and it's
like that's the guy from - Illustrated
scary stories - do ads yeah exactly
and then as you as you and auspicious
are coming down to the drawn and quarter
about maybe 20 feet away
you see auspicious disengages entirely
from the conversation and she runs from
you to a man who is standing in front of
the drawn courtier looking that he is
he's looking with some interest at the
acquisitions incorporated sign that is
dangling off making some adjustments but
when he sees when he sees icefish I run
toward him he breaks into a smile takes
a few steps over to her and folds her
and embrace thank you very much Josh hmm
is this that same rough night
we saw her with her there no no no she
says omen oh I didn't know you were
coming and he says I wasn't coming I got
a very very important message and I had
to stop doing the other things that I
was doing and I had to come here instead
and he's and he says he says but it's
worth it
I mean kisses her on the forehead and he
pushes the door aside and walks in and
says mother and prophet says oh it comes
out there's nothing there is no part of
the lieutenant here at all mm-hmm this
is this is the let's put it this way the
jamb is in grave danger so she comes out
and collapses on him and then he he is
trying to move and adjust them both but
auspicious is also on the back mm-hmm so
now there's a sort of tripartite
organism that is slowly shimmying
through here he says you you can't it's
it's gonna scald mom you have to you
can't leave it in there we're expecting
very people do you have a brand here and
you have to maintain it
Oh everybody everybody's talking about
it to him in water deep mom it's like
after last year there is a business he's
like a food sorcerer he came back with a
big review dinar featured prominently so
you better make sure that he's on staff
because there's gonna be a lot of water
deeper there's gonna be a lot of water
davian's slumming it up here and you got
to ring these bastards out for all
they're worth and that means having
dinar
dancing around outfit doing whatever
he's gonna do that's a big part of the
brand now you got it you gotta take
advantage of this mom does walnut he
Romans voice from upstairs she went
perception why me my passive perception
is 17 dude it pretty good my game 14
it's pretty good you definitely
definitely hear someone you hear what
sounds like it might even be some kind
of a fight or something oh man I got you
here you hear profit and auspicious both
oh my god pitching in at whoever is down
there with them I look at Rosie and I
give you like the two taps on the side
may go let's go I burst out onto the
like the loft area that looks down on
the yeah so right now they are all this
is perfect cuz they're all in the
kitchen they're not actually visible
from yeah okay I jump up on the railing
next to you and I pose I go I thought I
heard something
they got it just outside the threshold
of the kitchen so yeah yeah I smell
burning Jam no no they were able to get
in time it's just sweet
it's just a perfume so that's good it's
like I love the smell strawberries don't
you well know and it's just as soon as
hot it's like as soon as the as soon as
the cool breeze started to come in like
it's still warm in here from the kitchen
can we tell that the commotion is in the
kitchen now oh definitely
all right definitely let's go and so we
hustle into the kitchen ready to help
proper in whatever way yeah we're both
like ready legged I got like my sword
half out yeah yeah what are you doing
yes why ominous like he's down this is
all in character by the way oh man hey
omen omen drawn doctor rank - yes that's
me if I recall that's my name that you
said
you did sign it I have that laminated in
my room
she can't look at him she's looking at
the floor she's looking at the ceiling
I've never seen well not like this
before
especially not around a man yeah so Rose
is like are you okay yeah of course I'm
okay
uh-huh yes omen says I can take receipt
of the wild card license document while
I'm here oh yeah I assumed that you
would come for our nude God
oh that's all so happy that's also
happening Oh Rosie no woman have met
there's like a secret no exactly it's
just this wine is staring daggers omen
omen coming says shall we yeah yes
absolutely this way weird very strange
that he says did he give you any trouble
the trouble that led us to the Underdark
yes but other than that absolutely not
and we were totally capable of handling
it it was right upstairs he was a baby
for a long time and then that stayed
incredibly manageable
he says you're aware by now that he's
not a hundred percent moral like a
sister
yeah he blew that one why don't ya yeah
good do you know that as you're walking
up he's like you can stab I mean he
wouldn't be any worse
one thinks about it for a second and
then she goes this isn't a test one she
likes she looks it over for the first
time um and she goes I wouldn't dirty my
blade with his blood he's like your he
says you're in the minority do you guys
say yeah thank you
you used my dad this wasn't upset no we
work we work together before you
contacted other plane and went mad right
right right he never ate that yeah I
mean I do remember that yeah because
that said that was after that yeah the
only thing I remember the only thing
that had been unexplored was was me
apparently turning downforce great to
work with packing its dad which one was
better who could say some people are
able to work on both wink wink wink he
follows you up into the room and oak is
there in the corner hmm oh man just
grabs a blanket throws it off the other
side of the room what they never left
you guys clamoring out yeah then you
just sat there still just reading his
letter again going yeah okay morning
wake up and they keep looked over your
shoulder and he says your highness deny
doesn't know who omen is that's true but
he knows what you are
he's never met omen yeah you know sermon
is in name yeah I told he's been on
documents but he's never seen him before
right
so he goes random dude it goes it goes
what just elvish an omen goes over
stands over by oak
and says I have so many questions and I
have so many techniques Walla claps
smooth stone and rubs it between his
thumb and forefinger and whispers
something into it and you hear like a
and then the door pops open prophecies
don't you leave don't you leave before
saying goodbye and have dark magic fix
my door and omen says I'll be back I'll
be back soon didn't you think you'll see
and a portal opens up below this below
the two of them and they drop through
and its shadow council merrily mercies
you hey we are gonna go and we're gonna
use facilities we're gonna take full
advantage of them and then we're gonna
come back and we're gonna do some table
talk know you're in the bounce right
yeah I've got to go say see ladies a
club she's gonna see you today she's
gonna see Les Miserable that's so fun I
know right
so if she if she disappears that's why
that's what happens it's okay
she's fine she's watching a play it's
fine hey don't go anywhere
come on
you