time is the enemy of the past it
threatens the fastest weapon you
wouldn't make it past a second and
answer the question
play it brash and reckless to choose a
cautious solution you saw was prudent in
any sepulcher poker - don't become the
putrid it's that well-fed I pursue in no
mountain too steep for dungeon too deep
to send expendable marks up to the top
of the peak of beneath they see Yugi
they come like sharks to it while I swim
in that money build like Carl Barks
through it so send your national parks
drew it I'll send him home in a natural
box with a close tie the most of the
parts included save your breath for a
cleric confessor death is a lesson that
life is attending professor but if
you're seeking my official advice sign
on the dotted line and this should the
choice no no I am a minister withdrawn
CEO of acquisitions incorporated let's
see who else might I'm also Tycho Brahe
hey pancake tax slippery bill my name on
websites for many but today are you
hoping this and I'm here to run a game
of Dungeons and Dragons
for my friends in this revitalized
second part of the season thingamajig
those packs indeed indeed I'm bringing
Reva grated reinvigorated and it's
allowed me to create incredible new
words no yes that's a good to my right
Dragonborn narcissist dinar would say to
the right of my right reppin the natural
world while not dog grass yeah I won one
chicken nice for what there early to my
left
emerging is no it that's not it is it
are you we're off to a great start
except for those very case
from your grandma's grandma I'm working
for yours Rama dismissed shroud whoa
where she is
your your grandma's grandma Rosie be
sorry
it's sublimated that's incredible it
went from a solid to a gas second one
step to the left of my left emerging is
though from a mr. out cthe wrist Rao
butts his just route everybody whoa good
to meet you whoa great to meet it's so
there's another earth yeah yeah no no
yeah it's the sequel listen
it's never as good as the original now
gathered throng friends near and far
gathered in some local places I
understand oh yeah with fellow members
of the shadow Council City of Angels
indeed mayor livers please you the
second season we begin with the party
outside the drawn-in port and it is a
raging party there are lights there is
music there are special guests slippery
bill no no it's like the whole poster
goes on the denim is it it's like it's
slippery bill in like big like bubble
type letters but no no you have returned
there you are welcome to ask any
questions that you might have about
resolving any of those other things but
we are moving forward you're hurtling
forward in time but you're welcome to
remember any of those things and I will
give you information about what might
have happened this is a second part of
season two by the ways you have to
address the nomenclature yeah yeah how
long did it take us that it takes a long
time to go from place to place easy with
the magic spell it still takes about the
same amount of time oh it was
about three weeks her time had elapsed
oh how touching was my goodbye with
young tasteful young tasteful had no
words when you spoke to him
great well he had taken up a kind of he
had clearly taken up a kind of a leading
role he was gathering people up like
lifting them up off the ground the
entire process of the transformation was
large and before the party left to move
on their way back to the surface
you saw him help Carver Gaul to his feet
as well wow he really rose above his
station more on that note not anymore
what the hell we want to know what's
with this new race of green elves I
don't know it'll be it'll be very very
interesting to see we know what their
abilities and statistics are do we bring
it when the book is released I'm always
doing shit those in ours level 8 come on
three weeks down there three weeks he
gained a level
he gained level eight and then he was
attacked by gas but now guests not
guests from the current edition of the
game previous guests oh gee guests know
you have to get somebody to drag your
corpse back to you slash chords me this
is this baby wizard shit
this is this baby wizard who dropped out
of college because she was addicted to
EverQuest one what's the corpse Ren
would you love it
would you like me to incorporate corpse
runs in the game
Oh No thank you though you done did it
you didn't do it sir are there any other
how did how did gall yeah like so right
after incredibly poorly so your these
men your these soldiers of yours these
goblins are now gentle tall green they
bear no trace of hatred toward him
indeed they seem to pity him in a way
you think they'd carve our goal is
probably not a hundred percent cool with
it
hmm well you feel like there's been an
inversion here that he was not 100
percent planning for and maybe wouldn't
have maybe would have done things
differently
we've all had setbacks I'm I'm sure that
pitcher has had some kind words of
encouragement one of these like a
friendly cup refrain isn't a moist arm
yeah it reverberates throughout the rest
of his cephalopod flash' for that calm
at the head Jupiter we shouldn't tell
what he's made up we don't know yeah hmm
study this what else is there and we
traveled so were there events or travel
or was it all told through in order to
know the the you know the venture some
facts we would have we would have to
talk to Rosie okay would have to know
what Rosie story was in but but it
doesn't every weeks of speech I think
and there's no and there's no bare naked
ladies at the table that's now you tell
me
yeah year to you tell you this there's
no B&amp;B
Wow that's a it's a great day change
into some other out the game too long to
give you a really good story here Wow
I suspect I suspect that that would
probably be on point for Rosie
after the harrowing adventures of the
Underdark it would not surprise me if
this story she told were sure pretty
simple
okay it's like then we got something to
eat real thirsty
yeah I think she's like okay so she said
she's she's patent coriander but like on
a part the coriander doesn't usually
like to get like the knees just fatten
amazing and she's like yep so we get out
of the Underdark
um looks at Walnut she's like walnuts
they're done are is asleep the whole
time one time he wakes up anyone cries
he cries he crisis we're not there yet
back to sleep
this is absolutely a a hundred percent
normal the whole time which was weird it
was really wicked got it all out of my
system I did investigate the mystery of
what's wrong right with cthis he's like
what he was too cool nothing sorry about
that everybody now I'm gonna eat some
bones one thing that we that didn't
happen is that I didn't die anymore on
the trip home not even one time I'm like
yesterday hmm rough day for me it's a
nice switch yeah there's a nice switch
yeah you and your companions with a
light pop like a goldfish kiss just like
oh it's not are in the the cobbled
street outside
drawn and quarter there if you can see
there are a few a few couples at tables
night is sitting in over here I got so
excited when I thought that was a
chocolate it's no I saw the top of the
box come off and I was like mom your
tits man I bet I bet I could get one of
those a little matter like what
chocolates that's seen that's on brand
though with the the grant less where
yeah the cookie tin that's yeah I'm like
oh the symbols and stuff like a little
cookies it was like you know those like
things that look like peppermint candies
but they're they're like spun spun sugar
and all grandmas have them and they're
just know they're not great glass candy
they're just awful it's not the best are
you gonna you're gonna do some what at
the table are you biting my steez at the
table hood sir just you I want to make
sure the document see oh I want to make
sure that absolutely everybody knows
what is happening here so Kate has
gotten a candle and she is now going to
drip wax yeah undersell you actually
want to cause a scene with this can you
continue your candle and no your camera
too you know you're doing this to shit
don't worry about I meant to do this
before the show but it's important that
I gonna be done during game yeah okay
it's do it in the icebox no so so we
exactly so you evening so you see
exactly so you took so grandmother night
is taking a brief opportunity to do some
stationary yeah
she's writing letters a lot of kids have
written to her they're all they all want
money or favors or something some kind
of horseshit that she's she's taking
care of business and one of the letters
she's so rosy is in the custom of
checking the mail before anybody else
gets up one because she doesn't want
anyone to find her mail
it's private doesn't have anything to do
with our business here so nobody's
allowed to read it but also she does
open other people's mail
and read it real quick it's driving a
wedge in the relationship you know she
does that's a passive ability for
walnuts there's no role she knows and
she hasn't brought it up you start to be
like where do you open that conversation
one of the letters they got a lot of
letters say and unusually for the mail
is one that that isn't opened but she
holds it up or sorry it isn't opened and
it's it's not addressed she holds it up
to the light and she waits until dinar
has come down for the morning so long
wait long wait I'm like Jeff it's 1:30
let's do this kid dinar it when when you
come down Rosie makes a point of picking
it back up again and going to dinar
are you expecting mail fan mail what
that could be not uncommon that could be
what this is I know it's a freshly
sealed it's it's it's all melty is that
it came like that so it's northern wax
no I wash and break this beautiful seal
rosie has read this letter uh yeah just
fan mail oh that's nice
yes that's pretty neat I mean we hold it
for like a better part of 90 minutes I
was just wondering what it was
interesting I mean it's none of our
business but if you wanted to to share
it he looks over his shoulder whose
Shield of my souls that's what my fans
call me take it away
DARS is Denar like open to us peeking
over oh yeah I think that he's actually
definitely like just reading it yeah
yeah oh just like talking to it like
reading it to himself yeah
what is it what does it say no yeah so
Denari is saying that this is a fan
letter but he will read it to himself
out loud and then everyone hears it hmm
yeah you're looking at your shoulder
shield of my soul the winters are cold
and spring barren I'm sorry this is I'm
bad at reading handwriting without the
light of your Sun that it that it is
painful for you as well as somehow a
comfort forgive me many nights the
shackles of doubt tighten evermore a
sound in the distance the imagining of
your voice and the wish of you walking
through the door leaves me destroyed but
I've grown stronger every day I think to
weather the storm of your absence the
only promise I wish for you to keep is
that you return to me safely my beloved
for it was a worthy man it will left my
side and the dream that we still that he
that we still have lies in our love as
strong as you live come back to me CP
see I think it's that CD CD I think it's
a d they're pretty sure I wouldn't know
but mm-hmm
I got a lot of fans yeah very uh you
know excitable fans yeah sounds like ya
know better they do love what his
exploit what's not to love for him CD
whose CD I don't know wow maybe it was
for you walnut you're getting it too
walnut I think that's for her now huh
so sing it has been quite a while Oh
copper Dragon
I got it perfectly available for every
yes and wait yeah we did all hear that
did I audibly shot it or did I get
audibly shout I forgot but as I as I
said it has been a while since you have
been back in the homie front room of the
drunk courtier prophesies a little mad
about something that's that's one piece
there's a few new faces here in the here
in the front room how does prophet
express her anger she looks more like a
mad statue than usual okay
hmm so like rather than just being like
uh now she's like she's trying to she's
clearly trying to focus this tension
into the drying tasks you feel confident
that this that this cup is dry and
perhaps has been for well it may not
have ever been with there'd be no way to
tell so I wanna uh I wanted to ask her
if there was any mail so I walked up to
her and just kind of nonchalantly the
prophet after prophet I get halfway
through ask me if there's any mail and
then I'm just kind of really nervous
I go um is everything okay here
she uh she is looking at you but you can
see that her eyes are constantly
flicking out into the into the front
room and then looking back like so fast
that she thinks it's subtle I look what
it's like plainly it is it is like
trying to wave down a passing airplane
levels of obvious I want to do that
thing where I look behind me like do I
see you
is there anything going on back there is
she just looking green oh no you see
what seems to be a young couple okay
and do I know do I know them you have
you have not seen the boy before but
such creatures often pass your notice
here in town and elsewhere okay hard
pass generally speaking gotcha
not for me but exactly but the young
woman with like sort of like tight
cropped like blonde curly hair um sort
of like seems to be able to feel your
gaze mm-hmm like on the dishonor on the
hunt the back of her neck and she turns
and you think it's auspicious Oh I later
you have to do some mental calculations
to get there but you think that this
might be auspicious so I immediately go
oh slam my elbow down and cover my face
and then I pointed rosy and itís Koch
was he there in a microsecond turns
around she sees you maybe I knew wave
her over and then she sees prophet and
then she stands up like like squeaking
Lee heavy squeak from the chair every
every social circuit in the entire place
is just shattered and then she walks up
to you and says welcome to the drawing
courtier how may we be and preface it
you're late they were she was here
already huh when people come in then you
say it you don't see it after they've
already been here and I want just goes
oh no no we're fine we're you know she
says yes I think you may be fine thank
I'm fine too auspiciousness okay and
then sits back down scoots in big squeak
okay I go mm-hmm soon as they're out of
your shop I'm like is that is that her
how do I put this delicately paramour
she's really happy it's the big word
yeah syllables um Rosie uses her keen
knock like laser vision to ascertain the
relationship it's like it's like it's
like the romance version of like an
assassin's creed I think she's like yep
exactly was good I'd say they've been
together for two weeks
Sherlock stuff yeah yeah yeah hasn't
gotten serious yet but I don't approve
of him okay
know that the hands are perilously close
mm-hmm
I'm on top of this table like perilously
close like you can hear you can hear
just on the channel that all mothers
have huh
you can hear the klaxon beginning to
sound dude uh youth do you think that
you think he may be new I mean it's a
red larch as it is a town whose
population has a it has a core there's a
like a robust strong core of people who
offer services going north and south in
the long road the c-team of course is
included in this number stalwarts but
especially with spring coming around
there's a lot of new types of labor
there's been talk about maybe things
starting back up in the quarry obviously
this is a good time for you know getting
seed in does he look like a labored
house addressed yes okay yeah yeah yeah
scruffy roughneck kind of dude
definitely okay rough like rough hands
okay dirty nails this could be part of
the problem he's okay
so with a good scrubbing you think there
may be you think there may be cleanup
opportunities here how what is
was in his eyes as he gazes Alice fish'
is he smitten there you he spends as
much time looking up at profit as
professed bends over there it's like
there's like a parallel channel of data
happening on this other band here um but
you were so you were so bewitched by the
CD letter haha
there is also there is also a job huh in
the customary in the customary place
sealed indeed with the delivery of
acquisitions waiting before she died I
feel what I feel no I'm seeing as she's
always out there she's always up there
grabbing it usually she hands it over oh
no I was gonna say may I interject that
yeah if you've done looking at the
mailbag that I've been filtering through
it just yeah I mean you don't always get
mail and that's fine you don't always
have to get mail when mail comes so
sometimes you get it and then other
times there's no mail for you which is
not a I mean I mean who's who's upset
she she finds she goes through the
quests hold on don't give me that look
she goes through the quests she avoids
them she doesn't even touch them she's
going for the personal information
that's all right for like those handmade
envelopes so it's like crayons olives
and shit we're happy about wedding
invites had that kind of stuff this
isn't something the awesome this like
she wants to do like junk mail exactly
this junk mail plant pamphlet shit that
we get from HQ my mail coupons resident
that's me they're writing me back
finally okay yeah
say doing this talk about getting a new
roof yeah whenever you go look every
time this has been consistent when
walnut goes to look requests yes there
and there untouched or at least this
here untouched yeah I feel like that
would be a very I'd love to adjudicate
that um hello timely reception is
reality see if you could tell if they
well no no III don't think you I think
that you're being legit I don't think
that you would actually I feel like your
relationship with walnut is such that no
I don't peak the quests yeah that's a
good side listen I want to continue to
run this campaign in a spirit of mutual
cooperation right right we have
boundaries but anyway I do I'm like you
know I didn't I do think I saw a um a
quest but I didn't I did very carefully
and there was there was a official
material oh no other stuff done for you
and then quest the correspond and then
your mail of course not in there okay
well why don't you come over here and
read this official mail with me because
it you know it's the words person you
should probably look at this
I look at roasting dinner like it's just
convincing it all yes I should keep
doing it as the horse person you should
totally read this with me agree I was
wondering when I had to get included in
this process wonderful so technically as
an asset I go to open it up well here
here and I'm like don't I'm sorry I know
that you don't touch it so so you're you
are a little disturbed even at the
outset
oh no so the red wax seals yeah that are
utilized on official correspondence are
manufactured in such a way that that wax
ages rapidly okay it's a way it's just a
way of shorthand indicating how long the
job has been um sealed oh no
this is jet black so you don't know
exactly how long it has waited in you
don't know how exactly how long this job
has been here because the job at the
Underdark task was not an official job
as true there'd be no reason to believe
that you were not available for this
task and so jobs were routed to the
worst case it could be a three-week-old
job that's shut up the second we left
yeah yeah okay could just be a day and
they're just unreasonable know what
they're expecting us we did complete one
of our quests I have on my open quest
log let's put a new one in all right
what do you got moldy quest here it says
the village of promise requests aid
bandits will return in one month's time
speak to Maeve Perry as the thrust one
thousand silver pieces so that's another
that's another indication that something
is strange that's rough about this
particular job generally speaking people
do not offer the tasks in silver but you
do notice something in the lower right
hand corner it's a it almost smells a
little bit of a smoke like a campfire
type smell and you can see a tiny
handprint almost like seared into the
lower right hand corner
a tiny yeah how timing a child's okay I
was like a mouse no dude listen Mouse
quest I want to run this adventure so
you make a note and then we're gonna
make it happen you're gonna get a job
from a mouse fantastic thank you um
where did say did they say location it
said the village of promise oh right
okay so you might be you might want to
ask around about that but that is the
that is the task that they have offered
when they say one month's time that
be in about four days okay do you don't
have it on any maps but you do think you
know where it is I don't have it on any
maps but I do think I know where it is
it's uncanny yeah so yeah yeah should
the old lady still got it so what you
what you know is that the hills to the
east of red larch east and north what
I've been called the sambar Hills before
you found the roost of the wandering
crypt there one time but these hills and
there's many stories about them and the
people that live there but there is
something of a like a Gold Rush
happening there right now so there are
actually many very young towns being
founded in this place because securing
securing precious metals from just
blatantly clear easily accessible veins
like the mining out here is quite good
to the extent that even small groups of
civilians can set up an operation and
succeed there and so village of promise
is one of these such indeed yes the
promise is just the name of it but
there's a even though there wasn't much
of an East Road out of red larch for a
long time especially as work in the
quarry began to settle but there is just
through raw use there is starting to
become an Eastern passage out of town
that is it going it's going it's
basically goes east out of the town and
then moves up into these these massive
hills okay might consult the actual map
that I drew
now I consulted this map just earlier
today I got some I got some value out of
it yes but this it's not a it is this is
not a human hand
okay down in this corner six fingers
it's it is a Dragonborn handprint but
it's it's tiny oh but it's small oh oh
my goodness no and what's the name of
that of The Enquirer again uh yeah they
refer to themselves as Maeve Perry's the
thrust hmm
I'm Harry sorry is any of this ring a
bell to me me no yes you can to give any
reason why it would in particular okay
but that that handprint is a pretty
strong indication I mean do I recognize
the handprints but not exactly but the
size is right there um and if you
thought for certain that she had begun
to express some even as a very young
child express some affinity for magic Oh
whether it's the kind that can be
trained via study the kind that isn't is
just an inherence e of a talented
charismatic individual that's not clear
but there were definitely signs that
there was a this was a child of destiny
in the mystic arts and for her all right
so what's she doing in the village of
promise send a message on some magic
school I don't know
wouldn't when walnuts reading it out
loud say thousand silver dinars like get
out of bed for less than ten gold pieces
that's my job huh I say we don't take it
and then in saying and then he sees a
little handprint he goes Oh immediately
we actually do have to be because this
seal was red when we got it and now it's
black and she starts getting very choked
overs like this is official we really
need to do this job is it does it mean
the car changing it means that it's been
here for a very long time I can't tell
you how long but probably the whole time
we've been gone and I just after our
whole thing was accidentally going to
the Underdark and messing up that
nice trash trash which that woman sent
us I just I just need I need a win
killing we asked about the village of
promise and the old guys like Oh seems
joy the shattered trail
[Laughter]
so is this the the larch path that we're
taking indeed well let me take a look
here your ding-dong she's up there
anything to that
yeah it's removing out in December Hills
exactly right okay well that sounds like
just a short jaunt yeah yeah you you
think they didn't probably take you you
probably take you about a day to pull
into this okay to roll up to promise if
it's where you think it is it's worth
going hmm it's almost over is what did I
said before yeah worth going
I hope then when she sees the hand okay
so I'm saying we should definitely do
this and this is not like yes it sounds
like a decision is oh it sounds like
three to two yeah sure get in the car no
mail single tear yeah that's the
enunciation of no mail the legardie goes
no mess some no uh all right I'm ready
I mean if there's doesn't sound like
there's uh if it's a day away yeah
how much prep do we need to do couple
bandits easy house itself anything
Oh can I go grab a potion from upstairs
yeah absolutely
um yeah so I'm assuming my old ones have
just gone sour by now oh yeah it's just
it's all vinegar
after a while it's just to be uniform
tang all right so let's grab gastric
there it is let's grab a new one so I
when it's thick and rich yes so for
those who don't remember I have a trophy
upstairs that makes potions but I don't
know what the potion is did you get the
trophy oh by winning wizard cart all
right bye-bye me walnut being the best
at wizard yeah this is amazing yeah
absolutely
that was like an else world going on it
pours out a slate christen a slate gray
with notes of blackcurrant oh cool you
know what I'm gonna do for once uh since
we're in a hurry
well it looks at it thinks about
inspecting it more and goes nope and
just puts it in your bag will this have
that one for later we'll figure it out
um it means time Rosie is packing its
next Reds next day yeah and also
muttering to prophets about this
roughneck loser who is wooing auspicious
Roughnecks don't check the law and abide
no you don't um and because I think they
both have a similar insane yes it's like
he's just he's just rolling through town
he's no good for her here I don't know
what his motivations or do you see how
close their hands yeah she's like is he
is he gonna be here in 3 months that's
the question packing packing this basket
she's not he's not a good investments
not emotionally or financially frankly
classist just saying I was gonna spend
her heart or mine making that boy smile
and she's not worth it either owns Rosie
Rosie was doing this partially yes -
yeah and proper lighten up the exam
emesis know I can have us fish it
pack the cart thank you don't it's not a
problem obviously yeah I guess she's
kind of busy now anyway
yeah well hmm you know what you know
what though Bravo she's a smart girl she
reaches underneath the bar and just
pulls out a little cornerstone yeah she
has for herself just eats a quarter of
it and then just puts it back down their
desks off her hands treat yourself
she's just choose she choose and it
looks like it's little it looks like
it's been filmed it's like that 120
frames super slo-mo camera it's just
like it's an impossible shoots like it's
like everybody it's like 20 minutes per
bite and then as we leave I'd like like
to I'm carrying my cute little grandma
basket full of snacks there's like that
gets there's some beef jerky
oh nice like a cloth wrapped bottle
filled with her house she does she does
have some and as she as she goes out the
door to go get to the current she stops
by the table with the couple and she
says to the boy the hands just like
skitter away from each other like
they're like like crawdads that a
flashlight has been shined on there's
backwards as well she goes hello ice
fishing deer and this looks at the boy
she goes here's some friendly advice at
least take a bath she's trying to trying
to do him a favor
but if he's trying to win points with
prava you got to start clean the boy
gotta be auspicious
covers her mouth and laughs that rosy
heads onto the card just a shrug yeah
from today's wastrels yeah just there
just literally take one bath it's
disgusting
that's what it is no out here you can
see coriander lockdown pretty good Oh
after a substantial period of of ill use
of course come my my coin purse right
here how many how many is she take
what's the damage it takes 15 before
she's done oh you Mamma Mia
alright afford to get back we're doing
okay again but if she needs see you 30
gold we're gonna get regular a certain
point nice of you to say but as a bear
yeah let's just kill three parts oh yeah
no I didn't say killer
oh I didn't say killer you're thinking
about it yeah you thought it yeah your
mouth didn't say it but I thought it
your eyes did she's expensive what am i
icing right now you agree alright so we
do DM how do we do this I guess we all
kind of line up around her neck just
take swings is his horse killing
impressive you know is killing a metal
horse impressive and DMK gonna roll this
is a cool horse though yeah an ordinary
or no no so you haven't even after the
15 she wants to sort of like stuff her
her steel face like she's down into that
that laffy bag and the raphe bag yes
rajala of the bag is beginning to resist
it sort of withdraws itself very hungry
Golding avarice is not an attractive
quality
yeah think about it making up a lot of
yourself but each of these each of these
plates slides into majestic position she
has a new glint in her eye
a golden gleam and she is 100% a plus
ready to listen to her grandma okay um I
give Denard the bag of snacks and hop up
in the driver seat I say don't eat all
the snacks immediately it takes some
like the second thing you're handing
over before you say a word just like
takes at least a hint it's a thing where
she hands she like hands you the basket
like to take and then you start making
selections bag of trail mix he's just
already a handful but you've accounted
for it it's like the dinar tax on top
yeah yeah and the premium product is
underneath it's right aged goods okay I
see more positions yeah uh you back okay
so you were able you coax coriander and
she plugs out onto the street and up the
large way and it's only eight or so
hours
of travel this is not a will these these
hills are starting to pop like they're
starting to be towns and villages but
the larch way is a very very young road
compared to the compared to most of the
ones the c-team travels it's it's pretty
low-key mm-hmm it's so low-key in fact
that Thor's there over on the right as
the cart is moving through a pair of
hills that sort of rise almost like a
valley on either side of the of the
larch road you can see it from time to
time the rolling hills are interrupted
by small stone outcroppings that jut out
from the gentle slope and you see a man
seated on just such a rock outcropping
playing a lute and humming to himself
what's yeah let's see
sit back oh there's a ghostly gaze right
so I could jeez wait for 30 feet away I
can look through his uh his business and
let you know give you a full report
could see through objects up to 30 feet
away so you can seize bones boner ones
that's what you're talking about eight
other bones - good luck counselor like a
knight bard
like this some guy and then coz wrists
in the back is like his dicks tiny
moderate bulge
but it's no matter XO I don't know what
that means yeah I don't know if he's a
grower or shower yeah like you put it
very succinctly and we don't have that
in the Americas like that's yes that's
that's well put you text I know I don't
do it none of its gonna say you don't
you don't hate it okay
there's just that there's just enough of
a gray stripe to be distinguished a
gentle breeze is carrying the scent of a
of a rich hair oil beard well-groomed
well-groomed lute of solid make although
certainly not brand-new house fragrant
garb in general
not Supreme not prepped to draw
attention but not a popper by any means
Rosie would probably like look over the
top at you and do this at the do like
should we say hi oh well it goes I mean
the loop playings like only so-so
yeah and that's what she thinks you're
trying to things like this is good well
it's like yes I'm an expert exactly can
you give me a my perception role oh yeah
make sure we stop him from playing hey
you think we should kill this guy 25 oh
you don't think that is an ordinary loop
yeah I don't know I look at Rosie eilean
donan I go there's something funny about
that loop okay you you think that you
think that having had some experience
and indeed profound intimacy with
devices of this pine you can see the
seams in the structure oh that you think
indicate that it may be a war loot of
some kind now there's many I mean it's
more loot as a genre sure right it's
their customized for the person but you
definitely think that this is this is
this person while seated while seated on
this outcrop playing solo in this valley
is you suspect actually incredibly
well-armed so I'm only five gets you
that's what 25 gets me so I leaned down
a Rosie I say um we may want to be
careful with that one that's uh that's
not just a lute he's playing yeah okay
well like commanding was a dangerous
instrument
[Laughter]
Suvir TPK looks really cool no yeah
and you still come out with yeah yeah
spine legs broken
yeah and she does she she does slow down
and she says something relatively
friendly she's she's just like a big
dick what's your dick like it's that
it's just like hail handsome yeah yeah
oh he's a he says no you came at the
best part and then he emphasizes the
play and just like this like stares into
you while saying well lathering this
instrument this is just like in Hamilton
when Aaron Burr sat down and like gazed
into our eyes now I'm transported what
watching this lute player is exactly
like seeing Hamilton it goes from sea
level to a yeah is he like killing it in
this Oh quite yeah yeah yeah cream
that's and that's and that not just
because I felt like it like okay he
actually was able to execute he had to
roll this mmm to deliver it so I look at
point I am and then at you Mike
this as good as I think it is like this
guy seems great well just like I mean
you know it's no I've heard better I
nudge you are you sleeping at her know
you're okay because I pop our heads
it's sick Hey
denars like distractedly reading the
letter again okay I let you be then like
stop flaunting your mail stop you pop
out and say yeah why do we oh hello yeah
check this out
sounds really good yeah it's free free
entertainment you like climb over dinar
while he's reading it to put your head
out the window
yeah nice as the as the music resolves
itself down into it into a level of
sophistication that allows for playing
and conversation peanuts
that's like / yeah remember range / in
front of the church fantasy / ask whose
name / no no no no like well what's
what's your name performer that was
amazing this is a Merrick sharp but not
sharp but nice to meet you know he says
what brings you out of the larch way ah
we've come to stake a claim not exactly
we well my documents tell you are we're
seeking the village of promise promise
okay that's a ill-timed venture no why
would it be all time sir well there may
not be much of a town the joke became
real there may not be much of a town
left is it still called the village of
promise or has it been that long that
it's been renamed the current occupants
I believe refer to it as promise oh okay
so what happened oh nothing yet
nothing yeah you're you're headed out
there to help them yeah we have a
missive to stop the bandits really
better coming in approximately four days
time yeah three days prep out now okay I
look to Rosie I'm like I don't know
about this one
Oh he says he's that autumn good yeah me
neither
he's playing a gun essentially he says
he says do you what do they want to pay
you for it huh immediately well I guess
well to protect a whole town I mean that
is substantial yeah but they've had a
hard time lately really getting the
silver up out of the mine they've been
preoccupied I guess is one way of
putting it I look at I look at Rosie
like I'm starting to sweat on this
wheeling and dealing Rosie's got your
back 100% whatever you push for she's
gonna push harder um I'm well nika's
well and she coming out of her mouth she
goes says here five thousand silver yeah
but what's your cut
says here 5000 silver we we get egg
Rosie Rosie thank you
we get the cut based on how well we
deliver results and in what time frame
this is bullshit yes thank you but we
are a company known for I'm sorry I'm
gonna try not to laugh we're a company
known for getting results and that's why
they offer us the big bucks so really
yeah that's why it's this your taxes
right there finally and I say I have 600
gold on me right now
[Laughter]
interesting
okay well that's an interesting offer
let me put mine out very briefly
all right I will offer you
mm silver okay with no cut no head
office it's like let's say your cut was
60 he's like actually hang on a second
and he calls up for the top of the hill
and says I need 10 and you see 10
archers come out to the top of the ridge
and he says look look at these so let's
say your cut 60 and he's like 6 hmm and
they sort of shuffle over a little bit
to the right he's like they're gonna
give you that to die oh here's what I'm
going to give you they sort of shuffle
themselves back together friend he's
like all of it this is an incredibly
inconvenient abacus at least it's cheap
right at least it's cheap so here's the
situation that I'm offering no shares
full mm silver but here's here's the key
this is this is what we're talking about
this is mm bass
protect it I would like you to do the
opposite so I'm offering an additional
thousand silver pieces on suppression of
promise
now get this this is not my only
operation December hills as you may be
aware are a growing market we've all
heard the news we've all seen the
prospectus imagine a scenario where each
town you subdue
I grant 3% of that mines output annually
to you right now I see you got your cart
here
seems pretty nice don't know about the
horse but you could get yourself a
better horse what's the money I'm paying
and then people you know maybe people
wouldn't make fun of you when you're
rolling to a town dinners like I love
this it's just it's just a thought I
mean imagine a situation where you don't
have to trundle around the fucking
countryside getting murdered for other
people and then you just sit back
wherever you sit back and bags of gold
show up at your house I mean that's
that's the that's the other way I mean I
that's the that's about a good as good
as I can make the case normally dinar
would be like this guy's the best but
because of the little hand print isn't
gonna be in a different mindset honest
yeah here's all the boasting yeah and
it's an official document yeah so he
would like fold up carefully close the
letter that he got it stops reading and
here's this guy doing that and then just
kind of like pushes Chris Chris out of
the way
and then just goes counteroffer
the whole take all that money easy just
talked about
after I kill you and your ten little
things up there whoa whoa whoa wait a
moment
man we that's that's good that's good
money I just want to know what what
condition the towns in that's a lot to
pay I mean are we gonna roll there we
were riding into a trap and we never
received that this is this is an
investment that I'm making in a
suppression I mean the town is the town
is not large
I think it's ill named I think it's ill
named I mean the threat is implicit
is it even a town a couple bunk houses a
weird old midlife mmm
an idiot mayor and in bad shape right
now you know and some silver that's
gonna be mine in three days that's
that's the town yeah you can call
whatever the fuck you want after you get
it I mean oh that's cool
we have an official document I just
wanted to see yeah I think finally
sometimes talking to say I keep on my
threatening tone towards him I'm not
entertaining it you figure out the state
of the town without you yeah exactly I
will see it when we get there ten ten
people
can he count let's see Wow
let's see let's just we're gonna test
him real quick I'm gonna see if it's
good okay he says all right you know
what bring them all out how many you got
all right 10 more archers come up to the
top of the hill
they are flanked on each side by three
horsemen it's at all yeah that's the
whole of what you got yeah that's it
yeah okay so we're not gonna be able to
have examples of higher than 23 yes if
the maths and somehow yeah anything he's
got we're just gonna have to start the
horsemen are worth five fingers okay
okay so how much is that real quick it's
impossible math pretty yeah he's like no
no he's like this is higher than I can
count
so I think that I will and then he drew
clinic in Thailand and you get to do a
nearly tore conic now right well I'm
just gonna do clinic entitle this guy
yeah I think he's the only one I look
buddy cool out yes yeah he's yeah he's
like oh you're in the mid conversation
so you can you can work a little bit of
a promoter yeah that's good when the
situation dictates just when the
situation wrestling promos promo fun
she's like businessman well I'm a
businessman let me handle my business
stance so I take control of him okay
alright and I go tada what do you want
well now he is like ingratiate it
towards me so what we could dispel his
guys I guess I don't know I don't think
that far ahead then I was just like well
it now II just like psychically
flexes on this guy and goes I win we're
all like oh no ten minutes he's like
he's like yeah I look I can admit when
I'm my kid admit when I was wrong that's
fine this is a miscalculation laughter
and look I said a lot of shit I don't
wanted to come back and bite me in the
ass later no you know what you know the
important thing is they realize you were
wrong oh yeah absolutely the fact of the
matter is is that I I feel like there's
an opportunity for someone like you in
my organization or maybe I could join
yours
you know actually I think the best thing
would be find a closet and fall asleep
yeah
I've been approached a cart cuz the
archers are still watching us have them
approach the cart mush I'm gonna have a
little light glow from in here say hey
buddy turn in and tell him to be
terrified and tell them like leaves
these leaves this cart alone these are
serious customers okay there are no
closets in the woods like are we sure we
don't like the closet it's gonna take
him a long time to find a closet hey
head over here over here over to the
cart he's like yeah look I talk a lot of
shit about this cart you did coriander
good actually nobody makes fun of us
when we come into town there's no one's
like you but you you see it up close and
I'm like this is tough horse tell us
horse is what you like the most about
each of us most me can give me give me
give me his loot oh yeah give me
everything in your pockets real quick
well yeah yeah first give everything
your pockets yeah I'm listen I yeah of
course yeah yeah I mean what is it yeah
that's it what do I get
go out of his pockets yeah he has a
pouch that has a hundred and thirty gold
in it hey now daddy's got a hundred
thirty gold you think that you think
that the the lion's share of the wealth
he actually has with him is this
instrument oh yeah I say give the give
the give that guitar to my friend it's
like there's some like he is its he is
like some part of him is straining
mightily against this it's a shame he's
got a hand it hand it over
he said he says look it's title um again
I didn't tell him again SS get right in
his face I go friend he's like
all right
okay and he is it's like he's handing
away a child yeah and he's like dude do
you play the lute oh yeah I play all the
time I'm the best at it that's your
family with it but it's like it you're
holding backwards
oh yeah it's upside down stuff though
you can tell it's like you know how when
you're you know it's like if you're ever
playing like a racing video game that's
like you're always like leaning in oh
like you think this somehow that's gonna
happen
he keeps twisting his body in a way that
he thinks will help you hold it
correctly and he's kind of tilting over
like like like trying to give you a
little like she's like scratching her
nails on it and stuff but it's just even
a ring ring even these taps against
against the back have a musical payload
against this wood frame with this with
just this body this construction wow
this is happening there's a whole other
life I could have had and the people the
people up on the up on the hill they're
like that's what I wanted to do is well
this is going on because I don't need to
make some display for their benefit if
he's handed over his loot yeah yeah when
I want to see what their yeah exactly
that the horse the horsemen on the far
right uh sort of leans a spear over the
back of his shoulder he says Merrick
what are you doing tell him we're cool
yes he's like I know these guys they're
cool they're cool yeah killing it is
fine we're we're gonna work on we're
gonna work on some of the Summerhill
stuff together I think how are you guys
you just you come out yeah yeah with a
Sun Hat
I'm trying what time of day is it yeah
is a daytime still or we've done into
evening
oh yes it's it's a afternoon he's left
in mind yeah exactly so we're moving in
so as you as you open the window and
sick your head out you catch your you
receive light as you open the window and
look out you perceive light so I'm
seeing from your left I'm seeing through
lagari but now I'm getting a sensation
that my left eye is getting light in hey
what hey aria I'm gonna lift the
blindfold up and feet first I'm gonna
lift it up to see if I see through it
you doing I'm gonna swivel the gaudy
around and look at my own face it looks
like a random almost kaleidoscopic
collection inside the eye socket itself
and maybe out to the edge of almost like
raspberry droplets of of gems we're
friends I'm a Great Dane guys this is a
good job that's great archers the
archers like he didn't get an archer
we better he's got it up a little bit
yeah can i wink them you can try spit it
from the bow but they all link you we
will they all wink slightly half said
times and then there's the one on the
outer corner the small okay great like
you're doing fine you have to show off
how I imagined eyelids it's not good
I'll tell you there cos like it's like
yeah yeah you know I'll see you when I
see it I'm gonna go talk to the guys
about now you're getting in the cart
with us
yeah fall asleep what are you doing on
stage whatever no this is only goal is
to make okay all right we're not gonna
like I'm Kotetsu is rosy I think this is
brilliant
so please continue think you know he
gets in there and he's like yeah yeah
yeah I yeah I was mistaken
yeah I hand you some rope I'm like time
up I guess
alright you got to build it in here mmm
it's nice this is good in this best you
were wrong about this card
oh very wrong so don't touch the basket
curl up no roll up on the floor like a
cat that's not only no I'm gonna do that
I mean it's it's fine I'm just gonna
think there's a lot of couch here I'll
just lay on the couch no the floor I
said on the couch
like I said yeah I even I got ten in the
corner I want to be part of the team
don't you yeah this is the initiation
that can feel the love
so yeah definitely
so those eyelids got to be getting same
page there oh yeah they're pretty heavy
huh man I'm tougher yeah I'm pretty
tired listen I know it's him you guys I
don't know I didn't see well I'm still
talking
ain't I in his eye
together binds like yeah this is not you
don't have to like none of this is
important like I trust you implicitly
like obviously you know I I know what
would happen if I stepped out of line
like I don't this is not required this
is this is part of this is called being
part of a team
is it cuz none of you guys have any why
are you fighting me on this we did it
already we just on this with this guy
it's where is weird it's cuz I'm wearing
I like Ghana roots their ups we're now
are around our psyche yeah oh really
it's a fit elephant thing okay yeah he
gives us each our own rope our own
unique rope tailored to us okay alright
this is my rope then yeah I guess I got
a physical rope tube it's not my hands I
was gonna say I wanted to look at rosy
and be like be like I'm so tempted to
keep this and give it as a gift but
should we just break it I think we could
probably at least sell it those things
were valuable as well yeah and she's
like already got it overhead like are
you sure this this chefs like from the
hills around it's just a gag guys is
well not working something out if I
wanted to smash this loot that's also
organic when that is part of it yeah
it's like are you sure cuz I really like
are you sure cuz I bet
alright I just don't want him to get it
back fine okay sure yeah
alright well once we go away the cradle
and he's like I'm Gavin
give me my rope I guess like yeah I tie
him up good awesome
yeah this thing wears off do we want to
be any guy got be talking yeah we want
to gag him sir I have no sounds we have
like a burlap sack with the balls mouth
or something like that works right we're
like openly talking about this do it in
front of him to are not even doing this
it's like we just beat him unconscious
is this part of the yeah yeah this is
all jokes I could just cast silence on
his beard oh there we go there you go
that works
fight it up yeah I don't feel like beat
him delete blacks out
no no we should beat him with the loot
no it's a good loot don't do that
I do cast silence on your face
we don't wears off before we know you
didn't have a good beat on when it wears
off what's the duration it's his
concentration and it is a 20-foot radius
sphere so now none of us hear anything
[Laughter]
so then the whole wing cart is not now
I'm not making noises it just silently
plods along heavy feet yeah yeah it's
fine
and we got eyes on him yeah so we think
but we got look at the way all right so
your things about to run out
yeah that's we get 10 more minutes of
yours Rosie yeah so we probably have to
kill them but then how do we square that
up with is let's just go we've got the
bottle or those links and the boss
central cool so let's just move in
towards the town and see what they do
yeah I agree he's a hostage for a reason
yeah they made it this solves their
problem and we'll get the thousand so
we're out right and we can say that we
did this job before time runs out all
right I'm ready to go with favor
so you'd you're understanding which
we're gonna use a history check for yes
is that it's about a quarter of the way
in and to the left it should be clearly
marked by an ash tree okay because this
is this is like the the folk map that
you construct in your head it's all
based on things that you've heard yeah
you know halfway turn left at the old
oak ash tree big one mm-hmm and then how
far away do I think at time wise but you
you feel like you should be getting
close to this and being able to execute
this I'll take it
okay being able to execute this is is
valuable worse than on 11/11 it's pretty
good you don't see the hash oh ah okay
could I can script my druid to help me
find an ashtray oh yeah okay they're
super good a tight ship like that yes
trying to open this thing do you want to
play around is it okay there's only take
you a second if I helped me ran mother I
want to help grandma dice do a struggle
wouldn't it be like in nature
Danya sure they both cover a lot of now
let's do the one I got points in oh no
10 oh no advantage
oh no b-but but for you I didn't know in
which tree is which tree isn't that
super hard yeah you're always getting
like ash and maple confused always every
time you just like it's odd like you're
just right there by the cart yeah I'm
like oh this one it's so what I'm
staring at yeah yeah no that's not not
it it's not an F so I can't see the tree
for the trees
yeah can see the fruit for the other
type of tree yeah so this is basically
like I say this this seems that make it
up again if you had not had the
opportunity to see one up close for as
long as you did you might not have
noticed it at all
so you're basically you're just trying
to figure out how it how it functions
yeah I well it's like a puzzle box to me
right now
it is I poke the place that like I saw
Brahma do to activate her doesn't do the
same thing no so where Brahmas like the
main activation they can have multiple
different weapons in them
the main activation on hers is where the
string is attached at the base of the
fretboard and this does not have a
switch there can I do a perception check
to see if I doesn't open it can I take
it you can't
oh good - how's it - for the podcast
thank you hey what's your perception Oh
22:07
you bill do you remember building it
absolutely so there is a like where you
might have a strap or a carrying strap
at the base you learned that it can be
moved much farther than it should and
when that happens the back of it the
back of the bulb of it opens up two ways
like this and inside are a number of
interesting things you see documents oh
oh
for example there's like money and
you're like there's there's a few paper
currency loose in there there's a few
darts whose tips are covered oh I love
those right off the back of that yeah
yeah just dipping him no those are gone
just throwing them right out the back
i'm defanging this thing exactly no no
no you can see so the documents
themselves basically yeah yeah yeah yeah
they are assessments their overall value
assessments of different claims the
towns that are on them and then various
agreements with bandit outfits to
extract the wealth from these different
places so there are a few other there
are a few other towns named okay and
these are legal documents what did I
mean they're there it's documentation
for illegal seizures but okay they are
documents yeah yeah sounds like we own
the bandits now yeah so I want to go
about yeah can I like take his name off
of all of these yeah I want to I want to
doctored these somehow that's D&amp;D
whiteout I see yeah
no him and they're not gonna like it but
fun just keep charging that entitlement
and make them sign it over you have an
entitlement to okay his brain is gonna
be much he's very much been way too much
time in this guy's head yeah
grant free but they're not legal
documents they're just like they're just
basically like his here's the ledger of
operations all right well I'm gonna take
those yeah this is proof just transfer
them over to your other oh no you know
what I do is I'm gonna make forgeries of
them and I'm gonna put the forgeries in
there and I'm gonna keep his his
original do you have a forgery kit yeah
of course I have a fortress nice well
they're walnut forgery so can the shape
of the letters they're supposed to be
but yeah exactly yeah yeah so as they're
so you you have them piece by piece
just like in a arrange in a way that you
can see them like just get a quick
glance at different documents and
compare these values yeah they're all
held down by rocks from the top of
between the rocks the signatures and the
documents you see symbol you have not
seen know for a decent amount of time no
it is that sort of twisted five-pointed
inverted crown oh and you've
inadvertently constructed it I'm on the
top of the car
oh wow so it just like the negative
space between the documents okay yeah
well no it goes yes she'll start she's
gonna make like a like a little sketch
of what she's done up here of the thing
she's documents that and then the person
she would tell is Rosie so I guess she
doesn't tell anybody because you're
doing your thing I'm just driving the
car baby
okay we're all sound - yeah well it's
like do you tell the party line but if
you bang on the top of it like I'll get
a vibration I'm like what's it yeah okay
yes I start bashing on it yes yeah um
there were some documents inside listen
long story short you guys remember that
upside down crown that um was oak I said
I say what was it what was it oh we do
we remember them because was that not a
flesh oh no no that wasn't that did
happen I say do you remember that
upside-down crown that we were looking
for with oak um I found it what do you
mean it's up here I made it I made it
with the documents okay well if I could
do that that's a good job no but I mean
it's in the documents it's in it's in
them that's so simple I think you guys
don't get it
no you hear me going the side of the car
you see legardie coming up gesturing to
it like so violently he's looking at me
I'm seeing it like oh yes how did you do
just by accident it was by accident it
just appeared to me it was all here in
the forms
in every document just these I think
well while we're talking about the crown
and mentioning oak again I look at my
little oak ball I kind of sneak off the
Saturday look no that's from dumb
checking in three weeks that you look
down you look weak sort of looked at
okay so you've got you have all the
information here you're sorry hearing
about this but you don't care well it
look kind of reminds me so you open the
bag and you look down and then smiling
up at you from the bag yeah is it's a
just a jet black haired butt naked baby
oh shit like really well but we can't no
one hears it that's an incredible
opportunity to pause the events so we're
gonna sample the facilities of course
enjoy a beverage wherever you might be
and don't go anywhere because we're back
hello I'm Jeffrey que whore camps and
this is the c-team I still some
different let's go back in Lane I want
to add a narrative arc so let's let's
just let's just break it down let's just
go piece by piece
my meticulously crafted villain was
devoured by microtransaction DLC that
you designed Hey also Amy's nemesis is
now an adorable baby inside of a handbag
yeah is that most of it who's Amy
[Music]
exactly no I mean walnut dong crass well
now the elite well mm-hmm it was ruin a
Miss and I can't play anymore
goodbye goodbye
about this video brain he did say the
whole time just pissing it was terrible
I do not like to go to the bathroom with
anyone this man walked out I had to go
to the bathroom with engineer left and
then he came in some people like to walk
the hold my name will talk I want to
hear all about what happens I can feel
all I got like sorry we have a different
story ours gonna be awesome
yeah look hazelnuts at Jeff needs a
drink more water
for starters please knock exactly take
it to the PP town yeah exactly the show
yeah yeah we're looking for less Pinot
Noir Jeff and more Pinot Grigio okay
tear in terms of color what sherry is
that too much it's the same thing twice
is that wine Geoffrey take a nice and
long time since we've made the table now
baby he is delighted he is delighted to
see you it's just somewhat freaky baby
oh because he's been raising basically a
flesh basketball covered in hair and
that didn't bother him so honestly isn't
it a lot like having an egg that hatched
into a baby
this isn't it a lot like having themes
here yeah now let me ask you a question
would dinner tell everyone or would it
be like your secret like Welker bird my
pocket dinar has been raising this this
flush-mount in secret like secretly
feeding it and not telling any like
Starnes like but i don't think he could
hide a baby yeah but I'm the only one in
the car with you along with Marik and
but I see you gasp when you look in the
bag you it seemed audibly flail but
couldn't hear you right but I don't know
the bag isn't moving or anything I just
another one I'm like I'm like stop
looking at that letter
it's a really good letter
yeah dinner would come clean then yeah
oh really oh there's a baby in his bag
why do you come out eventually yeah what
is it what's on all right cards on the
table Kathir is really messed this up
this is his so we're so ready yeah first
of all I'm sorry yeah he apologizing
he's already trying to pass the buck in
here like already apologizing all right
so are you the Rope friend you Romeo at
perception real quick
may I advantage enough yeah yeah 17 plus
plus a three for me yeah 20 it's quite
bit a nominal time you see as he's
starting your story America is still
laying down there in the cat but his
face is now a mask of rage and you see
him mouthing words that are not words in
any language bull oh can i you never do
you one way like hold up of all that I
can um stab does he does he look like
he's got any kind of agency at always
saying words yeah let's see what do I
have that can let that happen a brick
yeah yeah let me um
stick the let me stick the shaft of my
staff of look at my rod like let me put
my rod directly against his lips so
here's a bite down on so you can make
Chris I want him to not be able to
otherwise yeah okay
it's not I'm not putting it in like a
plumber like I'm trying to put it in
like he's gonna have to bite down on it
gotcha
how did you get do you go get it okay am
i successful he's like yeah you can feel
you can feel the reverberations why in
the crystal
why am i doing the hard work young
Locati find a way to silence this this
this possible new friend yes not
permanently just a little while right
he he he squeaks a couple times and then
collapses and then just wraps himself
around the middle of his face okay and
then just like it is just right in his
face in front of him just like looking
at this human person like an alien yeah
just trying to assess him with whatever
weird organs he has yeah I'm gonna I'm
gonna bend down to him and and and just
go and then for a little extra saw so
I'll lift the blindfold them yeah yeah
Brad the brows is knit and furrowed it's
like that's like like artillery just
like a whole thing will kill a baby now
oh yeah our good friend our best dear
friend that's my water
oh we thought that was your giant metal
jug who died under mysterious
circumstances he I retained him in a bag
my collected pieces who died is do guys
no I mean oak our best friend I'm sorry
what what did you keep what I could grab
which was part of his head is that the
hair that you've been wearing on top of
cabby hmm
yeah okay yeah where's that where it is
who's that hey man stop wearing
no where's the hair dinar where's the
hair dinar it's in my bag
okay Ashton connects it to a baby oh I'm
sorry what you gave a baby hand you hold
the baby up I'm like is it nude yeah
yeah let me just go in here
America's miracle except it's just like
he hasn't this has been the worst day
and I'm trying to forge some kinship
because I'm not like this I'm not part
of that there there is a moment where
the both of you nod in a confused way
and there's a genuine connection rosy
drops the reins comes crashing somehow
through that tiny porthole window
there's a theatrical crash she lands in
front of you she's like
[Music]
yeah I got the baby
sideways yeah by the head by the softest
part of the head just fingers going I
don't I don't trust dinar I think I've
with provided ample anything fatherly
ability in the past
it looks good still breathing why do we
care if it's still breathing wait we
have a chance to raise a better oak here
I miss pouring the same one as before
wait we get we got to redo oak now why
is your versus nurture on this one baby
Wow holy shit people don't grow from
hair why is the baby kept hair a lot and
there's no babies on me it leaves the
party line did you like how I got louder
by one hand and then I was well mammals
work it's not this oh yes well yes - yes
yes yes it's and very very happy I mean
that boy reaching that son I left the
party line I cannot hear your nonsense
he's reaching up he's trying to get
those beads oh that's fine yes want to
jump
don't stop now Rosie Rosie jumps back
through the window with the baby mm-hmm
got the baby in one arm got the rain we
continue the accordion is basically on
autopilot
yeah isn't quite a shine yeah it's very
much for show but it's an important show
yeah it's a great show baby okay okay
you get out you can see that like at
something like a respectful distance
there are six horsemen and then a group
of archers like on the path behind the
heart and I'm just
and they did not have a plan for six
sessions they're in a very confused
place right now oh when I see that I
look at I go over to cthis he's just up
in front yeah yeah yeah I crawl over to
the front I point eight your your bag
I'm making you the motion open up okay
and then I have the war loot I want to
put it in the bag oh yes okay okay yeah
like a like a reticulated python it's
slow going at first but but it gets
there it gets there and and you know and
it's satisfied with itself and curls up
just a couple yep yes you wants a
particulate in your crate get some his
baby
hello small friend hello my friend
am I getting anything back absolutely
what do I get back just hello Kath RIS I
was trying to parse if there's any oak
in their left or if this is a new baby
you know you know my name
yeah I am this is embarrassing
I don't like to I don't like to bring it
up a lot of times people will bring it
up because they are trying to show off
I'm not trying to show off it's just a
fact I am a demigod and I mean it's it's
possible that I could die but I've never
been able to figure it out and no one
neither has anyone else
so I'm not I'm not sharing this by the
way I've just been probing this baby but
I thought was a baby
anyway you know we're from I saw it way
gosh you and Jamie God why were you
working for
acquisitions incorporated well I didn't
do much for them like you could have
done a lot if you wanted no you have no
idea how boring it is I have some idea
but not too demigod certainly oh it is
just day in and day out who so who sired
you will you the offspring of what I
know them what I have worshipped them
okay listen we're gonna we'll have this
conversation
if this process just takes as long as
it's gonna take another couple weeks I
should be able to have this conversation
with you you know with my mouth right
right and I don't know I I hope we can
put a lot of that stuff behind us a lot
went wrong especially with with walnut
I'd she's a loose cannon and we gonna
kill that baby there's things there's
things that she doesn't know about
Brahma that I think would probably
change that I changed the tenor of some
of these discussions ooh
well cover you know a couple weeks I'll
have enough divine mass to reclaim some
of my former capacity and it's true that
we are a little bit busy at the moment
yeah I want to ask ya you handle that ID
and if you could if you could please I
mean they can't kill me like kill me
kill me but if you could if you could
keep them from harming the vessel Wow
I'd I would oh you don't like my
favorites you know they're not you know
they don't grow on trees
baby but the other god I don't like so
we're yeah we'll see about that
what yeah listen if you're shopping for
a patron I mean I can connect you you
seem a lot more reasonable than my guy
yeah what
well we'll cover it I am really tired
now
finger asleep I read your lips and I go
soon he's gonna sleep forever let's uh
my leaky let's get underway will do this
will do this get this thousand silver
but right now he let me know I can't be
killed so that's gonna be a kink in
things walnut cannot say no to him when
he mistakenly yes sir it's pretty sweet
she's like okay yeah we'll investigate
it we'll have time after we deal with it
I mean she puts before mother back in
there
Oh clicks the sheet background she like
whisper sweet and she's like just not to
pay mother and it's not that I don't
want blood and I'm saying you put it
away
oh do I hear any of these approaching
horses archers
no me there they're there they're
attempting to keep it's like they're not
like shadowing you it isn't like this
like a stakeout cuz it's like you can
just look back and see them but they
don't have a plan in place okay they
just don't have a plan in place for this
we could pick them off yeah well I was
thinking about wasn't grab man see right
you could what's up I couldn't just look
like him I love that can I not
okay you have a mask of many things I do
you have a mask of many faces so what is
the what's our objective to get through
this without and get them off our
daytime off her bad side
yeah it's another way all right know if
I can do his voice does he have a
particularly notable voice cuz I've
heard him talk you've heard him talk
maybe independently your performance was
okay yeah so let me go ahead and and
disguise self I'm gonna turn into
Merrick does he blue he looks up yeah
yeah he looks up at you and he's just
like changing a child all the way I'll
give you lift up the whole bottom hard
to get the pant and he's he he doesn't
like it and he does but any resistance
is met with an instructive nip
from magadi oh I forgot so look now this
is valuable because I'm going to walk
out there with a blindfold how good are
these eyes and they're I assume they're
disguised by discuss that range at this
range it should be okay
depends on it depends on how close if
you like walk right up into them and say
hey look into my human eyes that might
be that might be good okay check out
these papers normal - that's how you
know I'm your friend
[Laughter]
which eye do you think is the most
normal like we're friends how long we
known each other
determine the symmetry so I get on some
of his garments enough for it to be
believable and I'm gonna take the
blindfold off and I have mine on seeing
I and my sort of seeing mess on this
side I step out of the cart and I and I
raised a hand to the no and as you raise
your hand the leader of the horseman
raises his hand as well and you see that
the groups begin to slow I start
clearing my throat
cause I want to know when I get outside
of silence yeah 20 feet okay yeah so I
chuckling to myself it would I'm trying
to make it look like for them and by the
time I actually get out of the range and
now I can hear my own the sound of my
voice
I say don't worry boys
we're gonna make so much money
alright let's see this relax
cool it joy yourself oh my god I will
take an image oh yeah what about this
Pete based on its kind of performance
that's gonna be a 23 for that one and
then this is gonna be your servant Chris
growls opera do a boon I'm not talking
about boons you know I'm talking about
that only wood dice case so delicious
full of dice for you your dice and box
like that dice and a box together it's
one prison and you get it from Chris
very cool well signing table talk now um
so so and then the body language is the
raised fist these fists are raised also
I bring my both amount of but look and
it's not quite what he do right it feels
right exactly like I'm walking a little
too much swagger
he tries things he's a cool guy ya know
the horse guy says how many Jim did you
kill in there that's the best part
with we're going into business together
they're gonna elevate our operation we
are gonna own red larch itself I'm
thinking we celebrate tonight well he's
like come on we still got some stuff to
finish up with them but well let's meet
at our usual place tonight and we'll tap
those kegs and let me sort this out and
hopefully we'll have some for everybody
just to put their signature on you know
I'm talking about a couple of these oh
no no I knew I knew we were more taken
okay pretty healthy pretty healthy okay
that that satisfies the horseman which
in turn satisfies the Bowman horses
there's big there's big nods from the
horses yeah this guy is a fucking guy
that's good exactly so so they they peel
off just knowingly like they seem to
understand this area quite well so they
peel off is a lot back clapping see if
thinks it's it it seems that things are
gonna turn out okay
I come on back into the cart and we're
Marek can enjoy the sight of me dry
heave from the anxiety performance when
you when you come back in by this time
the this the silences has ended okay so
you can make it an eagle oh it just
straight out in the middle of the floor
huh oh I did it for real yeah sorry
I go yeah my guy I vomited in support -
Rosie vomits out front but she makes
sure not to baby yeah baby probably do
it first - yeah
definitely bomb by the whole time what
are you get Roper no one's gonna steal
stomach roll to not throw up yeah seven
you throw Merrick you a very tough job
just kicking his feet bound for Amir oh
yeah and it's just like just like
dragging through this puddle
yeah I'm dressing him not he's just
buck-ass naked he's got vomit on his
feet he's all he's got a good
crystalline alien serpent as a gag we've
all seen it vomit because I junk talking
baby
driving a horse the driving the horse so
it's a your cue were continuing to pull
this bizarre pageant yeah up this hill
and you know little clearing sort of
built up against the side of a smooth
rolling hill you can see a small village
there is a small post out front that
says promised in common and elven okay
okay so if you're bilingual I found his
named promise promise double promise
can I do a I'm gonna I'm gonna pull
coriander to a halt and do just syrup
for a preliminary scan let's see if I
notice anything out of place before we
go trucking in there he's going to
assess that time yes we're ambush
waiting for us the American told us
about
I'll take advantage on this hole oh
that's pretty good 14:11 it's a 16 yeah
yeah so you you assess it it's it's
small there's things that you think you
might be able to parse just from how its
laid out there don't appear to be much
in the way of individual houses mm-hmm
they appear to live communally into
massive longhouses
on each side of a central well and
fireplace just past the tiny village
itself there's two smaller huts and then
you think that you can sort of see the
last rays of sunlight glinting off of a
river a sort of abuts the back of the
place off to the right you can see that
hastily fuck you right you can see
that's sort of the the beginnings of the
mind that they've constructed and
directly into the hills themselves still
I have to police
I don't give a lot of this over here you
know what I mean look when there's fun
being had you got to tamp that down I
get it so no so you that's your
assessment you can see people there's a
few people making similar checks against
the party sir right now but don't know
no they're definitely townspeople but
they're townspeople in a place where
visitors recently have not been kind and
so there's a lot of slow movements over
toward weapon racks hmm okay along the
side but these are makeshift weapons
this place is not this this place is
built according to very very different
principles from those that organize
ordinary cities we need to get out their
documentation first if you ask me yeah
I'm ready okay walnut get out yeah so
hop down everything's all been cleaned
up from the top and I come down to have
my official mandate out and I just walk
walk right right up to him and say we're
here to see Maeve Perry's the thrust on
official business
he says
I don't I don't I that could and a woman
comes out of a hut and just shakes her
head and tisks and then while he is
continuing to do this she just pushed
like a sliding barn door the scene and
he says she says that's the mayor which
is great for us order a man of principle
that's great what does Maeve like she
says she says she says I appreciate your
having come but Maeve is not Oh Maeve is
not well that maybe is in no position to
advocate for the town or hire people for
it we are to help protect the town that
is about to be besieged by bandits she
says but that's true but I think that if
you will look at our weapon racks look
at our hale and hearty women and men
here I think you'll find that and then
coming from the coming from her Hut hmm
you see a tall
Dragonborn woman whose poise is utterly
out of synch with this with this commune
emerge and then from from her chest
leaps a small a small glinting creature
that runs right out toward you and just
grabs your leg like this
does that look particularly familiar
this is this is 100% preneur and Cortez
and then the yes the woman says Maeve
you you shouldn't have done this
we we we can handle our own problems out
here and Mae says that's that's not true
and it's it's to your credit I
appreciate that you're a proud woman
but you'll be a dead woman in three days
and I I can't I can't accept that so I
look right at Maeve and give her a nod
like yeah it's as she gives you she
gives you a nod and I say we've seen
some of the enemy forces and I have very
good news for you about who we've
brought with us I say the leader of the
bandits himself
Marik who cares man
Marik sharp button who is tied up in the
back of our cart currently she says
really well it goes yes for real it just
so happened sooner was able to apprehend
him single-handedly hmm oh my god I
thought you went if I'm alone if I'm
hearing this in the back a little bit
yeah yeah yeah so you can't you're so in
the back right yeah yeah checking on
their prisoner mm-hmm um yeah this is
she's like well let's see him yeah come
on over and I'm walking but with it's a
big sweep it's like a wrecking ball yes
just this massive sweep yes exactly and
she gives her a little pat yeah yeah
it's all giggles amazing Sheila she
looks up at you and says oh you can tell
like that like freak well that's very
hard experience she's really not like
Sheldon yeah she takes out a knife so
take out a like a little you guys ever
play with like tree calls when you're
younger you get girls and they make like
a little round boys so take that one of
those I didn't give that to her
is it like EPA toy yeah central baby
Natalie nice nature's toy
yes Beckman said she you headed to her
and then it's just like one step it's
like off the leg yeah she's just like
juggling it and tossing it and playing
with it that's fun
she's just wandering a little bit away
from the village
so I go to open the cart and I just give
a real brief heads up to dinner and go
your friends here we go
tada I Rosie is hurting Crenn are just
from a from a from a distant she's like
just like oh no I love it
these people see like you communicate to
me I assume that the we're showing our
bounty yeah are you I'm still him but I
can dispel it yeah but you gave him this
close back yeah so you see so you come
in and it's tied up Marik and dinar and
nude Marik stop please
okay I take back this guy self take it
off and now just meaning this is an
upgrade better I guess this is free
bloom a medley with you yeah quite them
trapped Saoirse
Saoirse looks in the in the cart and
looks over you and says dinar ten I
would be very excited to see her
we go hey Sasha
Sasha good to see you came right her
friend did not come yeah yeah oh yeah
don't don't worry Jeff I know about the
cauldron Alissa yeah is that Alissa yes
I know where the cauldron don't worry I
know exactly how to use it Tori yeah
it's gonna be delicious for me but it's
professional but it's like respect right
and then she looks over and then she's
able to see sort of around the central
table she's able to see a couple legs
wiggling back and forth in sick and she
reaches over and just grabs his ankle
and just pulls him out like like
cracking a whip just takes him from
there and then it pulls him out through
the puddle and just deposits him on the
outside and then Crenn our looks back
and sees that someone has come out and
begins to bound over and she shouts no
in the in the Dragonborn skaaland
tongue it's it it's just it's like being
punched like if you don't know the word
yeah hearing it it's just like being
punched in the face yeah
and so the corner stops and then returns
her attention to the seed pod and then
as she pulls him out the limbs
themselves to get thinner and weaker
and she pulls him out and lays him on
the ground and you can see that he is
getting the limbs are getting smaller
and thin enough what to escape the bonds
now and the face has a just got a
thinner gaunt twisted cast to it and it
just shakes his head like a like effect
like if a terrier gets ahold of
something you know any like a squirrel
he's able to shake like oh yeah he just
shakes he shakes him out and then
immediately begins to try to lo Polly
come the cart can I do a grown man
Sandra da yeah absolutely
okay so with my baby okay Kate oh no you
don't and and then these shadowy vines
come up in and tangle him up get him
right near like the crotch region yeah
the sea well it is absolutely smooth
okay good oh and so these these shadow
tendrils are just like like almost
cruelly playing with him yeah like
they're just lifting him up like it's
just one leg and then the other one is
got the arm and then it's just sort of
keeping him in this suspended right good
state good and he's just hissing and
gibbering back at the cart and she says
yeah he yeah that Marik has a couple
doppelgangers high in his his coterie
of misfits I thought I thought that I
killed him twice and she and she says
grandmother do you have this under
control absolutely I do
and Saoirse says we'll manage him we
have three days to get this city to get
this did she looks at she says town
village hovel set of shacks ready for
the assault that's coming you are late
hmm yeah we were that stinks yeah yeah
in the midst of this craziness and the
dressing-down denier justice you not
paying attention and just walks right
past her look foreign are ya exactly um
and she you were walking past her but
then she is like trying to walk past you
yeah to just keep yelling at him and
he's just like no no now it's just about
speed oh it's they've devolved into some
kind of a competition and Josh if you
could please tip the called wrong the
wrong right on right on
Chilton towers so you are you're
kneeling down with Crenn are and she
says father so she's gone
sore she comes back with something broad
wrapped tightly in oil cloth
and she says she says to Crenn or that
she says
is not your father
but
does not mean that he is not a part of
our family and she sets up the she sets
up the package on its tip next to you
and says in our in our travels we have
ranged loan and I saw this
and thought of you oh hey I rolled a
seven on the church oh this is great
I I take it appreciatively and I say to
shake it push it over I say to to corner
I get down close to right go I'm I am
NOT your dad but you are my daughter
and I say - sir should I say thank you
for this and genuinely for in our points
at the fully wrapped package and says
sword ha spoiler yeah this is exactly
how it's like this is it a shield
did you get me a shield what is it she
is like on her back
yeah laughing this is ridiculous groans
you're stupid yeah so yeah I will open
the package it is a traditional Gennari
great sword hmm
like toothbrush yeah absolutely every
way so you don't have to change your OC
the fanfiction can remain but it is
clearly of superior make and has runes
around the hilt so this is a this is
essentially a plus one version of the
traditional generic sword like you
needed it hmm gosh I say thanks like
yeah weirdly awkwardly dinars really
attached to toothbrush yeah that's
what's awesome yeah oh no Jerry saying
this is great she's like you don't thank
you no I love it I love it
he's like being way more awkward than
normal and he's always kind of awkward
or inari he's like no this is great
between that and the letter he's like
really awkward it's been it's been a
rough day
yeah well this is making things very
awkward for him ah all right well she
says
well let's continue then uh and she
walks back in the people of the town
there's only 40 or so people that live
here mostly middle-aged and a few young
children but this is clearly a place
that families have invested their their
lives in they appear to live entirely in
these two communal bunk houses and this
is this is basically what you're
learning as sorsha is giving you the
tour she indicates you can see a pile of
of stone under a heavy burlap tarp and
she says we have we have some materials
that we can use to fortify the town over
the next three days we've done our best
she indicates the southern path into the
town has a sort of half wall that's
clearly seen better days and there's a
few beginnings of fortifications here on
the road but she's indicating areas that
she thinks her of concern for example
directly to the north the town is built
essentially at the foot of this hill and
that is an incredible yeah it is it is
it is amazing for them and very
efficient for the town but it makes that
North that North Hill is basically
situated at the optimal position to
assault the town that's at the base of
it yeah that's on that ob1 high ground
yeah exactly it that's exactly right
is that like a name of a weed no it's
from it's an Anatomy you might have seen
it
yeah yeah it's good dude I'm a whatever
they call the fins of it yeah
[Laughter]
but that's so she you gosh okay you know
it um so she now that you have arrived
she allows herself to be a tiny bit
tired mm-hmm she just she grants herself
the right to be as tired as the
situation actually demands for a few
seconds but you can tell that she's
looking around the town she knows that
this is not a she knows that this is
that three days is not a lot of time
yeah and it's gonna take more than she
can it's gonna take more than she could
do you know you know that she could
handle a lot of it just on the field but
it's more than just her here yeah and
she knows that and she has
she has invested herself in these people
you can tell as she is walking around
she's just she's greeting people and
indicating and it's a mixture of humans
and and elves in the same in the same
small town which is its self rear in
like like picking up corn on right up on
there and just like in just general
horseplay but still like walking around
like doing it absent mindedly oh yeah
yeah she's just she is with you she's
your conscious at first constantly yeah
tossing around but she's right behind
ready to catch she can have all the
babies no problem yep got two arms but
like like getting close to to sore sure
like as an aside not loud just gonna
like why are you why are you here why do
you even want to defend this place what
are you doing here
all right
you
I'm glad to see you it's it's like this
the fall of Scala
led to a result that I have long feared
and I think that I may be partly to
blame
the taint that the monks I knew it I
thought it's the right word but I knew
that you children I was laughing at
those different joke yeah it was a water
check the tape it was another check of
taint
I was right there it ain't you'll see
you won't see me there that's not where
I do here no so you there is a poison
hmm yeah let's go with this maybe maybe
this will enable some professionalism
she said she says there's a poison that
seeped out of scala that my in trouble
for any of that said all right great
thanks
stolen seeped seeping in tank I'm still
stuck in there and she says that I know
for a fact because I have stopped them
more than once they are the cult of TIA
modest setting up
cults and cells in the desert Valley
and they all start from a war that I
should have won
so are they who's going to attack Wyatt
that says why are you here this this
land rush in the sombre Hills is an
incredible source of wealth for a young
for an organization as hungry as this
one I have reason to believe that every
time we see a hand work here it is in
the service of another Hostin our think
about to you my well hey killed him and
knock them unconscious in that fight so
no not a fan just like the whole team on
the hit TMI the mother of dragons yeah
yeah you know I mean no he's on the good
dragon side right
did they have feelings about too much
he's like booty what yeah okay generally
yeah anti Tiamat yeah so so you mean you
can see that you can see the the weapons
now that you're up close I'm like
walking through the middle of town
this is not
this is this is no good yeah this this
town is not enough this town is not in a
good place I sneeze and a weapon rack
collapse yeah exactly it's pulverized
some she knows that they're gonna be
attacking in four days so do they know
how many people are coming what she she
the numbers that she gives you match
with what you said she says you know
anywhere from 15 to 25 Oh
Bowman it's like generally she's
generally speaking these towns are are
they're not they're not meant to handle
something like this like this this is a
lawless place days from any it's like
what's with red larch in a police
embryos
that's why we're here well yeah that's
the splash of cold water it's like so
are we supposed to protect them we can
stop this one attack how often are we
gonna have to come back here yeah
expensive yeah it is expensive never
gonna little more in Asia she
Banaras is busy Pangolin style getting
wild on the tail in the back zone and
Saoirse says excuse me for a moment and
she indicates to you walnut for a
private moment
alright yeah I come on over
yeah so cheap she thought it'd be good
yeah
squeeze that baby that's good Oh stead
start over Hey so she walks over to the
to the river which is very near the
washing house that they used to prepare
the or that comes out and she says I
said one you know that
I'm sorry
the loss of the death of Brahma must
have hit you very hard well it just
stares off at the river and it's clear
it should be very obvious that she's
hearing this news for the first time
she was she was an able warrior and
immaculate
holla
a good friend and I know that she was
more to you I
I know a lover's spat when I see it
uh one just kind of crashes down and she
back to everybody else
and she yes it's completely silently
crying
she kneels down next to you
and just place just places her hand just
right on this on the middle of your back
and just offers gentle comfort
and then she starts a lager blaring oh
and it's ugly it's not good it's not no
it's awful
Rosie's there in a microsecond because
she was already suspicious with this
interaction she's probably listening at
the door
she comes in like what the fuck did you
just say to her like evening sobbing she
says I did you say did you mention
Bramah did you even say Brahmas name
makes the baby she doesn't say it
doesn't know how to hold a flesh baby
exactly she holds it like a like a
hoagie
together old folks just so happy
Rosie gathers the like ball of walnut as
much as she can into her tiny little
arms and she's like almond she doesn't
say anything
but this tiny little ball of of one that
had now has a Rosie that goes like like
crying she's like she's dead like really
going for it um you'll you know that
I've never been the biggest fan of her
but seem like the kind of person who may
not really be she's inconsolable like in
our blowing her nose in your clothes
we've seen a body continues to cry it
out
okay but accepting of those that is a
super super good place for us to end the
first episode of the second part of the
second season
what an absolute pleasure to spend this
time with you yet again Hey we're gonna
take a quick break and then we're gonna
come back and then we're gonna talk
about it they're gonna play for another
five hours will do will do top bits
we'll talk about the game and we'll be
best friends you'll be super cool so
don't go anywhere
we're back
you