previously on test C teams
[Music]
so just is there anything we should be
aware of while we're down there
she's like you can make absolutely sure
you don't bring any of these spores out
with it I think we should maybe super
leverage these spores in some way as you
grab a as you grab a handful of them
your hand strikes something firm oh just
beneath the soil this is a tooth I want
to get out of here and I'm gonna teach
you guys how to use your fists and your
feet as deadly assassination tools
[Music]
do you have any resources that are left
over I am not unfamiliar with poisons
this I like
[Music]
we have another day don't we yeah we got
one more sore she is running into the
front of the town uh-huh
blood trickling down her mouth on the
left side and that is when the very
first fire arrow strikes the thatch of
the bunkhouse time is the enemy the
pastor threatens the fastest Brennan you
wouldn't make it past a second and as
the question play a brash and reckless
to choose a cautious solution you saw
was proven in any Sepulchre poker -
don't become the putrid it's that
well-fed I pursue in no mountain too
steep for Dungeon too deep to send
expendable marks up to the top of the
peak of beneath they see Yugi they come
like sharks to it while I swim in that
money build by Carl Barks through it so
since you're national parks drew it I'll
send him home in a natural box with the
post time for most of the parks included
save your breath for a cleric confessor
that there's a lesson that life is a
tenured professor but if you're seeking
my official advice sign on the dotted
line and wish in the choice oh yeah all
yelling you're the weakest fucking link
okay listen up I'm gonna introduce the
show to the people now and I need I need
to know that you're on fucking door well
you're not wrong
hello I am Tycho Brahe hey of Penny
Arcade pax also a min of us Harry weird
run CEO of acquisitions incorporated
Paramore to evil won't stop talking
about outside of the game every
conversation with Jerry and Ryan
revolves around this I'm telling you
that I'm in a position to ship at a
completely new welcome level of
execution people who maybe don't watch
DCA can you give like a 20-second
version of why yes go ahead my character
right another character a letter yeah in
a sort of like you know like how at the
beginning mr. Darcy is like a dick yeah
but then like near the end it's sort of
like he's a little contrite yeah but
he's still like rich as hell
that's that's I go for that last
comparing yourself to mr. Darcy Darcy
Wow Wow jeez might be my character huh
have you read the Bible no no all now
listen we're gonna get back into it but
today I'm here to game run of dragons
Wow you gave me some scotch and now I'm
a mess
but today I'm here to run a game of
Dungeons &amp; Dragons for my friends to my
right
Dragonborn narcissist in our blitz and
sorry you want to see me doesn't know if
she should be angry or delighted it's a
no she knows to cry you heard hey hey my
left not your grandma grandma except in
those rare cases where she is your
grandma's family rosy bee stinger yeah
we will we will indeed to the left of my
grandmama yes oh hey my god
delight the show my left emerging look
at this tiresome oh this crowd I can't
I'm sick of it emerging as though for a
mist shroud cthe risk drought yeah see
he still got it takes on a whole new
kind of visual angle the b-team know for
your health
yeah that's gonna pamphlet yeah yeah
yeah so most most of today's show we
have a new sponsor it's a bunting and
we're just going to talk about no no
dude you need you need to drink
responsibly no no I'm not I'm not
talking about like not drinking I'm
saying like shoes win to plan here
Joseph because it takes yeah make sure
nobody's gonna be fine
it's like ah there's another umma makan
saves up to get bingo get that cross
fill your nostrils yeah
shut up council mayor Labor's please
it's a great pleasure today pursuant
pursuant to this hangout phase there's a
celebratory action as well because on
the discord and on the tweeter we're
gonna put out the C team and be team
logos for you
use and in high dense rich formats Amy
what's a good graphic format jpg yes now
each face games but it gives you thank
you
pick I said where you wanted
representing here what do you say we
play some door engines and raster yeah
what happened
no nothing would bring me more pleasure
what happened last time was that
everything was great because there was a
whole extra day to plant and so our
party after off leisurely Wow leisurely
strolls near the river messing around
with teeth underground editorializing
that's what we call editorializing at
length no I was I was straight up
hundred degree fever like oh that's true
I had to watch the episode again to know
what happened oh wow it was like that it
was you were basically just a part of my
dream vision the the main thing to take
away was that the team did their very
best
along with sorsha and with m''d to
prepare the town of promise for the
imminent attack now at the end of that
day as everyone was preparing to settle
down for the night Crenn are noticed her
mother sorsa
entering the town from the east road
that indeed the very road that our party
entered when they first came to this
town and what she saw was her mother but
running at a high rate of speed and this
was accompanied by a single flaming
arrow that lodged itself in the thatch
of the southernmost bunk house she was
bleeding I would I would describe her
injuries as considerable yes great oh
she is not in a good spot I mean
historically she has come back from
these excursions of hers unscathed she's
just come back with a bundle of other
people's weapons
this time she has those weapons but
they're lodged in flesh so still still
successful run there's a lot of blood
you'd say too much too much so we won't
be fishing well you can fish I feel like
I see I see dinar you're prepared yeah
you've got a challenge you've got a
finish finish mid-battle exactly no I'm
saying that there is a situation where
it's like everybody else is like all
right I need you to I need you to go up
and make sure that nobody's getting into
the trench right oh you need to shore up
the eastern side what you know what's
your contribution fishing look here's
what I here's how I admit I things are
going terrible everyone's getting
overrun yeah everyone's this close
razor's edge of death one Hail Mary shot
in a million catch that lucky ass fish
turns the tide of battle catch the fish
all of a sudden then you got some sort
of a Rube Goldberg mechanism it like
takes out the whole army like a
butterfly like it's a grasshopper that
hits a rock that first six steps are all
bugs it's a grasshopper and answer the
meaning will do it but it knocks the
grasshopper like into a skills program
yeah you see what it mean yeah he learns
Excel starts mentor you know yeah home
refrigeration repair ok for gold for
gold yeah
so that that is the scenario this is not
yet an initiative yeah type of scenario
but refresh so where we were we were
sitting with where we are
yes examining one of those indeed an
apron or was actively trying to collapse
the toy mm-hmm
back in in in a manner like I suggested
before where you're trying to contain
the novelty serpents right that are
occasionally released from a can of
peanut brittle she has been taught by
Rosie to
some operate sick indeed indeed she's
got some basic skills with shadow and
also a kind of knack for the sorceress
even at a even even even at a young age
she is exhibiting these traits a lot
earlier than I've seen them before
oh no as as someone with a lot of
experience with the young well indeed
and including the very young this is a
odd thing you don't know if it's because
the children that you've encountered
thus far have been dumb and bad or good
before
Dragonborn back Dragonborn Dragonborn
childhood maybe dragonburn childhood
might be distinct I mean certainly a
baby snake is in a very very different
position to defend itself than a baby
bird yeah sure you know you know that's
da I said you don't know how like listen
okay so if I say Sasha and she's she's
goofed I mean I can I'll just give you
all the information needs like I say
we're not that's what I make sure that
you know this is a story telling this is
the I'm ready to do this is the storm
will you let walnut tell us before a
storm go understand like I just want to
give you the information you need so
that you can you can respond to
something um
as she is coming in she starts in at a
run and then sees Crenn are and then
continues to come in and this run is
losing steam yep the farther she is
getting toward the center of town
you should being pursued um it is now
nighttime so you are in the middle of
those very very dark morning so you're
in the middle of a very start well hilly
mm-hmm
it was a dark uncivil uncivilized place
um so so they're doing their thing but
um upon seeing her if she is hurt it has
like something her back I'm gonna go try
and
like help her so I'll run up and does
she have like things sticking out of her
back precisely so as she comes in she
kneels in front of Kenard okay and Crenn
are gives her a hug and Saoirse looks up
at you and just nods just like a grim
grave that's another shaking her head
and she speaks her mind she's a nurse in
a in a hushed Dragonborn like a dragon
board speech and
Crenn are runs back grabs what is left
of her toy and then runs at full speed
to the entrance of the mine okay
so shit out of here yes some magic to
that on my way yeah I want to UM do cure
wounds on uh Serge I just say get it
certain just below my only healing spell
immediately in the beginning of the most
important do though so well I feel like
she even do more damage than any of us
yeah so yeah I'll get close and put a
hand on her shoulder and heal her for
five plus eight nice there's mean
thirteen yes the number of the beast
number the Beast I think it is I'm gonna
beast master it is a number hey we know
that thank you so many you can so you
can see like on her back so she watches
from an Argo and as you cast this spell
you can see that her cloak is actually
pinned to her back by several arrows and
as you've cast the spell these arrows
and their arrow heads are sort of being
pushed out pushed out the back and think
you can just hear them like clattering
to the ground one by one crystal I
listen I just I guess have to tell you
what that happens how many were there
give me a number she says I think that
we have incorrect information you mean
we couldn't trust that pigeon I think he
had been operating under some mistaken
auspices was the traitor okay the whole
time I see that coming they're coming
from the south
she says we need to defend this city
from all sides all right I'm gonna run
after Akron are absolutely just cuz
sending a baby into a mine with a shadow
thing seems weird paternal instinct
would kick in and be like what getting
run after absolutely yeah I mean you
your stride is substantially greater
than this baby's so you can you can
absolutely head her off there Rosie
would probably yell after you it's like
you can't go down there we need you I
would keep running hey I need a
perception role from you
big get eaten there of the yum-yum on
nine and your perception is is goose egg
flat right yeah yeah you just use sort
of your you are you find yourself having
just caught up with Caernarfon okay
before we get to the mine
yeah absolutely a right at the mouth of
it it's just like whoa yeah I'd say
where what are you doing where you going
she said mama said Kate why safe
and I guess that makes sense you could
defend the mouth of the cave I guess
yeah it is probably the best place
before her
it's a giant's tomb yeah but all there's
worms down there mushroom right now yeah
I say all right but stay near the front
yeah see you push her in and see where Z
wants to yell it's like remember when I
taught you yeah yeah she just waves from
the mouth and you just sort of see her
shadow enter the mouth of the cavern
stay where I can see you best night
on the menu because this looks on and
says Lysander saves little children they
abide and they endure for this it's like
nope no but and there's a little wistful
look like I can't like that which guy do
you like beautiful innocence what are
you looking at me for this whole town is
going to die well it can't get a
perception role from you Rose a great
mate okay
you need better roles Thanks I want to
sprint to the southern side of town okay
so the southern side of town as you
recall is mostly sort of tall wild
grasses mm-hmm
that's way maybe about waist deep so I
will get low get low get low horrible
I'll get low and whisper to the grass
and you speak with plants which turns it
into a difficult terrain yeah I will do
that
my girl so you see you see walnut make a
break
for the southern and you recall that
there is a sort of ruin half high wall
down there not much of any protection at
all and what do you ask those I say what
do I ask them I say like find yourself
together and hoping that makes like some
little mesh little foot catches you it's
been a while since you went I've never
done it I thought there were vines in a
house that you might as well do but yeah
if you've never done it maybe you have
it but is there a particular way that
walnut like is there a cadence or a
greeting or an opening that she would
use that's different from animals when
she speaks of plants oh yeah what's on a
dating site speak your yeah your dating
profile on a plant site yeah like what's
here what's your interest or headline
what's your hair back um there would be
one but not in this situation and
that'll give me more time to think of
yeah I see the second emergency
emergency
exactly this is not like this is not
socialization time with the pill so you
can see that the moment is sort of
casting a silvery carpet over these tall
grasses and you can see this ocean of
grass just bow to walnut and then raise
itself up and just begin to like shake
and dance and shiver nice P just chunk
by chunk some messages being passed
around in the root system I watch her do
this I smile and I turn I can tell that
you have the southern approach like I
don't know what you just did but I know
that that grass isn't loving you so like
she's got this one and then Rosie starts
to pound her staff on the ground
goodnight and everybody's at in their
homes so she's trying to send out the
loudest on she can and she starts to
yell she's like it's time
everyone what we learned out to me yeah
flight attendants fragments also she's
gamma Turkey was a big boom make like a
big ol like a sonorous like Gong sound
afterward absolutely so the Gathering
Bell you can hear the the rough bunk
sort of creaking as people jump down and
they're in the center of town before
people have emerged a massive whistling
cloud of arrows descends on the
courtyard okay could I am are any of
them close man yeah you know you can do
all you can do all of your you can do
your good stuff on them to the enemy yes
okay so the thing that I want to do and
I think maybe this will gee I don't know
if I need a role but what what I'd like
to do is I don't know who's shooting I
assume they're too far away but as these
start to come I want to grab one out of
the air and look at it as the rest are
falling around me and just whisper like
it's here I mean let's do a couple of
these what's your AC 14 14 was right
you've been missed by six of these nice
oh you're looking pretty good so it just
like effortlessly like like plucking an
apple is there you just take it out of
the air and I come in examine is there
anything any telltale marks that are
interesting or their feathers crafted of
something interesting no some rugged a
speedo this is yeah let's whatever the
REI equivalent is December Hills nice
great I mean I'm really good okay so she
cast a look back at Walnut and then
throw zero away yes so people are
gathering at the doors they don't
they're not sure if this is a good place
to come out we have unlimited ammo now
though that's true yeah what bright side
anybody got like a neo Matrix ability
where we can turn all the arrows back
and a love mama you just looked at your
spell she drew a level six
um well I guess the thing Rosie would
probably do would be to fuck I don't
know if there's anything we can do I
guess
grandma man see ya tell me more ooh um
tell me what you gonna do with this
granny bitch
we're gonna do with all this guy messy
all this grandma it's the open your
chrome fancy Oh
so which direction the arrows coming
from they are coming from the east as
you can tell which is the road indeed
okay so then what's Rosie would like to
do is to whisper to her staff lovingly
affectionately making up for lost time
and she's going to extend her hand
outward and with using grandma Mansi
erect a wall blocking off the path from
the road describe this wall um it is and
you shall have it actually it's a solid
mass of like thick black shadow but
interspersed everson because she's using
this extra on the staff of the master
you can actually see star light
twinkling in this wall so it's almost
like she erected a whole new slice of
the sky in the deaths of it yes right oh
yeah this probably there's probably a
point like in your vision where it just
looks like these pillars are coming down
right yeah that is a awesome image and
it's not I don't think it's something
that they couldn't shoot through but at
least now they can't see where they're
shooting well exactly like I think
what's what's more likely well I'll tell
you what happens okay when it happens
karissa out
you have any any non hallmark
observations
I'm just beautifully today just the huge
oh yeah
there's I'm surprised at this at the
tears coming out of all of the eyes 40
immediately dehydrated way too much
fluid sale Creek okay so you just you
just put that wall up on the east side
on the road
yes so it's like directed here right
describe though where is the where is
that hill where we were building a true
story there's a bug of the cave terrible
it's in everybody nice that mental map
he filed it away no I would like a
perception role from you Chris trout
take a chance right
I will advantage it do you good
perception yeah I'm okay maybe exactly
yeah Kim a prize okay so that one was a
21 and this one is a five but when I get
for Terry rejected so in the in the site
that is granted to you by these alien
eyes mmm you turn your attention to that
hill mmm the hill we're just a day ago
when there was so much time to prepare a
trench was dug by the village of promise
and the stand stone walls were erected
on each side you can see for lack of a
better term meet up cresting the ridge
of this hill you can see entities some
useless mortal flesh attempting to make
a home of the town's defensive
French is that so it would be clear is
the is the idea that this is me there's
nothing that my vision gave to me it it
the property of my eyes parsed this it
confers it it's like oh this is prey
this is something to eat mm-hmm and
there may no home yeah is this also
interpretation of my eye no no this this
much is this much is simply factual they
have crested this Ridge from the other
side of the hill and have now made a
defensive Bastion for themselves in your
defensive Bastion
I see so they've they've like slithered
into the trench and are like fortifying
it correct our trench now do they do
they move as people though what Harper's
familiar to me yeah yeah but there's
always an editorial aspect just some of
these tile action right yeah who more
better stand up fellows can't see that
trench gosh I might hold because what
I'd want to do is confer with so I'm
beside you Rosie
and um I speak very quickly got two
options I I can throw a hypnotic pattern
but that is not gonna catch that many
uh-huh okay or we can get everybody in
the cave or away and I'm just gonna
throw a demon in there and I'm looking
I'm getting the vial of blood out Mike
we have other there other choices yeah
got my Bibles out there enough blood um
I am plan to plan B let's let's do that
one let's get these people safe and then
I just I want to see you rock and roll
it's not gonna be me doing that work no
I'm gonna be credit you're the manager
yeah you definitely manager develop
their career
mmm-hmm delegation skill yeah it's a
challenge yeah um so Rosie will say um
that she's thrown her staff she's
erected this wall she's she's been
screaming and so her hair is kind of
like wild around her face coming out of
the bun and she looks very disheveled
and she says I'm going to get the people
into the cave you summon whatever it is
you have to yeah cuz I the last thing I
want is for this thing to just start
opening houses like like cans yeah what
look like so many graves boxes raises
our sponsor this week they also make
dice so so Rosie you are starting to
martial people that's what it sounds
like and what give me this process even
though they have been trained by me to
fight they've also been trained to
listen and so yes a part of part of the
martial process is being able to order
them around the project management from
last episode so they I am going to get
them in ranks and it's it's not it
doesn't sound panics it's not I'm not
worried I'm worried about them because
they're squishy don't worry about you
guys you're gonna be fine
but but Rosie is commanding them like a
general yeah and she there's no mercy in
her voice and she's like this is where
we're going uh we are on vacation with a
grandmother I mean I know yeah I know
where the I know where the backstop in
essence for yeah so she's she looks them
all she's she's looking at these like
very pathetic ranks lots of kids and old
folks and she says um our task is to
defend the caves we are holding out
there they're attacking from above so
that is going to place be the place
where we are safest you'll go now okay
so you be immediately begin marshaling
them over and they had begun to
distribute themselves from the other
bunkhouse
because by this point the roof of this
I mean euphemistically the roof
euphemistically but also literally is on
fire and it has been allowed to burn
yeah we don't need no water well yeah I
mean water is plenty available you can't
have it so do not let sin what is your
next when after dinner took ran after
preneur and she's in the cave be hanging
out near the mouth of the cave trying to
slim in Clark more yeah we smoked Kate
all right I'm sorry you know yeah it's a
it's a glandular defect I'm very
sensitive about it
but no so let's no let's stop and talk
faster you see Rosie coming from the the
center I'm assuming that you're using
the fortifications to try to you're not
me
oh yeah what yeah this is mean this is
going from here to here the arrows are
not so they're coming wild at this point
so it's wheres exactly until so see you
so you're at the mouth of the cave you
can see her yeah basically evacuating
the village into this place so dinar
would summon Clark more I guess takes
ten minutes I got there well there was
ten minutes of other stuff happened
thank you okay someone to see what all
of the grass stuff and the groomer man
see Ewing he was over there just miss
now as everything's happening elke Clark
more yeah that's how he talks yellowish
can I please have you spoke I never in
Leila voice it's exactly like so when we
are ushering as I see the the people
being ushered into the cave tomorrow
would take Clark more over to sorsa and
like get her by the rain or bar just
like up on and rider yeah no I'm over
there I don't know it's not that far
right no
which closed its rate a picture and then
try to help her over to the cave not
knowing if she's still how one did she
is he/she/it
she lives at the cave if she likes you
and she's like absolutely not kids in
there yes for a reason yeah well won't
fight at the mouth how you feeling you
feel fully healed you need a top-off you
got can we I love it
I love a perception check from you to
determine this sort of thing perceptions
nineteen that's quite good she is she's
on her feet with a combination of just
like of valor and like a miscalculation
perhaps of her ability to retain blood
can I add something here what I like in
my head cannon is that dinar rolled and
you know rolled an 18 but the reason
your roll was so high is because you
deeply actually care about Saoirse so
you're actually like investigating
what's wrong authoritarian exactly it's
like degrees of care no no this it's
like the mean image where it's like this
is like like a massive dinar head if his
brain is glowing
yes yeah this is out of the bottom it's
using his entire brain he thinks he can
keep that off this ship will sink so
let's get attached she says I will allow
you just let me help you would you just
let me help you I will allow you to take
me to the top of this Ridge I well so in
my evaluation does she look like she saw
her does she meet anybody know she's
definitely hurt but her hurt is at a her
ability to succeed even though those
conditions it's not like a normal person
oh yeah I get that she's tough alright
yeah she's real tough yeah real - I get
it look look we all get it but I
especially get yeah yeah yeah so how's
she doing she's okay yeah she's actually
registered I
oh look I know I are you a giver I would
you like to cast a healing yes I will
lay on hands oh man touch your hand or
this is very important to lay on them
all right so I go like this ten healing
extreme this is courting yeah yeah this
is phase one of the courtship I'm gonna
everything you try to do yeah I'm going
to make official lar as to like the
Dragon returns of dragon boy yeah all
right so I'm reaching I pull out her
front tooth yeah I pull out my front
tooth awesome yeah yeah you know real
fast verb complete what is actually her
hand as I help her on to Clark more I
will do sir 10 more health points
exactly so and then I will ride her up
to the top of the hill as yeah did I
stutter
I mean it's intense speed so so you you
were you were below you reach down grab
her hand it's clearly a trick like she
is she has granted the healing and you
can tell that she is she tries to make a
she tries to be so tough that she
doesn't require it or need it but she
only she is only able to eject about
half of her refusal eventually she
decides it's not could find investment
but she places her left arm sort of
around your midsection and then you can
hear her you can hear her blade exit the
sheath mmm behind you and then I'll take
up to the top of hill like she said
absolutely now it's time to get some
initiative I'm not going to use it for
this exact thing we're gonna want to
have it
I want a band on this you can have
advantage on initiative I want
oh I'm not questioning I would take it
but it's so wasted telling me it
wouldn't even matter you'd roll one two
- yeah three okay - I know a few recipes
here twelve so bad go I'm a 14 Oh give
me that
okay perfect so Clarke Moore is quite
adept at this sort of terrain he is able
to manage his way up this hill but it is
a constant hail of arrows on the way up
to this trench serpentine serpentine
pattern go what's what's your AC
18 okay so you are the you are the
primary face of this operation up here
no you catch an arrow in your shoulder
hand out for MMA huh didn't hurt other
other arrows yeah other roles are
sailing around but none of the rest of
them come in contact with you but it's a
constant sound but as you as Clarke
Moore basically clips up you can hear
his you can hear his hook on the stone
wall that W built it right mm-hmm yeah
you can you hear on it and you are
basically standing in the middle of this
trench the Sanyal is on the southern end
of the town of problem one year war elk
yeah cuz the trench was cut we got wall
trench yeah I think it was on the
southern big wall is on the southern
side of it
it is relative to the trench so so you
were basically in like Clark or is now a
massive feature in this thing and
looking looking to the left and right
you can see probably twelve archers
how far in the trench or yeah they are
all embitters in the trench yeah they're
all immediately around you dummies
didn't bother telling analysts so I I'm
up on a wall and then they were down in
a trench he clipped over the wall all
right say why'd you do that
boy he stay only on the wall stay on the
safe side
all right well and we're just gonna rise
through them go first I'm gonna take my
sword out - all right no you have yeah
so I'm swinging all inside so it's just
swinging on the other anywhere galloping
through you're just weed whacking our
way through no this swing is you just
need to like grab it and just hold the
backside I'm just like to leave is
holding the shadow council know in their
perpetual gleaming wisdom saw fit to
reveal a bit of vars maelys lore okay to
dinar that's now don't know it's true so
you have a martial ability in addition
to your ability to command your conic
entitlement you have an ability called
the wrath of VARs malice which allows
you to leverage your Dragonborn sword in
an AoE like a a wide pattern that
strikes multiple enemies in a forward
cone it's not like a like a whirlwind
attack yeah basically it's focused on
the front but it strikes it strikes
anyone in front of how far the range
that the range that they didn't know
about this part of it but the range that
we have here is 15 feet
pretty good so fifteen-foot come in
front
yeah I'm just just because I'm curious
so it's but it's sword based so am I
like throwing this or you know you like
emitting an energy my this there is an
incredible and that's just a force wave
there and like a concussive there is a
chance we could see this move you decide
well I want to know all about it because
I'm nothing you see exactly and then and
then all the all the aspects of it will
be revealed but if there are enemies
that are in front of you within a
15-foot cone they this is gonna do one
trick they hate okay so this is uh this
is my an alternate alt yeah it's a cost
to it just how much damage does it do
so you hear you hear you hear sorsha you
hear her armor buckle and scrape as she
goes off of the back of clark more and
starts to walk the opposite way tunnel
trench alright just ambling yeah look at
her watch yeah her back to the fight
just like I well I say okay there's this
trench is full of people on both sides
Oh feel like being melted on a steed is
still the best place to be but you're
both hey have this conversation whatever
I'm having nice as I say that to her
like under my breath but still loud
enough that she can hear like my horse
yeah it's pretty cool me and star stuff
but whatever you want to make a Clark
more you first must emit the universe I
will use my new power as well it's right
there give it a try
I want to tell these ponies gotta listen
gal gallop know it's sad that's the end
of the day it's just sad it's just I'm
just a sad excuse for a boy all right
I do it okay now you tell me
you know a lot of the onus on me I don't
know what this is you need to be strong
now and forever yeah even with the
knowledge make me recite fish tax no
there's not gonna be any fish backside
all I want all I want from you
maneuvers of this kind always have a
very particular way of setting the blade
at first that's all I'm trying to get
from you okay I want your I want your
red anime intro first part oh my god I
just want to know how all right how you
how you draw okay how are you draw and
how you place it and then I'll take it
from there
all right that's a what if we what if we
sauce it this as such I don't buy doing
this but still not losing my my one
vomit ability right so bring the sword
up close right to my face and I whisper
a small prayer to VARs maelys and as you
whisper the prayer down the blade just a
little acid vomit spills out while you
say it and then when you do the the wave
attack it flicks it out like that's
that's the that's the ranged part of it
yeah yeah no it's like the blade words
yes it's right I think I accept it's the
blade barks hey so you so you bless this
ya mess yeah you bless this mess like a
snort at the end and when you draw the
blade back over your shoulder I mean you
and you can see like they're all trying
to get ready the people who are at the
end of this trench are they're trying to
knock arrows but all of their fellows
are directly in front of them the ones
in front are dropping the bow and
getting sword the people in the bow in
the middle they're not sure a hundred
percent they don't know where this shit
or go blind is the euphemistic term some
gonna be enough yeah exactly in each
other's eyes okay um
when the blade is set up on the shoulder
and you sweep it across in the
wake of it there is a brilliant gleaming
copper wing you can just see the plane
of this wing along the strike and it
extends a full 10 feet beyond the end of
the blade and on both sides the rock
walls are sheared in half and the men in
Merritt sharps company that he is trying
to subdue this December Hills with
largely meet a similar fate here in the
middle hmm twice did you see yes so you
turn back you cut five of them in half
huh so it's just this this massive
destructive plane of force shears to
walls on both sides yeah they just they
just crumple and fall in the middle of
it that you want
Saoirse to be impressed that assertion
is doing her own work on the opposite
side you know she's moving she is
basically moving from place to place
just target to target mm-hmm
absorbing damage deflecting damage as
you as you turn around trying to get the
thumbs up on both sides of you you can
see half of an arrow
nice split and just collapsed further
down the the category okay now we are in
real initiative are you want to do
initiative now for real now roll up yes
Oh
again no no okay I have all the numbers
I just wanted to have that in my back
pocket so I could yeah I'm like I know
where I'm at yeah I'm just standing
there like it's one action
oh that's buddies ready to go no yeah
it's in the same way that like it's one
action to like pull the chain on a
lawnmower and then it just goes just
take some wild that chain give you
trouble yeah yeah it could be a couple
hours this is the first time there were
some integrator doing yeah this is bad
news and I you know usually you talk to
your dungeon master before you take a
spell like this mention it are you gonna
summon this in the trench that I'm in
well this is what's now don't share is
actually my it's like I see you going
across usually I've made my way laddle
atlatl drinking vial of blood have to
drink a little bit for me a little bit I
just split it you split it in half one
that done grass
thank you thank you
take that I took that advantage for
nothing how are you increased so looking
around I see these thatched roofs
starting to yeah right right now it's
right now it's primarily fixed on the
left side yeah but it's spreading fast
and then as is the way this is the town
itself is kind of in a valley between
hills and so the air the night breeze
thing is just being is being put to its
work so what I want to do and I see
everyone is gone
like I said all the towns when I turn
around from the plants so I this I was
whispering the class I turn around
everyone's gone well all the townspeople
are gone and I can see it's not much in
the distance my decorative notes go that
far so I don't even know if I can see
what you're doing over there and but I
see all this fire and so I'll cast
watery sphere which is a 10-foot radius
and is normally a great spell to use
against foes which is what I want to
know for cuz it can restrain people
present
hmm it's like that episode of heard of
sailing yeah but instead I can move it
30 feet so I will summon it and start
using it to douse the roof fires don't
fuck with druids how big how big is it
so the temperature yes Jesus and the
radius yeah ten foot across radius how
long's it's a grant it can stick around
for the ranges 90 feet one minute okay
that's great absolutely yeah so tell it
so how is she guiding it around like
straight up tumbled yeah very water man
meticulous like I slow
yeah like rolling it over everything
making sure everything's choked out and
then moving to them right absolutely
yeah so you basically yeah you're there
this is just hot wind is whipping your
hair around and then it starts out that
starts out just this the size of a berry
and then immediately a moment expands
I'm sorry are you gonna apply it really
like pre-soak Oh am I gonna preset yeah
I mean if I got through all the fire is
it right now with this with your 20 foot
water ball that's a town what's your
intention what is your what is your
intention with my water or um so does
the fire and then I'll start moving it
to the roofs that have not been douse
and just start wetting everything I'm
just gonna moisten the whole house
multi-world insurance his wrist round Oh
drench warfare that's good for you like
this is the level of execution you get
from the c1 action I agree completely he
yells at everyone else when they make
funds yeah cuz my aren't good they're
not puns delete the show yeah
ideas concepts to dissect consider
exactly I can't wait I am honestly
genuinely excited to hear how you put
this together yeah that's her Oh a demon
oh yeah someone I have some I've given
it some thought so
so what are you summoning - well now I
use the thing we couldn't work this out
- but if you want that data yeah I've
got it I'm gonna need it you need that
but I don't know if cthe wrist is adept
at like selecting what you get I have
one that I think he's got the catalog he
has yeah he knows what we're talking
about
does he have like a kid at Christmas
going through the series is it five no
I'm looking for the specific beasts veto
here I'm gonna tell you right now I'm
just cuz and this is specifically chosen
because Rosie might be able to do some
of it is a shadow demon okay off the
rails play york for the enjoyment of the
shadow finebros we just stick it in this
shadow pencil check this out that's you
think about it yeah it's your demon this
is what you look like there's not cute
before I do this I won't understand the
lay of the land and you got you put a
road now you put a road to the east
where where are we aware of bandits
coming from I know we might right now
that the main that you need you know
that arrows have come from the east and
you know that this trench up on the hill
definitely has foes as well right now
that's buddies - that's that unlock yes
that's your that's your level of
awareness okay and you got the south so
I'm not I'm not doing it okay okay you
for that faith Wow - she can't - no it's
fine I put a water demon in that River
thing that really can't come - no no no
I like him I don't like I don't like
monkeys
it's not interesting to me exactly okay
so should you have the do you have the
the spell I will look I will let you in
and I will express it it's important for
them to know exactly what you're doing
as well yes fourth level conjugation one
action sixty feet okay V S&amp;M get them
all and you get that sweet mayor's blood
that's what I keep I got some of that I
got a violet to that and then
concentration up to a full hour last
longer dr. dr. Fowler demon been
substantiated for longer than an hour
there's got to be a better way you
choose the demons Titus yeah
demon appears in a nice type space with
the leg man I mean anything you want
appears that are not unoccupied space
you can see within range demon
disappears when it drops as your two
points are when the spell ends up to an
hour or a stop concentrating roll
initiative for the demon has its own
turns when you summon it on each of your
turns after you can command it if you
wish you know command it spends its turn
attacking any creature it within reach
that has attacked it at the end of each
of its turns it must make a charisma
saving throw it has disadvantage on this
throw if you say it's true name I don't
think I don't know that cuz wrist does
that I just know that on a failed save
it continues to obey me on a successful
save the demon my control ends for the
rest of the duration and it attacks
whatever it feels like what could go
wrong again most it I'll put that in the
trash an uncontrolled demon doesn't
disappear for one D six rounds if it
still has hit points wow so it's just
loosen for this particular boy at 66 so
he's a big boy
you want this let him drive it
I'll adjudicate yeah and as part of
casting the spell I can circle the
ground with that delicious blood well
it's large enough come to encompass my
space and I can create a space that the
demon will not trespass
and I could also summon it into a circle
if I just want it to be my friend look
like you hang out on the bus with her
yeah pretty good like home base circle a
room and believe it in their room and
just having a mole everything in the oh
yeah they never leave absolutely okay so
that's basically all you need to know
absolutely
so tell me so tell me about that this
will only end well so where are you
where are you pouring this out all right
okay first of all Chris is not gonna
make a circle he's and there's not a
measure to respect the circle no icon
and he starts to think about in the
blood is pouring but then he just draws
sort of a line a little bit back from
your star wall okay
so if they do breach the wall spell that
would greet them yeah it's just gonna
hang out also I can command it unless I
lose weight so you're summing it into
the circle no no I'm just I just draw
line now that'll put it it'll like trip
it up briefly it's like a little blood
how big is the circle oh no I just saw
wine stops there mama
it doesn't work that way at all with you
he's never done it before we have to
know we have to test it to understand it
so I shove away those thoughts of that
that shiny Sun who cares I know I'm in
there yes it's distracting I gotta focus
up on my demons and I start to issue a
call just like speaking to places
unknown sorry
hello I'm look I need a I'm looking for
a greater demon I'm trying to find a
just to come out I don't understand how
it's coming and I'm gesturing in ways
that I have not done before a little
smile
starts to spread it was like this is
some muscle memory has is doing the rest
of the work I want to put that demon
right right across that line for safety
I've convinced myself it's gonna keep me
how you gonna do you get on one side of
mine he tries to go around you jump over
this island you've got to keep going
around he'll get you dolled a couple
rounds of this yeah he's gonna be down
he can be done this he's he only speaks
abyssal and telepathy so it's okay
he's got 120 feet of telepathy hmm fruit
by the foot yeah so gushers yeah I want
I want that shadow demon and I imagine
that it is like a gosh maybe it because
it's shadow and it's right next to your
wall yeah exactly so the wall steps
through or I guess is it is it like have
like a ghost tale hell yeah I guess
incorporeal is it as it goes out yeah
yeah then I imagine it yeah that's
that's it that's how it should be so I
have you as you commit fully to these
authentically nefarious gesticulations
that is an evil dance that comes from
somewhere else you you can feel the
expenditure of the energy but you don't
think you don't think that it worked you
it seems like something would have come
through and then against this starfield
wall of Rosie's you just see two eyes
burn I'm all that startled I'm very so
it's created a friend it looks like you
exactly like this is you just been
waiting to be the right level to summon
friends from beyond right from Annie a
truly evil place I don't need onion no
no friend it started the two eyes are
there and then it just continues to shed
light and shed light and shed light
until it's actual shape which is
something
like a bat just the top part of a bat is
it the only way to describe it would be
to like dip into some love crafty and
stuff you have to describe it as a
commingling of other natural things
right I like the idea of when he is
coming out when it is coming out of the
start you can you see the burning eyes
but the only other way you can tell its
shape is because the Starlight is
Shipyard yeah yeah they just work right
he's he's so opaque that the the lights
like you can see their gravitational
lens exactly yeah and then so the eyes
are there and then you can just see this
crack of light below it and then when it
falls open it's exactly the same color
as the eyes it says I greet you warlock
I am the grave of men all friend
[Applause]
feasting what do you have any cool shit
a doer
maybe not spend my turn admiring this
great shadow boy so good are all the
people in the mind yeah yeah they are
there was a couple stragglers a very
very brief glance okay let's bring a
step yeah good okay so everybody safe us
yeah the burlap lady is making sure
nobody gets in too deep
she's waving that sack around rosy then
she doesn't have her staff so she is
she's got the ability to do some more
grandma man see if the occasion would
call for it but I think what Rosie would
do is hold on to it just in case
shadow is needed to confine this
unpredictable monster oh she wants to
add that she wants to have that in your
back pocket yeah yeah I got plenty of
charges but I just wanna make sure so
some go wrong ah yeah thank you but
that's kind of why I wanted you to do in
the first
um yeah I think Rosie's just gonna hold
and defend them out of this cavern that
kicks ass yeah trust me we're gonna
we're gonna be doing this stuff for a
while
you'll have an opportunity okay great
it's gonna be some hot shit
Dennard blitz in you are situated in
this trench yep before you there perhaps
seven more archers doing their absolute
level best okay um what's she after
after having seen what was there what's
uh Sasha dawn yeah yeah yeah she is
moving in her direction as you engage
with with this she doesn't know she
doesn't look like she's being
overwhelmed or anything no no you have
you haven't seen anything like that yet
okay um so there's how many in front
seven they about 15 feet away you feel
on the cone shape yeah you can move
closer and you can well do I have to I'm
saying how close right yeah yeah yeah
because these can everybody who is in
prison yeah there's no dead right yeah
well is it it depends on how you think
of it there's either twice as many of
them or they're all dead
yeah um all right I yield ass or should
I go watch me this time trot a little
farther up and as I'm trotting up hold
the blade again no there they are now
like they're jumping up on each other
yeah trying to go faster try oh no no
you know I'm trying to get to the top of
the walls like there it's like um rats
trying to flee a ship yeah well then I
pick up the paint so they can't get away
and then hold the sword and well say
he's holding this the newer sword sort
of the sorcerer guy
oh shit he says his little prayer up
along the blade and the little acids
dribbling out it's like lighting up the
rooms in it light up pain yeah they just
think just a little
just a little bit's dribbling out it's a
very acidic prayer yeah whispers is
prayer too it was the wait different
from yours is it is it technically a
better sword you like mad about it no I
think it's the same in every way but
stats but in terms of decor he's not
wrong like it's deeply and inscribed
this is a lovingly made instrument here
I've got runes it's yeah I'm down it
so what handles the same more wrath yeah
let's do it to it mm-hmm
so he's your first name is first so you
said they blade no tell me about the
tell me about the angle and direction of
this strike where are they so like I say
I mean they are jumping on they're
crushing each other trying to get out of
this yeah like they are going above us
seen it some are trying to get up and
out then at a somewhat slanted 60 degree
angle like try to whip that way to start
start low start low low in the back
exactly yeah so so yeah exactly so you
said you said the blade tilt you know
and bring it up and this time it's just
starting in the earth there is a peeling
roar that peeling banana that
accompanies this flash of light that
goes up through through men and indeed
through the wall and the earth so that
as you cut through the last few of these
archers the ground itself just slough
off it just falls down in a pile over
the men that have been destroyed yeah
there aren't very very proud of himself
yeah every time he does this he always
goes
his name very nice if you like to check
in and make sure social watching yeah oh
yeah and afterwards she watching just
she sees that one she is and you see you
see someone raise a sword behind her and
run toward her and then they just fall
down and she pulls her blade out like
this so I'm just one yeah what about
this yeah like fine so to the east of
the city you can hear the rumble of
hooves outside the wall proper and at
the at the announcement of these hooves
grave of men is starting to like snort
and sniff grave of men is literally his
name yeah didn't say I'm man said I'm
grave of men - oh yeah ' yeah he's just
like snorting and hawing and scratching
at the at the wall so from that from
that the east of the wall it's
impossible for us to see from here out
right we just know that they are on
their way now it's time for the the
grave admin is there any way for him to
get out of this wall having how solid is
it well he's been summoned forth I
believe he's fully formed he's just on
the other side of the blood the wall of
that trail yeah yeah yeah I think he
could have sensibly just move away from
us and go toward the road he just at
this point and I think probably the
unbroken circle is actually the thing
that you can traverse hold on a second
so he's got a speed of 30 feet but he
could fly also there oh yeah yeah it's
good to go highs this wall uh well I
think he can just pass through it yeah
that's this because it's a medium that
he is in the indeed in DeMuth
my suspicion is that it's not actually a
barrier kind of yeah you made all that
intend me harm that's my this is my
directive hey Jen so he the light of his
features sort of disappears against the
star field and then in an instant he
sort of flings himself forward through
this medium and he slows as he's in it
and then he's launched forward through
it but seeing exactly what he'd be doing
on the other side would be challenging
right now you'll most have to use your
ears I suspect walnut on grass happy to
keep it dead keep it damp I don't hear
those horses coming right that you can
feel them in the ground but they're
coming from the east yeah
do I can do perception or let's see if I
see anyone coming from the south
I'm all about this yeah absolutely I
also underserved on the west it's a
river no 20 yeah that's quite good you
can see in the just in the wave here
it's a parent when someone is trying to
traverse it mm-hmm it is obvious you can
see at least five at least
hmm great how how do you want to ruin a
day whose day do I want to run today
somebody's anybody in the grass Oh
tasty I did okay
grass the blades so it's a 3d 10+1 beat
oh no it's just a 3d ten okay so I will
drop my watery sphere having moistened
some glasses
where do you deposit weird right deposit
it yeah I'll just drop it off like in
the middle of town okay just make it
flashy you see you just like let it go
yeah I just kinda like everyone comes
back to the house as their link glad
we're safe but our hardwood floors this
water damage all of our documents um the
documents I will use call lightning
which is a 60 foot radius 10 foot cloud
that all within 100 feet of me and it's
3d 10 which means daytime it's multiple
targets this boy orbs of things it's
awesome
this a 60 foot radius 10 foot plant cell
Haley yeah definitely
situated over these crawlers yes and see
what I do one one what this happen some
9 damage of possible 30 but you did it
to a bunch of people yep
and I say oh yes and I say and there's
more where that came from
it's just a warning shot across the bow
yeah exactly
that's my scare I just want them to know
I'm here yes kids apt you bugs yeah hey
Christmas job gosh wouldn't you do it
was relaxing I'm real curious about
what's on the other side of that but
Walter your great lover can you feed it
um in so as far as I know I don't think
I could see up and into the trench or
what's going on up there
it's a you'd be hard yeah here well you
hear things it sounds like a lot of
vomiting and swords and given that their
archers I feel like
that's a good thing yeah it's not theirs
they're vomiting though yeah where are
you I'm at the mouth of the cave okay so
you're at the cave um I let's just go
home huh
so everybody's up there except for you
I'm gonna come down to the to the
southern edge the field yeah so you you
basically come shoulder-to-shoulder with
walnut dog rats
yeah out over this silvery sea of grass
you can see the last wisps of a cloud oh
wait yeah and yeah smell of ozone I'm
trying to be very serious but I like
[Laughter]
it's not really a concept yeah what is
help all these sub stress assets that's
a very philosophical lectures today
walnut you tried and I play out across
the grass I don't know if you can see it
and I go there's five here anything you
can do to help gosh so you guys need to
concentrate you maintain this I see you
control over yeah that's right so you
can't help so you can talk to walnut no
he can sorry yeah you tell me so be
careful about that yeah a lot of the
good stuff I got is Frank that's what I
recall yeah and I don't think I have
anything that took a stone which is what
I would love to do there's no dark
that's concentration i shit yeah you
really got to think about those milk
good
yes some grass okay well no problem just
water back yeah drink I can make a
sandwich or something are you hungry is
anyone then yeah then there's really
nothing else I can that I would want to
do you will yeah I mean I could do like
a like a easy one if some is visible I
would like to like let's let's let's
harass somebody's be a mom yeah that's
rough him up yeah yeah okay then that's
what I'm asking for
who can I see anything I'm just grass
well no you can you can see like it's
obvious where they are at in this in
this like tightly knotted grass okay
they can't pass through it with that
being like comically obvious no grass
pass no thanks pass so let me do this
then I've been a while since I did a
tentacle lash been a while and they
never work as we well why would they
start today Rick sendo never start yeah
one successful whip we haven't not in
two years
no yeah exactly so let's see so any one
of them that I'm any spot that I yeah to
my best of my knowledge contains a buddy
yeah contains a banded I want to see if
I can pull him how far away with it out
here yeah just worry about 20 feet away
yeah it's further than I can yeah I can
lash you can't we have them all right
misery free
so you see be spend a lot of time
thinking other things you could do
there's so many things in D&amp;D that you
can do not doing and like the idea that
there's like moving ants in the grass
like shit bunny yeah it's like a
towering old man yeah sorry dude with
this shirt this is innocent bystander
yes I can start a fire just like the
field on fire is this like wheat stuff
they want to eat later just grass these
are just is just a rolling plain of
grass south of okay
I'm putting fires out yeah not this time
that was it and now it's gone
I'm CAG neutral but I made a demon you
said that a few things
that's my chaotic basis so that's
terrible train as you come over and you
brag about your demon you can come you
can command the demon he says supportive
things to him all night
you should he's good is he
it's it's everything it's the bedrock of
a good relationship no horses I wonder
if it's invisible only yeah oh yeah if
you summoned a demon tell to stop those
horses whoo not you
you're you're a brave men but tell me
the other larger mammals appeal what a
Veck wine I know not well he's talking
to grave of men yeah exactly the way
grave immense hawk
yeah exactly me you we have to light
himself up that's yes like aurilla it's
a plight it's yes in yes and say they
need a day it's like when you go down
south and like adopts a southern accent
hey y'all laugh-in like five minutes
yeah Ireland right you leave the fucking
Airport hit how does a horse meat on the
other side of that shadow that's so how
am i playing that's marking for this he
says it I am delighted to discover so
but you were gonna be in control of
grave I'll do the okay
I'll do any dialogue that's required
sure but you choose what you how you
want him to do it and I'll tell you what
he sees out there all right yeah so he
so he has he has projected himself
through this solid shadow medium lends
himself out launched as though from a
cannon on the opposite side of it and in
front of him he sees no less than 10
riders yeah
I don't know that he's God hey guys say
it it's a different flow don't have to
do your way he doesn't seem to have any
he doesn't have any like area stuff but
how are these how are these riders lined
up since maybe we can trip up the first
just oh just outline like they are
writing
oh that's foolish of them I'm very
excited to do that not front to back
like a wide sort of a phalanx type yeah
let's see is there anything I could do
to confer advantage on attack role if
you want to use if you want to use
Chris's advantage that's okay oh he
would love to thank you so he's gonna go
ahead and just do a classic just a
traditional shadow demon claw melee
attack bog-standard
you know what uh yeah tried and true
let's see yeah +5 to hit reach of 5 feet
yes so he's gotta approach the first
rider slash at him how do we do that
I'm not a melee guy how does that work
can I do what he it's luckily it's all
right there in the block that's your LD
20 minute I will let's try I was just
gonna say it doesn't need to understand
maybe wizard no more Wow motherfucker is
in more than kindness to telephonist
that's true I Rosie all she do is hit so
no matter what so advantage is take a
nice so that's gonna be a 17 and this a
the creme of Metro Council indeed a
creature of your own native plains your
humble servant servant
hey indeed all the way down we keep
delivering that incredible product
what's that it was the first way is if
these two goblin gall stones oh yeah
found here verifying to look at even
more terrifying on your home table
thanks level up we will get those
shipped out to you know this is
absolutely the case so they so grave men
looks on this onrushing phalanx with
curiosity
and delights with us yeah a lot by the
way he is striking at the horse not a he
does 46 plus three damage what a fucking
asshole that horse to be it's a psychic
exactly it's that even with a claw was
here nine that's gonna be a fourteen yes
fourteen plus three seventeen on that
horse so he he's never seen anything
quite like this before horse and he is
delighted any of this oh okay
this is all this is all new a horse man
he gets out his shadow document no it's
like I self-empowering like what if I
could be a grave for more than a man
yeah exactly
it's it's like it's like you know at
this point in my career he draws his
hand back behind him and sweeps it
forward and just like when he began to
pass through the solid lensing medium of
the shadow he just drags his hand
through the horse from from the front to
the back hmm
and then the claw on the outside catches
the strap that holds the saddle yeah and
so he just brings it forward clips
straight through it and the rider falls
directly off of the back onto his own
back on the ground in front of grave of
men who looks upon him with keen
interest shadow counsel their labors
Phase II all of a sudden I was not aware
of it but I guess it's time for the
break yeah so we're gonna do the break
and then we're gonna come back and then
it's gonna be more see team you'll see
you'll see you can hold me to this don't
go anywhere
look right back I'm Jeffrey K Harkins
welcome back to this test see tapes the
Ryan show I hope you all enjoy exactly
who's right exactly
Amy what's in here like a sweet good boy
imma hurt nobody hurt nobody
yeah no walnut dum-dum grass I'm
punching you wanna done grass yeah tell
me what happens next
listen these turns I haven't gone in
several rounds oh well I was wrong
it is it I got fucked up because of
where is Rosie Rosie bee sting hey first
of all like I need a perception role yes
you can see all the people come from the
West
well yeah 12 yeah that's not a bit water
vision I mean there's nothing there
yeah when you ask for perception there's
never anything no there isn't
I just I just I just want to make that's
gonna give you NephCure I know that
rolling is fun and if I might set my
whole turn yeah you're done yeah you're
done with the game actually okay how far
away am i from these these ceilings
these goings on I mean these do these
shapes are fucking gone from you like
they're literally on the other side of
the village if you're at the north end
of the village
oh yeah you're the south end that's um
so I think you may take your turn to get
over there I look at that's what you
think
Moses some because they're Jewish by
Manhattan 10 15 feet long how long is
the village no for real I hope not 60
feet 60 feet uh well yes that would take
my old room this baby so what I will do
instead wait a sec
oh maybe it won't take my whole turn am
i not my speed is 40 feet and what I was
going to do is teleport shadowstep into
the field which is another 60 feet dude
this is gonna be animation yeah thanks a
bit anime uh so there is a running
little feet and then silence she gets to
about the halfway or so through the
village and then in the field I love it
and she's going to shadow step is get
bonus action so anxious to can still
attack this is great no are you gonna
train you're gonna get your rod are you
gonna punch the shit on these P know
that the rod is serving a very important
purpose right now so I'm just gonna go
with my with my fists no grab me man see
not required I mean the rod not required
to use gramma man see just for your own
okay you know what I mean like yeah it's
ready to manufacture a battlements like
gramma Mansi can still be used okay
it is like a constant innings okay so
you pop out there in the middle of this
yeah right so you should know you are I
mean it's just like your shoulders yeah
and little buns yeah sort of like
bobbing like a message in a bottle
through this yeah through this this
grass and I wonder I want to approach as
you are they're like physically once you
or once you are there the they stand up
do they notice me oh absolutely
like no no there's another rustle out
there that's a rustle there's a Russel
Wilson
yeah but basically so each of them just
sort of like stands up in this in this
pattern alright uh and they see me they
do so then uh Rosie says she says
something really dumb but she's excited
she goes no I'm here too
and she wants to go like Velociraptor
style through the grass like head and
all this looks scary
oh yes movement happening around her ah
and just go straight for the
nuts no it's um she calls herself a
clever girl she does and so she's going
to do on strikes which are plus six so
one's gonna be a 13 the other is gonna
be a 24mm and why not one one target one
target okay two nuts
okay yeah sure and then how far is the
next target away from me the next target
it away from them is maybe eight ten
feet okay so then I'll just keep whaling
on this dude I will do a flurry of blows
as well which is gonna be a fifteenth to
those all hit yeah yeah you're looking
for yum yum yum yum yum yum
okay so then I don't know what gestures
you guys are making but I don't
appreciate it like a cool anime moment
that's going to be a six she's nuts
tough a five a 911 he's uh he's already
dead he's already dead maybe delete
seven so the way that I see it is that
Rosie knows precisely no obvious it
would definitely knows kung fu and
obviously she knows where the balls are
but I think that the way that I see it
is that she knows multiple prostates
ball likes bowl like she wins every but
the balls leave the balls mine right
it's basically every it's like some kind
of acupuncture point like every place
your knuckle intersects this person is
connected to this massive network of
unpleasant signals
like Twitter exactly in their own
character unpleasant signal um and he
just collapses like you you and you you
intersect him and he is simply set to
the side
did I blow ten oh there's no one in
front of you
has there anyone left up there no not on
your side and sources just cleaning up
the last one on her side is he dead
can I get over there before she kills
him yeah yeah you have you got more I
wanna I wanna I wanna zip over there and
get the last time I need she can yeah
she's like about to go for the killing
strike let's go whoop you stole her kill
I need to know where I'm like I say here
and fight ads all day you know I need to
go for the boss it's Jeff I want to with
the the the game plan here is to and I
need someone left alive to interrogate
yeah yeah so I'm gonna I'm gonna
Clark more over and you wake him right
out of the way as she's about to chop
his head off I know she's gonna be
really mad attack so I do that okay here
so ma'am
give me your athletics give me an
athletics check I scream really loud
while I'm here guys yeah sure of course
my athletics okay I will take advance
because I don't get hurt seventeen
emotionally yeah yeah I'm not that
strong this is a dream journal haha
nineteen okay
he is sort of stunned and set up for the
final cut and then Clark would just like
definitely rubs like in the middle of
this thing like comes in contact with
her on the edge spins around yeah and
you're able to snatch him yeah and then
the her blade just flashes against the
yeah night mmm I say don't kill him
don't kill him we have to find out where
the boss is I'd say that so she doesn't
get mad at me that's the smartest thing
you've ever said yeah
are yelling from across it was very what
we know we need no we're bad man is so
eloquent you know more she's like he has
no insignia is a rank yeah is this a
high value yeah I just say it's just
weak to be cut down let me handle this
and I shake him by the scruff of his
neck
they say where's your where's your
leader listen you where's your leader
who sent you his target he's just sorry
answer me he say something just like
wriggling and your grass he's looking
over at this dangerous person
nice looking this dangerous per se don't
look at her like a man and then he looks
tended to elk Clark Clark or really
gives it to him yeah to both our faces
Rick really tries to intimidate ya the
guy gives a little poke with the antler
yeah thanks he does not respond he's in
shock yeah he's having a hard time he's
gonna give him a little too far
hello ed step slap okay I'm shaken out
of him I asked you a question buddy
nothing it's like well where's your
leader where's this coming from
yes yes yeah you'll see him all right
you know what all right kill him I tried
just toss him as sotius feet he hits the
ground and then she just pushed the
sword down
fixa stored up wipes the blade on his
tunic sword goes away let's see that was
Donner Blitzen out here in the bad guy
realm this this turn is also a part of
grave of men okay I'm ready he's ready
yeah
so the grave of man is continuing to
look down at this piece of just human
fruit that's just spoiling here on the
ground the rest of the horses have
ridden up and then been sort of like
they've had to pull back their charge
sort of stymied by the by the shadow
wall yeah and so then they they peel out
to the south to try to gain another
nimble guys I thought that they'd if
they're in a stacked up in a lion I
thought that losing a horse to uh you
know once dr. dead figured they wouldn't
maybe the last couple guys of your way
but they continue they soar to the south
tell me what's happening with our grave
of men this was the grave of men they're
like the bed of men like the couch of
men oh no there's the liner easy boy of
men exactly okay so how many have so
there's one guy on the ground and the
water divorce yeah and then who's deaf
peeling off to the south yeah exactly
they're gonna try to move around to that
I mean if there's their speed that was
great what was it give it to slaughter
where's five nice Thanks
yeah I try to do how many other five
only on this show it yeah yeah he's
gonna follow him and take take a SWAT at
him as in in motion if it's possible
don't deal with this guy it's leaving it
down a gentle force yeah so Graham
Mendes takes to the air and appears to
grow in size as the as these night winds
just sort of Buffett the shadow stuff
that makes up his form is a buffet
Cheeseburger in Paradise yeah
he is he is he is up these the rest of
the horses have their running basically
at top speed he can catch up with him
next turn but for now he has a he has an
eye on them okay okay let's see so he
has gone there now it's walnut dung
grass hay so fun fact about called
lightning call lightning is that one
they get to save for half so whoops on
that one well just save a half a half a
night but I can also concentrate it for
10 minutes yeah I figured it was hanging
around oh well you said that dissipated
oh it just wisps its wispy um so I would
like to try it again and you know going
for those bad boys in the grass there
yep so and you so you're choosing it
isn't just anybody in that area gets hit
sounds right because I'm thinking
there's somebody there now I'm just
asking oh really
I'm very dexterous I got all my hit
points okay we ain't less than lest they
get this try and get him to be the 15
tooth they're exfoliated decks or con um
excuse me
hold on wisdom wisdom Dex okay no they
don't need to not do well good well then
they get hit with a savory tasty eight
points a nice rough when you die
eventually did you think many years from
now okay so you get you could get light
lightly seared yeah ah he died I needed
a little like jolt you know yeah
honestly yes sorry I'm so sorry
you need to psyched it you you need this
something whose cut away kind of kitchen
get you in the moment
I mean way past my bedtime I'm very
concerned about the river absolutely
that's a completely reasonable thing to
be concerned with you getting your zap I
gave him this app okay perfect
Josh can you tip the cauldron please I
rolled wet enemies and all boy have
that's on my way a stable which I've
always had okay okay
walnut no grass great of walnut walnut
yeah yeah grave nuts use my favorite
cereal you you read you reach out slight
wave a little bit of embarrassment uh
you know to grandmother yeah sorry
she's like no it's fine and then you
have a moment to smile briefly before
you feel a blade intersect your back
right like peeling right underneath the
shoulder blade like the blade is in a
place that it can control every part of
your movement and it has been expertly
placed yeah the only comfort that you
have is that that's a suit that there is
a numbing that comes along with that so
the pain is great initially and then as
it starts to seep in you don't feel much
of anything lidocaine power I bet my
life on you might say you're a numb nut
no oh my god how much okay the the
strike itself is six and the sneak
attack damage forever on the back of it
is fourteen
holy Sh yeah hello you are also subject
to disadvantage as a result of this I'm
what breading everything our attacks
okay
oh this spreading numbness they snuck up
on both myself and Catherine it was I
what were you doing he is just
unconscious okay he's he's fine he's a
psycho sailing through the air with this
shadow friend and it just twists like
it's twisted with cruelty like your
basic it's almost like a yoke in a way
mm-hmm like wherever it wants you to go
is where you have to go thanks Josh
Rosie was making eye contact with you
when this happened to so she has seen
this sucker yeah and you and you
absolutely absolutely see it so you turn
even with foes around you yeah you turn
and then you see her just buckle forward
and you see cthe wrists engaged in some
kind of a trance-like state just drawing
hearts there's no book yeah nothing is a
clandestine is that it's like good work
out there I think a little rosy head
popping island grass I got you but like
a frazzled shocked hair good the thrift
robe to join my demon hold I'm gonna
assume that I did hear something or
somebody barks something yeah looks like
any other sensory input there's always a
measure of inconvenience that comes with
it what is it announcing this is what we
are but it'd be a mess let us be our was
it bein we're gonna be together I'm so i
roused myself enough to look at walnut
and this assailant what do I see
so behind walnut basically just moving
her body over like doubling it over as
if with a
lever you can see sharp blades that have
projected on either side of a thin firm
bodied instrument and he if it takes no
effort for him to do it it's just it's
like something that's just happening and
he's just around for it and he is
watching you with intense with intensely
clever curious eyes it'd be like if it
were like if you could dissect a
specimen without opening them up that's
the sense of that's the sense you get
from this gaze I don't like it I like it
a little bit but I don't like it at me I
like to make that look have it I'd you
know what I get it now so many people
were troubled by that look I am doubly
angry to have been ripped from my demon
reverie to see my friend pierced in the
back by this toilet man and I'm gonna do
something does not require concentration
I'll come back sweet demon with just a
moment great first are you okay hello
timeout I'm gonna do dis Annette
whispers on this guy absolutely
tell me about the whispers in this case
it is me just repeating over and over to
him this is who I am
think about exactly exactly mean your
own shadow seems to thicken you sort of
draw him into this seemingly Bob
bringing them all
so you can see you don't have to believe
what I'm telling you
absolutely so this this he saves against
this correct yeah he's gonna save wisdom
against it yes and he also had a little
something that we'd like to call fifteen
but you still gotta take halves
he's young he's to us to take cabs
evasion what does he does he get to
evade my half damage but wait but is it
only for deck saves well just read X Y a
well I like it my like my Billy Ray this
is super evasion yeah sweet so he is he
has saved roll those dice yeah I'm gonna
have to roll them all so you can figure
out what half of a mess alright so the
other thing I'll be oh yeah yeah we have
to have the full number 1477 the number
the beasts go
so that is 15 so half of that perfect
and you does not have to flee that's a
great just stay with that blade let's
see a baby than that and the higher you
roll them more damage scores less point
if this guy's stand there and I'm triply
insulted yeah I don't even care that I
made a demon roll at the end of each
turn to see if this demon turns out I do
know I only forgot one time after the
first command right mm-hmm
yeah okay after his turn right yeah
Christmas Eve buddy so now I'm great
with men oh I want to do my own thing
now nope don't get to it no Rosie the
messenger when he rolls anticipate
answer um how far am i from Wilma now
you are perhaps 15 20 feet away from
walnut okay with difficult terrain yeah
a lot of guys think that's gonna stop me
love yes um so
not again oh oh that's not a key point I
will immediately shadow step again out
of the grasses yeah out to whatever
shadow is closest to Walnut but before
that I go you stupid motherfuckers can i
teleport to her and can and get as close
as I can and then run over to her
assailant yeah he's right behind her so
it's it's easy to get to him okay
I am also in or shouldn't but it's
walnut you like Hades like this a bad
idea but rosy definite you're gonna get
yep she's gonna Thor style call the
staff of the master back hmm
as she's running and give them the whole
sauce okay so as you're as you're
running over you're just reaching out
with the expectation that this massive
facade of shadow mm-hmm he's gonna spool
itself back into the weapon that you
know yep and that wall comes down but
it's because I need that that extra
absolutely well and you did you did
guide them to another path they may they
did not have access to the east the
easiest entrance to the city so yeah
okay yes so uh as I'm attacking this
person do I notice anything is just
another bandit that managed to sneak up
on my walnut you you doubt very soon
this is this is Merrick sharp oh yeah
okay anywhere and this is not this is
not the other loop that you saw if this
is definitely a this is one of his other
collection okay back up
all right here we go that's gonna be a
fourteen lucky rule an eleven guy 15 ant
814 okay so as you as you bring the rod
in sweeping around he takes the loot he
takes the his
with the axe blade firmly implanted in
walnut mm-hmm pulls it out and just
scoots her away with his boot so
whenever whenever whenever you swing in
with the run how many attacks was that
that was fired right four total yeah
every every time you fail to connect he
takes this as an opportunity to respond
wait how many times I fail to connect
four whoa
this has gotta be a C on this bad boy
what season he is 16 odd oh man okay
good he's just like so only only one of
them comes back for nine points okay
and you can feel that along with that
along with that strike you can feel a
numbing presence
okay so disadvantage is real so it's
just it's effortless it's not monastic
it is it is whatever the polar opposite
of monk combat is I see so for the most
part though there's like eight attacks
total face we're like those cats when
they attack each other no it's a soft
pop if it's that like super soft so do
they actually fight yeah they're hiding
but it's just sweet good for the
animated so there is something let's do
something it's it's new okay it's I
don't like it no no no but there is this
is something that you have learned to be
cautious about okay do not what's in
everyone's dead around me oh yeah it's
awful
I congratulate myself and I take a nap
worst and I guess nice uh well no I'm
there with sorsha we killed the guy
couldn't get any info from him that's
man's here about will retreat back to
the town or at the very least I think in
this scenario would still own Clark more
get up on top of the mine and look down
and assess it see like well we tell our
guys what's everyone else doing exactly
try to convince sorsha to get on as well
yeah she doesn't know it won't be hard
okay it won't be hard just getting back
down into the site is is her math yeah
so a top Clark more you are gazing down
you can see the bulwark of shadow that
rosy beast enger' had manifest and then
you can see it all being drawn to her
hand as she engages with a new foe you
can see cthe wrists and walnut sort of
hunched over and then you can you can
see the entire thing with your your eyes
you see for expert strikes all repelled
and then responded to with Marshall
vigor what do I see otherwise like from
this high vantage point ya see a fight
from the c3 oh yeah you see for more
foes
now at their full height walking through
this tangle of grass okay and you can
see nine horsemen approaching the town
from the south
do you know that a group of foes is
called a tone a murder a tome a tome of
foes yeah what about you don't have to
support this what about on the west
what about Riverside's Riverdale what's
happening with those crazy kids in
Riverdale but you don't see any relation
okay just making sure
it's kind of hot where's that demon it
do I see the demon I don't know get over
near that demon
doesn't seem like it so they are down
here and then if you are looking for
this demon you can see it sort of
imagine a dark kite behind the behind
that wave of horseflesh okay running
into this out then I will come down in
the middle to get in the fracas exactly
next it's gonna take all of your juice
to get down there yeah but you'll be
bringing sorsha yeah with you
dual wielding actually down in this mess
what is it well Matt can't you what okay
if you oh no I was gonna say if you got
up to somebody you can do you can do
your special RAM attack because you live
more than 20 feet Oh cuz the court guy
oh yeah oh yeah it's got a range of 60
what do you want to set up for a charge
next ring yeah gunman so you'll result
in full speed yeah exactly
same formations before start show with a
sword out me with a swear down do you
want on each side me on that mines on
the right nose on the Left hunt of it
the image is ballin yeah it's exactly
how it shoots a warhorse right yeah
absolutely
thank you very much for your turn
dinerral too happy to do it
happy to do it look at the grave grave
of men is slavering there is so so much
down here to know in the way that his
kind knows things
thanks I didn't go to shadow spell I'm
Graham of doctors doctor of man graves
so so yes so he and he has his pick like
he's like I say he's just like he's just
like a consequence he's just sort of
drooped over the the affair yeah any
anywhere he wants to go he can have so
he is where where is he looking at
where is he relative to the the people
in the field but over
Oh on top so like a raptor so that means
that he's a top the he can look down he
can have this horsies oh no he is
available for the entire process he can
it you know how in the same way imagine
a dark midnight keulen airy tool in the
same way that it might be able to Julian
mmm dice Oh mints mmm some other type of
cut Slap Chop yeah yeah yeah maybe a
dark Slap Chop like a matte black finish
this is no Marlene this is not
dishwashers everything but yeah I'm
trying to see whether or not like when
the command is issued yeah so because I
want to inform it you after Merrick
sharp this is the sweetest meat that's
sweet me you ain't gotta eat dinner
first to get the dessert just come down
and get it come down yo rich mmm
absolutely well here then let's let's
see some will see some dice over here
brother man can erase down we're all
gonna be just a giant it's gonna be
great
yeah do your charisma check at the end
to make sure he doesn't yeah yeah he
doesn't eat all of your friends yeah
okay so and I just beer off like nope
they're sitting at the charge they see
then they're like no and then the
credits just yeah we just go to the mind
[Laughter]
rest show
yes whoops down he's gonna Claude this
guy and I will give him another of my
advantages if I may
yeah yeah I'm gonna see what we get deck
5 come on yeah
so that's plus 5 so that's gonna be 24
that is quite good thank God as he as he
sails down and puts out that puts out
that nib look she what's up what's the
damage on that it's like 46 46 plus 300
if he has advantage oh I guess he well
if he's coming from above yes that's
pretty good
he's also surrounded by foes and yeah
all right you know I'll accept that so
it's gonna be 9 plus 9 plus 11 did you
do a good job last 30 plus 3 that's big
sure that's very nice so he so he comes
down with a new delight and learns all
he can with his grasping tasting claws
one the dress Rosie says yeah that's
what you get you get a bite of that all
right yeah yeah let's do it
figure out he's got a plus four that's
right thanks again oh it's a total shit
show disadvantage yes subscribe to the
podcast what just happened yeah I rolled
a 20 but outside of the box and bounced
out outside the box didn't go in yeah
thankfully doesn't count doesn't count
can't count yeah because the box is free
the box but yeah somebody gets a prize
and we had a ruined yes yeah nobody
unplumbed a new prize we do the price
but we're not gonna all right so a prize
it's gonna be happen Elderwood this is
the coolest fucking one too here to put
a bucks yep put on the box try to roll
around there yeah you don't get to open
X the room oh you just put your goods
inside holders and is a miracle look at
yourself it's not the scrying they do
Dakota frying pool
crying pool is the frying pool yeah so
for the middle you know we roll the dice
for real dude does you said disadvantage
right I thought he rolls I know his true
name would it ah it's a fun role just a
regular old roll not at this time he
gets what why do you guys gonna be messy
I know it doesn't break free the chipper
shredder yeah I let my friend know
walnut I'm a good friend all right so I
have my back which he is no he has no
withdrawn to attack your other friend so
I feel okay the heat and wetness of
blood on my back yeah delight and an
unpleasant yes wasn't numbing sensation
but when I smell that blood even though
it's my own a woof and a couple things
about this wolf is that always I know
I'm gonna take to get you and I know
that I have disadvantage but I have
advantage when I'm near my friends
you're back
that's messed up so that's back to
normal pretty smooth and I'm gonna take
advantage on it so which puts me back to
having advantage and then and then now
I'm gonna try a bite on this be a
superbike 15 um is Tuesday I love okay
I'm sorry I'm putting stink on y'all's
rolls but I love that when walnut is
attacked and stabbed instantaneously its
woof time like that's her panic button
yeah you know like earlier I love wolf
nut so much and I feel like
okay I get two three damage plus plus
the last like six damage Oh another six
now that's from one tooth okay so you
you you bring it down oh and he must
succeed on a DC strength
Dec 13 strength saving throw or yeah
yeah he's gonna get knocked down he's
probably forget nothing fuck down it's
no good so at this point he get he
you're able to get that bite give a
little shake and then but you can smell
like the the battlefield is a complex
melange at this point you can smell like
horse sweat mm-hmm this sort of cold
acrid scent of the shadow plane and then
the four more warriors from the place
you can smell Clarke more coming in from
the mountain they just placed the entire
thing in here and this is you this is
what packs are for this this is what a
pack is for now so it is as we can see
from clues cool initiative tracker here
it is the bad guy turn and it is gonna
be a hell of a turn clogged by a demon
if I was not looking great it's kid
naughty today it's gonna be real bad so
these four these four fellows from from
the grass you've sty need them the
entire way and now it's time for them to
it's time for them to make a deposit of
steel these guys so uncouth
I'm absolutely
[Music]
your counselor oh really
does my ray of protection that I have on
give me a bonus when I'm in oh yeah
that's that's how people do to keep that
stuff Jerri it isn't like so much
awesome shit then you turn this other
thing 15 yeah it's within it's different
fingers no they're the whole time
sunlight so Mike so they surround they
basically surround you sure tell me how
tell me what that means for the nut I'm
late what is the instils our race but
she is like so dead set on this target
especially after she you know has bitten
him and like tasted him mm-hmm she must
have finish it war absolutely so so
you're so you are constantly like your
eyes are shifting between this new group
of foes and then back
it's you've seen we've all seen that
like with the toy or the stick yeah it's
just a shift and every time you shift
back to Merrick sharp another one of
these swords just catches great catches
your flank individually it is see that
six plus six seven plus Oh
cuz our brain oh boy I posted they have
to get to this Mike shout - Rex come on
man yeah it's not me this isn't what I
want to happen so they like I say
they're just it is the apex of cruelty I
am so glad they are due they're just
just swiping it at Wolf's nut I don't
like the horsemen come in and they try
to connect with cthe wrists and Rosie
but a detachment of them also go out for
Clark more I am like barreling it top
speed they are coming at you like this
man just shot all right so you have a AC
14 you said I have hurt me yes self it's
like currently I won I'm 16 okay and
what did you have okay wow you guys are
fine they missed no no no uh wrist yes
Kath wrist grabs it and it's no good so
the horsemen you can see close now no
swords they have bows slung on the back
of the on the back of their steeds but
they're carrying these wicked serrated
Spears on the back so they get a they
get a commanding reach from horseback
I need where's my D Atrus it's gone you
can't have it you can't go you can't
roll it anymore that's 12 points for
Chris Chris trouble okay um
the other three attacks we have to
please just while there while they're
doing their ride by the other attacks
are just swiping lower that's over the
top yes I think left I'm here so what I
would like from you
donar blitz in is an animal handling we
never get to use animal handling that's
true that's true
I'm so this is very an animal handle so
you're trying to you're trying to get in
and they are basically trying to break
this momentum and break this access
you're trying to get
- the okaying body of the troops
alright okay yeah I'll take advantage
yeah that's it twelve
I'm flat out nice at twelve okay okay
gang I think we're all in same number
twice that that's harder to roll in a
twenty and what's your AC eighteen and
what's Clark or say see I think the same
no or is he Elka stats these are 15
mm-hmm oh but do you don't you do you
confer anything to do with your lovely
cloak do you protect oh yeah does that
explain the cloak absolutely does
protect especially against
area-of-effect
abilities so as you're able to you're
able to break through they're not able
to stop your charge but you you do get
stuck for eight points on the way in -
yeah
gosh mr. Stroud okay so I just took uh
there's there's a UH there is a palpable
term yeah in fortune describe to me the
where grave of men is caught
Merrick where is that on his on his
person on his body
yeah it's gonna be his left shoulder
okay and he is where the way I
envisioned it is that we've got these
these men are attacking good night right
yeah basically like around right and
over here we've got Merrick looking this
way and then there's a big shadow muster
engage with him not sure where you are
I'm also within really distance America
and we've got some horsemen that rode
past and it took us why indeed in there
four horsemen hmm four additional
soldiers Merrick sharp and the shadow
demon right okay that's the that's the
calculation you're looking for I think I
think the horse
out of my league out of my butt you got
a lot to offer
Oh guys come back how long does the
demon last also by the way oh that's our
logo and our oh your complete relief for
a full hour fast-acting
enik relief I see I got that I got that
spear and like my my side I took that
chunk I see my leaky in wolf form being
surrounded by these low men oh and the
lowest I want to know where that wound
is because I'm gonna let loose of
tentacular spooktacular it was any
product just freshly dead matter in him
just up here i what I would love to do
this end use that to send bolts out and
kill these four motherfuckers stab them
in the back so yeah they like in a barf
tentacles yeah we can do that
I really appreciated it's always you
know an invocation of these of these
things that do is they wish but in my
mind I like it well here I do I do want
to get an hour kind of check from you
it's not gonna determine effect because
you're not trying to manufacture
something okay but I do want to know
what type of scale we're talking about
okay so classic Arkana no advantage on
that 26 or 27 323 okay 23 cheese
absolutely so in the breather
that Merrick sharp has earned from the
rest of his brigands getting this wolf
off of him he has put his hand and
trying to so staunch from the shoulder
and then from the hand itself through
the hand through the flesh of the hand
Rod's of violent amethyst pierce out and
as near as you can tell like from your
point of reference they don't appear to
have a termination point it looks like a
rendering error they never do right so
it so that it goes from one side of his
shoulder back through the bunkhouse and
maybe out into the river right and on
the front in an instant like maybe
pencil-thin infinitely jagged sharp rods
go out in a second and erupt and just go
straight through their eyes and so
there's a moment here where he is where
Marik sharp is the pivot point for this
structure that's been created and then
he shifts his weight and they all break
off and then all of the brigands
collapse and fall and is that that
squeaking sound that you hear like when
cheap like a cheap goblet breaks like a
cheap glass goblet oh wait I say keep
going if I have it if I had a minute
yeah totally you have a minute I mean I
was four to him I made that too I love
it hey wait the charisma check there's
the check please
appiy didn't go quick that would be a
really cool note just to wait for it
yeah let's find out it's a 1 it's a 1 he
doesn't know he's your best friend now
except forever
Shou council mayor Labor's please you
you have frittered away another Thursday
engaged with content of this level
Wednesday for whatever reason all day oh
you're killing it Oh
please show miss Reid a listen so
they're gonna go to the pie room and
then come back and then we're gonna talk
to you a table top and then we're all
gonna go home we think I gotta go to the
airport okay after that we're gonna do
whatever it needs to be done at that
time
okay but don't I wear Rebecca
you