previously on Tessie teams you can
either come with me or I can kill you
where you stand who didn't know about
this Rosie did you know my I didn't know
about this but nothing surprises me try
to tell me but I didn't hoards person
cthis drought Princeton are Blitzen is
rash petulant and arrogant that
acquisitions incorporated we have
available several decisions of erudition
and even temper considered German goad
Ranger of the spine who sought his lost
words personal for two weeks while
haunted by darkness do you request and
other decisions
[Music]
Oh men hey omen omen dry-docked man sir
rank - yes that's me if I recall that's
my name that you said it's sign you did
sign it I have that in my room
prophet says don't you leave don't you
leave before saying goodbye and have
dark magic fix my door and omen says
I'll be back I'll be back sooner than
you think you'll see and a portal opens
up below the below the two of them and
they drop through Oh almonds the time is
the enemy of the past it threatens the
fastest weapon you wouldn't make it past
a second as the question
play it brash and reckless to choose a
conscious solution you saw it was
prudent in any Sepulcher poker to don't
become the putrid it's that well said I
pursue in no mountain too steep for
dungeon too deep to send expendable
marks up to the top of the peak of
beneath they see Yugi they come like
sharks to it while I swim in that money
burn like Carl Barks through it so send
your National Parks drew it I'll send
him home in a natural box with a close
tie the most of the parks included
save your breath for a cleric confessor
death is a lesson that life is attending
professor but if you're seeking my
official advice sign on the dotted line
and this should the twice okay so it's
good to know that even in Ryan's absence
which is to say the absence of dinar
blitz end we still have a person in this
chair who is willing to project
themselves into the shared space I love
it I am Tycho Brahe hey of penny okay
impacts I am also a min if it's Hera
word run CEO of acquisitions
incorporated but today I'm Jerry Hawkins
and I'm going to run a game of Dungeons
and Dragons for my friends even new
friends including the creature to my
right Jared conovan Bower yes say you
may know better as DF from the waffle
crew that's right the waffle crew
everybody you guys just queue up the new
thing we have an awful class no to their
right of my right reppin the natural
world walnut done grass khakhra and
that's what I have for you yes is a way
more like sumptuously I'm like a bird
right now to to my left obviously is the
void obviously it's something that we
all have to face at some point likes at
any point during the show feel free to
gaze in this direction and see the
mechanisms that will result in your own
death to the left of my left emerging is
though from a mist shroud Carissa
oh come on yeah one for you I can't even
imagine what what it must be like for
you to see this to see this to see a
person do this surely and then expect
that there's gonna be
kind of your program has its own inside
material that we would be lost to be a
part of likely yes but we don't have
bizarre rituals in which to engage
ourselves into the show at the start I
think the only fear I think the only
bizarre ritual on your show is the show
itself yes and it is primarily for the
amusement of Christmas yeah because
there's not a lot of others another and
then also then he invites me onto the
show to torment you further you did yeah
it was great yeah I mean that was a that
was a thing there's there's issues of
overlap between deaath and unmanifest
ron who knows it'll be fun they may you
know some aspect of it may emerge that's
just very evening weird we doubled the
budget for this one so listen gathered
thrown waffle crew and of course our
friends from the shadow Council allied
for just this one night you should know
that you can tip deaath during this you
can see he's integrated right there into
the iconography deeply integrated into
the show and all bits that go to hashtag
guests go to the National Alliance on
Mental Illness so we're operating our
program but there is a charitable
payload affixed to the entire process I
know this is just an incredible new
technology and obviously we think to you
through being here with us please use
your gold pieces where India has none
yeah exactly like he can't contribute to
his own fund yeah like that's the
darkness that's the blight that dungeon
master Chris Perkins has established cuz
I went over there under their show
thinking I'd be able to come back with
some money come back with some cash like
that's what Dungeons ring is about it's
about the bags of money that's a core
assertion
I haven't played that version yeah I was
just gonna say you guys need equipment
you need money like none of it's
happening over there
listen anytime you want to I understand
your local we have you integrated into
the thing
yeah I'm come over here anytime you
wanna get some money you want to get
some level appropriate for this thing
yeah by my house yeah dumb place no
exactly like am i sure do look forward
to weekends doesn't see this thing and
every every night stovetop stuffing
daddy's throne when last we saw our
heroes they had returned returned
returned to read larch right there
nestled in the center of the destron
Valley you may recall that acquisitions
incorporated the C team has an exclusive
license to this treasured tract of land
but our scene actually begins elsewhere
indeed it begins with our new friend
deaath who has sought out the services
of a fortune teller of perhaps
questionable repute but incredibly low
rates huge savings opportunities they're
great for you and you have done so
because you have reached something of a
desperate state about the location of
two rings yes would you like to tell the
gathered throne of course your own your
own cadre may know well about them in
our campaign these rings are simply two
rings of protection yes
so unburden yourself D if please tell us
about your your desire for these rings
and what is it that makes them so potent
whereas you would see two rings of
protection of standard magical fare
these rings are actually infused with
the spirit of longtime companion of
Gaius Woodrow evil and maher zain
beautiful shining light Allah thandor
palden of all things good who has given
her life
kid Italy so that others may live
including as far as deaath can tell
giving up her own life and through that
somehow lifting the death curse off of
all the Forgotten Realms okay no I I was
its it was more complicated than that
but but yes omen helped so this is why
you have sought them out and they have
been gone since Winn like what how did
they get lost now through a wonderful
summoning into which omen drawn arrived
to DFS party whilst evil and was slain
he offered his services graciously to
raise her back from the dead and he did
and in doing so D Athens companions
offered these two magical rings that he
had that had evil and spirit within them
hoping that this would somehow a system
in some way or perhaps the spirits from
the Rings themselves can return to her
body and it was a success
evylyn who had perished once before and
woke up in a constructive body then died
as a construct we are woken in her human
form as whole as she has ever been
mm-hmm and then omen left his services
completed with the Rings the accident
early now dear yes I should I should
warn you that occasionally I do take a
sort of dark turns your master Chris
Perkins is want to do in this scenario
the incredible savings that you're
hoping to derive from this wise woman
yeah they come at the cost of of some
discomfort she plies her trade beneath a
barnacle-encrusted dock in the
waterfront and she is she has known to
those who have this need and as I
suggested her rates are reasonable but
it does require
a bit of light parkour to access her
domain should be a problem exactly so I
would love to have some acrobatics you
yeah you got it one of a few things I
actually excel in so much that is a 33
mess of digits on there I assumed it was
a good all right hundreds of hundreds of
years no one's around to see it but was
very impressed oh that's where you're
wrong
Oh hundreds of years prior to the
founding of Cirque de Soleil the flame
is lit the flame is lit here in this
unassuming
Waterdeep dock you enmesh yourself with
the jagged wood and barnacles and rot
and find your way immediately presently
beneath the dock that you had heard
about yeah and far back among the
pilings you can see like smooth like
ocean smooth rocks on your way up and
she is plying her trade back there she
has seen the entire thing and she offers
up a soft clap that echoes against the
stone floor you can see that her
operation consists primarily of her
addled mind a worn sea chest coated with
the wax of many candles on top with the
gentle clap death rather than giving any
kind of recognition of it just slowly
steps forward and based on the applause
alone which just says I can only assume
you already know why I'm here she smiles
revealing a single black tooth and she
says it's in my line of work
wonderful then we can make this
transaction quick oh I should hope so
she says hold out your hands
dear hold out what was love Dickinson
just know know that the palm boy the
palm almost almost hasn't an idea for
them I kind of retract a hand and slowly
hold it glove up and pull up a sleeve of
his blue tunic and then hold that out
she reaches out with the like the sort
of ravenous rodent madness of a squirrel
it grabs on both sides and just begins
to consume whatever information you can
see you see some lines you see you know
aspects of your life that get recorded
in the flesh she is seeing something
entirely else she nods a couple times
beyond this burn scars and other slashes
oh yes she is absorbing another type of
information and she says what question
have you for me I only seek the location
oh I'm okay with the dark light so
that's true key little bits manifest
let's manifest excellence here beneath
this dock right like a bunch of teenage
girls got their first Ouija board yes I
know I can do this shit and right DF
will say I only seek the location of two
magical rings still containing the
remaining pieces of evil in Helbig
Avallone America Mar thing holy
paladin's love the founder in my dear
friend she's you can see her like
mouthing trying to mouth Evelyn's whole
name I said evylyn Helbig
Valona of our thinking it's evil an
abalone abalone abalone I think Martine
with it's a hard end at the end and it's
family nearby here maybe you've heard of
them - North they are Thane MN yes my
thing
not quite close Thane like a servant of
some sort but Marvin oh just leave Allen
even ones fine I don't think anyone else
is called evil and just evil in finding
solace okay okay all right sorry okay
she opens up her chest rummages around
the candles that are on the top don't
move at all
as the as the lid is lifted out now
they're just sort of pointing like like
they're now they're just in your space
are they lit no in your space it's just
okay alright I guess this is how it is
and she has she's rummaging around you
can hear like a squeak of metal on glass
and she closes it again she is holding
in her hand a sort of violet orb that
she is gazing into Ethel evilly yes yes
I knew I knew deep within that was this
was a test yes for you young man now
what I want you to do is picture the
Rings picture them in your mind that gif
closes his eyes and does so she says
nothing not the teeth little boy I don't
want to know girl ring that's a girl
belongs to you all right I want you to
picture the ring itself the which is of
no concern at this Junction death closes
his eyes and focuses deeply I really try
really true in your move think down
about thing about the hand think
specifically about the hand where the
ring would be not the wand not the rod
not the broom we'll talk about the broom
later dear folks is hard work recalls
the specific memory of the ring itself
holding Evelyn's hand
her being vanishes and her spirit
traveled up his finger into the ring
yeah she her neck becomes tall as her
head begins to tilt back
imagine a dark PEZ dispenser and she she
says red large and large these rings are
in red large to the north of there have
you ever been I've never been terrible
I believe it terrible how far away is
that from here too long I agree she says
it's on the long road it shouldn't be
hard to find passage there if you want
to go I mean it seems like you really
want the Rings yeah it's not the
destination that concerns me is anything
else I need to know before I set out she
says well other than the fact that I'm
not going to charge for this hmm I think
you may need it more than me and you're
talking to a woman who lives and
operates with the tides yellow a jagged
largely collapsing dock she says if you
should ever return to town with a spare
coin I wouldn't turn it down but I would
start thinking about saving for
retirement Dave will give her just a
silent none of agreement and then circle
away his way out is it the same exit ya
hear y'all hear let's bow 32 we do this
never happens on my show absolutely so
you you you slip through the slats
of this decaying structure went like a
like a gum wrapper
being blown by the wind you just go you
basically this walk-up of yeah as
fragile as one - yeah exactly and then
you're out on the other side all right
you know that she is not she is not
wrong the long road that leads out of
the north it goes all the way north
through red larch Westbridge tribe or
and people go that far north so that
they can mostly so that they can go west
and go to never winter
right no one stays in these places
that's not they're not places one stays
in there Passover is at best yeah that
best yeah their Drive thrus okay you
know what I mean it's like you would
stuff to get a hamburger yeah
and that's it we're just getting some
food moving on kind of thing all right
exactly and it is at the-- is at this
northern gate that you can see several
several parties with explicit signs out
that say things like Help Wanted going
to this particular town security needs
contact things like that you can see a
row of three relatively nice wagons
upper-tier wagons brass fittings rich
oiled woods hail hail stock out front to
pull and there's a sign this as security
for red large great I'll just go up and
just examine them all just pick the one
that looks the most secure or possibly
the most prepared one to set out as soon
as possible yeah yeah it looks like they
are it looks like they're getting fit to
leave pretty quick and they take it on
most of what they're going to take on
you can see even inside the windows to
some of these carts you can get a sense
of what they're planning to do and you
can see
one of them is full of like pieces of a
stove like a dismantled cook stove in
multiple pieces laid out oriented inside
there and you you have you approach you
approach a man sitting in a chair by the
sign and he says his name DF coz in time
he says we're hitting the read large you
know that right it's like it's we're not
gonna pay you to come back we're gonna
go there and stay there though I'm aware
I just look into help get you there it's
I have my own purposes to know right
he says can you he is trying to identify
weapons on your person yes
as he looked yep over he sees that he
has a we'll take a normal short sword
upon one side at the front a sheath
dagger that looks mostly inconspicuous
and as DF notices as he's kind of being
looked over DF will pull out another
short sword that's very ornate looking
has a handle of a fox head biting onto a
red jewel ooh a keyhole on the pommel
well that winks kind of coming out of
that and a dark almost ominous looking
short sword blade probably impressive
looking to most commoners and just hold
that on just as I can handle anything
yeah he this thing comes out it's like
it's like you're sort of like building
up faction with this process yeah each
time you each time you reveal a new
piece of sharp metal and then as soon as
that happens it's like the lights of Las
Vegas erupted in his eyes that's a
couple times this is all right dear
you'll do second wagon you got it
alright you can see that there's a
couple a couple people who have already
taken that place on top of these wagons
some are riding inside there doesn't
appear to be a rule about how you get
this passage
yeah I'll probably find a position
probably somewhere within the wagon
itself if possible or if they want me on
hand outside I can do that too
that's a classic okay that's a classic
scenario better we will pop back to DF
northern journey it's like the
incredible journey I'm gonna start
incorporating just just to help you
relax ease down so that you know you're
among friends and not your own nefarious
dungeon man right it's gonna be a very
much incredible journey there's gonna be
cats okay it's gonna be dogs it's gonna
be so wonderful and pleasant I'm gonna
be so on good you'll never have never
one else this this is me you'll never
know when the bad stuff is about to
happen but cthe risks droughts hmm it
seems to me and you tell me if this is
true cuz I can't say for you necessarily
but you have indicated to me that Chris
drove spends a lot of time in this
dagger oh yeah so you should know my dad
I love my knife yeah the dads yeah so
you should know gathered throng and of
course for your use as well da short not
long ago cthe wrist route under dark
exile came into possession of a dagger
that when placed in or near the forehead
or eye does not damage the user but
instead takes them to a pocket dimension
inside the knife itself this is a this
is a place of research that had once
been owned by his own father so it
exists as a kind of study and eldritch
workspace and a spa and and space well
this sounds Pleasant hot stone and your
dad did this for you yeah yeah one I was
for him but I got it yeah okay Troy all
right reflexology
so tell me what it is you were
researching in there so that I can help
you discover these items a little bit
distressed that apparently when Rosie
was in here she did some cleaning yeah
and you know some of the my research
piles have been migrated onto shelves
for some reason but she I know that her
interest is astronomy and I am rather
than trying to figure out where this God
would the unity symbol matches my
unknown right patron I am looking into
the connection between the sanguine
a--the and the consumption of other gods
and whether or not this could affect
constellations because we had talked
about whether or not this is a thing
what anybody was aware of the type of
organism right right if it isn't a
recognized phenomenon right so you
should know also dear just for your own
use yeah this is this this actually
might be more for Jared sure the c-team
the warlock of the c-team without his
own knowledge has the pact that he has
is not a hundred percent like the pact
that exists in the in the book proper
doesn't have any memory of making this
pact and the entity that he serves is a
kind of dia phage right it's a kind of
it's almost like a crystalline virus or
bacteria that consumes divinity and then
reflects the power of those divinities
to its servants
yes so we say okay when he's when he
says that he's trying to figure out
those connections okay
that yeah that is what he's doing I
guess I want to be a good host I want to
make sure that you know ink you know
it's my pleasure that's why I make sure
that you know exactly what's going on so
you do find something novel and adjacent
you're wondering about the sanguinis
in general and the process by which it
consumes and you find something that is
like almost like a corollary to it and
it is a book full of notes from your
father and it specifically talks about
divinity as a as a set of laws similar
to physical law or magical law hmm that
it's a it's a it's not beyond these
things it's simply another system for
governing energy and matter right
it's just jealously guarded and of
course you know to their believers
you know judiciously distributed and
applied but it describes a process
something like a divine vacuum not a
vacuum like the like the appliance right
but the idea that it is possible to
create a divine vacuum into which a
specific God may be drawn inexorably
that's high value for Chris exactly so
it's it's it would require additional
research to investigate and to master
but it describes a process the reason
that he was able to discover this and so
you know that his library is full of
strange books deeply strange books some
of which don't appear to be from this
place and at all some of which appear to
be for example the book that Kate or the
book that Rosie discovered yeah details
with you know a high level of accuracy
the stars that you know from a radically
different point of of
perception mm-hmm right and the reason
he was able to put these things together
is because he had acquired a book of
this Donnie wisdom hmm
thus Donnie appeared to be a traveling
people with a series of with a very
jealously guarded mystery and power and
techniques but they have a their the the
vez Thani marriage ceremony has a
spiritual it's a ceremony that combines
all three of these metaphysical laws so
there is a physical portion of the
ceremony
a magical portion of the ceremony and a
divine portion of the ceremony and
that's what enables it's incredible the
the type of union it allows is
incredible and because it operates on
every one of these planes you wonder if
there might be an application of this
daddy
na'toth wrist would say that how did
they blunder into this I'm gonna use
this this like axis of reality to tether
a finite union to like two small things
that die after a couple of decades who
cares
it's true it's true but there are lost
my game would it be possible for me to
get a perception role from you for sure
what are you doing Dusit oh now let's
just use it as is what is that gonna be
what's my perception I never use it
gonna be a 16 total okay you are what
you are looking through this book and
these diagrams and basically it's I mean
imagine it's taken like the circle I
mean the circle itself as an icon is a
is already profound oh yeah but it is
this is a diagram that shows it expanded
out into a sort of like a four
dimensional structure and it is
detailing the mystical bonds
that that it this ritual which
functionally speaking looks like a
marriage but is actually a profound
metaphysical ritual and as as you use
your hand to pass the page over you can
see on your ring finger a ring that
looks almost identical to the ring in
the diagram I see now I know that
there's something beyond just a plus one
AC yeah this yeah yeah it's it's again
the the mind reels there is there is
something incredible at play here it's
bizarre that you should have it and
let's see and and cthis remembers that
he received this it was it via the the
hoards person via the hoards person
special exactly what was the reason
given to protect the party just gifts
gifts I would like to use us as a as a
vault to be broken and in by some other
figure okay then I could first parse
this it's there's a lot to parse and I
got happy to move over to walnut yeah if
you want to figure it out we can we can
come back to you I think you would just
think this a wonderful mistake and
continue down this path yeah yeah
absolutely so you want to do you want to
seek out seek out more books you want to
continue your research search let's see
how much more of this tiny stuff I could
find out go ahead go ahead give me
perception sure
maybe I'll goose this one okay whoa
she's gonna be a whoa i he off the table
okay right too excited I was an 18 and
this is gonna be a fifteen eighteen
perfect I can work with that walnut on
grass okay tell me about your morning
here at the drunk courtier um so what
having just met her here
it's incredibly special incredibly
powerful and Ron okay
he's behind the front come on it's not
cool it's not cool so since she got the
news that Brahma had perished in Scala
you know she Shh girlfriend girlfriend
uh should be sad she should be she
should be she should be more sad than
she is and she feels that she feels that
it was somewhere she feels it somewhere
in her but it just won't come out if you
know what I'm saying you know I know
exactly she's um
so she is in will say in the in the
common area between the rooms you know
thinking about everything that's
happened in the past 24 hours so that
being you know handing off oak and
finishing her paperwork always a big
deal yeah really a big part of this show
it's a bureaucracy it's a surprisingly
big part of this show this is this is
Samantha man yeah this is make you say
I'm Brad yeah this times this is meant
to say that maybe maybe you wouldn't
have as much fun here it's like your
choice is the Iron Maiden or a lot of
homework Oh double break um so yes
she'll just be kind of ruminating on
both her guilt about drama but then also
meaning omen and then also all the
things she didn't get to say to omen
that she you know had imagined their
first meeting would be very special and
that there would be all these things in
common yeah that's not that same thing
before and she got to say she got to say
none of it and she's just
second-guessing the impression that she
as she made on him judgin you hear a
sound it sounds like a like a ingot
striking a wood floor from your room
oh and then you hear a door squeak open
okay and it doesn't close okay I'm gonna
go investigate my room you go to your
room
you're a satchel is like tipped over and
the top of the bag is open I don't know
someone's gonna have to explain and the
door is open and in fact it's still
opening a little bit you have come in so
quickly yes I want to see what who goes
there
okay so you you walk out to the landing
and look down and you can see no layin
yeah her full raiment oh no as a Grove
keeper which is a kind of like ancient
druidic general taking her steps like
very measured steps down the stairs and
just looking all around her a kind of
horror oh no my ancient Tamagotchi is
come home to roost you she reaches the
bottom of the stairs she looks over at
the portrait over the fireplace and just
shudders and then looks back into the
room and then looks down and sees onyx
he says yield and tonics just looks up
and she says cat you will yield and onyx
is implacable well I run downstairs this
is serious shit I'm sprinting downstairs
and she turns to crikey really in turns
to you walnut and says why did you not
ask a tree
to provide you a home uh mom I guess
down the stairs superfast
she's huffing and puffing she takes like
a really hasty meal prophesies walnut'
[Laughter]
very powerful women and she she's
walnut' do I need this well I mean she's
like tapping something behind that yeah
well no no no no no I can handle this um
Monica no and these people they baby
know not what they do
they had clear cut the forest to build
this town and then she goes a tragedy
well wait she says they named this town
after the trees they cut down discussing
this is genocide it is yeah but a little
bit the forest grows again she closes
her eyes and sort of and synchronizes
herself with some mesh of energy you can
only begin to guess at and she says
there's an emissary here whoo there's an
atmosphere here yeah she says to the
north and west oh yes there is
I awoke in it and used it to trap the
wandering Crypt she's like she's worried
that she's gonna like have to answer for
some terrible injustice these are very
hesitant
and she says I think I may be more at
home in that place
wonderful let me take you there she says
I know where it is well looks with her
proper real quick and like a plumber
echoes like you can you can hear the you
can hear the metal head of the hammer
like click over once as she's sort of
like resting her weight on the handle of
her mall and okay she's so the grove
keeper nods so the growth keeper is
walking out by the door and looks over
at prophet just assessing Lee mm-hmm Wow
and the door opens without any contact
of any kind and no layin finds her way
out and you can hear her just shouting
at carts and squirrels uh she's like she
just what full-on like prepper like
crazy uncle like none of this like the
whole it's the whole modern world is
just there's a solution for it and she
knows what it is so long as extremely
anxious she look got a buffer at her
knee and yet preface is friend of yours
ah
[Music]
one day maybe um and well just knows
that like there's nothing that she could
have done just stop her so like what's
the point even being worried prophecies
come here okay I go over and as you walk
over onyx walks over just a little bit
faster mm-hm and jumps up on the counter
and prophet like football carries the
cat up close like this just give
a few pets big scratches up and down
gives her a kiss on there lays it right
on the camera oh yeah that's fine by me
yeah cat goes where it pleases yeah
exactly it's her own this cat is her own
but but the preparations are still
running a pace oh I think I'm back here
batters being made mm-hmm
there's still a small pot of jam still
going back there that gets the
occasional idle stir all right from
profit but how do you want to invest
your your morning down here um so
there's no mail in the mailbox
not currently Wow then just woman would
not know what to do with herself it's
you know it was so awful left with her
thoughts and that is actually the worst
prison you can be in so I think that
that is it that she would just be
hemming and hawing pacing around
downstairs trying to figure out what she
wants to do and just trying to do
everything possible to not be thinking
absolutely
do you food run yes back at it all right
so you are trundling north it's a few
days journey seems to be mostly you you
definitely pass traffic on this on this
road okay it's it's the road that you
use to go this way so there's plenty of
there's plenty of extra traffic the
second day in I need a perception check
from you you know you're you're writing
inside the the guts of the all right
they're like windows absolutely yeah
yeah every now and then there are so
there are showers yeah like like summer
showers that make trying to write on top
of the cart unpleasant yep but there
there are people for whom that sort of
thing is fine right
so perception that is a 22 oh that is
these are some see these are some skills
what OKC team
these are some skills it's all out of
combat skills if we ever fight well oh
yeah I've chosen my rogue expertise very
carefully yeah exactly no this is this
is straight murder so you can hear as
you're writing in your your solo inside
the cart okay and but you can hear steps
up on the roof of it of whatever other
mercenary mercy yes exactly
plying their trade up their rough
language guttural laughs the occasional
slip and laughs but you can hear you
hear something rattling inside these
stove portions like inside these inside
these pieces of this dismantled stove
you get the sense of they're not empty
and then you can't place the sound but
you know you've heard it before I'm sure
it's just something is loose in there or
broken they'll probably want to know
about that so I'll let them know and
just try to open up and peek inside and
figure out like a like a bolt maybe a
chip of stone had fallen out you don't
want there they're the products to be
damaged upon delivery so what you're
trying to tell me dear Woodrow is is
you're a very judicious employee right
I'm liking this I'm making note of this
this is great with a place for you in my
organization yes so yeah you're like
it's kind of a something simple yeah
stove is just an empty place where you
burn things in yes you you swing open
the belly of this stove and it is loaded
top to bottom with what looked to be
brand-new daggers just just a ton of
weapons yeah inside this part of the
stove there's probably 60 daggers I
it's probably all the daggers I've
thrown over the years it's been
theorized there's a place where this
daggers arrived it's like this is your
life you have to reunite with each other
with each dagger let me tell you what
happened so opening up this little stove
and like peering inside just seeing all
the blades almost instinctively he kind
of reels back and snorts behind him just
to be like is anyone else seeing this
and then realizing not he'll gently
reach in and just try to pick one out
and just give it a quick examination to
see if it's simple mundane pretty common
is easier yeah this is this is right off
the rack it spread apart eh
all right you look you're like reach
behind and like pull one out of his
throwing daggers and compare it to that
to see if there's any similarities it's
there they're decent quality if there's
nothing remarkable about them but this
is this is definitely this is definitely
a solid solid instrument right and based
off the job that I had gotten off of
this I was under the understanding that
I was just delivering stove equipment
that's exactly what it that's exactly
what it looks like and until five
minutes ago yeah that's what you were
doing well then place the dagger back
close it up and then I guess with that
information he'll begin to kind of
recollect the past few days especially
with his uh his client I suppose if
there's anything notable about this
individual anything they said what they
look like are wearing or any of the
other mercenaries seem to be aware of
conscious oh yeah here's the here's the
main things that you can you can take
away from it okay whenever whenever
you'd break down camp you know we can we
can just have one of the conversations
that you had during that time if you'd
like
sure you can do you can just be playing
it back over in your head trying to
assist and think trying to recalibrate
based on this new data yeah so
you the the person who owns this Caravan
is right there with everyone this is
this is a this is a jovial but like wiry
strength character like not not a
probably not a stranger to combat but
very but he you suspect that most of his
battles he wins with dialogue trees hmm
okay got it
right so he it's possible he's built
similar to you
character-wise sure you find out that
his name is galih breath well ver della
breath okay and he is from red larch
originally he grew up there got out as
soon as he could but he had but red
larch has earned kind of a name among
the sort of the upper crust as being
it's almost like a gentrification thing
okay like it's earned a place as being
like the type of poor that you can go to
and be a tourist and they have something
there they have a festival there called
last stones day and with all this
increased interest like in his hometown
that he was so happy to get away from he
thinks that he can come back and make a
big splash there's a there's a few
cultural practices that he thinks he can
make a pretty penny on gotcha as far as
I can tell gala breath is like a look
I'm like a chef or something or just I'm
a Mason who Addie dolls kitchen
equipment an entrepreneur got oh boy I
was a male entrepreneurs
he's a chemise yay okay okay
some of the people he's running with
don't seem like chefs no this is outside
of the mercenaries he hired for
protection these are just very humble
don't seem like they would be don't seem
like the keulen airy hmm type but what
kind of read what I have on them are
they clearly underlings just go ahead
with their underlings but they are they
have a perpetual they have shifty eye
syndrome or our SES
yeah and they're constantly doing deep
psychic boring on people staring at them
okay all right so toady is in front of
stove having all these things they're
not in a position to act or do much
about it but well you you want me to
absolve you you want me to say that you
don't have to act just because you might
be murdered by all these men I can't do
that I'm saying dear internally assess
to himself this would be a great way to
be liquefied yeah all right so he's
aware of this knows there's something
shady going on there yeah this isn't
this doesn't feel like the job yeah but
this is not a soul this is not a problem
that he himself can provide a solution
to on his own I think this yeah so he
has a name he has their destination and
based off memory all of that he
generally knows what their goal is and
he can use that information for
potentially righteous purposes upon
arrival at red large but it still then
it's been codified yeah until then he
cannot cause trouble for his own
passageway for his own volition
this is sort of freshen the person who
usually sits in that chair
we have created a two-hour detour for me
exact same scenario pull every thread
well it's early give me some time so you
take a you take this opportunity you
know door closed
you yeah in your mind you've call ated
all this information yes
stored it correctly the earth is easy as
ice recall yeah death is actually a
studious note-taker he's done
cartography in the past while in the
jungles of cults and the like so you got
to there yeah yeah so he actually like
just John's notes down on quick
parchment and stuffs it within his uh
pouches or backpack or whatever some
purposes for a recollection later but he
is but he has not written this down
it sounds like after seeing like has he
ever seeing all the daggers and stuff
yeah I think he'll simply write down
he'll write down the information of the
job itself Derek Galbraith what he does
the stone Festival location nice nice
so to operate from there yeah so this
your cart rolls into town through the
the southern road and you think that the
the wise woman might have been too cruel
to this little town oh so this is not a
is it quaint
it is it is quaint okay it is quaint it
has the correct wholesome amount of
bustle okay it has it has the amount of
bustle one could be one could find
comfort in and so the all the carts sort
of squeak to a stop basically just past
the first intersection in town there are
a couple Finnish blue buildings okay
that looks like they look like they
might have been like a maybe like a jail
or something like that in a in a earlier
more wilder time in this in this town's
history but now appear to be they're
being rejuvenated with new paint wood is
being repaired where it needs to be
repaired windows are being placed Wow
where before there might have been the
occasional bar riot the gentrification
exactly right exactly so this this place
is is is working up and in fact you can
see the one on the left
they're building a kind of edifice sort
of against the facade of the building
and there's two stone columns that go up
sort of on each side of the front
the main double doorway is right in the
middle and they are joining up at the
top and then there's a key stone right
in the center of it it has a massive
like a massive chunk of red glass huh
and I find this to be the most striking
in this town yeah it's a little it's a
little uh what it what's it called it's
a lot okay yeah all right it's a lot all
right so we have arrived though
absolutely all the mercenaries are my
job complete to see exactly the
mercenaries are lining up
they're each getting their they're
getting their five gold yeah great five
gold Wow guys it's gonna say I'm gonna
send you home with delight it's gonna
write that down I'm gonna send you home
with delight five yeah
death will collect his coin and as he
does give like one last smile look over
and be like collect information in
details about everything about you go
thank you
this is a terminator vision yeah it's
just
Dayna going this way yeah just like yeah
you're wearing this this you got that
scar okay goodbye yeah exactly
so immediately you're assessing the the
first thing that is noteworthy why'd you
give me more of this perception since
you'd also well sure we want to rule as
many dice as possible between the world
20s people get you 17
TC 17 off of a six collation make us
better yes so the main thing about it is
that one of these buildings one of these
two buildings here is being clearly
renovated and made to be a lot the other
one is being repaired but is not
receiving anywhere near the same
affection okay so it's not it's it's
being made habitable and whole but it
doesn't appear to be a part of the this
operation here but you can see workers
who are working on one building
travelling freely back and forth it's
clearly a part of the same process or
like the same company is working on yeah
all the way it's clearly a part of the
same project oh sorry I work but one of
these is getting one of these is being
taken to the next level and one of these
is simply being made so that it won't
fall over the next time there's a storm
okay so death has arrived here is aware
of these buildings and has essentially
arrived with now two objectives and he's
gonna give priority to his own
vendetta's so through so mechanically
speaking I have the city secrets
background future mm-hmm and also if
Yves can't so talking to locals and the
like to collect weather and information
I can to learn more about the building's
perhaps visit the building myself and
see what's in there and then ask around
and basically tell people he is seeking
omen drawn and is giving a description
of that I'm him like where is this
person oh that's incredible
seeking almond Ron he I could not I
could not love you more
absolutely yeah that says this is the
place this is the place you would go to
ask so you are you're fishing around for
information about the buildings yeah
and for omen drawn yes so because I was
told last I knew he had rings and that's
all that read large and clearly he's
either here or been there exact
hopefully still here within the day's
travel exactly um so you even just here
on the main on the main road there's a
variety of businesses and shops that are
that do some trade here locally in the
town but a lot of a lot of the
businesses like the like the wagon
business that we saw over there yeah I
mean these are these three wagons passed
by a wagon business and you saw right
and you and you saw you saw a wave from
gala brass to someone in that in that
first wagon shop
alright and they're a place that
apparently sells primarily provisions
and things for the road got to either
you know either and for longer trips or
to ship to other places okay and you go
in and just like casually mentioned home
and run and you see a smile across the
woman's face she's just she's just
finishing out a work order yeah she's
directing people in the back to take
these barreled like big this barreled
poultry and oil and they're loading it
onto carts out back and she says I'd
heard Allman was in town just a day or
so ago my my guess is he's probably at
his mom's place he's a mom frothing and
audre he has two months
dia has never heard these names before
the entire life she says what do you
want with them
gif hesitates for a moment and just says
BEC just seeking employment oh well he's
cut that he can't play runs through him
okay III had no idea that the drawn
residence was here in the red large cell
it's incredible it's more than okay do
they run it or just run so oh yes yes
yes yes it's the drawn-in courtier of
course they run it that makes sense it's
not far from here Oh actually she says
just head down the long road take a left
at that intersection down there right
around the corner you're gonna see it on
the left amazing thank you so much I'm
really excited I appreciate that
deaath turns and like takes a single
step before pausing and turning back and
then she looks like that and then brings
up I was on my way in I saw it's really
fascinating billing that's that looks
all Nate that's it's impressive you know
that's about her face crinkles up she
says yes the the well verb boy is back
in town he has gotten big city airs and
he's trying to bring big city horseshit
to read large you know awful I'm sorry
to hear that
hmm well thank you I'll be on my way and
as DF turns and now with like a
determined almost stomping walk as he
makes his way towards the the drawn-in
absolutely walking on your way back it
is precisely as she has described it who
left at the first intersection just a
little bit around the curve you find it
there's a long alley that you pass on
the left and you can see sort of a
rustle there in a like a wooden box of a
waste box
and you see the lid open tentatively and
inside you see a squirrel likely pout
much as you did in that Cirque de Soleil
way okay for them this is a perfectly
natural habit lifts up just like right
out of the hole like ribbon like a like
a pinnacle yeah just slurps out of this
thin space and you can see it jumping
away and in its hand it's carrying
something that looks like a fork the
squirrel is carrying a fork let's grow
is carrying a fork and so as it pops
away it's a and it takes a quick curve
and darts to there right behind the
building dear seeing all this just says
that's adorable
yeah we have as you get to the front
entrance
it's about midday it looks like it might
be a situation where another one of
these customary summer showers has it's
promising itself and as you are thinking
that it makes good gotcha
so you can see the wind pick up a little
bit while you're looking into the the
warm and welcoming front window out
front you see a sign swinging on a chain
that says the drawn-in courtier and then
just below it the hated symbol of
acquisitions incorporated yeah in a
small sub sign that swings according to
its own chain yes
destiny before that you know ominous
weather kind of picking up as he's doing
this just clenched fist give himself a
quick reassuring reassuring deep breath
it's like you can do this and then watch
for and like door open every throwing
matches left you you swing in and
there's no
one at this at this juncture one would
expect a peel of horns you know like you
feel like I feel like the universe is
not backing your play here as you you
enter a place of warmth and affection
it's literally the material opposite of
omen okay so you wonder if he's like the
black sheep of this thing you can
looking over to the looking over to your
right you can see what looks like it
might it's like a small raised area it
could be it could be a stage next to
that is a warm is a fireplace not much
need for it
right now in summer and then near above
the fireplace near to it is what looks
like a painting of three children there
there are a mess of tables spread out in
the center of the room to the left there
is a bar and a a woman who looks like a
statue come to life very like very
strong features and there there is
something in her countenance that
reminds you of omen drawn very chiseled
looking yes yes a similar hairdo okay
also all right
so she is a she she adorned with
equipment at all or just looks like she
is she actually looks like for someone
who is operating again she looks like
she is ready to lead a battalion great
okay and she's only a person present at
the moment yeah exactly right yeah right
right now it seems like this is this
must not be there a big time for them
okay she says you're soaking wet boy
yeah I just arrived in town and the
weather had just taken a turn for the
worse I'm afraid that's why came
I'm seeking seeking shelter yeah she
says welcome to wet larch listen she
pours you she pours you a little tea and
then just sets it up on the on the bar
and she sees I assume this is DF sprout
yeah
not just Jerri what's happening here she
pushes it toward you
hesitantly yes like actually approaches
the bar their stools there that's it no
you just pick things apart I come back
so he's dancers like not even looking
down at the drink just eyeing up this
woman is like how much is it this isn't
anything but when you get a room here
I'll take it out of them oh well thank
you gift takes up to the cup or mug or
whatever it is looks into it you'll get
the brief smell hmm quick sip I imagine
it's tasty depends it depends I'll tell
you what it tastes like
sure his reaction sure exactly so you
had seen out front you could see the the
tell-tale like the thick trunks of
gripping hop vines sort of climbing up
and around the in on the right side yeah
and this is essentially like a it almost
tastes like a lemon tea but you can
actually see hop cones floating in the
in the water so it's been be like like
tangy fruity alright dia flex it they're
not surprisingly tasty he was expecting
bitterness and hatred but shockingly is
like oh this is actually quite pleasant
um it's true walnut uh grass this place
is also your home I know well he doesn't
mention anything I was a blue I just
assume he's one
many tourists that we get in town there
have been a lot more recently but it's
something new to focus on other than
this like the crushing the barren
wasteland of yeah emotional well-being
right now so she'll just like you know
her ears perk up and she's listening but
not doing anything yet alright death has
not noticed walnut at all there is I
wasn't sure if she was still down here
okay sure
but yeah it's possible that she is yeah
just there's a single person at one of
the tables
red leather armor elf dark skin slightly
dirty but not too dirty okay
like thunder she probably tried ATVs or
some tow yeah yeah yeah there's that
like motocross dojo thanks um but she
but on her lapel you can see an insignia
of office a kind of wax seal stamp
interesting with that yeah basically
feels like he's like deep within the
Dragons oh yeah sides you can feel that
pressure yeah beginning to close in just
like one slip-up and just clamps down
yeah this is great
so deer still at the bar looks over to
this woman and I guess says maybe you
can maybe get help you've been already
so kind and generous this is the one
behind about yes oh she says prophet Ron
oh hello proper good to meet you
good to meet you my name is DF idea hi
prophet and a prophetess Oh a suit okay
it's short for okay yes I I just need a
room I have those I would like one
please you may have it how much is that
so per night yeah it is one silver one
sliver okay
if pulls out a single gold piece that he
had retrieved from his job and finds
across the table
it just says keep that for now I'm not
sure how long I'll stay but if I need to
give you more actually she says she says
here you're getting in you're getting a
room at the right time last stones date
is coming up on us fast are you familiar
with the day oh I've heard of it I was
just here just finishing up a job I was
gonna rest for a little bit maybe enjoy
the local locals and then and then make
my way back to Waterdeep that's all
absolutely well she says hate yourself
oh she says she says do you how long
have you been in water tea oh uh you
mean recently I was born there I'm sorry
I grew up there but I only just recently
returned there it's a couple of weeks
ago at best she says have you ever seen
Audra courtier play I haven't I'm not no
just you spend any time at all in houses
of music courtly intrigue things of it's
kind of like nobility or no no not at
all even in secret not at all
yeah he'll he'll respond saying sorry
the only music that I really listen to
even frequently is that of one famous
pulsing SEPA The Bard
perhaps you've heard of the drunken
dying tour starting to kick up check it
out sometime he gets jammed my Audra
your our job Oh others my wife she she
is in Waterdeep often to play really wow
that's so fun and and last year during
last stones day I had to
missing because I went to water deep and
I heard her play at court at court
that's that's wonderful
she says now I don't know if you are
looking for a job but my son a minute is
drawn is the owner of acquisitions
incorporated and I know that he needs
he's always on the lookout for young
people like yourself talented Esmond as
she was saying this dis was drinking
from the tea and he says all been just
[Laughter]
do you already know him any friend of
omens is a friend of mine yeah I'm not
going back
EF say I actually only know you had said
so earlier
dias appreciate it I've only only know
of them by reputation well that makes
that makes sense of course it does it it
precedes him it it hangs upon him yeah
like a warm cloak so home I'm iffy
listen so if you have never been to last
stones day mhm
let me be the first to welcome you now
you're not supposed to make them ahead
of time but everybody does and everybody
wants to and nobody really cares do you
sit down you sit down you sit down oh
but I'll sit down walnut huh keep this
young boy company oh well you got it
right so once she has engaged walnut in
this task yeah she turns back and
immediately it sounds like
a dwarven smithy in the kitchen there's
just a growing yeah yeah belching heat
something is happening back there
something is being birthed and you don't
know what it is okay
almost not quite intimidated but gifts
has an air of being just suddenly so
unsure about himself and is a purpose
prophet prophet says dear you're
perfectly safe
you're not her type and then she goes
back in and starts working dance well
then go over and just sit at the table
and sit right down just yeah well so
you're not here for last stones day that
was it that obvious
fairly obvious to the trained eye what
what brings you to read larch I'm just
here I'm just finished up a job I was on
my way sure
yeah and I'm only here look you like
oatmeal I kind of lean in mhm
I'm actually trying to find almond Ron
well you just missed him
what he was here he was here we need to
go last night um through a portal and
away what that's not a bitch it's just
like home
that son of a bitch um no way we're
talking about omen you know oh man and
wrong yes
omen if his hair were drawn that's him
worst kept secret of Waterdeep what what
do you mean what
so I mean gets about fare very well of
the packing yeah yeah on there yeah it
shines in the life
anime yeah yeah the life signs but you
don't which that's like a Sam Raimi like
the shove your face and looks impossibly
it's just branded on my see you're
hanging ah you can see it within my own
I just had nothing else yeah if there's
like oh I get it
you work for him I do so between you and
me and I mean this as earnestly as
possible sure why because I mean listen
I don't know you well enough to get into
it
you're right right I'm sorry
sorry I didn't mean to pry extremely
personal question you just come into
town just ask these deeply invasive
decent people you're right I apologize
walnut i I have nothing against you you
seem like a wonderful person thank you I
just I need help trying to find him okay
he has something that belongs to death
can you rube we're gonna we're gonna
continue the rest of this in spite would
like a perception check from you I'm
sure this will go great
it usually does still a 13 can I use one
my turkey thing yes yes you can my
charger things I take money away from
yeah exactly it's just deleted from that
you know it's been rough yeah but I need
a good role so shadow Council and
gathered waffle crew throng
your servant EF has offered on to you a
boot yeah we're gonna give you away
something cool I have this it is from
eliwood Academy it has a beautiful tiny
Tikes inside it has a clip Fricke it's
so crazy and now somebody's gonna get it
thanks a lot to you excellent work
you're welcome
so you're looking around and you see it
I everything everything exactly but you
see everything on earth
but you see you see like the termites
inside the wall you can feel them
through the soles of your boot yeah and
it's like as you're saying this you're
sort of looking down you're trying to
collect your thoughts you see something
on walnuts hand and you're like mmm and
then you continue to hold forth and
you're like what the fuck oh I
your hand is bearing the ring visible
it's visible oh shit
shadow council we are gonna come back
after the break with more Dungeons &amp;
Dragons fun with our good friend dia
don't go anywhere we'll see you soon
hello this is Jeff or kick or Kim's and
you're watching tests see team's know
when when last we saw our heroes and
indeed our new friend deaath DF had just
determined with a very valuable natural
20 that walnut dawn grass heir of the
enclave panics anima is literally
wearing one of the rings he came into
this town to get but we're gonna take
the camera we're gonna move it away from
that tender moment over here touka
thrist Rob who is you are still hard at
work tell me where you are
tell me where your investigations those
are leading you I was trying to
determine you have heaps and heaps of
books no on very specific topics
specifically a theory of your father's
about divinity as a kind of physics
destiny wedding rituals this would be a
time for to ask a computer to cross
index well as this scene I say this is
this this would be an opportunity for
for some dancing like on the screen
oh yeah all those numbers and yeah lots
of right right right and so I'm trying
to figure out whether or not the rings
would be tethered to this power or are
they the literal like three-dimensional
shadow of this construct yeah I mean
and that somebody has taken and carved
and like decorated because I assume that
there are they ornate no not especially
okay okay but they it's a metal I don't
identify but it is metal absolutely yeah
I'm I'm so excited by these by these
prospects and and and I'm I I don't know
which way to turn and it's because I am
so full of energy that I don't want to
be inside which is a weird feeling
because who doesn't want to be inside a
knife yeah all day what and maybe
because I want so I will I'm gonna I
remove that ring this treasured ring I
put it on the study desk where all the
other papers are because I am aware of
this power and you tell I need to tell
it walnut about this I'm gonna exit that
knife and maybe get a little Sun on my
cheeks I don't know why that seems like
a good idea because it should hate it
it's like it sounds right but it feels
good I think I'm gonna do that so yeah I
at the door you exit the door
retrieve the retrieve your father's
laboratory it's kind of appreciate it
for it blankety your your blinka TI's
make some adjustments right to this new
context i restore the blindfold because
maybe there's children could be children
just so it's perfectly clear festival
coming up exactly exactly just so it's
perfectly clear both to new friends and
old kethry Straub's eyes are not eyes in
the classic sense they are a what
appears to be a almost randomly
distributed cluster of gem-like eyes
that blink independently yeah it's Chris
I used I'm not saying it's cool i D
I think it's great oh man
what these guys have done for me so you
will hear whistling and somebody
descending the stairs and the whistling
keeps stopping intermittently as I like
yoi I'm gonna come down and I see a
stranger and you see it at a table at
this at this point I want you to roll in
our can of check ooh
all right let's do it and I'll I'll give
it a little extra flavor for a dollar
more okay that's a 49 yeah yeah so that
yeah that one was a the other was a
fourteen imagine that so you get down to
the bottom of the stairs and you see the
group of them and you're like wait a
second and in your mind a diagram begins
to form that sort of concatenates the
concepts that you were working on I
think it's it's completely the wrong
time to have this epiphany it's
happening and then and then as you're
and then as you're thinking about it it
just there's a moment where it just
loses coherency and it's just like a
cloud of minnows it just and now there's
all this new tables and a restaurant
yeah worthless oh but I so what yeah
what kind of from just your postures are
you like this is it heated is the moment
that DF saw Evelyn's ring yeah it was
immediate like stand up so fast the
chair behind them falls back over not a
threatening stance but just like an oh
my god Wallace freaked out yeah her
hands gone for an ayah oh shit scared
yeah dude I reacted that like it was a
real thing okay is real reason they are
real thank you finally some of the most
real thing in my life for now thank you
this is great uh have a great time yeah
yeah so you see dear flex - before I see
that these stances change and then not
really knowing what the play is I just
go look out looks around I mean hello
everyone so in the middle of this profit
is - invested in the idea of
communicating to the next generation the
value of tradition mm-hm and Jam sure
and so in the middle of this like hand
on knife your back is beginning to arch
kisses at the base of the stairs
thinking about something she says all
right now don't tell anybody and then
she puts a plate down in front of you
walnut played down in front of you dear
and she says snooze you lose chorus
that's fine that's always true so in the
middle of this so there is this up here
which is anger yeah and there is a
person there and you've just met them
but you don't know why they have it you
don't know why they have the ring and
that's a huge problem but now there's
also a hot pastry down here rolled in
rolled in powdered sugar it looks like a
like a brick like a light crisp brick
and there's a little bit of jelly
beginning to pool around the base of it
and then there's a fork I just I'm just
I'm just offering everybody the
information they need so that they can
continue to roleplay there see please
get to it dear standing before you sure
clearly tense yeah so they're ringing
like went away on to the knife yeah okay
helos like to put hands up right away
let go no harm like not trying to attack
you anything but just like way
did you get that this oh it's funny you
should ask this is a gift from Holman
his hands went from open she's like oh I
know pretty great yeah so then I
eyebrows like Pharrell his stared
becoming more intense going from his
hand back up to you and says he gave
them to you
well he gave one to me and one to my
friend here then looks back it snaps
back I could throw a sand just cuz just
jaw like slowly just send he was like
there for work why are we upset it lasts
stones there how long were they in that
knife walnut okay somebody should get me
if it's been weeks
[Music]
so I'm but I've heard this so I'll come
over like why don't you what do you mean
the Rings they're not important for
anyone to know why do you have them
death takes a moment realizing he's
still in a public area to collect
himself and bring his anger back into
check
picks up the chair sits down and kind of
sits down that before you buy silver in
a tense position sure focusing more on
walnut cuz he saw the ring on you right
and I'd imagine does not see it on
Catherine okay in a lowered almost
growling tone DF will say those rings
are not nothing almond drawn stole those
from us okay alright
they belong not to me but to a different
okay while I'd love to take you at your
word these were a gift from omen who
we've gone over is great and we love and
respect as an employer and
anyway I'm not just gonna give you this
ring
I respect omen he's nothing but a thief
a charlatan who tricked us out of sorry
friend I have my own feelings about omen
but probably unwise to say that stuff
his mom's house she just baked you what
I think is a delicious above ground
delicacy and taste it no mushroom not a
single one yeah
can I get in that kind of check yes you
can that's a additive 20 okay please
continue to ramble and I'll tell you
when to stop okay now you yeah you're
fine I'm tell me what with the pastry
yes I what I know of Ullman is he's a
man of a man of means I don't imagine
that he would have to steal something
like this that he would give to it
valued employees such as Thank You Aliki
and myself but when you say maliki yeah
you look down at the two plates and you
can see that in walnuts you can see that
it is completely contained there has
been no spillage it hasn't been plated
it is just the square right Deus is the
is the cornerstone and it has the spill
and in your mind you begin to propose a
question to the universe in a place
where the veil is thin in a place where
gods have walked mmm would that affect
the ability to create this divine vacuum
would it be easier there to pull them in
so you imagine a model a conceptual
model that represents the prime aterial
plane the laws of magic and the laws of
divinity and meshed in a single
sophisticated geometry and you wonder
idly you wonder if you were to perform
the vez thani wedding ritual with the
rings in the grove at tribe or where
Maliki had already manifest could you
create a vacuum that could attract even
imprisoned the divinity of Mallick of
mela 'the when you come to you are
supporting yourself on a chair breathing
hard alright you've witnessed that and I
and then under my breath these rings
they were ours they were are you God no
what no are you sure I'm pretty positive
no no God hmm Jerry dad couldn't be God
not sure I am NOT a god I don't think
he's a god thank you I'm glad we can
agree on something
yeah and this is the only thing don't
rings themselves they were created back
when surely you are aware with the death
curse that was yes yeah yes I too was
suffering from the death curse I was
rotting away every moment during my
existence and there that death curse was
only stabbed off thanks to one evil and
maher zain paladin of a founder shining
light within this black world so you so
you hear a little scribble in your
document
oh I immediately check that out please
continue all right and through her own
sacrifice of her life thanks to uh
ancient I just miss Donnie ritual she
gave up her life transferred her soul
into two rings hmm those rings are not
just rings of magical protection nothing
soul maintain mundane those rings have
pieces of evil and within her she
perished once more and graciously thanks
to ohm and Ron she was restored to life
and then took those rings so even though
her body restored she is not so you you
have this and you're listening to this
and you look in the book yeah and you
see the word
evylyn yeah and then you see it get
distant you see it disappear yeah and
then it says dear evylyn oh no and then
it gets erased Vanessa's dearest okay oh
and then it gets erased and it says my
dearest evil and it gets erased and then
it says evylyn but over the eye is a
little heart oh my goodness um evylyn
spelled wrong yeah right could you
there's no line go why to form the chi
right back you can so i write on it i oh
man question mark this is he and i say i
right it appears these rings you gifted
us are of some import of some small
importance he says to who I hear it
idea idea dear
hmm hmm okay I say should we return them
after you make use of them negotiate
their return well it will be done
it also says put in a good word for me
with Deus and I'll be sending you a new
document see ledger without some of the
concerns your current one has understood
is immediately like I need to tear all
the pages out of this one so that I can
keep them well we'll deal with that
later um may I frame yeah as we've
returned yeah so now you return your
attention back and I have explained some
of my like why the rings are important
like in terms of trying to free these
deities which this this interloper
patron God has disconnected me from my
true patron how we're trying to actually
stop this entity and an entity
responsible for this mess one gives you
a little but from that I start going
down none of which would have been
necessary had I not attempted to help
omen drawn right and lost my sanity
rights thank you setting me back and my
work yes there's nothing you can do for
him it doesn't come with a cost is what
I'm talking about yes and you know I I
don't know I'm very well personally but
I just just seems someone you don't
treat people like that you know what I
mean like absolutely need to you lose
your mind you talk to a god you think
it's the God you want to talk to turns
out I don't know which one that was and
now I got this whole thing you know I've
heard just about enough Chris I know D
doesn't fit at the omen but I expected
better from you we have to admit he he
did knocked me down a couple pegs
well maybe you deserved it that's true
great I did that pictures wouldn't have
thought that here Josh can you tip the
caller please oh no so it is at this
moment that you can hear that just the
purposeful weight of profit drawn
approaching the table and she sets her
own plate down our own corner stand down
roughly with a fork and as she sits down
she brings a mailed arm around the plate
almost in a like a defensive protective
measure for the cornerstone she has a
she has a fear that the cornerstone will
be eaten by another and she has provided
some protection for the cornerstone and
she says what's the problem over here
nothing at all just uh a few
disagreements about a longer ship friend
of omens is a friend of mine dear how
can I help how can I help these two have
rings that belong to a dear friend of
mine as they are a part of her literal
pieces of her and I only seek their
return no hostility no animosity only I
just want to make help make her whole
again
no well no time Chris yes why can't
their rings be given back cuz omen gave
them to me that's not a good enough
reason
because they're a material nexus for all
of existence by which I'm a free God's
who should not have been consumed by the
vile one that marked me what and that's
both rings not just one of them I
suspect there may be more as far as I
know how hurt was this friend of yours
how many rings the cheap I'll integrate
into only two okay
Ezra huh well only only the two you you
need both to save gods if my
calculations are correct we would
attempt a ritual after which you would
be welcome to have them I have no
attachment to them I kind of don't like
the way I feel wearing them
he said prophet says cthe ris walnut hmm
what can you give dear in the meantime
that is of value hmm there's a lift the
promise that these rings will be
returned being an adult is very
difficult this is it I okay cut there's
my girl you have things of value you
keep all of our things of value that's
true dears almost interrupts and just
sounds like I don't I don't need things
I just I just need evil and back or at
the very least your word Catherine I
believe you and everything you're saying
and if these pieces could help three
gods there is nothing that evil them
would want more Oh friend even Owen
would understand that I appreciate that
very much but you don't know me and have
no reason to believe me or her for that
matter or any of this therefore prophet
says you're not selling this because you
did let's go back let's let's go back
ten
second you felt okay with it yeah okay
thanks Josh
divine intervention all right are we
good yeah Oh are we good yeah well I was
merely you were saying that there should
be some collateral we're good and then
she stands up brings her plate and then
finishes it on her elbows on the bar so
and I this is the greatest game of all
time I don't mean like what we're doing
right now I mean this fucking game yeah
this is crazy
I get out my um kourt's person bag oh
one moment Oh for our gathered friends
from the waffle crew and our new friend
of course TF in acquisitions
incorporated specific jobs have specific
tools associated with them so a document
sir had basically like a mystical means
of filling out documentation and
communicating a horse person has
something like a combination of a
commitment and a bag of holding so it's
like a creature that has one belly but a
bunch of mouths that they can wear since
a central location that the belly is
gross okay it's as gross as it sounds
please continue these rings I think
could be the key to freeing MELAS then
we can't give them up not yet not yet
not until we perform the ritual but in
in their stead how and so the exact how
much have are we on the hook to return
to the main office because I can I can
just hand you 653 gold pieces which are
yours to hold on to as trust that we
will return the Rings i I suppose it's
done
653 of them
they're everywhere yeah like they are
everywhere they're rolling like one is
rolled into a crack one is rolled back
into the Mousehole so 651 3
monix is chasing one no going back and
forth at 200 so I think I agree the two
nights over I think we're we grave
robbed that from my dying house in the
Underdark right launder that yes it's
that one clean get that one cleaned out
I mean hopefully I don't I don't know
where you hail from you seem to be a man
of culture and refinement and but
hopefully this is enough to show you our
serious intent deaath seize the money
annexed responds by saying there are
more pieces of evil and that need to be
restored and I think this alone could
could help with that I didn't even have
a I even have a plan for that part but I
think this alone could only use the
Rings but then then we give you those in
the night but I get this part back it's
not a run oh yeah oh I'm sorry
right now if now if we should lose the
Rings for you're welcome to enjoy that
coin which as the acting horse person I
can say has no meaning to me should but
a kind of circulation on underside of
the organization only collateral and I
understand that and you have my word
that every single one these pieces will
be returned in good faith right write
that down your character sheet yep
because Chris Perkins is gonna fuck me
with that I know it he's gonna fuck me
with that no it's gonna be everybody's
getting busy you like oh there's a hole
your bag right
and I say I don't trust you but this is
the bargain of straw
I have no way of knowing
keith has nothing of himself that you
can actually offer back as like a
counter collateral in that and almost
like aunt Pat yourself down be like is
there anything I could possibly I got a
viola sticky poison yeah like you forgot
his wallet
yeah he doesn't carry one that's why I
have poison there are more places than I
needed all right well if there's any way
that should you do this ritual and it's
successful and it works and a piece of
evil and can help you and help this
plane of existence free gosh just let me
know and I will return in good faith and
honestly it's refreshing to meet
acquisitions incorporated employees as
well as Noble as you are definitely
would say do I like live here or is this
place important to you yeah wedlock is
extremely important to us great I'm
ambivalent how about this is a piece of
collateral I have information
I believe information of import you can
come back to this show like it anytime
like just any time you want to just to
come back you're either word my dude
just come back please continue
I don't know if this place is frequently
in danger from strangers or even
possibly people who actually live here
but does the name gala brenth mean
anything to either of you Cala Brown no
with a G no yes her name her it was his
first name pet what kind of first name
merchant I came in with him I was
providing just simple protection for him
along the roads they think nothing
happened because I probably would've
gotten docked to pay but he had arrived
here claiming only bringing stoves and
cooking supplies did not even at any
point say that these stoves are gonna be
filled with sixty daggers Oh hmm where
are these two
delivered do I know okay I tell them
yeah it's like maybe two blocks from
here yeah like those buildings back
towards the entrance do we know the
place or this is like being it's
absolutely
oh yeah it's it's you know exactly where
he's describing it's right up on the
main road
there's a sort of a grassy section in
the center of that it's one of those
sort of like um almost like a triangle
like a pie shaped block yeah it's it's
it's literally on the other side of the
curve from red larch mm-hmm
except it's on that and the part of that
curve that faces the long road to - they
were jail houses but they had been
purchased relatively recently no one
knew who had bought them but they had
heard they had been purchased and were
being renovated and because that that
the facing on the long road that's a
very limited real estate here and
especially with some of the bumps in
local population and certainly with last
stones day coming up like there's
definitely some value out there and it's
probably better at something else than a
jail house are we concerned that so
there's their stoves yeah before
carrying contraband or something I'm not
one to meddle and these are not this is
not a business of my own however I am
very keen to danger or when something is
off
so are these not then maybe the type of
utensil you'd used to cut open a
delicious course down no this would only
be used to cut open lives but could you
also use it to be with like most blades
yes maybe they just got the wrong
Shipman then they wouldn't be hidden
inside a stove and intentionally
concealed from the rest of us hmm
[Music]
we are we're all worried that there is
like a guitarists were worried is there
some sort of a last stones day
fly-by-night fire festival scenario
where so where people can go and and
feast and then be slaughtered and then
the purge happens or they'll get nice
yes I'm concerned
absolutely oh that's right there's a
festival happening there is a festival
and the establishment that we're
currently at really does its business on
last don't say hmm but anyone's
smuggling weapons in at all it's
frustrating this is high value
I enjoy this plane conversation when I
determined the the nature of these rings
I was worried that I would have to
employ some of my artistry as an actor
Oh pause to see if there's nothing no
she gives you nothing okay and but it's
but this is so much simpler um how long
ago was this you just arrived maybe an
hour ago it but best literally just
arrived they could still be around I can
even find the wagons themselves and
point them out to you shoot Oh gonna
miss someone up just us
yeah I can accompany you absolutely you
can we're now where where are dinar and
Rosie dinar is the process that he uses
to sharpen toothbrush and now his the
new blade from sorsha mm-hmm you have
never seen it he it's like it's like a
elephant graveyard type thing um the
care that he takes with these weapons is
it's a completely solitary process
that's a good meditative process no
Rosie is currently attending a wedding
for one of her children oh okay that
makes sense we don't need that
it's just sixty knives yeah you don't
have sixty people even better great
actually with when we when I took that
job for della Brantford gala breath I
loved her yes how many of Fay's like
actual company not the mercenaries he
hired how many people were there yeah so
outside of the mercenaries have sort of
kept to themselves separate from his
yeah Michael Condrey underlings and he
says he has three with him that never
left his side okay I say there's Gala
Bram three others best I can't imagine
the mercenaries themselves are still
loyal they seem to collect their coin
and fucked off mm-hmm
fifteen knives a piece you gotta watch
some tough customers uh yeah let's just
go take us there
I'll show you will get up and
immediately show them as quickly as
possible
do you want to take like the back
streets we're in there in broad day it's
been raining yeah true enough
yeah we should go do you know of like a
back way to get to the southern southern
road entrance definitely it's it's
something you guys did red large is not
large right you know you'd have to you
know eww dippin chase a squirrel or
something like those things like this
happened there is there is an area of
greenery just behind it it's all that's
all we're actually really on the map
which is the best part more you said
this fucking Riddler oh yeah else on
earth
so yeah yeah there is there is a little
greenery that like a cops there perfect
that you can yeah that you could
leverage okay to examine the space so
then almost naturally without I mean I
mean this is first time ever here dia
this evil able to easily lead you to
this place that we can kind of sneak up
on and at least observe and try to find
where these bakken's were mm-hmm
absolutely so you find yourself it's a
rainy day and also there's the fact the
matter is is that walnut and cthe rifts
you live here and you've lived here for
more than a year now
yeah like
you're citizens of the town no one looks
twice where ever you would go in this
town and DF is with you
so he gets sort of a pass these in this
area this tweed area if you will you can
look from here at the back of the
buildings that you were seeing renovated
yes
so the backs the backs have definitely
not received the same level of affection
one thing that you do find highly
noteworthy as I said the second building
isn't really getting isn't getting the
the Disneyland Chapman the odd thing
about it is you're not you're not afraid
of a lockpick no you see a door on the
left
that sends a thrill of excitement
through your tendons okay like the door
might be worth what the building's worth
damn the investment that was made in
this building is purely to do with its
access point in the back all right
did hold point out this door of this
building and just say I can get us in
there great please do I'd love to see
this great this door would be like
imagine that there was a door museum and
but every quarter or so they have a
special way they have a special exhibit
a limited time exhibit yeah right it's
like one month only I think this is the
sort of door that would be like that
okay
Youth Gazette just a handsome spec wait
here and he'll uh very very swiftly
crouched in stealth make his way up to
that door using the sounds of the rain
to cover his footsteps through the mud
and the grass and keeping an eye out for
any possible password bias as he sneaks
his way up to this door I love it but we
like stealth we're not really a stealth
game and so nobody ever gets the role
Estelle
let's see it oh please don't be
embarrassing eighteen shows my rogue
expertise know your we care right here
this right here this is a cure this is
earn to survive
yeah right yes alright so I'm at this
door no you you get to it and it's like
this is a door you can see yourself you
can see yourself with I could live here
long-term yeah and you're like your ears
finger just plays over the plate yeah
and I feeling to myself I would pick
this door again oh yeah you would it's
like you want to lock it just so you can
pick it a second time
Percival's okay I'm glad the nars not
here alright so so then right away thief
tools out yeah gets right into that lock
and start yeah yeah yeah all right this
is exciting
oh geez 37 no no it's it's like good job
you know the disappointment of the
boudoir well I thought this was gonna be
a hard lock in a moment in a moment it's
all done my fingers like twirl with the
tools as if I was casting a spell
they're just so nimble in using these on
black legs yeah and it's just the door
the door can't it can't wait to let you
in yeah so it's just yeah
Suzette's opened it turns back to get
the wrist and walnut just kind of goes
up we have to like have to stifle like
I'm about to applaud runs off plastic
yeah no yeah so yeah so you can you can
you can get right to the back of this
thing from the wood from this these
trees in the central courtyard you can
slide right up in the front I mean
there's still people working and
pounding out front when that that work
is not happening on the back those
sounds are not coming from
great great no no it's it they they are
working
frenziedly to get to get that facade
ready for primetime all right
it's a limited time opportunity to ring
this town out okay
so you you find your way in the back and
you and you had heard from multiple
sources that these that these buildings
were jail houses for yeah for another
era a while yeah era of the city and
another bizarre reason for a back door
yeah exactly it's new that is all new
back there and the when you get in
that's proven quite true you can see you
see cells and inside these cells which
are individually locked you can see
crates and boxes of various kind
some of them wrapped in some of them
wrapped and gleaming oil cloth this is
it's like a warehouse but it's like it's
it's good it's like a nice warehouse
where it's like if you were an up like
an upmarket wealthy crate this would be
where you go so still a lot of cells
like with the bars yeah yeah exactly
right now they're using them as a second
level of protection fan montes with that
being revealed as the door opens as we
see this for the first time you see a
dance composer just cracked a little bit
hmm
yeah it's um the the hallway itself is
lit by a perpetual sulfurous green flame
and and you can see this the light of
those flames sort of just playing on the
fine fittings on some of these some of
these crates in fact here right in the
center there are a couple boxes perhaps
that were recently brought in in
addition to one of the stove pieces you
had seen before oh I recognize this well
absolutely
and then just beyond that there's more
stuff but interact as you will I want
I'm gonna leverage my ghostly gaze so I
can oh yeah pierced through without the
need of a lockpick you're what I'm gonna
see through you and everything in this
room everything I can see it all
oh yeah so let's flavor that though like
what what is when he uses when he uses
this vision you know how does that
pertain to others what can what changes
about their perception hmm what does it
look like that's super interesting is it
like another set well yeah like I'm
thinking that it's it's it would be like
those to link those two way beads beads
well yeah yeah like um a sequence
sequence oh yeah I think so like but I
mean but there's truth here like I'm
looking through things rather than just
this facade yeah and even though it's
just more facade that's deeper down I'm
comforted by that it's the inner facade
yeah absolutely yeah so I'm and this is
up to 30 feet I can yeah first guy yeah
you see daggers short swords bows
without strings you see something that
you've heard called a naked wand which
is don't get crazy it is it's basically
the wand before enchantment oh I see
so it's made from the proper wood proper
course but it simply hasn't had the last
phase performed on it just like and this
is it's an arsenal in this room it's an
arsenal and so you're looking around and
as your gaze passes beyond the middle
inside the stove you can see a number of
knives and sheaths and then just beyond
that you see what looks like a pile of
shields and barrels but there's a
complexity there that is that isn't
parsing and surprising to you hmm
I can't just easily see through it it's
like I'm just still so no you can see it
but it just it's a lot it's
comically complex oh I see it's like a
it's like an x-ray of a yeah yeah it's
more like it's more like a blueprint for
like a blueprint extraction
yeah explosion of a GM of a geometry
okay
I'll point that out and say that there's
a object in the corner there that's way
more complicated than a shut box that
most of these are all right so down this
hall do we see another entrance or their
possible exits no this one in fact you
think it might have had an entrance at
one point it has been replaced by new
wall this is the only one mmm that's
weird
right we got him by the bucket has to be
right Carissa show me where that box is
will not close the back door yeah keep
it up you're out listen for anything
look around for stove pieces or anything
else oh it looks similar to see if we
can concretely say that this man brought
these weapons in here okay I'm telling
you everything that's like a half an
inch beyond what we're looking at with
normal vision is a weapon this whole
room everywhere in fact if we were on
the roof looking down I think it would
just the building would be a huge gun
very good Oh better idea
Wallis see if you can retrieve one and
see if it's like counterfeit or
something this is supposed to be a
peaceful festival yes all right no we've
only been to one but I think so
there has to be a reason all these
weapons are here mm-hmm see what you can
find and then through Krishna this
direction he'll make I'll make my way to
the yeah strange absolute container so
as you sew as you as you approach it and
look close you can see that it looks
like a like a heap of shields and like
trunk like heavy barrels and there's
more armor you can see in sort of in the
center like set on one of the barrels
looks to be a helm we've got massive
helm with a beautiful red plume mmm but
as you get up close to it and examine it
the shield lifts up and then you can see
an arm and a fist unfold from beneath it
and it swings from the ground up
directly at your head it punches me the
shield is punching me it does
what okay you take 15 points of damage
do I get an armor class thing this hit
you're in the class oh okay oh you can
see it
alright so even with that deaath has a
second sensitive danger and as it's
coming in uncanny dodge I love it
alright so I'll take half damage from
that so eat and now let's get socked
right in the face and real basically you
just move by like you just you write it
like you just get a hold of it and just
like just let it let it absorb the yeah
thing and so at that it it continues to
it continues to gain mass and this pile
of armaments and shields is something
that is here explicitly to protect these
things oh I'm so I need initiative role
oh goodness
already my favorite number gonna be a
seven do you get for yeah 13 I got 12
Wow
alright so this this thing is yeah it's
just moving smoothly on its on what goes
for its hip it is just be sort of
gliding in the middle and moving through
the through the place just assessing in
mechanical calm the targets that it has
been blessed with how big is it uh it
goes up to the ceiling this is like a
large creature yeah yeah this is like
this is a large construct large contra
Oh gray construct oh so he is like he is
almost like it's like the plume is
brushing the ceiling mm-hmm oh okay um
so I'll go ahead and get real startled
about it
[Music]
yeah interesting that and um I'll cast
Moonbeam well it's a great beam
yeah and I'll cast it at the higher
level to get the extra d-10 baster goose
yes and he gets to do us save that
doesn't tell me what's a V gets to do so
your dealer's choice it's just against
your spell
yeah it's against 15 yo just do one no
perfect lemon Venus 16 plus 6 damn kid
only 222 I like what I'm seeing
nice good god yes
okay so the the silver light shines down
like it's this found this Holy Light has
found every crack in this structure and
so there's this dappled slices of power
are coming down through the floor itself
and if anything it's burnished this
creatures metal like it is it's gleaming
off of the edges and the damage that
it's done is only served to make it more
imposing somehow in the silver light in
the Silverlight is it is as though it's
at home that was just for her benefit oh
no all right about 10 that's not you
here you are gonna be a little goatee
yes yes yes you are standing in front of
something that is very very tall yeah I
just got hearing that all right so
there's plant containers crates and
barrels and things yeah here in the
center just behind you there is a crate
and then right behind that is the stove
you saw before other than that this area
is lined on each side by cells great
so from where deaath is large
constructed in front of them yeah he'll
actually hop back onto one of the
barrels behind him withdrawing his
short-sword gutter mm-hmm
Venus leaps from that and tries to like
grab onto the contract from like the
shoulder back area whatever to get into
a point where you can just stab this
weird mass in between the equipment I
suppose exactly exactly I know I'm gonna
I'm gonna least I'm gonna crave on an
acrobatics role yeah to do this because
if you're trying to get around to the
back it's gonna take some doing that's
21 that's fine yeah and get up run back
and do it and then try to so this is
like a this is like a jump up grab the
pauldron get around that guy so it's
like even if you're doing it it's like
it's like moving its arm up like to
catch you in midair that's you're just
over the edge of it a couple quick steps
on the forearm yeah and you're there
yeah
and then it's it's a I guess I should be
a standard attack role for this
I can't sneak attack constructs or
anything like that so she's done they
don't like it yeah just an attack ha can
I keep this d20 yes yeah Ryan won't miss
it yeah 28 it's a monster yep that'll
hit all right and then eight points of
damage
nice and then D F let's kind of hold on
yes you're always yes I'm just like
they're on him so that if anything else
is like reaching at me and not from what
I can mostly tell the generally
unarmored Chris yeah well except for his
ring of protection I took it off so
Chris trout you are standing in front of
an insensate otamatone that knows only
to destroy the interloper that's that is
the law in the whole of the law that I
respect a thing that knows its purpose a
little bit jealous I'm wondering if I
can not on my turn but just because I'm
still able to see through this thing
apps can I offer that information oh I
tell you where to put the sword listen
to this now we're talking yeah now we're
talking yeah so because that would be
the challenge right yeah is that a
construct doesn't have Anatomy
yeah it doesn't where I could be
provided
by your friend Chris I love it yeah so
would you say to that dungeon master no
I think it's okay but I do want to hear
how you how do you communicate that
because it's sort of a sophisticated
idea give me a little give me a little
RP tell me how could this constructs
this so I see you that I see that blade
plunge in and then do whatever damage
that it does well and you can see it and
in fact you can see straight through you
turn it off is just how you see now
you're ok with it right yeah so this
sword is is right in and you can see
that it is stuck right between two sets
of meshed gears mmm
and a tightly coiled spring yeah so he
is he's found the single place in this
quadrant of the creature where he has
not made a mess of its insides yeah so
then yeah what I would say to you is
like yeah based on where he is or like
you're just you're three inches from the
from its main spring like like try again
a little higher higher higher up yeah
all right so with that you know do you
pull sword out and then thump on his
next turn you can try and get another
stab into there I love it
the the entity balls up one fist the
left fist and then just tries to bring
it up and down on took a therus oh no he
doesn't do it he the fist comes down and
flattens the stove and then when the
fist is comes back up is just a
porcupine yeah
shrapnel and I didn't move because I
forgot that it is material and I'm
material because I'm seeing through
everything yeah
so I got Holograms oh geez okay
it throws its right arm up and then it
does something that a living creature
would find very difficult
which is its elbow spins completely
around oh good and then it reaches
directly back to grab you great a new
1780 yes he goes back and he just starts
he just starts to like pat pat yeah so
for where I'm at really congratulations
everyone where I like twist out from my
body so he's like hitting like this
space here right above my arm as I my
fleet basically like dangling from there
until he's done and I pull myself back
up and around and get that shorts or
nice we're gonna we're gonna we're gonna
play the Colossus issue the whole
Colossus game and and yeah right here in
the game alright well the dog rats um
it's your turn
seeing this thing just look at that
Moonbeam gone right I still got that
Moonbeam going I know it's good
alright but let's do that right I'll
continue to wail on him but good so this
time he does safe he does on this one
yes if he takes half time oh damn 25
would you get off that first coat dad do
some damage exactly just peeling the
armor so I couldn't go to work what's
easier to stab ya do you oh yes it's
your turn you have been given some very
novel information from your friend cthe
ris yes it is very foreign to death
having this kind of combat feedback from
an ally before very exciting yeah so
then like because he sees where his
previous puncture was and then it's
precise as you can according to Chris
just a few inches above that goes right
in give it give it you know what I'm
gonna use one of my charges to do so I
want to make sure this goose they're
juicy that's that's a 25 like it hey
there it is there's the DIA Twitter over
now yeah but that's why we used to
charge yeah but that was the second one
yes so you rolled a million yeah so 26
that's great so that said are you
allowing to make attack damage I am it's
gonna require eat each time you make
damage to enter odd it's gonna require a
second scan from Catherine's but yes
okay I like it so this is so one sneak
attack
good god what the heck is nine thirteen
sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty-four
Wow and like so you guy gets it in there
and gives like a good like shove to kind
of make sure he's getting those like
Springs and gears and things that you
were just moving or construct nothing
like that yeah Christ dude right we
don't this is not how it works on my
show we don't roll fucking handful as
the dice a people it's rude um so so you
you're like he I know that he told me
this I know this is exactly where I
should do it and then it's just like an
inch off and right on the tip of the
blade it catches something that was
moving inside and then you hear it sound
like an animal growl reverberating
through through the the full body of the
creature and you see the arm the right
arm just begin to shake like this oh all
right so I need from you I need I need
like a climbing South Lennox hold on
sure not great at that one my weak
points - oh okay yeah yeah it flings you
off okay and gutter is stuck in the back
of it okay so it's it's the right arm
it's just yeah just shakes me off and I
lose my Krypton exactly the right arm of
this thing is just moving back and forth
you want me taking fall damage or like I
can't you know that you're not that it's
not a high ankle um wrist you're out hmm
so then so you can see it work you can
see inside you can see a like a heavy
coiled spring just burst into ribbon
against in the interior cavity of the of
the entity you know what I've never is
this even the right time to do it
because I'd be I'd be shredded but I'm
curious if I can see it can i misty step
into it
if you wanted but that's because I would
allow that Evan is it's great I haven't
been able to see through things very
long yeah not for very long and I'm just
so excited this is a new ability of
yours it's pretty recent yeah yeah um
time maybe I don't have to do that I
wouldn't work
you'd use misty step as your movement
action but then my body would be the
melee weapon would you fit inside the
thing I would be destroyed sounds like
you you have your answer cuz I'm so
excited about is the ideally end yeah my
Robo gutsy yeah I'm so excited
oh here's the other question how does
how does a wisdom save work for a
construct like could I use hypnotic
pattern on it
would it notice with care right I don't
think I don't think it would work I
don't think but also the other thing is
that if we want to continue to assess
internals and continue to offer
sneak attack damage yeah to our boy here
that require you need you would find in
you need to find a new interior weakness
Oh like a different component to hit
exactly this is this is the Legend of
Zelda school of boss fights there's only
three is there you're not so the arm has
broken right I mean it's well Indian
internal is broke something is fucked up
with it you think it would probably
still hurt real bad right but I'm saying
there's no like oh I can see through
here there's a hole later right oh no
that you think that arm is probably off
the menu
no I'm saying can is there a physical
hole that I could shoot in I'll just
blast it or something like that oh oh
yeah you could oh you could definitely
just tack this creature
absolutely yeah I just want to find the
best one because my best one is again a
psychic attack yes and it's worthless so
what we're gonna do instead is let's do
a classic hunger of Adar cuz I'm sure it
doesn't like cold
so that is so yeah it's got to do a dex
save I don't imagine it will succeed you
know what sex is not there's no the best
nope that's trash
I don't know a couple of the damages cuz
none of my sheet cuz it doesn't hit okay
so there's the dragons everybody one
moment
okay the wrong angry Heydar as far as I
can get it away from us 20-foot radius
this is this is your tenth year tendrils
the tendrils that that space on the
floor is gonna open up and it's going to
just turn pitch-black
and those and those milky tentacles are
gonna rise up and just start to all this
is what they sent it yeah sort of beat
about the life exactly and so you're
doing this in a way that does not engulf
your new friend I assume I am trying my
best deal he's still freaked out by the
yeah oh yeah
and so it's gets it's constant you're
look at the damage
yeah okay it's constant all-out war this
is it's like a microcosm of of alien
anger yeah it's so difficult terrain and
it's gonna have to the damage I left to
because it ends its turn
it's different for the damage yeah the
damage is different than if it begins
its turn yeah okay
so now it's hard and he's gonna have a
hard time getting out of that space so
right so like right at your feet
yeah you can see these you can see these
milky sightless tentacles just moving in
a completely alien fashion that's like
right basically at your feet take a step
back from it just almost instinct to me
just yeah it's it's revolting
yeah July realize like it's Catrice
himself kind of manifesting these go of
them yeah okay the the biggest restart
sister and what does it look like there
he's gonna take a 2d6 cold which is a
gentle damage but let's try it anyway
it's gonna be six hey that's pretty good
right and like it and it's really cool
oh and he gets burger cold so he
takes his left hand reaches over gets
his arm and pulls it off showers got a
club and swings it down @cthe RIS still
standard he hates you he does he really
does hate Chris this time though I'm
gonna react with my misty step since I
can do that and hate oh yeah forget how
much because I never use it like that
even sorry about that everybody how does
it work I also okay with being crushed
yeah they say here you know what yeah
here's the new rule no i teleport it's
fine yeah it's simple you can teleport
as a reaction to a melee attack well Kay
casting time one bonus you do the damage
in the negs exactly alright you
investigate these things know anything
down I stand here and then we'll use
them next time you're taking like a
chance of facing down I realize I forgot
to move again yeah 13 points of damage
just another oh it's just the writhing
hand still twitching at the ends a
vibrant he brings it down and then
smashes Chris with it right smash this
gets wrist with it and then leaves it
and then whoo twists facing from over
here twists around to the other side and
brings his fist down on Diaz okay
no he doesn't alright yeah I dodged that
no mmhmm yeah he was just like right by
you it's like you're scooting away from
the writhing tendrils yeah and he goes
like this yeah I was riding tendrils
creep up and begin to seal themselves
around the hand and he's trying to pull
his fist up out of the I got a citrine
wanted unrest um I have a question
our constructs not objects hmm yeah okay
all right I like this is you are very
very much
my protege in this sort of thing how can
this universe be of assistance to you
one that does so long after seeing this
get smashed is looking up at this thing
and it's just feeling so hopeless and so
she grabs for mother and transforms into
a tree in into her tree form and she
gets big she gets large he's as big as
it she gets big as big as it she's long
she gets large sized larch and the great
thing about this is that I get to slam
attacks you do you get to slam it stacks
with a plus six to hit oh that was just
a ten I'm gonna take advantage
oh it's a 69 that's crummy alright so
one hit okay she took advantage of that
I took it okay so take that away from me
a nine and a two so that's 11 plus 3 is
14 but if it's an object or a structure
it would take double damage what do you
think yeah what do you think this is
exactly some massive wide range this is
why I made this thing it doesn't look so
you see on the other side of this thing
so his brother's fist down yeah and it's
trying to get this out of this like dark
butter it's like trying to pull its fist
out of this thing and you can hear the
servo just whining inside there and then
you see on the other side of the on the
other side of the entity you see as
unlikely a sight as you can imagine yeah
a forest grow in the darkness of this
place and just a thick thick swing from
one of its branches knocks the top of it
off and it falls over on you but um and
you are in the tiny place between its
head left shoulder yeah yeah it's very
taken aback by this as he is not used to
seeing a bill
or spells like this at home absolutely
there's that growth keeper now from Z
that from the helmet yes breathing out
you can see a there is a mist of a
sickening color summer being yellow and
green a vile poisonous color and as soon
as it comes in contact with your skin
and you take a breath of it it is it is
you know that you are engaging with
something that is just inimicable to
life oh cool all right
that is thirteen points of damage hm
you know you know that you have to leave
this place like it's a fight or flight
Oh
like this is like this is a noxious gasp
gonna fill this place alright great
I'll be out of initiative yeah exactly
exactly
alright so with that d it's like putting
a sleeve over his mouth we'll just shut
out like this whole place is gonna fuel
up leave now or we'll die out I go over
to in my big form take the club off of
you and turn back into myself just help
you out yeah so yeah I was gonna say let
me you got a mage and your your traps or
did you grab it I hadn't yet yeah grab
do you want to like maintain that so
I'll pulls it out and like in midair
I'll use my cunning action to use my
bonus actually to - so just like super
fast as I'm running through like I
grabbed that floating sword thanks to
your mage and immediately see that as I
make it fall down disconnected from the
rest of those internals you're able to
yank that thing back out you snatch it
by-god backward yeah way yeah yeah it's
super cool exactly a cool on your way
out
you burst from that back door make your
way through the trees
the door behind us to make sure the gas
doesn't get out yeah there may Chan
maybe sure yeah yeah yeah shut the door
behind you
and then as you're making your way out
through that forest it's even darker
outside than it was before the rain has
intensified and between the buildings
you can see the silhouette of a figure
watching the party leave shadow council
and gathered waffle crew Pham this has
been the c-team this is the type of shit
we get up to here I want to thank DF so
much for coming to hanging out oh my god
I'm gonna have it truncated thank you
guys tabletop guys trying to make sure
we got through a cool fight where
everybody had a chance to get together
but like I say don't go anywhere we're
right back
you