time is the enemy the pastor threatens
the fastest weapon you wouldn't make it
past a second and that's the question
play it brash and reckless to choose a
car solution you saw was prudent in any
simpler poker to don't become the putrid
it's that wealth said I pursue in no
mountain too steep for dungeon too deep
to send expanded remarks up to the top
of the peak of beneath they see Yugi
they come like sharks to it while I swim
in that money build like Carl Barks
through it so send your National Parks
drew it I'll send him home in a natural
box with the clothes Tyler most of the
parts included save your breath for a
cleric confessor if there's a lesson and
life is attending professor but if
you're seeking my official advice sign
on the dotted line and list of the
choice hello I am Tycho Brahe Hey of
Penny Arcade impacts I am also a mini
fest Hereward run CEO of acquisitions
incorporated but today at long last I am
Jerry Wilkins and I am going to run a
game of Dungeons &amp; Dragons for my
friends who I missed last week because
an interloper had taken control of the
game but never fear I've got it all
worked out you weren't here I'm enraged
to my right
Dragonborn narcissist dinar would say
the best one indeed revering the natural
world walnut dawn grass Wow to my left
not your grandma's grim might be
potentially whoa Mike could be
potentially where's the bee stinger need
to do like the staff I don't like it
there's just something bad crazy about
it it's getting bro all right let's
staff you hold a stat all right well
have to file a stash later if I might
continue emerging is though from a
mister out its kiss wrist Rob Chris
trout now so strange
horses shadow council mayor Labor's
please you strange forces interceded and
and made our
communion with the twitch portal less
reliable
that's all sort of in game right does
that make sense yes on the way there
back you know no yeah listen if a wizard
had done it she would be fine this is
what happens when Wizards don't do it
yeah yeah well some [ __ ] went awry with
with Jim so maybe it's Jim it's true
it's true let's let's let's move forward
as though Jim is to blame it is well and
canonical canonically Jim is to blame
that's exactly exactly go and blame Jim
now so did we have did we have fun where
we able to resolve Jim's issue
yes fine what was he a shoe yeah he's
not he's not a chicken anymore
three you should have three chicken so
he's not three chickens he's more check
problems but not the usual kind this is
911 problems but three chicks ain't one
I got those three he's good I had loved
all of it
yeah I just listen I'm just happy to be
here so walnut on grass there should
inside your documents yours pouch the
new one with the nice stitching there is
also a pouch with a hundred gold pieces
in it when I went back and saw the
episode I don't believe that Mike I
don't believe that my cohort offered up
the gold that omen said that he
convenient indeed that Holman said that
he owed you since then we all got a
hundred actually that's a lie apart from
the pit of hell yeah did you watch the
whole thing he did say that he said I
got 200 yeah he didn't he said you're a
real handsome yeah that was handsome
he's away right now but when he comes
back I'll do karate onion during during
Table Talk he was tell me how handsome I
was real real life Ryan I saw that yeah
not the dragon I was not just drinking
it yeah yeah he was my daddy be really
proud so when last we saw heroes I guess
technically there's two layers here so
when we last saw a parentless they were
competing in wizard kart a whole IP that
is wholly owned by Penny Arcade
completely original it hasn't seen
anything like
Oh reflection please I didn't card with
the K that's how it's changed yeah
exactly we put the script yeah but when
we had seen our heroes before that
mm-hmm
there were a couple different scenarios
that I want to refresh the shadow
council on so that they might make their
will known so on the Horde a river going
house of chants operated by lizard folk
Brahma is performing on the stage I keep
singing ami but it's not a me it's not a
me it's walnut on grass you're right
walnut done grass looking on hard face
ready to deal with [ __ ] and very nearly
had to because splooge off on the upper
deck indeed split off the returned had
to be got a protect in Deva so to speak
had to be wrestled away from the edge
after being dominated by a strange
rhythm from Brahmas lute now in the
belly of the ship and indeed beyond
share be stinger played this afternoon
by Jerry Hawkins we tried we tried our
best but she has she can't just come
play D&amp;D with us which is all I want
yeah but share and Rosie be stinger as
well as cthis trout had emerged through
a strange vault that was controlled by a
weird skeletal serpent that longs to eat
not creatures but their deaths it was a
very odd conversation but emerging from
there you came to a place that seemed to
be between worlds half stuck in the
physical plane and then bleeding the
other half into a dark and wispy realm
that Rosie be stinger recognizes
instinctively
as a place of
mm-hmm so as we discussed before rosy
bee stingers
monastic tradition uses shadow as a
metaphor but you're starting to wonder
if there is a deeper meaning to all of
those lessons if it doesn't refer to an
actual place and the denizens that live
there seated on a table that sits itself
between these two worlds appear to be
reflections of one another you can see a
lizard royalty a lizard king seated on a
throne almost like a but emaciated
almost like a mummy clutching a purple
gym
indeed the gym that it was suggested
would be on this boat and could be
strolling that might be very difficult I
guess I guess we'll see how it goes
across from him is a is a more Hale more
Hardy reflection of that same figure and
to the shadow Kings left is a woman in a
black and red cloak and by her side is a
sword that can apparently kill maim and
dismember without visually being removed
from its scabbard indeed one of the last
things that occurred when we played a
couple weeks ago was that a challenger
named dawn lariat who seemed to think
that he at long last
would be able to test himself against
rosy be stinger was in fact functionally
speaking filleted in a matter of seconds
and then to R and then what was left of
him was dragged away by the shadow Kings
guards here are the things that you know
as you came into this place you saw
whoever was you know standing to the
right
the Lizard King had literally been flung
into the sky as near as you could tell
you as you approached it was implied
that you were some kind of replacement
intercessor someone here to bargain on
behalf of the Lizard King
with these strange agents that are
arrayed on the opposite side of the
table okay
the agents that I can see are the Shadow
King indeed and your servant to the left
the cloaked woman indeed and it sounds
like there are guards somewhere hidden
that hauled Dawn lariats pieces away
indeed so just beyond you would describe
it as you know tastefully beyond the
conversational area as clearly that the
the remit of this royalty and these
intercessors they sort of form a ring
behind that that protects the
proceedings from people like Don Lariat
who think they've it's you know it's
their time to shine right
and Don lariat came in and made a
declaration against rosy Pete's dinger
indeed um and I've never seen that dude
in my life I don't know who that jabroni
was no no no you are not familiar with
anyone named Don Lariat now people
instigating marshal contests you know is
not unheard of sure you know there is a
there is a hierarchy it's not one that
you prize sure but there is a hierarchy
of martial skill right you know for
Rosie I think it's more of a means to an
end
right right and I suppose having people
come in and challenge her martial
Authority has been something that has
happened to her in the past so perhaps
it's not completely strange but it is
strange that it happened here yes you
did so okay all right so our job is to
look at the notes secured this is this
is some documentation it's gonna be now
some casting for this for them so don't
don't say anything we can't take back
I'll make a map
it's a good map the here's what we know
about the the Lizard King he kills
people who displease him he's been the
ruler for 700 years the Shadow King
needs an heir and believes that the
Lizard King needs to provide him that
air is that correct indeed and in
exchange the shadow king will reveal to
the Lizard King the source of his ale
okay you can tell that from even beyond
anything else what afflicts the the
Lizard King is not a cold okay he looks
pretty dead this is keep this is
functionally speaking a mummy right that
is clinging to this Jam
sure and and again again you'll recall
that this gem is constantly sort of
bleeding and leaking this shadow-like
substance okay and then on your way into
this area you can see energy of this
kind flowing down from the ship right
this was the same energy that I
harnessed with Grandma man see ya to
open the vault door that was just a
shadow that was you manipulating might I
don't I think in accordance with your my
grandma your you're packing okay your
classic skills there this is something
else and as I said these whispers and
wisps of this energy come some is
collected in the gym and some is heaped
up to the right at his hand and they
appear to be wagering with this energy
okay while the intercessors have their
conversations okay does he think all
that same stuff absolutely he is his his
senses aren't as attuned to shadow sir
but he is perfectly capable of assessing
it via you know arcane means okay I'd
like to speak to the halfling woman in
the cloak um and approach her I can't
make out her face
as I recall it's enshrouded in shadow
and I'd like to ask her what is the
process
that we need to follow in order to
secure this transaction how do we find
an heir for your shadow king were you
not informed of this process before you
accepted this task uh not exactly no
well they're a little light on
information and we've had it makes sense
to a certain extent we have lost five
today yeah so I imagine the time that
might historically have been spent
training them right you know assume we
received we've received no training that
seems relevant at all to this situation
and explain to me how we can make your I
just want to make your life easier I
don't want any approach if he has to
qualify actually yes throw men at the
problem right right yeah if you could
make it out you can tell the way that
the voice is modulated that she's
speaking through his smile okay she
rests her left hand on the pommel of
this sword and says here's the problem
we need an air you need information as I
suggested before any one of the lizard
Kings sons would be a perfectly apt tool
to be used in this situation okay we can
we can help them navigate the shadow sea
we can bring them into our realm we can
make certain that they are treated with
their with the correct deference and
they will help us to continue our line
in the world that we do it where do we
find the lizard king funds that the
lizard king stirs it's immediate it's
unpleasant to look at the the limbs sort
of Bend incorrectly like whatever is
holding them together is not what holds
together living things I've got limbs at
that dimension of the Suns
he's twists and like clutches even close
her own to the gym are his sons in that
gem I'm asking this of the halfling
when people speak to the Lizard King on
this issue
they are occasionally and when I see
occasionally I mean absolutely every
time curled into the sky got it yeah I
figured as much do you need do you need
time to commune with your power here
would you like to speak to the The
Lizard King and perhaps come to some
kind of arrangement yourselves well if
you're advising me there are three of
you here sure I mean he couldn't fling
you all at once I'm sure I'm attached to
these ones emotionally so I'd rather
none of us get flung is this audible -
yeah okay that that cuz this goes so
okay if we if we so much as mention his
size then he's gonna throw us so we have
to talk to him without mentioning the
fun somehow that would be my
recommendation okay great you're back
okay can you see that at this she leans
over in confidence to her Shadow King
okay
I would love to enlist your assistance
my mate yes um and yours share because I
know that you have a there's a there's a
soothing melody that you play that tends
to calm emotions and it does seem like
this is an emotional issue for the
Lizard King don't know a lot of lizard
folk songs I know a couple swampy ER
Tunes it's swampy is great
swampy sounds really nice swamp let's go
like that we'll go with that
can you potentially communicate with the
lizard king in a tongue that he would be
able to communicate back to you because
I don't think he's gonna talk to us I
think it's just gonna talk at us and
your voice you hear in your mind you
hear a voice
it says I am perfectly capable of your
speech intercessor oh I don't know that
I'd call myself an intercessor really
here is that an intermediary I'm a
mediator come here can we go with that I
am just here to settle this situation
because we need information
I have heard I've been sent down here
because your gem is under threat I have
heard that there are bandits in the
Horde that are here and so I was sent
down by security and I show like
whatever official yeah yeah I I I'm I'm
here to protect the gem so I'm just here
to make sure that nothing happens but it
seems like you might be exterminating
people so maybe we can settle this
squabble out because you are an outsider
I will reveal something that the other
intercessors did not know great I have
not sired a son for 200 years I see hey
raise your hand if you're in that Club
sons I think I've sired a lot of them
and they're no picnic Julian probably
some lizard man the occasional yeah I
mean let's get busy let's make one so it
seems like you're kind of at an impasse
with this shadow king who needs an heir
from you but you don't have an heir is
that correct correct
okay under knows there's no circumstance
in which I can reveal that I have no
sons mmm oh so he doesn't know that you
are the only one that knows it okay and
the only reason you know it is because
no one would take you seriously why do
you have scales all right I got inner
strength
scales right on this heart either
jumping I have psoriasis that's up I got
shingles yes the sames close he said he
says we need the information he has to
find out why the ritual no longer works
I have been resurrected every hundred
years without fail uh-huh for 700 years
right and I have led my people to
success sure the ritual no longer works
I can there is a piece there is a piece
of me I can get back okay
did you run out of sons were they being
sacrificed before for this ritual
there's a new demand notice there's no
sacrifice oh the last 200 years I have
not been able to be blessed by a son
okay hold on
let it go to the Shadow King we'll see
if we can work something out okay walk
over there walk over the shadow king so
ma'am if I may uh it seems that the
Shadow King needs an heir a son of this
Lizard King but he does not have any
sons will the Shadow King blow up a spa
yeah the training is this the confidence
yeah I don't care
[Laughter]
he doesn't any sons the purple gem hits
the floor nice okay yeah is it broken
no no no no and you you see this this
shape of the Lizard King just sort of
wrap around it almost like a like IKEA
has a lamp like this it's like a wicker
orb
yeah oh yeah he just wraps himself in
around it and then pulls himself up onto
the table they're playing the game on
okay Dark Souls stuff yeah
this is nightmarish at this point now
hold on now hold on I didn't say this
for no reason is there something else
the shadow
King will accept in order to lift the
curse and continue the ritual the ritual
that we have not cursed
the Lizard King okay let's let me be
very clear about it's pretty cursed to
me but we are not the agents of this
curse okay there they're rich will no
longer functions okay why does why does
that why does why does that reflect upon
our kingdom it's a good question who who
cast the curse
ritual it is it we never tell our side
of the story first okay this is
something we learned from an ancient
circle I'm familiar what's really that's
a good move what else can you offer uh
what what does the Shadow King value
sons Sons my moons um we got uh we've
got sons how long do you need the son
force does the Sun go to in their realm
forever no who's this is she cost you
this that's interesting what's the what
are their duties entail we need to
expand our line in shadow I mean it
might not need to be permanent leave
being a shadow son only the worst in the
world hey kind of science sounds kind of
off okay but how but I was given to
understand that you had no sons
and this wicker gym ball starts to roll
around on the table before calm down I
have a I would say my cup runneth over
with sons and I'm certain that one of
them would suit your needs just fine I
can go get one
Ranko ones right now was I get you yeah
it's just son you need a son got a son
right here this guy had a mom for a
while just curious about the how how
time works there or was there any
equivalence that we can guys can we have
him there for like five minutes and that
would five minutes an art plane it could
be like a like one you are well I need
to understand the contours of this this
air dumb lizard folk only not drow we
all got a little lizard enough hello
that's true thank you good paddle word
this ships crawling Lucas grab a lizard
guy off the deck anyway something um ok
I'm a dragon so you just you need a son
so a lizard lizard boy and you need him
now and then everything is gonna be good
here right
may I inquire this may be you tell me if
this isn't an appropriate question but
if we're to provide you with premium son
experience of best possible son we may
need to understand that such that we can
convince them is there anything about
being an errand that a given lizard male
you would find unpalatable such that you
haven't been able to find one at this
point is there something about this
that's unappealing to royalty we need
the line not just any son then we needed
that line to refresh our own so you just
need a shot and pass off yeah I'll try
it if you want to try it
alright can you go yeah I said where
yeah where are you presently he's
upstairs listen I know exactly where it
is
I really missed this listen I know
exactly how to get back up there it's
very easy um can you give me like ten
minutes because I think I have a
suitable candidate for you I do this by
mind - we can just you can yeah you get
on the car yeah let's jump in already
the plane what actually the little is it
you might be able to hear in this
ossified okay
but he's just a wicker ball rule around
enough for him anymore I'm very
fulfilling yours any any time you try to
access the party line there's just a low
level just rattle breathing yeah yeah
it's gonna be good reception on the
shadow side is not incredible you kind
of to get more bars because I have to
scooch over a little bit right right
just like feel it out like static old
hold it hold it up yeah let's try seeing
your tippy toes so this is the play if
we can get if we get Denar down here
yeah are you on with us yeah now you
don't have to bring you down are you
are you busy what are you working on I
got my hands full with what would play
you get this message you have it since
pulled him back yeah and he has made
this request of you yeah and on your
arms and armor oh you see what looks
like thick green paint what and when you
look at SLU goth mm-hmm you can tell
that where you have gripped him like
where you have wary where you have
pulled your arms away yeah
what's cool what's going on super AI
been nothing you having a good time over
there
you can see just like like crisscross
stripes of where you had to physically
restrain yes blue goth you can see that
you have let though you have rubbed off
this green paint and you can you can see
that just underneath it
you didn't occur to you to look closely
before yeah there are black sores
and lumps underneath and so he doesn't
appear to be less spry hmm necessarily
but this is clearly something that he
doesn't want people to know conscious so
he immediately he immediately pulls up
the back of his leather cloak and
basically flees the scene you see him go
back to the table
like hunched low okay snaps a couple
times and his people come and this is
the strange thing to go with him and two
others that stood sort of Sentinel
looking away from the table shimmer and
disappear yeah
so you see you see the Moussa going up
the right staircase okay heading through
the golden doors perhaps to the high
roller
all right sort of Stegosaurus things in
the back okay potentially towards his
room yeah it's a good guess okay yeah
yeah well sure what are you up saying
what do you want I got it's just uh
forgot going on we just it's down here
we just where we we just need a voice on
this yeah we're doing ask me right now
you gotta see it you just gotta come
down you know what Star Trek Kevin do
you know I don't want to come just tell
me the turbolift I got it here it's
really easy you just go access beneath
the stage to the kitchen through the
service quarters to the structure the
free living area at the end of the vault
now here's where it gets tricky I heard
something something vault guarding
directions to come on man
all right those things yeah I want to I
want to follow up only confirm he goes
to his room I want to follow us blue
goth I'm nothing if not duty-bound this
is my job to follow the guy I wanna make
sure he doesn't get in trouble I'd had
to stop him twice from killing or being
killed yeah yeah you thought you follow
him up that right set of stairs you know
onto the High Roller area you can see
his kids coterie just just as it was
they came to the boat on their on the
teleportation circle okay
it's the is this a tactical retreat
alright so they're covering every corner
they're mentoring each room before they
do it
there's they're identifying it to the
other and you can just tell you can tell
there's sort of a hole in their
structure they're missing they're
missing two of their number okay but no
then they they proceed through the
golden door okay and then go down the
right hallway yeah okay
click-click okay well I'll grab a guard
and be like tell your boss a room I'm
done I did my job
no all right yeah where do I gotta go
see you try yeah everybody daddy
important boy over here I'll give you
the directions and you get there and
it's perfect I'm just so happy for her
see so you see you're you're leading him
down so now not that way yeah yeah yeah
I'm in the chart what do you see what's
the story did you see your son yet sex
with a lizard man
or did it wait why son what it's fine
what no he's inside thought what he
doesn't have to be my son but he has a
royal son and you've lizardy I got it
what yeah okay what is all this I'm down
you're gonna get it you know it's really
important that we have a royal dragon
man that down here is royal drill I am a
royal dragon sort of coronation yeah
it's like that yeah yeah okay yeah it
sounds fun yeah yeah okay sit down
okay so you you approach you see this
whole scene and I think he gets through
the door in a mysterious way very
mysterious but well directed yeah okay
navigate Rick's and so I point to dinar
and Pat him affectionately on the leg no
this is his his entrance yeah here into
the Shadow Realm is very very US
magazine Oh
like it's 100% the tail just lizard folk
have tails I'm gonna say good dragon
born generally speaking gonna have tails
the cries what earth lesser and story
yet exactly during him I mean he he
comes in and it's I mean it's it's it's
almost you hear that it's like you hear
the DJ like oh nice yeah you're just
used to this yeah I'm not is your head
constant yeah guys are all here yeah
everyone else right yeah it's louder
than normal so Mike Nicola quemic the
King rolls around on the table that
spills some of his coins off the edge
gross yeah this is what is this he sort
of D can't seem self back on to his
arrangement of meth it's just an array
just a mesh really mesh swimming that is
a case for the gym yes yeah is your
curse to be like as undignified as
possible in death it's pretty good he's
he's just he's just pouting now I think
yeah okay so I'm gesturing to this this
beautiful [ __ ] dragon man and being
like you know since we don't have any
airs from the Lizard King
in two hundred years sorry about your
secret but it's important that they know
it I make his vibrates yes what is right
move I would like to submit this
gentleman for your arousal
that's the it don't worry about it I got
you first sidebar maybe laughing so hard
that she is hunched over and her hands
are on her knees huh that's the halfling
woman yeah okay okay
yeah it's sorry so she's not blown away
but heard her cadre there's there's
definitely some rumors going on here
this specimen of superlative draconic
heritage right okay now let me be very
clear what what do we get in exchange
for just trust me what do we get in
exchange for my friend here who is a
royal really a royal boy what exactly
what do you get and I can vouch for
because he's my son and he's your
sweetest avoid sick message so powerful
as his his lizard genome that's my
lizard growl DNA was fifth this filtered
out it was destroyed and it came I don't
be sure a lizard boy I am a dragon
lizard the lizard king I make shoes out
of lizards no you don't ha ha you make
shoes for lizards as a royal cobbler
continue with the discussion don't
listen silence husband Arthur Shadow
King raises a hand and he says I've seen
enough he says bring the litter and
within minutes
within minutes whole King lizard men
nice bring out a royal litter and then
rested on the ground and that nice
that's great I don't know what's
happening
security yeah this is gross thing and a
jam yeah now I'm being sold instead of
standing aside and they're there
directing you wordlessly onto this
cushioned seat now he is a very valuable
asset to me so I want to understand
exactly what this transaction is what
happens if he spends certain small
amount of time in the Shadow Realm what
do I get in return
as the intercessor you get the adoration
of your key sir and your King receives
the information that he was wagering for
to begin with okay when when do I
receive my asset back from the Shadow
Realm is my son you're talking about oh
I have strong feelings you'll find this
you'll find that time passes somewhat
differently here are you tricking me are
you kind of caught up and so you get on
the call yeah you figured it out yeah
yeah okay
then I'm being sold well we're trying to
play for what we're just trying to get
him to let go so we have so much why do
you care nothing Joan that's nothing
what track how about we just don't do
that job I don't get splitting the
slavery or Sonny wherever this is this
is like the other half of taking this
like the back half of taken imagine
taken but he yeah G to be taken we're
taking you as your yes you were gonna
get it we're gonna do it taking on you
what's wrong with that I want to be
taken out of so specific skills that how
much are the the Lizard Men Fe palanquin
they have put on a set of finger cymbals
and they're sort of like cleaning them
together rhythmically presumably in the
in an attempt state take it dinar on two
to lure him yeah can we you don't feel
necessarily very drawn to it you know
say that again high quality oh yeah I
don't know am i doing here yeah can we
be their God I have to go to a Shadow
Realm yeah okay and we can to my ass
yeah well let me cuz okay I'm gonna say
goodbye to my asset
now hello hello give me hugs
it's been wonderful but time to go no we
are I'm trying I'm trying very hard to
on my feet think of a way to do these
fools so what I think I want to happen
is that you get in that house get it you
get in that palanquin and um and then
like I'm gonna try to just switch around
to yak we build like a paper mache
version of you and swap it Indiana Jones
it are you asking me that this is not a
great thought-out plan what's the
downside here I get banished to a shadow
universe really hoping that you can like
contribute to this plan it's a
meaningful way we do have to another of
Jarama banished yeah yeah yeah thanks
man you know how much it eight tentacles
with some shadow is I kind of like a
lizard in our ape that is not gonna work
um I couldn't use yeah I have my
shooting well yeah but what is crazy
thought we just leave the gem alone
you just don't do it somewhere you're
here Wallace no yeah
how that's gonna get really mad oh well
that's a shame yeah I probably should
just be banished to shadows forever so
walnut just doesn't get slightly upset
yeah I want to while they're trying to
sort this out I want to go over to the
woman the bloke woman and ask her like
how are you able to describe the time
scale difference what what are we
discussing once he passes through the
portal and returns it will be as though
no time passed here for certain oh boy
yeah that's talking about for him pass
is there in the Shadow Realm how much
time will that be independent how long
they spend there oh I see doing spending
they're doing what you okay my guess is
you're gonna have to continue the line
so I think you're gonna need to clean
the Bona lizards yeah I think you're
gonna have to but Queen they're clean
yeah you're gonna make a shadow son
royal to yourself huh you're gonna have
a whole family in there that you didn't
get to just leave it come back so they
just get to abandon yeah yeah yeah
alright that's a good idea yeah this
sounds great
this is your first plan okay
this was option a here's my proposal you
distract the intercessor halfling with
questions as you are so want to do sorry
and then I am going to cast
accommodation of darkness on you and
minor illusion in the litter in the
shape of dinar but what is it the help
does that confer you a create a whole
creature shape I create the sound of or
an image of an object within range it
lasts for the duration
that's it if a creature uses its action
to examine the sound or image the
creature can determine is an illusion
with a successful intelligence check but
they're not gonna be looking to close at
you because you're royalty and you don't
want them looking directly at you okay
yeah that's your last demands don't no
one the fear no one looked me in the
eyes peons okay yeah let's try this just
right all right that sounds good that
sounds like this is really very tight
yes
I know this darkness I'm gonna ant I've
met a game this why is it this King
giving us this much latitude we should
all be dead this is not working at all
you're distracting okay right
distraction duty is that it okay let's
try it before I was excusing the
attentions friends I wish to inform you
that my son is very precious to me he's
a sweet boy
it reminds me of how my own seed was
obliterated within that within that
royal Buras in which he was carried and
I had not treasure him as knowledge of
Mike worthlessness but so in his stead
Mary offer a series of different heirs
perhaps to please you and tantalize you
hurry quickly my children I will have a
cavalcade of Sons for these Royals men
she says you are an idiot I'm already in
process it can't be stopped so I create
so dancing lights is the first time I am
out yeah I have raised 300 sons and
daughters agreed to legendary martial
prowess and every day of my life is
marked by their attempts to kill me none
have yet succeeded leave this place okay
probably want to leave well he doesn't
look impressed
I'll miss U's child every time you call
me your child I just like visibly
shudder just like this saying you're
even a little bit of a drunken boy so
you have you know undertaking your
process to disappear here you gotta sing
his line yeah so then I hug you I see
but okay but in the while she's berated
yeah exactly I have produced the the
glow man out of
but I've bothered to give it a tail and
it's just sort of cavorting like this
little asleep it's like a geocities like
all the 1998 website I have to think of
there's a page counter underneath the
shovel is that so
when the illusory dinar materializes
well I I have to scream yeah nobody oh
yeah
all right I'll do it my royal loins burn
hot and violent nobody look at me don't
I'll do it but so help me God no eye
contact
and I make a big scene I'm gonna try
really hard I gotta go because I want to
kill just yet log into the air for this
okay so then I'm gonna try to cast as
closely together as I can
darkness on you illusory dinar in the
Linea palanquin yeah there's a stereo as
they pause yeah there is a pause right
he's just that great the cymbals is very
good the the cymbals are you know
withdrawn placed into the pouches and
when the lizard men raise the palanquin
the leader of them sets it back down
again and then he passes his hand over
the do it intelligence check its way to
no way is no waste a slender it's fluffy
he's not that slow hot-air dork right
now at the gym you work yeah
the into the inter censuses that's
enough
can you solve this problem or not it
would seem not willingly can i there's
also an option
can I offer an apology you creep back in
you're outside you and glow man come in
with glow man out yeah that's the way we
were informed that some levity was
required at this proceeding and clearly
that's not the case and had we known
that I wish we've been informed of that
first before we came in made a mockery
of this proceeding just me we made asses
of ourselves this is clearly not I can't
believe it this is clearly not the venue
for art no I should see me I'm in
darkness yeah she she draws her sword
and the glow man seems to notice it
somehow
oh okay holds this little glowy handsome
the animation stops and he is just
annihilated tip-to-tail is cleaved as
soon as the sword comes out he's
reacting to this and then it's like a
magic trick like where a drape is drawn
off of a table yeah dinar is standing in
plain sight right there you went you
rascal hey it's me so much comedy before
yeah oh wow that's five more minutes
Egon I terrible dream that there was a
shadow and she tried to take dinars she
started tried to take dinar away trying
to sell Dena
no way so there's a couple things going
on here yeah is there a company vote
about whether or not dinar Blitzen is
going on this magic carpet ride I can't
make them go against his will
I can't either unless I got clarity on
that time if it was a couple days sure
but they're they're gonna keep their
gears okay yeah I don't live that long I
gotta send back bones
that's what's gonna add out to be the
Baconator oh by the way when when the
glow man is obliterated Curtis cozy huh
I don't care you have to throw that
spell away now that real yeah no I
definitely yeah okay no it's not gonna
work are we doing are we cutting yeah
Princip banan yeah okay all right
well not your grandma's grandma yeah
we'll continue this adventure in one
moment yeah we well we will a quick
commercial break
of course if you're a subscriber you
just see cool c-team stuff I'm back in
just a second was here why not hello we
have returned
when last we saw our heroes they were
making an absolute hash out of a
relatively rudimentary and concerned Wow
yeah whoa nice big your cell anywhere Oh
appreciate I have suspected this is the
equivalent of that you know you have to
put exactly three gallons on the scale
yeah as the jugs yeah you're just trying
to three gallons of lizard's semen yeah
I'm here doing it I've seen die hard so
many times you think I'd be good at this
no yeah I've got a gun taped in my back
nice yeah the list of men are very
confused about their palanquin okay
guitar will do it for them being a raspy
voice scratching their frills dude do we
look heartbroken but yeah I mean they
thought they thought they had a good
thing going here now look they're gross
they're gross monsters just could
improve think think of what you could do
for them
think of the lives you can improve just
by being near them I'd say like shirley
is like dinar that's inner I mean I'm
not convinced this is what I think to do
either but because it's you going I
think that you should be the one asking
the questions to make that determination
of this woman
I wasn't we weren't lying when we said
he was royalty but he's not my son she
directs her sword toward the exit and
points it at your chest the best ones
over there
I said wordlessly I leave dad know he
really is my dad has a double double
swerve double agent missile so yeah
we're playing we're playing cute with
the with the verbage here like what do
you mean continue the line what
specifically are you looking for here
yeah we're offering you something akin
to godhood akin to isn't God I mean I
think you'll like it again this is very
cryptic it involves sex I don't like
that does that help
yeah no toys all the bushes with so
here's a question would dinar how like
have any demands that he would want to
make in order to like make the deal
sweeter for himself yeah has he you go
yeah yeah yeah I got a lady isn't that
the scenario the scenario we're offering
it's very straightforward you will dine
on the finest foods
while being worshipped by hundreds of
women oh yeah are you sure I sense yeah
it could be rough Rosie's now like just
messing with you yeah like you don't
have to do it if you don't want to and
well I don't know maybe if it helps the
team in this for the team I don't want
to put you in a situation if we've got
to get let's forget it guys have your
heart set on this gym right yeah I mean
it's it's you know you're not here so I
guess yeah keep looking at mine yeah I'm
still here still living it's not
important you know what let's forget the
whole thing
all right okay all right you're right my
mother's like no you're right yeah no
just kidding you should you should
totally go that sounds awesome
yeah as you as you oh my god okay as you
get on the palanquin and I raised up you
can hear like clicks of approval from
your from the Lizard Men carrying you
through there is an exit there is an
exit on the air side just very similar
to the one that you came through here
I forgot I found them gross yeah and
then basically it's like you see that
you see it's like walk through and then
you see it come immediately back out how
does he look
yeah hey how are you harrowed yeah just
just a beard yeah
got a Dragonborn beard just like
wild-eyed yeah how long were you gone
why I don't know I did DM hasn't told me
Long John
longer than you think ya see some water
sobbing yeah this is real dreamed about
this for so long it's real are you real
set him down front
except they say set him down in front of
you in front of the table and then a
handsome lizard man with all those like
golden cast helps you off and he says
are you all right grandfather name name
damn it is clutch ceremony at his club
ceremony what is his name Walter tell
Bobby it's fine you don't know how many
days in it be ' he says will you
remember your Walter in the New World
I am pray to God I don't and so so the
bones continue that are wrapped around
this Jim flop themselves back over and
reassemble themselves around this gym
and he says and he says kid no I think
what's tell me my thing what's my what's
wrong what's my problem
oh yeah and then the shadow king says
that there is a force that has been
unleashed on your world and as its
source is far away from where you are
physically but its power remains and it
knows when a person has a piece of the
grave in them and it makes that piece of
the grave grow until they're consumed
the old rituals will no longer serve you
Mike
I'm sorry sorry are you back in the room
no well of course you're waiting outside
patiently and the that bony serpent it's
just sort of like looking up from the
water it's like did the king mention me
at all I wasn't there long enough to
find out he probably did I hope so
if that's what you want did he did he
mention hussar no I can be a service to
him in life and intent and name didn't
come up but I wasn't in there for long I
it almost certainly did come up I could
I could ask when my friends return yes
yes please do huzzah thank you fitting a
deck years friend at ease you look like
a tentacle of bonito yeah I'm not
threatening like this this is fine yeah
right so this so it's a Walther with
obviously with your message for Bobby
mmm still fresh on his mind they
retrieve the letter and go back into
their realm not even a goodbye no I want
nothing erase this from everyone else is
the ritual having been concluded
Tom's in the Shadow Realm yeah the
shadow you weren't there
all right I know I start freaking out
I'm like I spent how long to hear that
that was wall that's what we needed to
hear this guy's screw at the end if he
had been there he could have actually
yes up together yeah that's excellent
well really I know that so I was like if
you were there and really oh yeah I knew
that I'd have been like
the his entourage the shadow Kings
entourage
sort of provides similar to splooge oz
provides a tactical cover for escape and
you can you can you can tell that for
the Shadow King is it's not it isn't a
small thing there's some reflection of
him in this decrepit mummified creature
you know and the culture that he had
that culture that served him for seven
hundred years that has that has now come
to something of an end so as I've said
they are pulling themselves back and the
the halfling woman just watches you for
a while she's the last to leave and you
can tell you can tell as she turns
toward you you can feel the staff of the
master almost like pushing against your
back hmm
like it is it has some kind of impetus
okay it's nothing it's nothing you can't
handle
sure but it it is responding to
something okay I take it off of my back
but I hold it not in not another attack
spinning that pathway yeah and I I just
make eye contact or what I think is eye
contact with your shadowy face and I
don't say anything but I hold the staff
out yeah she says it's not time I have
no quarrel with you in time we could
even become friends but this sword and
that staff hate each other mmm I see all
right I put it away yeah I put it back I
have a lot of respect for that sword who
are you
not clear you'll have to forgive me this
is my first time encountering the shadow
selves but she pulls the cloak back and
to anyone else's perspective it looks
like rosy be stinger different scars a
different life lived but to you it is
just a mass of warping shifting shapes
there's something of there's something
it isn't like a mirror there is
something opaque about her like this is
a part of you that you don't know and it
is it is not pleasant
yikes okay how can I contact you again
after this like how can I get to know
who you are and where our relationship
is just you then you follow the path of
the shadow or what they call the path
like the shadow correct where you're
from
yes it's path leads here I look forward
to finding you again that's not you is
it why trans ghost of a portal who does
not have the experience he had behind
the port totally different situation
is it different Rosie yeah yeah
you are your you're watching walnut
you're watching the rest of this
adventure this this sonic adventure I
mean you're going to places too you're
going to mysterious realms with the
assistance of this virtuoso what pay me
a picture yeah I mean as as the as the
music is is clearly reaching its
crescendo as we're moving into the end
of the performance people have stopped
doing what they're doing it is it has
ceased to be a casino and is now almost
entirely devoted to a kind of worship a
worship that you understand quite well
um halfway through
just this this blooming crescendo at the
end she pulls her hand off of the
strings and like it starts to shake her
hand okay that but that's yeah yeah yeah
like like and you can see that her face
is pained with it hmm you can't get a
perception yeah sure whoo I see a lot I
see a lot from my girls yeah oh the
stone keep a stone in the ring mmm you
can remember this this this hand was
very near mm-hmm
it has changed from a green stone like
from an emerald to a ruby stone mm-hmm
and so she is she is like shaking her
hand in this bridge so at this point the
song has completely stopped okay um
she is she is reaching over trying to
get the ring yeah but every time she
touches it so at this point I will um I
see that she's in pain and I see the
crowd is still in the moment where
they're like oh this is like part of it
there's a moment yeah okay
bless you shadow council okay I used
forest friend the use of juice um yes I
use for his friends and I as many white
doves as possible as many doses you can
get as many times as possible and I want
to use that as cover to pull a
switcheroo with her and get her offstage
because face like yes like visibly this
was the end of her performance and I
want to hear so you pull you pull
switcheroo you like you just open up
your cloak and yeah just like they're
everywhere know exactly like basically
you you are looking up and then you
summon from that wild part of yourself
and then immediately out of every
documents or bag it's just like 20 doves
come from there yes side satchels two or
three doves in the coin purse
little doves poking out its out of doves
it's just those four days yes and as the
doves fly up you can see that she
finally is able to get her hands on the
ring and she just power us through it
pulls off the ring and throws it on the
ground and then looks over at you for a
second and then steps back through the
teleportation circle so when the doves
are gone
she has gone off haha well I'm the place
the place erupts into applause okay
great um whatever doesn't care about
anything else that's happening out well
runs and like unceremoniously jumps on
the teleportation circle hmm she does
again she's making that sound and then
at this point she realizes what's
happening and she's like in a panic and
she's just slamming her foot over and
over and over but no one's mellow mellow
for rushes the stage
um do I see the ring yeah uh it's just
it's situated situated just right there
on the right there in the circle um I
snatch it up and crank away it's how
hard as hell it is come it is burning
hot I need the Khan check yeah oh she
has left I mean it's this 15 yeah yeah
you can get you you pick it up fast
enough and then we're able to get into
it as a pouch great and then I um
do that thing where you will see if I
get this fart but you ever do that thing
where you don't know where you're going
you just need to go and while it just
continued a promotion yeah like I need
to get away from this situation and if I
stop moving for even a second I will die
but if it contained yeah or any have to
contain this
so she'll leave the stage and then look
like she's gonna patrol whatever but
yeah it's just complete ignoring vision
and heading up the the stairs at like
back to where they like where the the
high-roller Suites had been yes
the golden doors yeah absolutely so you
you you were able to put all this that
you're trying to put this situation
behind you you have it completely under
control
you have you have erected a version of
yourself that can manage this situation
obviously not disappointed now you know
what I mean these things happen
so as you the the sort of skeletal
serpent just has a lot of questions as
soon as your splishing your way back out
we're holding this gem that we won
you cannot get the gym why not I don't
know why he was in it you ever thought
withdraw the gem from him what is that
is that what's happening if you want to
try to get it what I think we held up
our end of the deal I just assume we got
the gym out of that I think it was a
theft it was supposed to perform not a
reaction of it this wasn't hashed out
before I got here you're casting your
mind back like you don't know how many
children are slowly fading and it's like
you see there's like a tree that's
brought in front of you and it's just
like slices of papaya and mango dried
meats and it's just like you just the
urge to vomit just rises up in your
throat yeah what we do I I get on the
call to add whoever's there that I know
to just ask how's it going and and I get
some of your something from you yeah
like some some thoughts which I'm like
chase memory right yeah I'm like an old
man what get who's on this call at the
same Rosie what's going on there there's
a lot Hey
yeah we got it
can you come back in here actually the
sword is gone if I'm not destroyed yeah
come back come on and come on back in I
see your drawing Union or your new uh
bone worm friends I am that's real cute
well I was just tracing this in the dust
near the UH you know where okay through
that yeah as far as you pull back as you
as as you're pulling away the head pokes
around the edge and says asked about me
[Music]
good for you uh sorry
well yeah I kinda I need your I need
your advice about this Jam does not look
like we're gonna extract it in any
conventional way you never do like an
hour can I check on this head I'm just
gonna do that first we stood on this
scam okay so I want to come back I can i
is that something I can do who's left
what remains it's just this it's just
this mesh defecated so no bone so the
shadow beings
oh yes and then you're just duplicate
yes they're clones my past with yan yeah
and then they're the rim of guards or
whatever that was in that case guards
whose guards are gone like the shadow
part of this the shadow part of this
Conclave is gone and you can see the
material world sort of encroaching paths
oh okay so this shadow version is sort
of fading back okay and I and tonari
yours
well chairs why he's greasy Hagrid he
feels greasy yep and cold did they get
like a crown or anything is yeah cold
wherever he's not too hot yeah what did
I come out wearing the same clothes it's
aged now they have a nice patina hey I
was gonna say a little bit lonely he's a
grayscale every once in a while yeah I
want to take advantage on an hour can I
check on the
gem and it's carrying case if I can yeah
alright let's hope for some advantage
that's that's garbage
caught horse garbage so what but your
arcane of us is pretty good yeah yes
yeah so the best of those is eleven it's
purple yeah that's what I thought and
shiny I'm too distracted by dinars
heaving like just over there um what can
I try I can add command show my friends
we were the one who was way into it by
the end all right is our friend as I'm
dead I take it so I can't see pretty
undead command will not work if we just
talk damn near damn nice yeah a
straight-up intimidation well sure why
did you what's the principle of the
thing
written there so yeah not really a deal
yeah no there's no I didn't go through
all that not to get this Jamo or it'll
attack this a night and you're angry on
our bad young girl obviously but yeah
yeah I listen I'm the only thing holding
this guy back he's gonna go [ __ ]
dragon [ __ ]
ape on you and it's it's a thing and if
you I mean he's I've got him on the
leash right now dinar we look scary or
something like but we made we conducted
a transaction to help you in order to
get that gem you didn't get the answer
that you liked but that's not my problem
my problem is that gem and you're gonna
hold up your end of the bargain or this
guy is gonna make you into dusty
sandwiches and then we're gonna eat them
so what do you think about that what
bargain around a little bit the whole
thing your transaction your highness
I meant listen I'm gonna play Good Thief
bad thief here we we were sent to steal
this gem that you have apparently
there's some miscommunication
and they believe that it belongs to them
my question to you is is this an
existence you desire what this this this
resurrection end and oblivion does it
please you I I'm in that genuine even if
I wanted it to
it's so nice to talk to someone calm for
a change even if I wanted to I couldn't
maintain it there's some force that is
keeping the resurrection from occurring
but I long now but I long for now is to
rescind the crown and see new places hmm
does it have my own adventures sweet
what if we took you with us on our
adventures he loved the chattering
school yeah we have we have some friends
some compatriots that you might get
along with very well we go on all kinds
of into the worlds that we've seen
there's so many desert folk on this boat
how would you get me off how would you
get me past a metaphor uh we have our
ways why don't you leave that to me if
you're amenable I will take care of the
rest
all right you hear from outside you hear
the loudspeaker voice calling for share
bee stinger okay um I guess yeah you're
up she show must go on
guess so I mean I don't want them down
here looking for us
and you're probably safer up there
anyway get up there and play your songs
fine
yeah you see you see Cher look back look
around the room walk over see hasar
reaches up
and she's like it's just gonna be a
thing and he's like no no no it's fine
it seems like you're friends so she she
peels her way out goes back through the
vault okay he says let's try let's do it
in order to do that we'll have to get
past oh sorry
he says he's in your service he's the
boss I he was asking if you know he's a
particle about I thought that when
hussar died that would be the end of it
I was wrong
see is he being held back from that in
the same way that you are I don't know
what his problem is there's no way to
like him enough there's no way to like
him as much as he needs me to like him
oh poor guy I'd say that's a shame but I
feel a little closer kinship right so he
he he sort of dismantled himself falls
down off of the chair not crawls over
and then rolls up for easy storage yeah
perfect easy yeah he crawls up
underneath your cloak and sort of wraps
himself around you underneath somewhere
over there stars okay yeah yeah he has a
gym but somebody's gonna need to carry
this gym okay it's about the size of a
basketball okay all right
you look carrying basketball size stuff
I can carry it
yeah can't hide it garyun your urethra
not again all right do we see anything
we could like wrap the gem in oh you
could wrap it in the velvet I carry it's
no problem
yeah you got MELAS you could have velvet
conduct it for us if we want hide it
under there sure uh yeah let's do that
what wait a minute yeah Kelvin hold
something like that
yeah where's a way
we could that could velvet hold the gem
under his little velvety cloak one of
you would probably have to hold it all
right okay yeah you velvet though so we
sure right let's wrap it in the velvet
okay and then you carry it and it's your
new eggy so tired yeah how many children
drive to lose I used to I used to
destroy memories on a regular basis
let's see if we can talk yeah we'll see
if we can fix that yeah about in rapid
succession about 300 distinct clutch
ceremonies selves over in your mind just
keep and there's like every now and then
you get to double that's nice that
that's a new sensation for me like that
don't go there you're wading through the
brackish water in the vault house are
you can tell that house are sort of
thinks he's coming with oh I see
Oh friend Oh friend SAR what what are
you doing
beside I serve the king and death and in
life oh well that's good that's why you
would need to remain here but the king
is no longer here what do you mean I'm
pretty sure he's still Brady is are you
what a moment
clatters out yeah it goes around we
gotta go let's run okay wait hold on a
second no oh my god so we do run out but
you all have gone in front of me I've
used do I have it I do I've used
prestidigitation to leave a note for him
let's say my brief friend
wait it's from Karissa it's not like
from the king no it's from
exactly so so this is my onyx chicken
let me get my bone snake yeah it's it is
a the next two days
wait okay oh no you're you're just we're
playing this together well it's gonna
say um when when do when do I see them
next so so after they have emerged from
this secret place that you've only heard
about but not seen mmm there is a number
of different scenarios in which they
could do that how do you guys want to
deposit your every now and then
especially when you pass a lizard
lizard' folk guard there's a little
giggle like a little pig giggling so
much fun inside his first day out um you
should get the [ __ ] off this boat we
should get off the boat I just want to
say like I wanted it like it and alive I
think it's such an open net but after
they come back and they have whatever I
see them I see Rosie and I want to walk
up to her and her face is like clearly
like she looks like she's a mess like
sand and it looks like she's been in a
fight like like she's been punching
something like her knuckles are all
bloody and she just comes up to you and
she goes like where were you we were
supposed to be doing a job I'm supposed
to be able to count on you we're
supposed to be part of a team we're a
team we're gonna stick together and it's
just puffs off and then I would assume
does not see much of them for the next
two days we just couldn't take Mountain
- exactly so share is filling in
masterfully nice um each each show that
goes up is better than the last
she's definitely she's definitely
building a following it's like you know
her MySpace has got some juice yeah yeah
yeah and there's definitely some heat
and there's well there will yield and
visuals here on this vessel like this is
you know especially you know it's about
patronage at the end of the day exactly
very very good venue for sure that's
awesome
absolutely good the book is steady good
yeah absolutely so so yeah the next two
days pass in the most unrelenting
boredom no one will even give you the
they won't even do the courtesy of
fighting everyone isn't completely
everyone is completely jacked on Giants
and halflings there's good times blue
goth isn't seen from again during this
part of the leg okay
[Music]
basically the the dragon's hoard pulls
into the next pulls into the next dock
that they've established and there is a
car here that can take you back up so
clear the barge right doc okay um is
that work no of course not on the boat
dad mellow forest is doing is he's he's
holding it down okay um so I want to say
in the most like just scrunch all the
way we'll nut has her hand on the wizard
Kurt Cup that they got the giant one
it was just dragging it behind her just
like stomps up two stomps up to him um
the the farm elf or right um and just
like shoves a document in his face it's
like we did our jobs sign it who
protected your boat sign off on it he
just he's just he's just letting it
pause he's he wants to know what the
next thing you'll say will be she's just
excited she's just like sign the paper
sign the paper is that one of her new
quills doesn't even time to talk about
how great it is
hands at to mom's it's like here he's
out of line he's like what I need
something to write on I don't know she
smacks it
plate because it's where is this the guy
whose butt I dislocated yeah I'm gonna
shift menacingly at him he's just
laughing oh I got it
he signs it right on dinars breastplate
all right everything's in order
I'll get your I'll give you anything all
of you
I'll get your I'll get your payment sent
to the head office fantastic pleasure
doing business with you and then I'm
gonna sue me it's share here to see
Rosie off yeah baby I shared the shares
you need to write back yeah yeah who are
you right so he's up in the driver's
seat with me I want to say buy this
Luke's blue gospel is he selling a book
what I guess he hasn't been seen from
since you know you can ask Miller for it
yeah well I know roughly where his room
is right
yeah yeah yeah before you before you
disembark you want to go yeah absolutely
so you see you just keep knocking on
each door one will ask nah I pass
realize which rooms blue God's he's a
VIP yeah yeah customer yeah yeah he said
he says well what do you what do you
want to ask him about coming sure he's
all right I was watching him the other
night
okay things got rough he did have
protected him and your boat it wasn't
seen much well after that night yes
which is why I want to check in on him
before I leave okay he gives he gives
you the room number okay it's down off
to the right side premium cabins of
course in the weird spars that come up
off the tail yeah
would you knock on the door there is no
answer hmm just like I'll knock again
louder it's not more aggressively yeah
try again everything all right
is this part of your door thing like is
it kind of worked in yes nice I'm afraid
of doors you did this to me
Brian's talking yeah that's all right
you did this to me
alright I'll try it yeah peek in you
can't do these all these doors are I've
whisper locks on them alright a whisper
open open up door no no it has to be
there
stick you like a section where you go
down you're like AI socks yeah yes so
there's some other there is some other
way off this boat yeah you didn't
teleport out and just maybe probably not
miserably okay so you can be right under
my clothes for all I know
yeah yeah yeah thank you part that
Cartwright is the Cartwright is
inclusive it's not it's a part of the
thing if you come down as part of the
crew yeah so you say you're hit so tell
me tell me what it looks like when
walnut done grass is having to ride back
in a cart for about a day and a half she
is on the top they let you do that oh no
they're gonna do whatever she wants um
it's not really designed for it oh no no
this isn't gonna keep you from doing it
it's gonna make her do it even more I'm
sure go ahead it has it has sort of a
more of a convex sort of surface that
water can roll along okay but this is
this is where she does her thing
yes she's like on it and it's like
arching her back it's always the wrong
it's always the wrong shape a little too
much and she's just like completely
sitting there and to the untrained eye
it looks as though she has not moved
I can I I'm gonna give the I don't know
who's driving give it up it's just
functionaries of the organisation okay
I'm gonna flip up there after about half
a day because we haven't talked in a
little while I know you're angry with me
but I pop a Crouch next to you and your
weird splayed out pose and I'm not gonna
say anything I don't say anything for a
while we kind of just ride along and I
know you know I'm there
but eventually I ask you did she hurt
you
well that is just looking up at the sky
she like refuses to make eye contact
it's like she's not even acknowledging
that you're there and I'm like I'm
starting to stop a couple times and then
you can see she's like really fighting
it it's like just like her eyes are
getting glassy and she rolls over and
just buries her head in your knee and
just lets out what sounds like the
weight of just like a thousand sighs
mm-hmm just pay a high psi yeah just yep
I guess sign and I got we got I got my
little halfling arms and cut your hair
and I don't I don't ask any more
questions
we ride like that together yeah when you
get back to when you get back up to the
barge right docks
just a little bit east of the barge
right in as you might recall right from
from the previous part of the trip you
can see that coriander has almost
collapsed in size Oh huh
so when so for whatever distance you
whatever amount of time you've been away
this is as long as you've been away from
coriander since the conversion but
typically you can sort of see the vine
and bark sinews between the plates and
then when you come back to the place you
can see that the sinews are not visible
at all it's almost like compacted so
there's no pengie yes yeah exactly so
there's no there's no access to the
interior parts I think we should know
what are you and you can tell you can
tell that someone has tried to has tried
to do something to coriander like either
steal the cards or to steal this
creature I thought and your suspicion is
that they were not successful yeah at
your approach you can see you can see
coriander sort of expand and you can
hear the vines internal to her structure
stretch haha and she whinnies and sniffs
at your creepers
I I don't think I have much yeah we got
the wizard Kurt with aliens we got the
gimmies oh yeah oh they oh yeah yeah I
don't care about this medallion I'm just
gonna give that whole thing yeah I feed
my whole medallion was like this was
done you're just like an apple like
multiple bites like yeah yeah and then
just eaten it serve like and eventually
that you know just start have fun with
it yeah just the nibbles all around the
edge and then just BAM right through it
right through the clasp that holds it
onto the ribbon yeah
just a few more thoughtful choose shakes
it out and she's ready for the trip home
I got all that money from when I got
that house money right I got the cheap
all in and I convinced them to give me
house money to hang around let's go guys
oh you know so wow you got chips or
actual gold yeah if they were chips I'm
cashed it in with him you know I know
exactly how he would do it I've been
with him so you're a become one yeah
you're you're rolling you're rolling
past north up the long road you can see
you know after a ways after a day or so
you can see the doone-gate in - you're
right there's a sinus is closed and then
below that it says spider problems well
been there yeah spiked rubs its diseases
yeah see so you're you're you're slowing
up yeah well it seems it they're they're
good so he's okay I have a feeling in it
yeah exactly exactly this so um but
share is up on the seat with you usually
there's usually walnut is up on her
perch sure boys you know to the on the
side equivalent yeah boys on the sides
with in the inside and so you guys so
unlike most of these trips you actually
have a good company on top and so
there's you can tell your stories to
coriander and share yes finally there's
hurt them yeah like serious listen fairy
baby let's be honest about this but as I
say most of your adventures have taking
you north out of red larch and then as
you as you roll in the south obviously
off to the left and see well-versed
wagons hmm don't see well ver but you
know he's there somewhere underneath
something doing something unsafe
anything where you shouldn't sleep you
take that first right and that brings
you right into the front of the drawn
and xl has that has she ever been here
before
no okay I explained the whole oh she's
heard of odd record here okay oh yeah so
this is the her her place her in I guess
she and her wife friend this buddy did
she ever play here yeah um we saw her
once or twice I mean it's pretty it's at
odd intervals but sometimes yeah she'll
show up I would kill to see you play not
really I want to do here is do not kill
I want I understand you don't hear any
music and you hear you hear like a
scraping sound of a werewolf it's not
you know it's not useful phrasing no
numinous proof is farther back in the
throat Wow sorry come on
anyway so you hear the scraping sound of
a wizard
yeah that's not true what's got three
echelons use a limit clause yeah you
hear it you do you're a scraping sound
um that's true that's great yeah let's
get in there it's where I've been in
it's nice anyone we know I've been in
the I've been in the ride with you yeah
and I may have a heart-to-heart you
stretching out no I think you're
surrounded by
literally inside and out I'm laying on
my back
holding the gym up like we're supposed
to treat this in I supposed to do
something with this yeah the noble nice
purple reminder that life can I believe
I would like I've spent the time with
you like you haven't said much I'm
assuming you don't to relive it
even if spoken I'm trying to catch you
up on what's happened since you left but
it was only like a fraction of a second
so I'm like wow I was out in the room it
was a snake bone snake it's like nothing
then you came back so you've been you're
caught up that's pretty much it every
every facet of this purple gem you can
as though it like an animated series of
some tawdry festival you were forced to
take part in yeah help them yes
shift but you keep thinking that if you
look at another part of the gym you
won't see them anymore
now I've had I've read of ways to
eliminate memory I used it on this
scrying slate which I used now I'm
assuming catharsis where if such things
like you're missing your memory right
how do I get some of that yeah brain
damage Roman long enough apparently
there's a look forward to no but I say
do you want to make it an effort though
to make use of some of this my book of
secrets and and and locate that had
procure that spell to use as a ritual
that's not a thing I'm gonna be able to
do anytime soon you mean you mean like
to wipe memories yes yeah
cuz that yeah I read yeah when I didn't
mind my current level it would be much
good but one up
I could I could clear yeah yeah I say
that's nice I just say I just need to
lose my troubles for a while
summon glow man have him dance for me
have him dance away my show with an
ashen face yes like as one who's been
there
I conjure the glow man who feebly dance
yes yes yes that's what I needed a
little twirl my troubles fear users can
leaks out to observe this the folly two
or three teeth yeah hit the wooden floor
yeah this place celery man and then like
for the next for the next you know 20
hours these teeth just just vibrate
around on the floor as he roll into town
it definitely seems like if the energy
is good but red larch is a good is a
good place it has good people in it
you've had positive experiences here but
it definitely seems like it definitely
the energy of the town there's a lot of
bustle okay well we were at now that
we're caught up on yeah so now your ears
are scraping mm-hmm werewolf okay yeah
but is you gonna come out - I'm gonna
get out cuz I'm I'm tired of being in
this cart and I know there's a lot of
feelings in the air I'm avoiding like
intruding on what's on what's your
situation is yeah yeah yeah I'm gonna
someone's a ice scraping their car yeah
exactly you're standing to it but yeah I
want to come out it's coming from the
inside yeah yeah alright
it's came from inside the end right um I
throw up in the north there's there's a
couple guests they occasionally you can
see what occasionally tries to go over
and get proffers attention thinks better
of it sits back down you know looks deep
into the glass tries to find some secret
liquor oh boy
um she has pushed several tables
together in the middle of the drownin
quarter and the armor that she is
typically wearing is out in all of its
pieces and you can see that she is
scraping dirt where it is collected you
know off of the Greaves she is she is
polishing yeah the middle of the place
is not looking great
she is polishing all of this armor
mm-hmm okay you can see shares share is
like she's never been here before and
she doesn't know what her relationship
to this sort of thing is supposed to be
mm-hmm and now there might also be a
crazy woman yeah so she you know in a in
an effort to help it goes over and sits
on the stool that is on the small stage
by the stove and starts to play quietly
and then in an engaging way she's
feeling this situation out Thank You her
yeah yeah yeah she gives you quick nod
I'm also gonna start picking up empty
mugs and refilling them while you guys
go mmm no emotional labor left rags the
cup which had potion and it splashed
yeah yeah so it's just spell II and
she's just dragging it up the stairs oh
um but the thing is is that it never
runs out
no no so it's like it's coming down the
stairs exactly just coming up because
it's changing yeah every few seconds
it's back to you to see work involved is
some slump and then it's just like and
then ultimately you know the stairs are
sort of greased by the potions that
provides a great benefit yeah so inside
get up put it in the
you might hear like the sound of like a
muffled person like dropping a brick or
like maybe punching a wall and then back
downstairs and then just stairs that I'm
assuming there's not a fire on the
fireplace fireplace leg and she's
holding the stuff like like she should
be filling out paperwork yeah nothing's
happened oh it's just like a sheep the
Sheep is out yes and it's ready to go I
go yeah I'm go over to prophet and I say
I could help out or do you prefer to do
it by hand you're going to help out oh
you've been staying here rent-free for
weeks that is true yeah so you are going
to help out and then she'll she lifts up
the play you've never seen this like she
lifts up that she lifts up the pauldron
just start buying it on the edge like
you don't think it could be cleaned
anymore like you think that it is all
exactly right yeah you're not sure how
you could help her clean clean armor by
triangle II I guess she says laughs you
she's your hand oh okay yeah no oh very
sorry
I like I have to remember not to scrape
too deeply like on the floor yeah she
says I have chores
I have jobs for all of you I am going to
water deep to see audre play and I need
your assurances that the drawn and
courtier isn't going to completely
collapse for the three days I'm gone
have fun oh you never know have every
assurance that we will okay so did you
just yeah yeah so show it so she she
stands up and like in the middle
of the drawing courtier begins to put on
her on her armor okay
she's like the carriage is gonna be here
it's gonna be here any time can I um
I'll help
lace her up however I can it's like
tighten things strap her in yeah at
first at first she is not she does not
welcome this type of interaction she she
feels like she knows how to do it sir
but about halfway through she'll let you
get some of the lower I can read yeah
exactly
yeah but but the mental image wrote the
mental image of Rosie up on a chair like
coming up that is actually pretty sweet
all right we got it we have to make it
happen right yeah she says so she starts
going over like a mental checklist in
her mind she says I need what is it
I need the carriage house has been a
mess since the kids left
I need that cleaned out I know I give
you this motion start taking notes yeah
she actually puts pen to paper and it's
like the it looks like like stenographer
like like what is it called trans short
yeah yeah I was gonna say quick and
weird but yeah okay charge house cleaned
out it's just deep god damnit I it's
last stones day this week I need you to
prepare everything that's required all
the traditional last stones day do you
know about that of course not a problem
no I need you to prepare all the
traditional last stones day meals no
worries
and I need you to wait a second and then
she she is like but she still needs her
right arm put together she goes over to
the she goes over to like behind the bar
and reaches out and gets a little a
little pouch like a leather sack and
then on the sack
it says grandmother night and she says a
halfling brought this for you
mm-hmm while you were gone I don't know
what it's about you like to figure that
out too
I need you to promise me again promise
that when I come back here there will
still be a drawn in courtier promise
yeah it's our bane to God yeah yeah all
our stuffs here so just wait and then
she looks over at Cher and she says
where did you learn that
and Cher says I don't know everybody
sings this this is the song you have to
know and she says can I borrow your
daughter you're gonna return don't don't
burn her down either I won't burn down
the sin we'll make a deal all right
yeah little for me a little for you
sounds great okay just of renting people
out of yeah I I kind of stepped toward
you like so that we're both looking at
you like I know I know consult with
sherek she's gonna go see Audra I know
you're excited about that so you get
like a free trip to go see aunt
recording that sounds pretty cool right
yeah there's there's a skip in the strum
yeah is that cool with you you want to
tag along she is she's a badass nothing
Bad's gonna happen to you plus you can
handle yours I'll live through it
somehow all right so now as you're
having this conversation with her now
profit has proceeded to sort of pacing
in front of the drawing career mm-hmm
just pacing back and forth you can sort
of see the edge
the cart just outside the window you can
see coriander there shaking her brass
mane and then you can see another cart
pull up that has a few other people
already in it and then prava says child
to share and cheers just like yes I give
before share leaves I give her a basket
of baked goods that I just grabbed out
of this wrapped this how and also the
right gauntlet that profits like in the
basket it's like the little flow flow
yeah it's like a baguette yeah she she
hands that over and then shares like she
likes loose she looks back at you
through the window you can see you can
see she's just she's right by I situated
right by the drawing courier sign uh-huh
with the little acquisitions
incorporated logo just below she the
coachman jumps down helps the two of
them into the cart and they roll out you
have but this pouch that's in your hands
is right yeah I don't let anyone see it
is heavy okay it says grandmother night
on the front and on the other side it
says Marvin ironbark oh oh alright
I so we got the other two taken care
about I think it's a Sam I think it's a
package from a friend of mine anyway I'm
gonna go look at this in my room goodbye
yeah it jingles metallically don't worry
about mm-hmm money it's you know what it
is none of your business is that like
the flame might slam the door
oh well and I open I'm I'm I'm rattled
by this but I open though
so you'd you open it up there are the
two small emeralds that identify this as
a protection payment oh and this is this
is even this is worse so two emeralds
identify it what type of payment it is
so when this would have come in he would
have assessed this right away but this
is the worst part
it's light that's our game for today
thank you so much hey sorry we got a
late start sometimes computers are
[ __ ] hey we're gonna take a quick
break we're gonna take advantage of the
facilities and then we'll come back and
get some table talk don't go too
you