time is the enemy the pastor threatens
the fastest weapon you wouldn't make it
past a second and last the question play
a flash and records to choose a car
solution you saw it was prudent in an
sepulchre polka tune will become a
putrid it's that well said I pursue in
no mountain too steep but dungeon too
deep to send expendable marks up to the
top of the peak of beneath this we
become a shark to it while I swim in
that money there like Carl Barks ruin
essential national parks through it I'll
send them home in a natural box the
closed top of most of the parks included
save your breath for a cleric confessor
death is a lesson and life isn't any
professor but if you speak in my
official advice sign on the dotted line
and list of the twice well I am Tycho
Brahe haeth Penny Arcade and packs I am
also a mini fest Hereward run CEO of
acquisitions incorporated but today I am
Jerry Holcomb and I'm running a game of
dungeons dragons for my friends
specifically to my right knee best
friend yes premium supreme friends
Dragonborn narcissist dinar Blitzen to
his right repping the natural world
walnuts on grass one of these days I'm a
workout and that's going to be like we
get it in post
yeah any we put this up when I say me of
course we want it if you went downstairs
right before I get your pumpkin workout
oh yeah no I believe it workout I'm
saying just go down just do a few yeah
yeah and just get whatever in five
minute yeah okay everybody hold on we're
going to send our druid downstairs into
our nature to the answer I'm trying to
maintain the metaphor to my left not
your grandma's grandma rosy bee stinger
Oh
because like she Wilkes milk that's not
a real personnel not here who the
is that
sorry I'm on your that no also
Chris Tristram I like that guy wow I'm
gone to I'm in this continuing oh you've
got big
by so inviter is it good I probably
reach in there why do you have beef I
don't know it's fun I don't know
yeah under people everybody here is
stronger than me I don't want to show up
I think it could be like this I think I
need to get to looked at these are not
muscles at all no this is cancer so look
at this upper arm edema Scituate nice
tonight
so lipoma looking good smooth looks good
for now yeah see ya bum ya get your
tumors tight when last we saw our heroes
they had escaped from the haunted house
realm of NEMA's ear and authentically
evil City a corruption of the druidic
ways that walnut dong grass represents
specifically some kind of sorceress
manipulation of their natural power a
siege engine used in times fast called
an EM Azir had been converted to
essentially grow an entire city from a
seed a seed of which walnut on grass has
in her possession now and then once she
plucked this seed the entire city was
torn apart by a defier plant just like
this at its core upon leaving obviously
very action-packed you're welcome to
examine the archive for more info
functionally speaking seeds were planted
to mark the occasion by walnut they were
dryads seeds noted denizens and
protectors of the natural world planted
on the hill that overlooks that town
that was at least one last you saw it
being absolutely aggressively brutally
reclaimed into the bulk of the crypt
garden forest then you then you drove
home oh also you lost your spoiler I
guess that's a spoiler lose having lost
the spoiler aesthetic
spoiler if you haven't seen the last
Everly went off yeah none other read it
none of the other recap was to shout out
to the amazing resurrection of ours oh
yeah don't forget don't forget a moment
a moment for Rosie and her best friend
coriander now but there have been there
have been suggestions as to you know the
coriander nomenclature now met coriander
is one Cory Android is available I mean
all these URLs are out there calendar
nope oh the dollars are like that the
calendar is very good as a pasta person
I really but it's not because it's your
best friend if there's a modification
that's required there I would leave it
but it is it is definitely it is
definitely your friend coriander having
returned a glossy bronze coke over a
living structure of you know muscular
roots and nice yeah hell yeah now an
appetite for yes compensation exactly an
enthusiast perhaps an over-enthusiastic
gold coins yeah as a treat and maybe
even her entire diet so but as I
suggested you had returned to read large
acquisitions incorporated desra and
branch centered in the drama and
courtier operated by prophetess drawn
what time of day is it right now it was
midday when we really left
yeah yeah exactly so you can write up
there you know yeah you have you have
returns we can we can snap right back in
half let us suggest to stitch the two
games together that a cinnamon cake is
now being withdrawn so to speak right
from the oven right and connector
withdrawn withdrawing courtiers I I want
I want to let you guys know that the
cinnamon cake doesn't look like anything
special I think that probably
what you expected to see with something
a little more decorous but the kitchen
in the drona Cordia is not especially
well-appointed for the construction of
pastries so I had to do what I could
with what I had but I think you'll find
that the flavor and texture of this cake
is I don't want to spoil it for you but
I can't believe it's not magic but this
is a we allowed to have it I thought it
was for profit
I think I baked it for profit but I
suspect profit might be willing to share
it's the entire thing but if I would say
so I take a moment is it that was
grandma's fought out like I don't know a
grandma who doesn't just like go in
there and make plucking the gold and
then bring it out it's like you're like
what the grandma is like well there
was stuff I had laying around right
exactly they didn't have the kind of
clarified butter that I choose to use in
The Bachelor sorry this isn't my best
hole it's like pretty out or not gonna
like yeah I'm in the bathroom it's
exiting me and you're all apologize door
listen and even that hilarious
yeah probably cinnamon already fresh
bacon to this is a city magic city
magical you're loving it okay so
prophetess has chosen to sheriff with
the group right they're not your clips
they roll for it okay a little left over
maybe a little better
no no lick the spoon no job
prophetess will join you in the kitchen
great just grab a pile of plates and
then she just you know not sir head over
toward the great room plates you know
silverware lays it down on the table
love it again everything she dragged she
screws squeakily drags a few chairs in
from around okay well this was cooking I
was doing all the paperwork I already
said that
got sent out so night was completely
like covered in ink and very important
that you know when she gets this cake
she does not wash your hands it's just
just go he's not even bothering with the
fork no and also probably didn't wash
ever but definitely not after our last
encounter to us Bloods all until we went
some places recently it maybe yeah
minutes or blah all over you
better day okay fine
Monday's am i right kind of but this is
this is what I'm talking about it's just
like full-on just like but no it's not
it's not even a thing right grabbing
handfuls like eating it like an apple
right yeah all right then
it sounds like it's consistency is that
which would allow for you to pick up and
grab invite but once you get it in your
mouth it dissolves like butter
yeah I guess yeah it just wait another
part where we find our poison this is
like a george RR martin are you talking
about audience member whistles the
chroman have a lamprey pie in the oven
anxious there's a THS i don't i don't
know if it's actually from the book or
if it is just something that I made up
like as an amalgamation of hold the food
stuff do you need you have a mental
image from the first game of thrones
book of beef juice running down a
woman's arm into her dress probably I
don't have a read I hope what I heard I
heard that mmm I hope that I did not
invent that because I usually use that
to make fun of him which is but it
wouldn't but if what's actually happened
is that I made that up then we have to
make fun of you well it's an easier now
yes Owen okay and if he has either died
or refute son let them see it he'll go
but jake has been sliced I've also made
coffee
did you sent Coffey of Coffey in do you
I made you coffee weeks ago so I already
rented coffee I got nice copy of ancient
yeah I'm insured okay because indeed
coffees JD copter and you don't have
coverage
yeah it is like a cup of Dunkin Donuts
coffee our place
branding facing outwards wow that's a
handle jug yeah none of this is real
it's real it's from the cook garden for
us and as well most people are
specialized in brewing it range here
from now on have to have those cool
perspiring on the table yeah one drop
that goes all the way down yeah so
refreshing but good why is your father
here especially I am looking at you are
you still working paperwork right now as
you you eat okay um I'm from everywhere
I'm going machine you're eating very
slowly delicately from a piece and I'm
just kind of watching walnut and you
guys I don't know what you guys are up
to please roleplay this out but I'm
waiting sectors you're stuffing your fat
face okay good I'm not stuffing it I'm
small a like a mouse but I do say the
destruction of an unnatural city and now
Kate could take a picnics great day yeah
leaving shells and homeless Souls
whatever happens I yeah we sure did some
good work did I have yeah good job see I
really feel like we're starting to pull
together
clink Forks and I put my fork out to
clean as a toast so we do have to be
dragged aboard sue has refugees have
they had to come as far as red large I
may be even further the number of people
displaced by the city you've only
recently arrived back in the house truth
you might see you might see things
change here but as you left you saw
people going north
you saw carts you know rolling to a stop
even people coming out of the city
finding passage with the vehicles
because River it sits along the long
road so you think that West bridge would
probably absorb more people closer to
NEMA's ear than red larch probably okay
that Trevor is going to do a business
and then I've been is going to do a
business good for Trevor great I mean I
do a good yes oh yeah yeah oh my god I'm
on idea
yes yeah yeah she doesn't really know me
this is in the case um yeah we sure did
a lot of good work you sure did
you sure did walnut uh yep does anybody
have anything they want me to put in
this mess of the head office because
otherwise I'm just going to button it up
I cut and dry um I think we could
probably stand to include maybe a little
explanation of what the just
happened
well mo looks down looks really serious
has just kind of been preparing for this
moment and she goes well what I can tell
you is this was my intention to share
this but the you know heat of our battle
I guess some things came out my people
work from where that city was they're
gone now and that city had to go so good
job
what where is where did where did they
go good you're just placed but kind of
like I am way if you do you know where
they are are there any left
yeah I'm lost and it's my job to get
vengeance for them which I've done so
years of toiling for that is that an end
and what I do next is well that's my
business right vengeance
yeah they all killed
everyone's no dead I believe so yeah
oh well there there's always more things
to take vengeance for sure um keep busy
that way yeah and I think what I what I
will said because you know doesn't it
doesn't matter but I do believe those
cultists that we have dealing with our
sir
bring a dark deity one that I think has
infected that necklace that you like so
much
yes necklace oh yeah necklace
that's little vessel yeah emergency this
is decoration I meaningless baubles
right so just in case you learn now okay
I have about a few hundred more
questions
but I feel like I covered everything
okay products I want to provide this
just process takes your plate
excuse the chair away but like tries to
scoot away quietly but it's not possible
on this floor it seems to take about a
hundred years for this sound shop she's
going to do anything to it what moves
over to the side takes your plate and
then script it in very fast and you see
you're sort of disappear around the
corner where the stove is in the back
okay was it the city blowing up sing
that what got her you think hmm sure II
never said that just a heavy
conversation yeah that walnut doesn't
seem to want to have how can I be more
in tune to that than you are well I'll
connect what to kick the world well
we're going to work with each other or
not dig into each other's personal
tragedies so that's not in my contract
in the mall monsters pulling out the
contract like she needs to show you guys
like it's actually not it
it's like abstract I mean I'm pretty
familiar with this but let me check it
out and be my legs and the snakes like
proofreading for this is like that in
there ready music wow does um your
little snake your danger noodle have a
name yet no she hasn't asked him what it
is you know okay
okay she will just cap it's happening
alright um I'm the last thing I'll say
is that I do think it's a it's a
a shame that those people were suckered
into living in that horrible city and
yeah well too bad for them well not to
you did you go glasses free so that you
could rock this drama Roman look at this
a motor now cuz I wasn't give that well
because I usually I do is like actually
in the documents at hand but huh but I
think well yeah you are welcome to just
do the adjustment motion with no lessons
that's fine at this table that's all
yeah yes that's real zero yeah yeah okay
I'm perfectly satisfied how about you I
really would like to know more for a
selfish reason if this dark deity that
they serve has infected my precious
arcane focus and it's much better symbol
I would like to figure out how to purge
this one that I don't like and I do make
it in front of you as best that in do
the three dots really please I can't you
bet okay it's this one by you yeah just
helping mmm-hmm sure
um don't do that it's it's bad luck for
my people don't do that ever I will say
you know the coincides with our new
missus that we're doing I'd be happy to
help you
wait really chuckling she's like really
trying to hide the fact that like she
really wants to get to the bottom of
what's going on is trying to play closer
like yeah I wouldn't mind helping you
would be a problem with your necklace
whatever shot getting to shined up yep
we can do that all set on this from the
docket to just get that expunged okay
how you guys are getting really close
okay becoming friends it's very quiet at
the table describe a menorahs on is like
sick me to take is I would like to
another cake
like a carrot cake yes want me to teach
you how to make on yes all right
it sophisticated this is this is the
show that I want to watch this is the
narrow that I want to watch oh my god
you guys are like great red large baking
show go do it it is questioned it's a
great then great that is how I want to
go a great Messer and baking show it was
just like and you can totally see the
two voices okay Ruby fairies and our
Hollywood week was that I don't
understand if they're faking it wiggly
Oh big yes thank you
I'm much better how much a lot of I take
an hour back in back I like okay kid if
you want to learn you follow me I guess
you teach and make the meanest cinnamon
cake you've ever tasted even better than
that last one what you got
alright ain't go work yeah all right we
go in the back I want this competition I
want to I want to give you guys a minute
do this talk about the smallest thing
just in case you're shy about talking
and waiting from us here does have an
elf sing about an hour
yo now the tensions yeah so yeah like I
had now we can have it now we can talk
and maybe it's not so weird and the
Gotti the guy to cons up there's an
extra little piece of cake that I
haven't finished and it just it just
opens the and then just like those like
tiny like pea tendrils it's so fast and
blacks it'll be another punch if I catch
that YouTube video that weird sea worm
yes where the wind goes out anyways just
ran out yeah you don't want to look at
that you don't want you seen it I wish I
made it worse but it's basically it's
like how many
tendrils are so many but I like that
better oh man where's like it comes out
it starts to like fractal out yeah when
is it done I can't do this anymore still
going somewhere how many your coil up
back there you know more tendrils and
tentacle and then I'm like now we can
have a serious talk and just making this
loud like Google but like some weird
crunches drawing and the why is it
always like I know I'm only interested
in big and one thing some answers
okay well sometimes our quick dinner
clothes like okay dry yeah I'd love some
answers as well ugh okay
it seems that your your group must have
had some history with this this opposing
force that they would bring that symbol
which I won't do because I don't have
enough hands sure I guess I guess we got
easy to fight it don't ya sorry we know
we're talking about
but there must have been something
seriously interconnected that would not
only lead them to the site of your
former birthplace but also connected
with the Crypt and connected to the ER
on my focus and the god I one day hope
to surge instead of this the yucky one I
don't like that much I'll talk about I
don't want you to talk about anything
I don't know if I can hear the yucky
ones like the only one the grain yuck
Smith so what are you asking you want to
know all the deep dark secrets in
history of my people yes sure let me
just know what about just some of them
that would assist us top three maybe
there could be yeah start at the start
of like the the lightest secrets it's
like the ones that a lot of people do no
I'm just saying okay and then we could
maybe see a face I'll tell you that if
you tell me what your end goal is would
you big creepy under the ground demon
God because thanks for a second because
there's a lot at risk but in accordance
with money with ketosis ideals and his
bonds he has decided that
this is possibly a worthwhile exchange
of information
oh wow from the kitchen you guys here
Rosie go actually you're really good
this a large clang light and not the
right size not a dragon for kitchen now
this is not an anywhere in kitchen in
every respect when I came to read larch
I had amnesia I had made a pact with
this other god this intercessor this god
of mouths who promised information about
the beige I seek I made a deal with it
and to this point I don't see a reason
not to proceed with it as long as I can
learn that which I seek to learn if
there was another way to get that
information I would abandon this red god
of eating meat and mouths because I
believe that the God I'm seeking is
stronger than it I believe we got I seek
is stronger than all of them and that it
would protect me that it would there
would be safety there okay well you told
me something so I guess it's only fair
that I would tell you something some
thing of of my people don't want it
looks really serious and she goes on one
of our greatest secrets is that if
you're trying to get information out of
someone don't say your thing first growl
[Applause]
error in cute others look at him like
what like she thought they were going to
have like this tete-a-tete Julie and I'm
like did you just watch how that's very
opposite
tear down we had we had a gentlemen's
agreement of sorts I believed great but
husband for sweets you know even yeah
her name is malice of a traitor and she
must be stopped
oh so with the civil use that word Mela
symbol do I know anything about meals
I've heard this name when we were in
when we were in Nemus here yeah that is
hidden ringing this set of druidic
knowledge and druidic pantheon and under
dark warlock there's no overlap there
yeah in terms of that you haven't heard
anything bad nothing specific but that
but that feels true to you knowing from
knowing it as you do that you basically
bear this symbol on your chest
constantly you believe that that is the
name of that symbol you believe it the
same way that you know that there is the
name of the other simple sounds true
sounds right yeah yeah they say the same
thing I think we have the same pain I
don't know why you call her the betrayer
I don't know that I need to know why but
both of us are trying to expunge her you
from a much larger surface area than me
I just want her out of here short but
same goal I'll say this our aim is the
same we do need to dispel her in any
place that we see her but you should
know that milk wasn't always the
betrayer she got that name by doing
something and honestly if you think that
whatever God our deity or higher power
you're following if you think that there
isn't any potential that the same thing
could happen be foolish this is what
they do
there are good and kind ones but they're
never
they're not here for us I agree with you
hundred percent I'm disturbed by the
fact that there are good and kind ones
and that there are evil and cruel ones
to a god that should be nonsense all
those gods are meaningless to me I seek
the one who is so great that he does not
contain any of that none of those
components truly beyond understanding
and not petty like we seem to be where
one can go from favorite to betrayer and
maybe back again but back the other way
that's what I'm that's what I'm seeking
oh love to hear more about your
religious philosophical stuff but I feel
really because I have a well thank you I
mean okay so we're going to come back
out and in our I would like for you to
do with your honor of describing the
cakes that you have created under my
tutelage I I come out with this cake
that is C+ but really perplexed and then
I realize after I've made this like if I
can make this myself now no one will
make it for me anymore Dorian I believe
it yeah that's what the energy throw the
round yeah last like third I was like
wait a minute now I'm self-sufficient no
don't like so I kind of just like think
you think I want to believe me wait like
this balloon deflating you know stand
about it inch yeah I think it's lovely
dear
well I'm stuffing hmm oh you see a
shadow shape sort of move along the
front window you see the door pop open
it's a alabaster Krynn also known as
Aldi
raise the mail around here some mail it
never failed mission director yeah yeah
she she she opens the door just a crack
pokes her head in she said a male oh
yeah one moment please
walnut runs upstairs um and then grabs
each each here like paper just and then
she comes down and she has a the expense
report reporting on the quest progress
reporting on their dealings with elder
Brian and then also the discrepancy
report about their previous day nice see
just I put a piece of my cake in an
envelope and I'm like just think oh like
this I do well just a little really bad
bro you do yeah oh and I also want to
say that there is a there is another
thing in there but I don't want to say
what it is here but I'll tell you what
it is later hmm I want to ship something
back to the head office yes okay too far
have that office great back here secret
okay oh there is also mentioned though
of corianders situation right oh yeah
well that's in the expecting your answer
for it oh yes it's a new circuit I it
yeah all this mail doesn't go to the
head office this is just mail in general
right but you you can send any mail you
want to a with he'll be because I around
stairs when I get a letter I give to to
I just give it to her she's got an
address on it okay what's that should it
go with wall it's a letter I wrote it is
that to the head office no I don't know
none of you read letters to the head
office right my job
oh I get my letters from the head office
great yeah why anything my face so she
is now this is what the third think
there's just additional ways of mail
checking coming in here coming at all I
was a mail to onyx comes out drops a
mouse in the bag
right Dorothy's probably been writing
letters to her family - oh yeah like a
63 yeah it's a personal letter get sold
um they're like they're all basically
the same thing like hi you just checking
in made of cinnamon cake today promise
that we liked it oh you would love about
that kind of yeah exactly harm
letters but you guys get a kick him out
she gets mad from that one grandson all
the time though right that's true that's
here's a palace
I mean sweetheart oh yeah so yeah
that'll load yeah I get like I'll give
her a pile of things exactly so it's
like hazard letters it's exactly so she
really bundled no bet you know what yes
yes kaity Kristen there yeah I was
thinkin and so to get in there and then
she looks to you and her head like
I I go she says she seems relieved she
pops out and just - taps the doorframe a
couple times though as she leaves um I
haven't no none here figure out what up
with that dagger is now a good time yeah
so yeah yeah you're welcome - so the old
business no yes it was I mean but that's
that's true I mean this is this is
literally like a meeting of Jo I'm a
joint of the officers of a corporation
you like do I need to attune with it my
sleep or can I bring it out for you
you're welcome to your well you but so
you bring it out yeah and just set it
right down on that on the table in the
middle of the room is this like dope a
snake exactly exactly
is it like a dagger yeah the kind of
curve comes out at the end okay so the
dagger the dagger itself is almost like
um like a blood channeled sacrificial
thing like a Chris oh yeah is that that
sort of lead leveland yeah that bizarre
sort of serpentine blade and you can see
that that sort of forms the last part of
the tail and then the torso
everything past the blade the hilt
itself is like the torso of a thoroughly
snaky a snake centaur
though yeah sort of thing yoga I wonder
yeah you aunty I think is the new aunty
yeah and as you said it as you set it
down yeah on the table lagari you can
feel the gotti like flex and tighten on
your neck you see it rises up you would
his first head is like this yeah turns
his head like this boy but he's trying
to he is engaged in some kind of pecking
order he's trying to establish a pecking
order with the dagger like a dominant
behavior yeah I know I yeah yeah it
looks like it looks like it's trying to
assert itself rearing up yeah yeah it
disturbs but it's like but it's
tightened up around the neck like it
you're not going to die
but it is he is definitely like trying
to do the gym thing like he's just
trying to like just rippling muscle all
the way out to the end just turning his
head what I think he likes it you check
out and you can check out okay again I
get him off my neck of something I can
putting down next video I'll put him
down next to zero I don't know what I've
got no attachment to the standards he
strikes like a like a lightning bolt
like as soon as he's down on the table
close to it when he can't pretend to
establish any kind of framework for
their interaction it becomes a it
becomes a battle he's playing the baby
so he strikes it and the dagger clatters
off of the table and strikes the stone
and clinks a few times you see onyx rear
up with her back to the wall and you see
EULA Gotti leap off of the table and
then wrapped his tail around the the
Jade portion of the blade
and then just begin to like parade what
like like would the rest of us yadi
uncoiled is just like yeah it's just
kiss now that he has accomplished his
feet now that he's established that he's
better than this
pretty syndicate object okay now he is
it's like it's like a like when a cat
brings you a mouse an animal term so
yeah a fab you can understand it the
same it's like it's like um I got it is
it have you ever had that ever happened
to you what cat brings me dead things
constantly yeah yeah so it is parading
that although it is actually here
[Applause]
another bird it Clem's like I know anima
yes applicati does this but when my cat
brings me a dead baby rabbit like he
does all the time now he sings to me
before he I know he deposits it at my
feet he'll bring it inside - if you look
at ease like that yeah well you know
nice I don't know but it's like just
play me like imagine imagine like like
Sachin waiver when it's that's what I'm
talking about
Jenner ID oh you're going to be like a
cheer but I'm picturing it like the like
the oh yeah yeah yeah exactly but it's
this awful sideways snake mouth this
does it beautifully presented yet is it
presenting it around the N or is it back
to me with no no right it is it's still
performing this thing but it it's always
in sight of you like it's definitely
wants you to know that it's a big boy
hmm
and you can and it can accomplish great
feat someone coming on afar like an
animal fighting ring get out my throne
yeah no but but he has it actually held
as he has he is sneaking around yeah he
has it held high Oh as one like a
scorpions yeah exactly he has it held
high in the back of the tail hey come
here come the other guy what's going on
here what you find
boy come here
okay I don't you do that it's like come
here yeah alright so I draw him to me
yeah and just seems pleased
oh chuffed haha shop just do I
get a real team do I get any idea that
he'll release the dagger that I can try
alright alright I think we're trying to
figure out what it is so let's so if you
need your hand goes to it it stops being
a performance and it's just like
watching your hand
oh but am i able to release it no no no
it's as soon as as soon as you reach for
the dagger
it'll guards it oh how bad do you want
to say it looks like it's yours now is
fine Locati is it mine can you talk like
yak meat I don't know if it has a I
don't think it has a mind I don't think
it has a language yeah yeah we're going
no idea is know when I'm in a beast like
like you could speak to it it is
literally an alien noodle right when I
yeah when I went out of your boy I gotta
voices it's not just you how I in the
same country with you how I use it so
generally you might be added nice for
you I don't I could take it hey you know
what I can't take control of it I can
look through it again but can i order it
yeah it's true oh yeah well let me let
me command it to put the knife down then
am I able to do that come on wait but it
gets a minute I guess it gets agitated
alright aye it does this guarding
behavior and then it relinquishes the
knife but then it's sort of like circles
around it and now that it doesn't have a
grip on it it seems to think it needs to
assert itself okay we're back to one
essentially this could try and get it
again yeah I just didn't trust it oh
alright
are you able to check to your the thing
you need to do with this serve I'm just
trying to figure out like what its whole
deal is but this is fascinating
laughs I think it's I think it's a
snake's weapon I think it's in love with
it you equip it in your snake slot yeah
it's like a phase as once weapon is not
a lot of customizations do you want it
you wanted to spend some time with it
and trying to figure out what it is I
kind of I kind of won I kind of want
Locati to have it if he wants it
okay so wouldn't keep it if I if I have
a sheath can it put it there and know
that it's it's his and not like have an
open blade in my clothes all the time
yeah you may have to come up with
something clever okay a little knot a
little bag holding
oh it's around Agati and then just the
knife in his mouth yes oh you know
Alexei yeah yeah okay I don't know if
that's going to work that well when we I
mean okay I plunged the knife in is it
into its mouth what is it completely
ejected oh my god now I don't want the
voice exact you know what we move past
it now what oh yeah
they still some room Saturday mortal can
you fight big in Nice Ricky yeah okay if
you're all right maybe I'll explore it
later but for now that's okay whatever
the guy wants yeah it's a it's a loose
parenting style yeah we'll see where
this goes yeah what it is until it
becomes a problem there's a problem
Rosie types of their staff she she is an
ascetic and doesn't particularly like
morally good so you can have it no
problem free tiger I feel like I feel
like a wrong has been committed like
I've taken something of yours
that was for my child because he was
being petulant yeah I know I know I
can't teach him a lesson about it can't
hit him a trouble for you - yeah he's
not old enough when we get home oh man
I don't have it not in the middle of
grocery store only you know your trouble
yes yeah I do realize something I wanted
to do and wanting to do for a long time
and I get down on one knee and this is
not my ship I take the ring that I've
been wearing my AC plus one ring that
was given to me or what I was found from
the Goblin David Wright says you should
you should have this you're too
important to this group and also you
have an item that can kill me and there
we go so you should stay alive that's
right because I have my little necklace
that can check you out
I didn't at any particular point so
you're sucking up to me right now in
physics and you guys found him one knee
because because I thought I kicked on my
shoe generally but I forgot I was
wearing it today just you have to get to
the lovers that's right yeah yeah that's
no problem
all right yeah I'm into it I got down on
one knee presenta see what could have
been like that get this elated this ring
is a simple unadorned metal and so Rosie
because Julie accepts it I thought it
had a red that's probably not around
right now I lose it Keisha lets with the
strength yeah everybody yeah in the
garbage oh yeah so and with that my my
AC goes from 15 to 14 okay I got
something yeah and now I no longer have
the same AC as a combatant which I don't
I should never have had that high of an
AC I think if dress might might be in
that soft way continue oh yeah yeah this
is a case do you need a mountain of
pudding on the shape of iron boy
continually trying very hard to not care
about anything but yes make sure you
close out with that theoretically a
little I knew you're the right person to
give that to this
I really sure you up I love the idea
that maybe Victor so just start being
like don't heal me know what just see
what else do you take 15 points of
charisma damage I just gently wear
clothes right it's like a DNR like yeah
don't resurrect me don't worry
yeah resurrect yeah I love it
sorry okay oh yeah any ups do we have
any other room
any other business items anything else
that you want to give me cool
who is your letter to okay who are you
right now you can't possibly have family
yes no that's to my sister oh good there
you know yeah ancestor don't I have
parents and a sister and well I figured
you know if I'm not sure that's enough
exposition to know Rosa sister all right
I'm just a good man are any hack story
grew three times yeah well yeah yeah I
mean you are in the your corporate
headquarters there are empty cake
platters you have access to your jobs if
you're interested in looking over the
text of those yeah more clarity we
should we have a Forks path ahead of us
if I recall correctly more - Pascal Lamy
value so we can um I'd be happy to read
I haven't pretend wall months doing it
yeah exactly in the walnut way no oh no
here's know how to start height you
shouldn't with the thing that you made
for the streams because that's also
attachment you just read it don't do it
no well I hate to use hair documents
this is part of the secret skill yeah
I'm documenting and I want to hear how
you say some of these plain words Oh get
ready
it's all in character so yeah so we're
establishing that we don't want it's
wrong
oh yeah that uh Oh Wally walnuts does
not read and write so well okay Rob the
hoard for 500 goals the noble knife I'm
assuming the people that posted it upon
the lizard folk vessel known as the
hoard is a violet gem of immense size
which our patron would prefer to own
upon acceptance of this task secure
passage and expect contact okay
or more accurately for the Horde
requested also 500 gold posted by the
dragon hordes River going houses chance
okay exclusive River going gambling
parlor demands equally tasteful
protection well alright
tall order arrived us the barge right
doc between the in and WOM furred for
assessment barge right doc between the
inn and Wong furred um further I would
that be between the the in the in okay
I'm going to say proper noun but well
it's like the big guy big guy
okay mmm good did we do we have any
documentation on gettin our to Scala oh
yeah there is there is that third option
these are the two jobs here but the
third the third job is dinar Blitzen is
to report to Scala in one month time one
month one month there's one gold piece
obviously on offer for that exclusive
job yeah but apparently that gold piece
is to be returned to her upon yet
arrival its how ice coriander doesn't
eat it yeah yeah are you eager to go to
Scala not even a little bit so why on
earth would we do that let me I was led
off we tear that one up got taught or a
month off okay works works work we
shouldn't get on a gold piece of yeah
yes the pains not great and you don't
want to go
so why wouldn't do it I have a
proposition let's hear it
what if we did security for the Horde
for whatever time they determined that
we need to do the security and then
after that time is done we rob them well
I was going to ask what are the yeah
what are the victory conditions on both
of these can we do both yeah yeah I
think we should do that thing exactly
hmm I would argue though that by
planning to rob it even if we do
security beforehand we actually are only
robbing it we're not really doing the
security but the security doesn't say
against people stealing this gem I
assumed taken forever
yeah done this no okay yeah permanent
security yes now it's our retainer
situation why does no one touch the
opticals right yeah it could be a thing
where this gem is like passing through
and we have to do security until it
leaves again so we will have to both
secure and steal securely it would be
the ultimate way to case the joint
exactly exactly when does a new Keturah
in town yes well I mean everybody
already joined I was incorporated for
their own reasons and nobody was like
I'm going to really do good for the
world this is the organization for me
right is it not a show exactly the good
guys were they adventuring island of mr.
toys yeah exactly we we should
definitely find it the security and see
if we can find us that violet gem
anything I would I would I agree with
that I would feel better from knew more
about one party or the other just to
just to contextualize it morally well we
can ask we asked my beautiful if she
knows anything about the noble knife oh
sure sure sure yeah she's not in the
open room right now she's in the back
how could she
miss popping in and out back there she's
in gay
some kind of task she because when she
walks back out to the bar who sort of
looks out the window see if anybody's
coming waiting for someone
no maybe I was going to ask her that
yeah yeah wait are you waiting for
someone Audra is supposed to be back
today sometimes there are extensions
she's she's in demand not just by me
well that's like give her a knowing nod
and goes long trishul I'm sure she'll be
back soon
in the meantime no better way to pass
the time than a little light
conversation what do you know about the
noble knife
god I love her hello what doesn't leave
my character I love well daughter you're
really suffering emotionally how about
my thing yes what about that I want to
talk about what about all the innocent
people I want to mind taking care she
says the noble knife the noble knife and
then she goes no well Noble nice swirl
tree brainian involved a fir yeah maple
maple she says that doesn't ring a bell
what's the what's the context um they
want us to procure a gem from some
wizard folk who run a casino
she lassen she says I've been around for
a while and I've heard there's a lot of
organizations that call themselves
things like that and typically the the
truth is a bit of a bit away from it so
the nice part of the mill bizarre yeah
the the horses uh yeah I'm just nice
like she says she says is a little on
the nose what I would say okay well
this is worth it so your Lillian night
edition is why I like acquisitions
incorporated hmm I feel like the Holman
was really onto something with that name
hmm
these names you don't like whoever named
deans did a bad job well we do what it
says in the name that's true do you want
something gotten there are a group of
people who can do it
that's a good name let me ask you this
do you know anything about the Dragon
hordes River going house of chance
usually it's just called the Horde sure
that's that's that's a way the way the
river they travel on isn't far east from
here but it's very hilly it'd be hard to
go straight to it where are you supposed
to meet up uh at the treasure heart
barge right doc between the inn and Guam
fir'd okay so you'll head south on the
long road for a waste sure one rare yeah
once a once it starts to turn to the
east you will pass the barge right in
the very next town is Wong furred just
see the dot between those Oh easy enough
got it
hey you Crawford and look we've been
sure we passed it easily ten minutes yes
and and papa I didn't have my snake for
a while what's that I'm trying to
comfort her I didn't have my snake for a
while either but I was so relieved when
I returned so and then just stood like a
club to the back like ya know but it's
just like I've made you feel better no
but she she is accustomed even under
ordinary circumstances to a dress like
she is getting ready for war so you gave
her pauldron a couple good Pat's
yeah um what was what if she she doesn't
have an answer for this with Audra's
favorite treat should we get something
ready for her arrival
she's got expensive tastes I can work
wonders negative she she says well here
I'll go back and get the recipe and so
she goes and she goes she goes back
brings out a little like a tiny chest
yay big opens it up it's full of Scrolls
these are deeply in floured Scrolls
I feel so comforted like the most
grandma thank you really mean it exactly
have no Tina
exactly no it's just like egg like the
bottom of the recipe is crisp yeah
there's like doilies in there tradition
is that like once it's gone too far and
there's too many ingredients encrusting
it you fry it and you eat it yeah
exactly Turkish coming all out there I
mean aren't ready to go just meat it's
crisp like it's like a seal oh yeah all
those layers of parchment um hey there
is a from she says she says yes there
will be something in here that she likes
but she has reached in and adjusted
things a little bit so that wedding cake
is sort of like at the top but like
there's a little bit of plausible
deniability because she has manipulated
the chance matrix it's just like pilatus
it's like something like one of these
she likes all these I think okay these
are all good ah dressings you can just
you starting to get more and more sort
of sort of flustered like this is a
tough-ass lady but around ah dress she's
not hmm she loses a few points of AC
which let's put it that way let's note
that on the character yeah okay so uh
Rosie notices the wedding cake and
pulled it out and she's like well that's
one of this right that's one of them no
judgment not judging yeah I think you
the rest I don't a lot of people like it
I it's not just Audra like I like it I
like it
it's right it's really good you guys
like wedding cake right good wedding
cakes crust I would eat that it's so
sugary
and it's terrible for you okay mom it is
I do think we got a minute
I think we have everything back in
that kitchen we're over you aren't I
make this for for Audrey's arrival well
you know there's don't you do you have a
I thought you had a job
oh this won't take long and you guys can
get ready without me I mean I guess we
could I guess if we wanted to we could
go to sleep because it's the same day
yeah yeah and then longer yeah why not a
long risk trying to look all the talk of
her talking about heroin was like yeah I
gotta go file some paperwork and she's
going to go to room and look at her
window sill and Mike is like Oh is there
a message from Brahma is there is there
yes and it's just sitting every time you
come back yet and now she's just
rereading the other way do you
heaven want daddy
of course right please visit some summer
I so halfway through making this cake if
I may
yeah fast forward a bit I'd like to have
Rosie just casually casually drop the
question
not the question not the question but is
this for any kind of special occasion
not even making eye contact just just
fussing around mixing bowl checking the
heat well it's a special occasion any
time she's home of course of course
these days it is it's the cake we had on
a special occasion
I see I think this is your wedding cake
yeah yeah I wrote it get going yeah
great well I hope I can do it justice
and there's the exam yeah yeah yeah
and she she says uh
should help you make that cake
has three children hmm I had three
children
Oh menaces auspicious and pretension I
haven't seen pretension in a while she's
a tough girl
almond comes by a little more often than
maybe I completely required auspicious
died when she was a girl I'm sorry to
hear that she was at the wedding she
draped the flowers you have good
memories of her
of course everyone does good I'm glad
how about seems really personal yeah
how'd your daughter do you know
definitely wins your personal stuff over
happy
yeah I mean I table talk for one second
okay definitely tell us that when we
asked her about the Crypt didn't she she
gave us this whole backstory oh did she
yeah when we first asked could we asked
her she died almond wood let it go yes
there's this thing not you know that you
don't know you do know this info you
don't have to okay you don't have to pry
for it you you know that there is a
difference of opinion here between
prophetess drawn and omen drawn right
about auspicious right and out of
character there's a I know that omen is
on a quest to bring her back to life you
got her on ice out around ice okay okay
okay exactly but that's but that is not
her that is not her perspective I see on
the street but I still wrote you got my
ice okay
okay well we do a with your cake we do a
cake yeah and it's beautifully frosted
and we do a cake and it's waiting
waiting for for Audrey's returns again
in our dreams yeah and you guys are
having those dreams and she just and
then I was perfectly frosted she's just
turning it slightly right mission
to find like angle she's trying to find
that like awesome that that angle right
that will like bridge the gap between
food and art perhaps a certain serving
an angle right Park and I want to put my
arm on prophetess and probably like
lowest the lowest part of her arm
because I'm very small and say sometimes
I think you probably notice sometimes we
lose children but we can find children
in other people and in in situations
that we didn't even know we could and so
I hope that I hope that you have found
you have found more people to love and
nurture in your life since losing your
daughter yeah she will chill turn and
then kneel down and how you hugs
back-traced kitchen love then I'm gonna
I'm going to sleep when you that was
really sweet thing I want to ruin it for
when you were like looking at the cake
and going you know sometimes you find
children we sticks cake that looks like
it's the cake the other propped up
everything's fine ah marionette come see
Emily Union sorry
thief thanks Emily
right here but you felt it in didn't
even play that card is it good mom okay
okay
go sleep yeah is the mushroom isn't
alone yes with what you think oh yeah
what happens you put it I is my spikes
earning 9 it takes a little bit like
it's just like you know what I mean we
hear it we're like god damn it Sam
I like the idea makes fart noise really
no no it's like a freshness seal right
yeah I think it's like a Tupperware like
honestly any time he touches it anywhere
anywhere on there yeah well it uses its
eyes conveying of
the tweet uses eyes to convey motion but
also like when it gets angry because it
you can communicate it yeah you don't
know it best so what we just need you
guys but you know that these sounds mean
certain things yeah yeah they've worked
out certain they've worked out certain
bits of information anything he's just
farting around yeah yeah it really just
like a little oh my gosh
Layton with his mushroom no no but it is
you won't shut up guys it's a mushroom
was it just like five minutes and you're
like all right
does he have a name uh Cappy Cappy
Carson on the brand captain I can well
yeah yeah tell me would tell me how you
want to get things bump in the next day
big hearty breakfast yeah nice shower
hmm cap on emissions shower yeah yeah
moist yeah I'm gonna keep them moist
yeah yeah I'm get the paper cup of cup
of joe papers with the papers yeah Joe
I'm already down and I'm watching a look
at you yeah
I should have tuned got bowl cereal like
no I'm Weiss's I'm watching better I'm
watching lagari just circle with his
proud probably with me baggers yeah yeah
yeah I'm like one finger tired of it no
no you're doing some fine I mean you're
seeing and he is again there is a
performative quality to the whole thing
where have you ever I've never seen
crabs yeah
what I what are those tell about
mythical DMZ classic beef where I see
the rump have you ever seen crabs engage
in dominance behavior yeah it's
ridiculous so fun yeah I think exactly
but if it is a little dance and then one
the cause is way too vague right now
it's like hey mother what you
want like the whole thing is just like
this this bizarre dance and it's just
like that and then he occasionally
invents new steps oh yeah no I about
crabs not about a guy but like I think
I'm right or a misremembering
like that huge show claw doesn't have
any like it's too big it's way too high
the only thing or is doing this
up
yeah I mean for us doing that up
dance am i right yeah what's it all
about
we sloping the crab talk you know in
color okay yeah first time uh hey I
really love crabs very percent I recall
a long time I crabs first time with Club
a long time trailer father we're done
caller we're done alright now what's
next what's so everything read though
that like do we understand whether or
not the can we do both of these jobs
yeah actually we should we should all
get on the same page the plane it's a
scam um right scam I'm good yeah let's
try to do both there if we only do one
that we can't every job we only have to
do one then we do the first one and then
we're like yeah we're security and then
we just steal it simply okay if we can't
cash in on both at least said one thing
we're playing an easy mode yeah yeah
good question
yes what what are the general
populations feelings about the lizard
folk lizard folk yeah are they disliked
like the drow how do they often
yeah run the government good look at the
bank are conspiracy conspiracy I don't
know how it's supposed to top that in my
life I'm glad it's like this I'd be
generally speaking you know it wouldn't
be hard to find a person who was not 100
percent Pro lizard folk generally
they're not they don't they don't they
don't expose themselves like this like
it isn't it there's not like this the
Horde which you have heard of is a
successful venture okay it's very very
well regarded but this is not common
this is not common lizard folk behavior
Oh to ask for that's it exactly indeed
and into it but was it to engage in the
broader
society they tend to be a secretive folk
or anything environment in ancient thank
god damn it I'm not nervous all night
something something melt steel beams I
want to be part of this okay yeah all
right I don't know whether or not Chris
would feel a little bit like a little
guys and dark trying to step up in the
light guided those many years ago no no
God except oh yeah how big is it
yeah great that's all boys substantial
okay it's all just got a 911
geez those are folk is this table talk
yeah yeah between friggin Amulya back in
the game
that's ridiculous okay yeah okay well I
don't even yes wizard folks some of you
are whoa
no I'm just trying to figure it out ah
[Laughter]
cool oh it's not cool oh no god dammit
er I see this as serendipitous I see
this as a fortune like yes we could do
both of these jobs I'm not at put it I'm
not put off bike I'm interested but
triangles I've been watching the sunrise
with coriander
hey so ready to go when y'all are yeah
already ready chief so hungry as hell
what's cop enough gotta get all these
jobs gonna keep this for work ha ha ha
ha ha ha say 1 2 3 4 5 si 5 does it
shoot jump around chewin
yeah it's chewing him up it's a big
mouthful yeah just wad enough like a
like a lump of like a big league chew it
the sauce gold coin just getting
worked many $1 comes out every scene
with Nyjah who looks like that gold look
around yeah they come out of bricks yeah
Senate data
yeah okay extrude it so we're going to
how do we talk to both of these and we
talk to first we are going to Rafi I
don't know if we need to make contact
with the noble knife I think we just
guys will get the jack yeah so I think
the thing to do is to go meet with the
dragon hordes River going blah blah blah
in the barge right upon acceptance
secure passage expect contact isn't it
flow secure passage means gotta get on
the boat so let's go down below yeah
we're just here pad though yeah then I
think I'm gonna be on yeah that's right
that's mine you'll have your you'll have
your documents your kid how would they
go for I'm gonna have the big boys into
a I thing ten times we're going to roll
up in this is anyone who has that so
cart yes she's wearing like a lot of AI
stuff yeah can all by our store I have
loaded up the cart with pieces of
wedding cake wrapped up in napkin for
everyone Lulu and I have pointed the
cart stuff we're ready to head them over
marvelous once we get there so now we
are underway I'm assuming yes Gulam so
you're inside the best or the classic
scenario yes if you have a wrist robe
and a dinar Blitzen within within and
then you exact asleep by the way right
okay an orange like Jesse goes like I
wake up given a car too much but is
there's never a moment where one of them
is not snoring yes all right
I like the idea that they did with the
eyes of the like you're sleeping but the
eyes of the mushroom are like they act
as though they can see what you're
dreaming so it's a lot of like shaking
and it just like you see like they're
round edge of the Hat like sort of turn
into that like peanut smells like you
just yeah clamshell curious dismay yeah
so but yeah is it are you in your
classic zone loss on top up top which is
ironic oh I'm serious or bottom did you
guys not see like an Italian but what I
was going to say was if we have to meet
with two separate parties for these two
separate jobs that make sense that we
not like are completely separated but we
just actually
we don't know each other we split into
two you interface with the lizard folk
because you represent a kink and then
the people who are not emblazoned with
that logo could talk to the noble knight
maybe maybe the folks who are generally
associated with criminal underbelly Fifi
is not naming any names first off I'll
go with you here's my family one person
to make contact as a robber it's true
yeah there should be someone Shady
yeah and maybe a little subtle yeah
that's nice so I don't know is wrong
with you sleeves off I'm a paladin Oh
honorable I've done job better yeah yeah
that makes a lot of sense like a
gleaming armor I'm here to rob this
place no one would believe it just giant
mushroom on my countertop see it cuz I
put my negative 1 decks there you don't
believe my stuff yeah makes me speak
maybe I'll get lucky I'm 22 that's a
megaphone
anyway gig okay are past the barge right
past the end between Vienna and one for
behaviors I don't want to write to like
any music on the way there you won't get
that skull come on now it on use it for
later
I don't pick it up okay there though
behavior were coming back it looks
exactly cheese yeah yeah even even when
it's obviously even when the the skulls
mouth is locked it's always trying to do
a little something oh yeah I'm sure nice
this is your production warning yeah
thank you I appreciate it
no I'll give you something good
excellent remember we buried fire got it
it's all just all bad music yeah got
rock you actually put a lot of wisdom
I'll shut these ventriloquism right
amazing with everything maybe what they
accomplished if you drink water and say
I don't know what else to do all right
yes so how does this how does this work
and you roll up so who's so who's who's
going to do what um well that I think
walnuts dinar and I got to be dinar he's
so big okay that's true look about it
earlier that's your issue and you will
once we get onto the hoard then you will
sneak off and make contact with the new
life yes I'm good
also I just want to point out not naming
any names are looking at anyone in
particular but it says that they demand
tasteful protection like a gleaming
giant paladin faithful Sakura will be
druid I've stared at the joint parting
mushroom yeah I enjoyed myself with well
Frank about not showering she's kind of
bragging you never talk price well as
you are you are partitioning yourself
into these groups functional task
oriented subsections if you will that's
the official name for them in the
document yeah yeah yeah obviously walnut
knows you you know you you have you have
been this for ourselves from read larch
before one I know it was at that time it
was later in the evening of course it is
getting late now it's a substantial draw
away from red larch it's almost going to
be time for you know maybe not maybe not
a short rest maybe a long rest why and
why not do we happen to see any kind of
in you have to use it in fact in fact
along the left just as you are rounding
a corner you can see a sequence of
torches begin to light themselves up a
path that you are well familiar with
what color is the green flame obviously
is leaping to life
on the torches and you can see that the
the gate is there in front as radiuses
that doone-gate in and then below in the
most wretched handwriting you can
imagine it says under new management you
got close so close proud of us what do
you mean looks close I feel like what
they was writing like this what's the
difference looks like I can read it you
can read it it's not really letters all
right all right it's good places any
yeah ten minutes make our picks out yeah
maybe a friend of Woody's yeah it was
the place huh so you work you roll up
perverse curiosity exactly as is
coriander coriander approaches the gate
she gives it a good firm nudge with her
steel nose own bronze I guess
technically squeaks open she pulls the
cart up and there are other carts here
already you can hear sounds of merriment
within Oh sounds vampiric hmm I don't
know it was how does that sound
I don't care you can party and I better
it I'm all about the party yeah I have
fond memories of this place no less than
we did so charity today we're doing it
again
Yeah right sunset yeah funny how life
works anyway whoo I'm gone I'm inside
you guys you guys are behind me almost
undress this is the forgiveness that she
ever saw Brahma so it's true yeah all
true specials ladies like looking around
like as if she would be there like
obviously she's not but she's like you
know when you're like in a crowd you
know maybe I'll see some this is
somebody here you're just like looking
at it trying not to make a yeah yeah I'm
not I'm easy going in just because this
was weird so weird about yeah man I
don't have strong anti feelings I'm like
yeah a lot of harder happening yeah yeah
it was a very gruesome scene like you
more opted in
yeah
is more convincing people that we didn't
kill a large group than I like yeah do
to have to do
hey we got paid paid not enough not
enough
you filed for it that's the main thing
so as you enter you take in in an
incredible sight the place is the place
is jumpin its clientele is incredibly
unique diverse I think is is the term
there are at least two ghosts Wow
goats well know it from me if you doing
a goat I used to think that they were
just like a male sheep we're dogs
- hold on click horns dogs but they're
whole different times indeed hanging
from the chandelier is a spider very
small reelers smell like that no no a
substantial size and the light that it
casts sort of shines through that
abdomen and she appears to be knitting
scarves and sweaters and whenever she
completes when she just drops it there's
a couple down there but you can see
people here with scarves on talking
sweaters into satchels Wow nobody's
playing at everything else
oh but the the bar is open you can see a
bipedal werewolf back there working with
a frustrated expression on his face
Oh frustrated okay gosh I'm at the bar
yeah he is just he has just set down a
bowl of hay
been fishing your mom or dad ever to
keep a shot like well though it's a
specific fishing memory there's crabs
there yeah
crabs crabs no there's a specific
fishing memory you know look you buy
like the live bait it's like the little
Styrofoam cup that has like the snow
soil in there and then it just worms
yeah yeah so this is a bowl like a
ceramic bowl full of dirt and like half
hotdogs sized white grubs and he has set
it down in front of a giant mantis
person um playful super good
I'm live here big yeah but there are
three empty bowls right by visible and
the Mantis man who you may know as a
threat cream yeah so reaches down
multiple multiple tiers imagine like
that like it was a beautiful wedding
cake but instead it's like bug arms it's
reaching out with a small pair down in
the town in front and he just brings it
up and then the mandibles go down sort
of into it and like excavate the bowl
and then when they come up there are no
more grubs there's a few riddles and
then the musk goes back into the bowl
and he sets it down and then looks out
that driven Wow
expectant Wow character says five bowls
is the limit yeah you don't drink
nothing huh yay never ordered a drink I
will show you how to drink he reaches
back gets a bottle makes a drink who
shakes it real quick drinks it like that
you put the liquid right in your craw
we're all doing it
hey everybody here's doing it except for
the ghosts they can't do it it ain't
their fault I'm sure they would drink as
it could god I want to be here he looks
over and sees the the party having
entered and smiles and if anyone else
had seen it they would feel intimidated
and maybe terrified so you know that
this is great you know that this many
teeth is actually a good sign
shadow counsel I invoke you may our
Labor's please you we have a short break
you know take advantage the facilities
drain yourself and then returned to us
refreshed for the rest of the seating
thank you so much Cubs word hello I'm
here for a cave our camp and this is
test C teams Chris trap is drawing the
mail assemble over and over again which
I know is not okay right now we're going
to fight yeah my like my side of my
packet because remember the my focus did
consume three daggers that's why I know
it's there's three of them
nice it's three the the infestation is 3
dagger strong so I'm gonna figure out
how to yeah we got those evan is going
to eat that as a killer that's that's
that's pros here he looks over at you
massive wolven smile and the front door
opens to the doone-gate in too hard too
hard it was opened with tremendous gale
force look over and then you see you see
a creature become as small as it can and
then scoot themselves I mean basically
birthing themselves through this doorway
and then when they come out on the other
side they unfold their full height you
see a massive hairy feathered beaked
creature and you the the the room erupts
and everyone including traverses
and then the Beast raises its sort of we
pause and says and judged shambles
through the holding out its holding out
of pop you know hands are hitting pause
wings whatever you've got he's ready to
give it to you
it's whatever send love from bless them
at cryoxide
alright the burden and heretic i right
there a cockerel yeah yeah now that no
no no it's like a massive bipedal owl Oh
huh is my car Rosie things yes it's like
on the list yeah like it's if I got a
weird bucket list called the avian yeah
yeah and even say in the fur community
oh I think I think it came a fourth
library I just released around the other
a throw me on the line yeah your scaly
yeah I know about scaly where you talk
about yes care call house call is less
bless is about eight and a half nine
feet tall okay and I'm screening uh see
top that's a tree he could climb yeah
I'm drink out of that photo avian bird
daughter kicked that bird out of the
nest gonna be some kind of a bird game
what isn't unknown but Trevor Trevor
Trevor going to merges he doesn't have
time to be frustrated or annoyed by this
insectoid a grub Feaster not not was not
when friends are in so he explodes from
behind the bar comes around it's putting
the paws out he's shaking hands he's a
power what you've been doing I'm running
the doone-gate in refit I got a great
job this place looks awesome look at all
my friends little my new friends this
wow this is way cooler than before way
cooler yeah I'll say those vampires
that's the only rule that have no
vampires if it was a problem early on
but we worked through it new policy -
vampire free establishment I figured we
clear them all out last time
real real vampires cleared
out here all the time real no cops
around I think I have how much d1 note
god no you know what no you know I
thought about you drink
what I wanted are we buy me Oh God dig
around there yes okay I gotta arm lee
Bailey okay thank you that sort of like
a buffer that sort of fear that werewolf
blood class you see you see you see a
dog walk out of a swinging door back
from the larder smoking a pipe guys I
don't recommend mushroom trip again
yeah what you're doing you'd not evil Oh
Kathy love yeah a murder I wish I had
that dog hey dog sure who's a good boy
yeah yeah he looks up yeah anyway I had
like the dog you know that that's sort
of like smile pant yeah as they have he
can do the smile pant but he can just
sort of adjust the pipes with hops
inside nice yeah he's he's ready he
doesn't he doesn't appear he look like a
regular dog he can hear but doesn't
communicate such like what's your
packing in that pipe take it easy
wow I just got here that's a party and I
party hard-working tomorrow
right this way went downhill you hope
you understand you see it's just like
when we were the scritch all right
that's Gretchen all right good drug that
buy me a bunk yeah I asked my dog I want
to dealing now with the group anymore
like you Rosie is found like her like yo
yeah and his dogs hi dogs hi dogs
without the lighthouse
pick up the scarves yeah I definitely
want to our fellow stars I want with the
discards yeah I'm do this there's you
look over the pile that was there at the
at the bottom is gone so they must cycle
pretty fast but if you look up you can
see a scarf so light wholesome silken
scarf drops down from the chandelier
sort of snakes through the air on unseen
currents and histogram I want how big as
it might come over here yeah it's like a
winter scarf I have you know a mommy I
need a bigger one okay but does it have
any you hear a weird sound from up there
then you can see that that you think
that she might be working on something
for bless it's like a it's like the bits
of gigantic you know almost tent like
sweater you might be able to wear it
over your armor which would be tasteful
yeah but you you may not be the intended
audience for this product to market
there might be a demographic mismatch
okay I look a examine the scarf is there
any doing it was it exists do I get
anything yeah enhance
what quadrant this scarf looks like the
scarf or area exact right this car for
Regions yeah no if you wanted if you
want to take some time hand it over to
Chris Chris
well I'm sure any any Boone's orbanes no
no I don't like dumb it's gonna throw it
down do anything I take it immediately
so you try to interrogate the scarf
that's the my feel any stronger dumb
need to discard you that look so good
now the Sun he'll never fly off never
again keep up with us so road I take
that scarf because I want to get a good
whiff of that that's fresh
real fresh silk if it be there's so much
of I'm so used to that yeah now the
normal
like when you were walking - huffing
spits when you're walking to drough
school you know as I as a young man you
know your mother might have tied
something you know right around this oh
yeah right around that neck made your
gloves off for you
mm-hmm probably a lot of a lot of spider
silk there - yeah yeah just for the big
Garland's of it around around my town so
people are it's a porous bar people are
passing into it
securing product speaking of Porto Santo
or s1 yeah yeah anyway
you villain you go to jail that's that's
why you can't come to a game in the
future and not the actual reason you're
going next week it's added from if the
punishments random and from my heart so
but you can see like down down at the
very end in in a shame and decrepitude
but you can see a man it's hard to say
the raiment is like the sort of thing
that you would bury someone in yes Wow
yeah yeah a little dressed up for the
occasion excited like yeah it's there's
some there's some tatters with the Bema
no no exactly like it's it's not a
hundred percent you think that it would
have been nice a long time ago like a
long time ago
and this entity there's way way into his
cups down at the end of the bar my visit
to him bits he's close to me this is not
like a weird like Oh spider oh well no
no the reality is that there's you know
it's he is where there is space oh
please move down to the end okay wait
drinking friend lots of this time for
I'll have I'll also have one trick
Trevor over here is this and he is one
of these nexus people you know he is one
of these joiner people he'd
he and I keep makes love connections and
he says have you ever ordered a drink in
a bar I've seen it done I've read about
a lot of people keep coming to the barb
that don't know its business
I mean I realize it is a business
talking to you catch it chop talking to
you fix up writing it down yes uh what
it what it what's popular here what do
people like to drink alcohol
that's the only the only variant too big
part of what I serve you
Allah I'll have one
I say magnanimous excellent well thank
you see he goes back makes a curatorial
selection for a Leah fight embarrassed
produces a glass for you and for your
companion brings them down sets them
down to Chris brow this is this name I
have on my sheet of paper what well
mother I got it over no okay he said
this is conundrum the ever live
oh boo that's not for you that sounds
like a nightmare
sounds like boy Chris that's right
what's that like sucks and I can only
imagine yeah with you I don't have to
imagine it have you tried everything
well it's my fault
oh no the night of wars kind yeah I cast
the spell and now I don't know how to
uncashed it and I put the time in I put
the time in
no it looks like it ya know it you would
repeat in your death like you're so
close oh yeah oh listen and it's not
it's not for lack of trying
you know what you mean heard that yeah I
got problems already lectures experts oh
yeah
I tell you yeah tough racket yes this is
good just yeah well now I know we just
met
now you notify lactarius oh yeah I Chris
doesn't remember but yeah this probably
does yeah yeah sis well I uh I lost in a
dice I'm lost uh my phylactery you ever
go over he had just this little bellhop
hat and he says I told you can
understood on that file actor II do it
where did where'd you haven't alou's it
he puts he points a crooked bony thumb
and just points behind him you look
behind and you see one look like yes
nice piece I see the dice manga I
started with them exactly we're told me
yes like could the dice monger make it a
dice so big he couldn't yeah yeah
alright the question no one right you
see what looks like a ghost seated in a
chair inexplicably there's no real
reason to sit on the chair seated across
from a skeleton an animated skeleton and
they appear to be just talking to one
another idly good perception role from
you sure I'll use this lovely die
Oh whatever a lot of roll what am I it's
what I'll call yeah exactly me I'd down
the whole thing yet so that's a no it's
trash is what it is it's a field give it
to me it's a head bills whole numbers
and they sense now this number that one
I can't even tell what skull looks like
exactly so I can look at it
already lips but all if you'd be another
this this there's something like me the
conversation that they're having does
sound odd it sounds a little strange
[Music]
does anybody else want to take a gander
at this scenario there or is there
anybody between us or is it like a
straight shot it's a straight shot okay
whoa you so when when the spider drops
its massive sweater and it sort of sails
down like a leaf it shifts itself on the
chandelier and you can see just for a
split second the contours around these
two illuminated so they are seated
inside of a transparent cube that
shudders and wobbles slightly in
position okay I'm going to tap on it
nothing happens oh yeah yeah yeah it did
it reacts like it's being tickled ah
sort of pulls away a little bit and it
hurts the tip of your finger like it
doesn't feel good to damage is that yes
you're annihilated can you guys see when
I tap on this can they see yeah yeah
when she driving when she draws your
attention to it you can see it
immediately they are suspended like some
kind of like Easter treat but imagine a
depraved grandmother yeah making it a
doomed treat for the devil yeah when you
put it with you so far yeah so the
cinnamon cake from before I got it yeah
exactly
the commend imagine the polar opposite
of a cinnamon cake it's full of
skeletons and ghosts and sort of pie
yeah
cronut is a pie this is really a lot of
shark buy a jell-o salad
yeah horrible yeah yeah a demonic jell-o
salad okay full of odd you know odds and
ends okay
you here's a boot here is something else
and you can also love you
you yet yes I bet it's exam is exactly
what it is that's a great term for it
thank you let's call it that from now
yeah yeah yeah look at that yes you see
between them on the table you see an urn
that is more or less nondescript but
they appear to be impressed with it and
they occasionally look over at your
drinking companion and then they look
back and they literally high-five over
this urn I literally do that they really
do not figure it goes to ghost goes
right through though right
no Dave's work this out of his or like
they both stop it yeah oh yeah yeah yeah
it's like it's like you don't know how
long it took them to practice this heat
but a ghost and a skeleton can high-five
now we know yeah be okay I have one
corner if you might believe let me say
this matrix ministry let me tell you
some creative amazing things about I
asked I asked can undress how did it get
there the cube the membrane so clean
that's probably the cleanest one I've
ever seen you can even see it right away
it's all it's all acid he looks back
it's just it's like a acid monster but
even it lays pretty clean in there but
it's still as well even the suspension
is pretty tight I'm glad that you like
it the Jews run from are disgusting you
can tell ya know that they're not will
maintained
yeah well let's talk about this cube
smart so they they played a game with
you you lost yeah what do they want with
it
really think they want me not to have it
do they do this every night like you've
been a lifer it looks like a long long
time it has happened more than once
hmm so your factory is inside the urn I
asked him it's like it's like no sound
has been reduced is there a way that we
could win back your factory friend if
you fought up if you want to play
against them if you want to if you want
to bet against these characters what
ways it's narrow wells hmm what if we
did get this back for you what's in it
for us well you've got other stuff in
there okay like well if boot let's take
a look okay acid foam rule keep he
pushes back and walks over and in the
same way that you might look in the
glass window of a shop
he sort of peruses the the treasure
offer that it's established here and if
he gets as he gets close you see the
skeleton and the ghost both look at him
and they're like hey back off
just shut up Proust and he goes around
the corner Skelton doesn't say me he
looks around the corner he's like yeah
okay I see looks like there's a loot in
there not like a like I lose like an
instrument not like an instrument yeah
there's a loop yeah yeah one loop yeah
he's sliding a lot of a little bit like
it yeah it's like a locket luck it goes
around the back corner gets the
three-quarter view just see some gems
hmm he's like what color that I don't
green flames violet we can use it with
your override it might know
nice nice um so he's looking around in
there he's like I don't he's like I
don't press myself I don't trust myself
to get this back from him I don't have a
good history playing dice against Proust
we got to lose well the last thing I do
have dignity they won't they won't play
for that your underpants don't think I
haven't tried
Underpants yeah what's the last thing
you have yes he's size and he removes it
looks like a almost like a papal just
like a papal sort of conical hat takes
it off the hair comes with it goes over
here sit sit on the he sit sit on the
bar terraces cut Damon he's wiping
around it like every square inch he can
possibly clean and he removes a gold
chain with an ankh like symbol on the
face of it and he says I will loan this
to you if you can get that urn back I
think I look fine to play that there
game you look great in here what do you
want to try it I mean I guess um like
are we are maybe our luckiest person
should try it
yes it's going to kill me yeah do you
have any kind of like turn on dead so
palliative Turman did yeah okay what
about not be undead anymore not like
turn into undead with get rid of I can
detect them and it's going crazy right
now
yeah yeah well I'd turns up and nothing
good maybe somebody that can troll one
yeah should be really nice to know you
got it if you have that apparently coins
okay oh okay yeah I got it all right
I'll take that same great does it have
any special properties power
first before I put this thing on oh yeah
it curse to be everliving not curse not
cursed cursed you put it on your face oh
it's a semantic difference really what's
gonna happen eyes with Assad cuz it's
strong everything okay fine
air quotes follows up all right come on
all right and he says did it play Giants
and halflings in the monastery yes they
do I know every rule ha ha oh it is one
for each of us my god yeah yeah learn a
game don't worry don't worry don't be
scared there ain't nothing to worry
about it I was chemical I got it oh no
no like all right he's like listen and
he reaches into his own ribcage and
pulls out a few ancient Dyson he says I
can teach you how to play before you go
in there okay
okay that'd be great thank you okay
all right all that fun already there's
crazy all right this is so you have
played it it refresh me it's important
if you haven't played it I it's been a
long time I can give the necklace to
bliss I ever use those big paws but I've
never played I would love to see it yeah
let's let's get let's go ahead and get
some rules all right
lesson I have business later you are the
halflings plural right okay but you're
also the halflings in the game okay you
have to halflings
those are your dice either my halfling
those are your halflings okay i have the
giant okay your halflings have six sides
right the giant has ten sides right okay
and if you so far yeah if the giant
rolls of one think of to think of 1
through 10 as the Giants body okay right
your halflings have to try to hit my
knee okay that's how you win all right
but if I ever roll a one you lose oh
that's called the kick okay
okay I'm gonna roll the dice for example
this time I got a one okay that will
kick you Milo you automatically lose
automatically lose okay now that was
also one let me try again
let me get a different dice a - okay
this is great great all you have to do a
sling
yeah is roll higher than a two-on-two
dice so is that a 3 or higher or a 2 or
higher it could be a 2 okay it can't be
a - okay seems highly likely on both of
them yeah oh I'm both died that's right
okay well I gotta go three six now in
this case you would win now because I
rolled a two yeah knees that are set at
two or three pay one to one so if you
gave me a hundred gold right now you
have 200 gold C right okay if the me is
four to six that pays two to one okay if
the knee is seven to nine that pays
three to one and if the knee is ten god
help you yeah because that's very hard
to roll on - halflings hep does seem
impossible to roll it is very hard but
it does pay five to one okay now there
is something else okay if you roll
higher than I can roll on a d-10 on my
10-sided dice here the giant right 11 or
that's the mall the giant eats you up
okay we're too high okay now there's one
more rule that you need to know right
okay if you hit the knee exactly you can
double your bet take your dice split
them into two and roll one additional
dice for each one interesting and try to
get your money that way okay fun all
right
and I may split a second time if I wish
to become legend you wish to become
legendary yes you can split the dice
again if you hit the knee again Wow
okay what about a third time yes what
it's unlikely we'll cross that bridge
when we get to it now to be very clear I
want to make sure it's not this if their
knees - I don't have to roll like boat
this is this is a six yeah you can deep
not ten threes you know he said
something if you're if you're value add
to add up your halfling right they are
higher than any didn't also be fine I'm
you win okay I have you win now great
there's also there's also one more rule
okay
if you roll two ones yeah a snake scares
away the giant okay okay you keep your
bets
everybody starts over okay push okay uh
Trey look sure do we are we all plans oh
it really is a sick addiction of the
civilized world
yeah I could not agree more let's roll
suppose okay see this will be easier
well we can peer behind the veil look at
my I'm looking phonology graph
paper whoa Lucas no no pants is that the
song yeah whoa the giant rolls it yeah
good job Lou cute again okay okay and I
rolled a six alright
in this case you win that game okay 101
so what do you bet you get that exactly
right now I'm not placing bets except I
want the phylactery correct exactly what
exactly in there that gold doesn't last
long
sir so they just like things it's like a
little museum for them okay they just
want you to bring in things so people
people come in and bet objects okay yeah
a lot of garbage in that color you know
give them your oh yeah no I got that for
show all right here you know you look
some more practice okay we'll get you
ready for free okay okay what are the
skills in New York yeah feeling good
about that
what's a nine okay okay so that would
take a little one young D all right
before you never know what makes you to
want if you don't try one
now you never know when you're going to
need to know Giants and halflings that's
true you never know when you might need
to know it and now we know there's
places there's places where people use
this to solve all kinds of problems I'm
so glad we know have you ever heard of
pickpocket uh I don't think so
no tick pockets a Thieves Guild game
right uh same dice slightly different
rules better odds for the house
generally speaking people think of
Giants and halflings as a friendly game
okay it's not friendly this time proof
but again it is you fight you free hate
that guy
but generally speaking explain among
friends okay 10 2010 your money in big
money but but I have to roll exactly a
ten because if I roll on 11 or 12 then I
get eaten all right two are two to one
it'll push so nice to know yes
two ones is the way to sneak Yeah right
goodness gracious
okay okay oh let's see you go you've got
a third when you got the necklace got
the necklace whatever that means you got
the dice you want to bring my dice in
with you yeah I'm feeling good about
these actually don't take my dice in
those are the dice that got me in
trouble all these other times okay try
these other dice okay all we need is to
give you I don't need to get you a fifth
of a phylactery you hit that yeah we got
it
let's try back now what I have on my
balloon yeah it does seem like it might
interest people who might be obsessed
with the phylactery yes it is also will
so what all do you have with you going
in here I have you've got all kinds of
weird get eyeball jars yeah I think
it's like rival seems like it might be
the thing that they like the most it
might be I gotta help given that talk
about all we have a writ for a delivery
of a statue of a nude man oh that's
right honey statue of what has been his
prominent buttocks haven't we put that
in our base in our yeah but we
we would have a delivery shipped yeah if
I glue it many times I think you're the
skull the skull is going to another
world other than air so there could be a
situation where you should be a
situation where you have to constantly
go out to the cart yes and getting some
right hands we got I got this horse one
in fact once we also have a vial of
undetermined oil all right way to go
hoards pearl yeah I got it so we just
like grab all this from the cart
and pile it up what do you like we're
holding from the outside like this huh
yeah we have got all kinds of good stuff
are you gonna make you a disadvantage or
any of these while we're gambling who
knows I know can use lucky a few Rolla
one oh well I'm going to say what does
one have specific rules yeah
in this so it's a double one obviously
means snake and push right um but if she
rolled a single one I would say why not
okay I think that's a cool and fun all
right now and if you want to if you
wanted to use an advantage roll that has
been granted to you by the shadow
council their power is immense okay even
down to you know manipulating wind dice
were manufactured out of what materials
by whom gee okay possible right yeah so
so proofs and his associate right have
been watching this instruction sir with
some with some predatory interest
it's just Oh are we a part of this
conversation did anybody ask us if we
wanted to play giants and halflings do
you a lot okay please come in alright
and you can see that in the in the
middle of the gelatinous cube it makes a
void for you so it pushes itself out
gelatinous Li and the rest of the rest
of the volume slightly increases and
there is a little Hollow the size of a
halfling and a corner of the table to
play on and I'm like
well good luck do you want me to just
misty step in and take it
mm-hmm I'll give you a signal which is
going to be gonna be this just in case
you get out all the time no other
Atlanta just token like them oh you're
really good she's the problem misty said
only works
I only do it one time so it's probably
not ideal if I jump in well we'll take
it as we get it don't worry guys talking
about um just rats just some luck yep
are we playing giant giant
apples or what I don't know what stand -
chill out a little bit
seriously God y'all let me take you
think first you think you're in my house
now okay hey why the non face yeah you
guys have to deliver burns to take you
down SiC em outside to get words any of
them you had all you have a wooden you
had the little corner of the table and
he says what's your bet I have this
extremely mysterious jar of eyeballs
that I've been carrying around for I
don't know how long it's definitely got
some kind of like necromantic power to
it and I know that the first one that I
saw when we broke it open turned into a
giant monster so they're not been
holding on to this one his his bony
companion goes I know it's a spruce
looks over and sort of Cox and I at his
friend and his friend goes alright so
that's that's why guys so you see you
can just like set it in the air in the
air and it floats yes next week so let
me just be clear about the terms of this
bet if I win at one-to-one that gives me
my jar of eyeballs and this phylactery
is that the would-be elephant yeah
what's the what's the payout yes okay
great
oh so just a one to one for a friend
friendly games aren't like the coin hot
okay I see I see okay
all right so Jon my jar of eyeballed
against your
uh unremarkable phylactery do we get to
pick who who is house - I mean yeah he's
house house yeah all right in his house
do you guys want to bet on the game all
right
yes I ride better over here you're on me
jump in no I mean there's other people
side action no there's there's all kinds
of people are intrigued by this you get
me impressive that people watch this
cube like television around here dude
one looks like just chowing down on one
of those grubs yes
just straight-up just steady greven yeah
yeah I mean keep them coming to you can
see that you can see that he has a like
a like a braise here like emptied out
brazier if it's just full of soil and
grubs all right and he just scooped them
up in a bowl and set them out it's the
peanut yeah all right eatin popcorn oh
yeah yeah I'm gonna take side action
all right here 3.50 gold whoa and are
the progress is like well I'm not gonna
want some oh my girl now let me take
your night night yeah I'm loving it
gotta feed that horse yeah go horses
like what I mean is that it thank you
are you are you the horse yeah I don't
understand that yeah there you go
don't you boys go forth if you had the
Horace Horace me so you can sew it so
you use you slap down fifty on a table
near the action and no one no one joins
in do you see people like sort of
standing close and then they're moving
back and then they look up and on a
strand of silk in a little pouch hmm it
hits the table in front of you take with
a clink why I stuffed that legs yeah I
love it
all right something terrible happen to
my my device Emily it wanted to update
itself know that this is a classic
problem for me whose crimes it's fine no
it's a time no are you ready yeah are
you going to take this
give me this advantage don't you roll
this for me okay
all right you're calling me right in
this all right no tablet no yeah exactly
I did take triple dissident giving my
most intimidating stare to Proust he I
was working because easy ghost and he is
100% good fearless he is 100% ghosty
okay um is it I mean my Mila yes exactly
so he bring he brings his hand back into
the gelatinous core of this thing shakes
it slowly and then you see it cast out
through the liquid oh this is exactly
what I need
uber haunted three hot roll there we
have very nice today yeah it goes more
like a shade damn push push push
step 9 yeah you're gonna call this real
on this process snake
snake now since I am lucky can I choose
career oldest make alright no and we
know know Ryan was very thoughtful and
correct on the snake we push that's me
buddy give us a single one you can
reroll it yeah because lucky doesn't say
we roll all ones forever
yeah just says reroll ones on an attack
right alright I'll need this alright I
didn't do anything I was Ryan yeah
look it I'm gonna jog it didn't really
lose Ryan I'm gonna call that a warm-up
round yeah exactly how we blow word
warm-up round yeah
key phrase shaking it but this hey
brings it back in shakes that he's doing
some sigil in the air
hey you come here and then he thinks the
better of it change his hands right oh
yeah this - you too - and he he
he just pounds the table just behind me
just like
and you see took yeah your ghost man's
on Joy's end before oh yeah hmm goddamn
he says it's a stupid anyway I agree
it's a stupid urn why you can have that
urn I got other stuff Oh what hey Karen
let me let me just take my urn my jar
eyeball right back take them out towards
person Becky what you got okay
exactly yeah exactly
he is like sort of like moving around in
the in the stuff just like taking things
like pushing them out of the way they
sort of float for a little way yeah
never if they ever hit the edge of the
gelatin they stop against the membrane
and come back in a little bit
he's just here and he's like this and he
reaches out and then in the muck grabs
from inside of the boot a chain that
comes out with a silver locket at the
end
hmm and it brings it out he says she's
trapped in there I don't know how I
can't fix it I can't get her out to her
he opens it up where was he you see a
girl yeah okay inside the locket just a
girl just some random girl yeah anyway
new it opens up she looks at you and
looking like as a new person like a
recognition right and with a piteous
gaze Oh God she like there's a membrane
there's like a wall no no no she just
looks up like you'd like you'd imagine
that you're like just looking at a
mirror oh she's just like okay but she's
aware oh uh I don't know like what yeah
Rosie can't leave a small child you know
now what was into it now she's like oh I
don't know with it better all right
I don't know and purses like I didn't do
it it's not my fault I don't happen
there's a lot of in here where did
you get this
it just listened and that's my skeleton
yeah I'm the ghost yeah sure
we died in here yeah you know the only
ones okay there's a bunch of in
here okay what I know I had that's worth
like three of these eyeballs cares yeah
well cut them and throw them it
shouldn't be betting for this you should
be reporting them to be a Thor I was
gonna say like you acknowledge this is
messed up writing small five we're not
bet on a tortured child let's let's
definitely do that we're not the most
popular with the police and then
particulars down so I think we probably
don't have that options to sound loud
please Rosie is a sort of unable to not
help a child and even if it's like
tortured like maniac who's presenting as
a child it just doesn't have that
actually now that Morgan yeah she does
whatever would have caused her to
separate those two all right
okay sure um draw bowls again that's
great no okay all right don't you guys
uh that oil we got this oils oils what
is that and it's really good ruffle oil
well it's a vial of oil and it's right
do we still have a health potion oh uh
uh you have the ice the metal I do have
one wish I have one yeah okay he's like
you think Viggo
he's just a health potion ain't gonna
fix what I got lady yeah but you get it
oh it's not my little skillet kinda
helped you know it actually is relative
it's worth what okay yeah it's great I
love it oh yeah but I can totally see it
like she is with the poorest person yeah
and like she's got a thing going to
where she was hard as hell of course
it's not about to fall off a cliff
there's not like a Denarius like oh my
hey Charlotte double double or nothing
I'm into singing skull asking the one
it's cool kind of trying to clear out
you wouldn't care about the lungs but so
so the shape she took the thread a
little bit and the sack falls off of the
thread oh you
I'll go double or nothing sounds like an
F minor action okay want it I'll let it
ride all right listen okay this is it so
that that would be a bed of a hundred
well I'm leaving a hundred example yeah
and now you're ready you're ready for
another hundred to join yeah yeah Suey
can you do the presentation oh you see
this okay oh you see the just like a
like a sack of gym so you just see the
eyes of the spider just looking down and
then you see the light glinting off of
them and then you see her four legs
reach out and grab a little figurine the
golden figurine that she drops down so
sort of weaves like a little noose
around it and it drops down if you think
it's a comparable gold weight okay you
guys just went double or nothing
yeah I'm gonna ride that okay my my
compatriot is extremely learning in
these arts very familiar with sup with
items of the occult things that might
interest you he has an interesting
proposition yeah I'm down the rest of my
drink some I feel sure right so I and I
snap my fingers and I have sent velvet
out invisibly to retrieve the the
crystal ball from the cart so it's sort
so it floats in my can i grab it i go
for haha impress that now that's because
the ball has many properties but the
only one that we're certain of is that
it will permit a view of outside if
you're retired just boring old in
imagine beyond yes do you know how long
it takes for us to get anywhere I see
we're going to go somewhere whether you
enjoy it in there no I believe you and I
support this bet fantastic I think this
is a ball that does more than I said but
okay yeah I have tactical powers never
gone with the skull they sing yeah I
heard you're really really quiet like
yeah exactly
alright now this is the hell
deal for you but we'll see how this goes
mmm
I'm not like my boldness has definitely
been reduced I'm like okay I could
listen let's put this rollin let's roll
these bones see what happens okay
Thank You Volta my help with that one
hey yeah yes uh oh you know what's funny
did they give you another advantage is
yes sure did yeah I like I'll take
advantage and let's talk about how that
applies exactly exactly so advantage in
this case allows you to re-roll both die
yes okay wait okay we're good okay we're
gonna copy
he just curses at the top of his lungs
he's grabbing things is this like you
scoop up your you skip up you hear a
hiss from the chandelier yeah next time
Charlotte how's the crowd tickets like
newcomers coming in okay no this a it
like a like a tactile wave of energy
from the two dice bouncing on the table
has altered the physical properties of
this space he is in there he has picked
up the table in the goop and he is
throwing it at the wall and it's
bouncing back and forth and then he gets
it again and throws it the other way and
the bones just like I'm not a good look
for yeah yeah exactly I snatched the
locket and the crystal ball back no and
it is a new you're you you pull your way
out and then as the thing is bouncing
that void is starting to test Fillion
okay I'll give you back the crystal ball
that my locket stays with me and I open
it she is in there and she puts her hand
against what looks like the surface of
the locket does it look like a flat is
it like a picture like the air over okay
oh my god okay
mmm real quick can I attempt yeah eunuch
a with Italy do I get any intelligence
from it lock it friend seek speaks in
locket
yeah let's see it clearly telepathically
I'm gonna try aiming no when you try to
communicate with it your barrage by like
the sound of rushing water whoa uh-huh
yucky wet when I speak Russian okay hang
on I got a check today throw a dinar
blitz in here your face was really good
all right at once I want that chip oh so
so conundrum has been watching this and
he's sort of like that he's watching the
dice play he's almost like shadowboxing
like he sees the dice to music and he's
his you know hunched thoroughly drunken
village is he's gained a couple inches
of height it seems like it seems like
it's depositing even without his
incredible hat yeah like just baseline
he is looking like a million bucks I
okay you're giving back this oh yeah
this is death friend you don't want to
give this away we don't gamble it away
you hold on to this yes Pacific I need
to put my finger right on it yeah I need
to write on it he says he says Trevor do
you have a quill and he said I do have a
crew out the front desk
he took a quill assault I'm massive I'm
everyone with us Natalie feet he comes
back with a quill and ink pot and then
can undress dips the pen thanks for a
moment and then on the side of his own
phylactery he writes no bet blows on it
to dry it hands the pen back and then
you
thinks better of it gets the pen back
and then turns it around to the other
side and writes know that there as well
as mark thanks Boris nobbut nobbut yeah
that's his name yeah I love one
oh my god and so he places places it
back pushes it away and Trevor Trevor
just sort of takes in the scene of all
the people the entertainment that his
friends have brought him and his his
rowdy crew out here at the doone-gate in
big grin rollin could use a free drink I
say to the crowd large yes they line up
okay great
say they line up there is a room at the
bar the grubs are flowing not sitting
there drain it's not looking so good
even really heavily on the Mantis I know
it'll create no it's a thing where it's
just like you have like an extra half a
grub you're like I can't do it I guess
generally you get having to energy just
like kind of like spits it out and then
she's like looking for a place to put it
like you guys have to do that
I don't mind he's already there she does
it
yeah he'd rather yeah baby burn it down
but yeah but it's it's there so there's
a supply coming great again yeah you're
up there oh yeah it's a mess okay um
you're making friends buy a drink for
the spider yeah exactly
hard feelings nice harlot why does
she drink oh my god yeah something
just a bug yeah example flood it's just
explained it's like it's like one of
those novelty drinks you would get you
know what I mean it's like the kind
where you get to keep the glass yeah
it's just a big bug yeah yeah all right
loving it huh no no around throw my
friends exactly exactly like this places
you can see that Proust and his
associate they want to like slink out
but they moved like an inch every 10
minutes so he doesn't want to be here
but he can't really get out and but he
wants to feel like he's a choice he's
making
but he'll be making that choice for
several hours tonight sun drinks into
the gelatinous cube for fruits in the
skeleton guy yeah sure all right I'll do
that
yeah I was a flash and I was a ghost
that I didn't hear English drinking
music and it just floats of magic I know
so I know now Trevor so what once once
you find out what once Trevor finds out
that that's what you want to do he says
well it just happen from time to time
but he goes he gets on a stool and then
he just pours the drink on top of the
cube nice and in the Cubist that's
disgusting
it's 100% great I'm like I played two
and a half sheets a twin and I'm looking
for blessed yeah just to just bless ya
get that bless ya what hashtag shoot
what's she up to shoot Larian blessed
takes up you know those like big beanbag
chairs yeah that's the situation yeah
but she is it being back to here
basically I think she is like a giant
beanbag chair like all fur and feathers
nice you know what I mean yeah what if I
shut up shut her up yeah yeah but you
have to this someone else they're
currently okay but it's a good thing
it's a ghost you think you might be able
to you think you might still have a shot
you think you might have a shot you
might have advantages okay all right um
Oh wingman you yeah owl bear yeah the
albear wingman I can help out there oh
yeah um so I have monopolized a lot of
the role-playing here would you would
you find folks like to do some I'd love
to just at least I'm yeah hi I'm here um
you doing anything I like to just go
over to Trevor and be like just do a
little check-in yeah yeah Hey totally
hey man yeah good job thank you thank
you very much yeah you doing okay after
uh yeah yeah yeah somebody somebody
where are they they're they're from
another region
a northern region yeah how North look
you probably wouldn't know know them uh
they live there far away and then well
they're very special and they they live
very much
well my cuz I also like someone that
lives far away but she's real hey we've
all seen her alright yeah hope it's not
my girls routine
yeah both of our girls are very real
yeah shut up quite quite real yeah long
as well okay well I'm having for you
self-confidence is a portal to figuring
better things yes I don't know I'm not
gonna be a richer French seller in in an
aversion hmm he puts a massive paw on
your shoulder and he says you've been
talking about me how are you doing
you don't seem right I don't think it's
just the gross I'm very confused
conflicted trevor i did a thing that I
thought I wanted and I don't feel any
better after having done it so you know
just the agony of existence I suppose
yeah I know I heard that I hate here -
there's mortal coil ritual - it's better
way listen there's a room upstairs we
can get the official suicide done it
won't be the first time right place is
broken in well friends we're going to
leave that we'll leave that night open
use it use it as you will that is this
episode of the c-team thank you so much
shadow council as always I hope our
Labor's please you we're going to take a
four minute or so break we're going to
leverage the facilities we will come
back to you fully refreshed and ready
for tabletop
you