time is the enemy the past addresses the
fastest weapon you wouldn't make it past
a second and land the question play a
flash and reckless to choose a course in
solution you saw was prudent and any
Sepulcher polka tune will become the
putrid it's that well said I pursue in
well mountain to Steve but going to too
deep to send expended them marks up to
the top of the peak of beneath they do
they come like sharks to it while I swim
in that Barney build like olive barks
through it so send your national parks
do it I'll send them home in a natural
box the close title most of the parks
included
save your breath for a cleric confessor
that day the lesson would like to
pretend professor but if you speak in my
official advice sign on the dotted line
in list of the twice I'm Rochelle oh
hello I am Tycho Brahe hey arcade and
packs
I'm also god damnit walnut
really in no uncertain iterate so
continuity error yes very exactly I have
to ship in a full Gatorade listen okay
listen also I'm a manifest Hereward Ron
CEO of acquisition incorporated but
today I'm Jerry Hogan and I am playing a
game of Dungeons and Dragons
with my friends specifically to my right
bragging born narcissist dinar blip says
right also also also walnut dong grass
revenant natural world coming up coming
up with a pretty emotionally wrenching
arc beyond on you can check out with it
for the rest of the campaign physically
be here but you'll also be beyond beyond
to my left not your grandma's grandma
Rosie be stinger and I got I've got
important news I've just gotten the
results you are the mother oh oh
cher beat here be singer
start dancing exactly I mean my Lewis
incredible creator joining us at the
table filling in for Chris drab so
exactly he can emerge from miss clouds
but he can also apparently recede into
the fifth cloud that's know also it's
the thing to happen right yeah so when
last we saw our heroes they were on
their way south specifically to the
barge right doc between the bars right
and ferd are you go what what are you to
talk about what happened last week oh
yeah no it's gonna happen it's gonna
happen no it was pretty cool it's pretty
cool and that'll give us a chance to get
share caught up as well but on the way
south one of your first jobs took place
at a at a venue called the doone-gate in
which was at that time operated by
sambar blood drinker a larper of the
highest order
indeed he and his coven LARP so well
that they attracted the ire of authentic
vampire hunters and they were no longer
able to iterate their prized hobby
because they were liquefied it's a
danger of LARPing - like indeed in that
you want a toast to death interaction or
what - you gotta there have to be you
know there has a verisimilitude there
has to be like a pause button on it yeah
you know as soon as the swords come out
but you also met a teen werewolf named
Trevor who was you know at a rough he
was sort of at a crossroads he was at a
rough period a rough patch he got some
good advice from Walnut dawn grass this
allowed him to seek out and sort of
become a new person with the help of the
party he's now operating the doone-gate
in and which has become an inn not for
weary travelers but for weary creatures
of various kinds that don't quite fit in
anywhere else it is a strange menagerie
that the party walked into
ghosts and their own skeletons playing
games inside of gelatinous cubes witches
that hadn't gambled away their
phylacteries spiders that so scarves
from silk it was an action-packed venue
obviously novel snacks in the form of
the occasional grub 6 topic a chick job
yeah yeah I never spending a single coin
on drinks but more than happy to go wild
on these grubs mm-hmm for perhaps five
bullets of grubs in is sitting they just
walked out our grubs complimentary does
no oh yeah oh yeah that's our that's our
do I say that's the deal pack their
complimentary but they are not free you
know what I mean I do yeah so that's the
that's the news from Lake Wobegon or
whatever the Pharaon equivalent is sure
the very last thing that happened you
tell me if I am wrong a Rosie B singer
you were trying to get on a an al bear
yeah accurate yeah bless and you know I
don't want to kiss and tell I
mean obviously let me just go into it
we're talking about a beak you know what
I mean they talk about that yeah boy a
pig no no I mean a beak and to die for
she had what eight feet on me holy yeah
just just you know run a few shin-hye
yeah after you in ya know you just lose
yourself it's like a like a waterbed you
know what I mean would you label up now
and go I know what that won't go back
explain on the cab on the way here is
destiny I mean if you you're just
and you just sink into that downy
feathers yeah I mean what happens next
obviously that's fifty I also I will say
we tried to make it work anatomically
speaking yeah but there's there are
certain things that an owl bear and a
halfling just like can't make work bow
their best and we ended up having a
really lovely conversation yeah exactly
like you were able you were able to find
sort of that that crossroads right here
because it was talons
yeah it's battle gesture it's like that
everybody knows that one oh yeah yeah
dorms very private for you
I know it's rosie got up on al bear and
we're going to ask what good up on means
but I don't know what I'm going to
remember this I'm gonna bring it up
later I know it's what you thought it's
what you thought at first yeah listen
that's you know if you ever come back
and play with us again yeah you're gonna
see that there's a team you know what I
mean hey I didn't have all these kids
out of thin air
yeah yeah I mean you know I played two
together eventually yeah exactly you
know more siblings kept showing us yet
you you wouldn't look bigger than anyone
else
I have you seen it firsthand but morning
has broken at the doone-gate in it's
basically you know party central around
here overtime is still going
it doesn't stop of what happens is it
you know when the when the evening
starts to roll around you start getting
those those you know a certain clientele
and then you have the nocturnal
clientele the solely nocturnal clientele
right and then you got people who are
waking up when the Sun is out
blueberry special you know what I mean
like there's a there's a there's always
another cadre sort of sweeping through
you think Trevor must be making a
killing in here except for the
occasional you know teetotaler thry
cream it seems like coins er seems like
coins are coming in he is he is serving
an underserved market um sorry targeted
a demographic I kicked this off by
saying that walnut laid in bed last
night wondering if karmically they had
offset all the other things they had
done by how much good they had done for
all of these we were folk suppose you
can get in but eventually she found
sleep so I guess so yes it like still
uncleaned up blood like in like the most
like yeah it was just like that's not a
copper in here everywhere why she just
like to see Scott all the time this is
your tongue on a battery like that the
entire second floor anyway downstairs
looking at her not watch as she has
tapping her wrists as if that motion
means something
fantasy world being like we gotta go
yeah chop-chop usually Rosie wakes up
very early and I'm style does her
exactly usually up before the Sun and
hanging out coriander or doing morning
kind of like Tai Chi type rituals but
she rollin out a little later today
little Lola unkempt and yes with a very
minimal
it's just down felt down and she's she's
smiling but she should give bless
meaningful like a pat on the belly and
they they part ways
just that zone and that's enough yeah I
mean you you meant you know Mary part
yeah you know we have very meet again
exactly exactly so uh lucky this yeah
there is a at the front desk as soon as
as soon as you are seen to exit and come
down the stairs and begin behaving it in
patient entering my pulse exactly on the
on the top of the bones it's a new
system maybe look at maybe like a chime
you are handed an envelope by a creature
without a mouth then you don't 100%
recognize the genus and you were also
given a pouch that jingles with weight
as its said and it is a letter from
Chris wrist robe he says that he regrets
that he had to leave without warning but
that he will meet you on the Horde as
soon as he is able and here we did
another betrayal from this camera thank
you you know one was just like uh yeah
so based on everything their their
conversations thus far one that's like
yeah okay this guy's got a got up mmm
doesn't going on without unreal this is
just like another tick in there I'm
going with yes
yeah what's in the pouch yeah so what's
in the pouch she looks yeah exactly
you have to count it but you're curious
enough to do so as the document sir
you peel through there are
our two hundred gold pieces daddy that
loved us are allowing William as the
horse as a horrid Iverson Tyson yeah as
an orange person he left he left some
wealth what's the party time sloth like
I'm not even I'm not even supposed to be
handling them I'll solve it all right
I'm the interim hoards person 200 gold
pieces for me
exactly I walk downstairs just with all
my money come on yeah I'm sorry okay
sick with yeah like Oh was like 200
bucks that's cute
what'd you get I was obviously - no -
with like winning these life-changing
objects so uh 250 super here on top of
what I already had hanging
cleaning my tooth third corner well
since you have more money you get feed
coriander yeah it was the point I was
obscure I was waiting for the place that
glory don't hold me a glossy abdomen
that is sort of attached to the
chandelier as you as you were as you
were walking out you take notice of it
remembering your victories at the
gambling table and you get a little
salute from one of the pet helps well
played hmm no hard feelings significant
but about a gallon of toxic slime no
yeah well that's the expected I get a
handful of coins we just your stupid
horse yeah a significant grant our asked
Trevor do we owe you anything from last
night
we could do we well we settled up as
well let me put it to you this way
occasionally there are creatures that do
enter the establishment that have
problems I can't solve problems that
don't that don't go nowhere after a good
night's sleep
hmm I'd like to tell a feeling like that
that I know somebody who could help
Trevor we are extremely down you just
let us know Trevor you let us know the
instant you need our services puts it
puts it right in there you can see
slides it in yeah says Trevor
slide the card right into the Trevor
pouch this will think you'll be sad to
see you go but it'll be nice to see you
again
we'll be back don't worry hi Trevor I
coriander starving gotta put her down
yeah oh she's a she is a mortal now
because I got a bit that honest after
the sixth gold coin six after the sixth
gold coin she seems to be satisfied and
gives you tries to give you a nuzzle
even they even they don't reciprocate
music oh it's just like trying to kill
of it to turn it for them level on now I
push her face hard away from me every
coin cheats I just get like more
insulting looking horse goddamn
horse
stop eating free this is a long pause
after five yeah nobody's open oh yeah I
start pulling away - come on but you're
just trying to do just trying to get
right into the next own just trying to
give you a little nudge the lib no no si
happening you know no no you know my
Mike
I love happens when you bring things
back to life unnatural yeah I mean
you're an abomination
you're a Mel abomination you're eating
all my money I've never met face it I
will be the one that kills you again
it's just like I don't like you I don't
feed it will it die can I start it
what happened because are running
through my head yeah crying hurts
already girl if we don't get or get it
wet we're never going to find out okay
we're going to know yeah yeah you jump
jumbo card customary locations yeah for
the party even more spacious in Hunter
here without any warlocks you know what
I mean
that's a huge that's a huge relief a
scratch out
oh yeah it's a huge space saving me and
Kathy here in the back oh yeah
right on there and you and you you can
get a very nice you know here's the
issue this has been the issue in the
past
is that you pull the curtains closed but
the natural motion of the card is always
sending no matter where you try to sleep
there's always this golden shaft of
light unwelcome you know what I mean and
intermittent like you can't get used to
it
yeah Cappy slides right down that moist
slup yeah fix for nap oh yeah then I
don't have like a weird growl leering at
me that nice that's nice 24/7 yeah even
though you know is doing their Lear eyes
closed but you can feel it I sleep and
he sort of hovers over I assume my eyes
are closed but you can feel it yeah feel
it yeah undressing me no no anyways and
it's the sort of thing that enters into
one's dreams yeah oh yeah you watch what
kind of dreams do you get with Kathy or
on your head all the time
you didn't think like mushroom based
yeah you'd be right no we're done Eric
Engel
yeah okay you're just right in the web
yeah yeah up on top I'm driving you're
driving coriander I mean this is this
has been the first couple times like
this is really the third trip you've had
a chance to take with corriander 2.0 yes
tell me about her upgrades a performance
life look at a horse power we dealing
with now accurate okay after I make
those noises when I'm mad at myself I'm
about 11 exactly because there's a type
of happiness that you don't like my kids
good oh god that's so coriander 2.0
whose ultimate coriander a Android I'm
like in cilantro cilantro is very
tasteful as well but the the main thing
that you notice is that coriander was
not really up to pulling this cart
very well previously yeah that that's
the main thing you notice is that this
must be what it's like if a horse is
matched to its task ah coriander
coriander did her best but there was a
lot of there was there was clearly an
enthusiasm perhaps even an enthusiasm
for you that allowed her to manage that
along with the occasional druid spell to
bust the strength but yo yo exactly but
the coriander is is a horse you can be
proud Oh wonderful my little metal freak
mm all right well I'm still up atop
telling her stories like she's not made
of metal implants now she's still
getting the the most basic rose would be
singer life story yeah like still going
where we barely hit the team so she's
got she's got a lot going and you guys
can be interested probably because it's
alright yeah it's so great you're
missing so much backstory on backstory
that you doesn't want it right here in
front of you making a meal yeah yeah but
we know the way to UM to barge right
yeah I'm a teen film and WOM fir'd yeah
it needs between the barge right in well
the end that's that not film okay you
need okay I don't know okay so if we do
that we go there okay again just south
along the long road starts to curve to
the east barge right in is present
you've moved directly through that small
Enclave and then you can see even in the
distance you can see what looks like a
large ship and it only gets larger the
closer you get well absolutely but it
seems big from back here and then it
continues to impress with its internal
volume you can see that it's it's clear
that this is not a minor stop for this
vessel it's clearly being is visit quite
the operation underway here
to restock this pleasure barge you can
see lizard folk directing traffic
directing carts like full carts up into
the guts of the horse right and so we
should take a moment to sort of detail
what type of vessel we're looking at
here sir so imagine imagine in North
with a classic riverboat style sort of
block multi-deck block of seagoing
prowess now
imagine that there is a water wheel in
the back that turns but draped over this
massive wheel is a gigantic wooden tail
that goes over the top and you can see
coming up from that tail there our
spines almost like a Stegosaurus spines
on the tail cap it comes up there's
three on each side and as you get closer
you can see that these have windows and
liver and O's on them
so it's this is this you don't know
about the rest of the lodgings that are
contained inside this vehicle but you
can tell that they are there is they
have an aspiration for a very very high
level clientele okay on this craft those
seem like the luxury that we got here
that's your guess and they are
substantial ok but as I said you can
tell there's definitely multi deck
structure but you know in terms of it
like the outer walkway there really is
just one main one that goes around you
can see them being brushed and swept and
like I said it's substantial enough that
entire cards full of supplies are just
wheeled straight up and into this vessel
then the closer you get to the front you
can begin to see that it perfectly
mirrors a dragon's body so that tail is
draped over that wheel and then just
beyond that or two haunches
once on each side there ha ha family
show funny when you launch yeah so the
face that launched a thousand ships so
remember we say haunch a lot and really
huh so imagine the tail comes back and
then the two rear legs sort of go around
the front sort of Bend around the front
and the wheels contained there so the
whole body sort of looks like it's
clutching they sort of look down thing
as it floats in the water and you can
see that each of a massive dragon on the
front of the ship and in its mouth
from left to right all the way all the
way around the front of the ship you can
see in an elaborate stained glass
construction it's all tall triangles
almost like a almost almost like glass
teeth hmm sort of go around the front
and then the closer gets to the front
there's more inner structure to support
it geometrically okay you can see that
you know even up beyond that you can see
the dragon's eyes and you think you
might actually see people in there
somewhere
sounds like a Disney cruise or it's a
themed cruise there it has character
dining
um don't see those with that I will
believe well the character the dragon
yes well normal is also very good leave
me here
it's the mouth of the Dragon Tama like
ah did them at you that the mouth is
definitely open but it's the entire open
part of the structure is plastered
completely with these interlocking glass
triangles okay is there a pool
oh there may be a pool in sight away
vital yeah you want a boot boogie board
yeah okay okay it looks really good
so cenar as our burliest
I think that you should probably the one
be the one to find the security detail
job that we are applying for it's true
okay we have to go find the person we're
reporting to yeah okay who is a boot I
don't know if we had a name now posted
by the dragon stores River growing house
of chance yeah the whole boat but I want
to point out this might be easier
because the dress not here however they
said that's a river going gambling
parlor demands equally tasteful
protection so right we just all be on
our best behavior
understood no problem is it really well
by the docks
yeah exactly I look for the foreman I
say yes make man yeah we're the boss
great I mean yeah he is Kia's currently
you try to introduce this piece of
information into this system and you are
not yet a part of this system you can
see people being people are lined up
almost like in a military line and
they're being upgraded by a lizard man
who is just some of them he's trying to
make adjustments trying to bring them in
line with what they require even just
visually and some are not able to do it
some are very very small okay and
they're not allowed on so I'm yelling
hey you stupid snake person I'm here to
talk to your boss and they're just not
responding
I can't believe how rude Disco's yeah
it's weird it's really surprising comes
on rude okay grandma bar yeah I don't
know if there if I can do much better
but can I use perception to try to
figure out someone who looks like
they're in charge yes yes with some
eight it sucks
yes I know okay no this is it you try to
perceive this and you end up looking
completely somewhere else
okay you can see you can see a hassling
woman walking up so like I say there's
large you know bridge style paths that
entire carts can be pulled up into to
restock but there are also an assortment
of smaller foot bridges that have been
laid out for people to board and their
their passage is being checked you can
see a half some women check it and she's
sort of obscured behind it and then she
passes beyond the ticket taker and she
has two instrument cases with her and
she is your daughter
[Laughter]
okay I'm I sometimes I have a lot of
kids so I make I make sure because this
has happened before
like no no that's definitely her that's
that's her you guys your head my dick
sure sure sure
oh very very fancy oh yeah Wow
what what are you doing here is it so
great I'm currently an understudy as of
the war loot there's a performance on
the ship and so I'm you know and you
know on the cruise like this in case of
infirmity you know I I ran out of
statement but the lights on the left
when I got a letter from you you are
still in Barnes College I think yes is
my first paid job so tied mother a gig
the big moto exciting night is my
daughter's share she is my my first
generation she is a your 100 yes your
you are looking so good for a hundred
but it's been a very long time since
I've seen her and I'm really excited to
have you guys get to meet my daughter
share she is just very talented she
played at my 100th birthday party 20
years ago and she wrote a whole song it
took 25 minutes to play but it was it
was beautiful and I everyone loved it
and and she's just she's just wonderful
and the wonderful thing about the
or loot is it's got the retractable
blade on the top and so then we carved
up a foul that's true yes sure our tea
was really actually it's true is there's
so many uses for for a war loot I'm so
proud of you there was one debuff like
very uncanny is she related to every
hassling ever values me yeah well dream
Lee racist people scary likely but
racist you can't okay beautiful cam my
work associates and I are here to Rancho
become where your forehead signatories
we are we're here to you know just run
security you know way to say it's a it's
a job where they they hire the the
strongest toughest most fearsome people
so you know and I get Mike yeah I get my
little jacked
granny arm out it's like it's ripped up
but it's taught it's because it's so
like there's us all tendons but I just
show you my you know Oh mother I'm
familiar check out the work at my lute
playing arms oh look at the lute playing
arms do you see that so much sinew is
what's us it's the best for playing the
lute and for kicking but but yeah that's
where we're oh I know it looks like you
need to board the ship but when's your
performance can come so some finding
well only if some the the headliner of
is it but how do you pronounce the name
is it Varma Lu ta I think final appear
if she falls ill then it's entirely warm
but she's really one of one of the
Great's one of the great war league
players okay well you at least get
treated to her performance who's really
wonderful never heard of her
while I was like rummaging through her
pockets watching oh I didn't take you
for a connoisseur of the War of the
Worland I I'm not I'm not I just like
well you'll have to catch one of
barman's performances yeah she's she
played she plays so beautifully that she
could I reckon she could walk right up
to you and just cut her arm off big
performance and you wouldn't notice how
you went to applause
she's SSSs she says she does she does
sound perfect doesn't say we
no brahma right like we remember team
Bellerophon did we know her name though
we I mean yeah we haven't named roster
then we got the nice we got names from
everyone from proper right Oh prophet
okay so we know who this is
you understand Brahma okay okay I'm
going to still just play like I don't
remember though I feel like she sounds
mate doesn't even like she says really
come on
I would really love that but we should
go we should actually maybe you can help
us get inside we're trying to oh right
did the job we are trying to run
security but we can't find a foreman can
you point us in the right direction kind
of like you absolutely I mean basically
right down there you can see you can see
a extremely muscled lizard man as I said
before just sort of going along a line
of people and then either like gesturing
them up on the ship or putting up a hand
about checking up on the ship hand hand
okay it's like duck duck goose but for
your livelihood okay so he clearly
hiring folks so we should go get in that
line we should go get let's find each
other later okay so I'm good that's good
awesome okay right and you as part and
parcel of your task here on the dragon's
hoard gambling house chance you have not
the premium room now but you do have a
room and board on the vessel in a sort
of the common quarters downstairs yes
very good exactly like it coming come it
comes with and if you're not given cliff
you're not called upon just if it's just
a vacation yeah just a windowless like a
yeah yeah we're something works again
crazy bono soda Gators like okay so guys
let's go get in line I think they're
picking the security folks out right now
so we need to go get down there and as
walnut said let's see beautiful Yeah
right right okay so what do you lose
you're so considered tasteful um can I
roll history check on that
yeah sure hi that's a natural 20 yeah
actually oh yeah remarried at this time
because
that natural funny yeah oh well you
accept charges that's not a professional
name I remember shadow council mayor
Labor's pays you your servant Rosie bee
stinger has a delivery jeweller reward
you got that under control
marvelous no this entire this entire
scenario is an aberration from what you
know about lizard folk oh they are
intensely secretive you know often you
know often in the sway of grim deities
the idea that there would be a an envoy
that was not that did not parlay at the
tips of swords this is this is this is
new okay like this is a historical to
have manufactured or commissioned to be
manufactured a vessel like this like
public life integrating into the greater
society this is this is new for this is
new for for lizard focus you know it and
follow-up question do weathered folk
tend to appreciate dragons enough to
build a boat in their likeness they have
a particular fondness and reverence for
dress okay do that but that's in
character okay
you'll so these are just these are just
some lizard folks who decided that like
time to make some cash and we've to get
in there the stern bell
yeah the lizard folk yeah yeah okay they
have a they have a you know it makes
perfect sense why it would be okay great
except it's very unusual okay so what I
know about lizard folk is tasteful means
strong tough ready to do battle so like
I know bare your teeth you might maybe I
don't know if you feel like it but like
a bear nut
oh honey nut might might get them going
I don't have much but like negative arms
I have
hi thank you so much money I could spend
with shoulders and we could put a cape
over the two of us and we could just be
a very tall person get a lot of options
here so but we go times wastin okay
exactly so I say so he's he's getting to
the end of of his current crop of
adherence yeah all right let's run away
yeah I'm holding up the imaginal not a
badge acronym incorporated I'm like here
all right help here for a security
detail
yeah there we go plenty there it sees
you in one of those point points a claw
of his weight on the deck I go assesses
you well I guess I like glower her most
darkly and like you have your sword yeah
he laughs he does the full walnut
assessment seize seize the blade and the
the pommel makes a note you you eyebrow
and he directs you ask and then when he
sees you he has to look down
substantially right I smile and then he
holds his hand up excuse me I'm with
them actually were connected as a group
you're this big I'm a little bigger than
that thank you very much okay you're
this big how much you got grandma its
security she's disguised eyes I am I'm
disheartened that it would come to a
gatekeeping experience that you okay so
you have emotional issues also require
okay you require a show of prowess you
may get your negative three points so
far there's a point system yeah you're
losing right now I think it starts at
zero okay cool
well then I guess I'll just attack him
I I love it let's see what my role is
him our shy to go oh yeah we would
definitely real initiative okay he knows
his way all right sorry you two I want
to mention that the three of us are like
up on like I don't know oh my god Renee
like intervene and like nobody was nice
that's a 15-2 initiative so like I'm
seeing here I have a 13 so you are okay
okay right yeah so he is basic right
yeah like a tree made out of muscles
like this is a this is a person who
hurts people professionally okay you
know what I mean well yeah yeah how is
he heavily armored but no he is not
I didn't say in fact he has very very
simple garb okay all right I want to
make it very clear as I'm lifting ready
myself I'll make it very clear that this
is just a demonstration
yeah and expect this is a demo mode yeah
this should not be attempted unless you
are professional and perfect this is
this is not intended to hurt you but I
could you up if I wanted to and so
I'm going to go ahead and and do my my
my good my fancy little bit of
which is the 1 2 3 ok oh I know what
this is and I'm going to I'm going to
I'm going to really like play it up in
you're in the theater of the mind
everybody but like imagine her just like
adding a bunch of like flourishes and
what
Jeff spent but like doesn't yeah huh she
doesn't need to but it's more
frightening to start this away this
thing yeah like you do that with a
disadvantage place almost Oh Jefferson
okay okay okay okay okay so that's a 23
and that's what lucky yes that's what 13
okay no these are beautiful he's not
Anna Lee armor okay okay dexterous but
he's not heavily armored okay so then
I'm going to I'm just going to keep
going I don't even want to roll damage
on him okay
like yeah totally it's not an image you
can track this many you like okay okay
so this one is power rules this one
around up very small I've come around
and whacked him in the back of the knees
exactly and then connect recall that
anytime the staff of the master strikes
yeah it disorients opponents okay your
melee strikes become da facility six
right so while he was disoriented I'm
going to punch him in like each of his
butt cheeks launches right into
conscious um so that what each but just
about hunch and that's a a disparate
hunch 24 to 15 did you do this available
punch arise around the tail just pop pop
in the but that's all I can reach right
in the bird yeah yeah and I know my
daughter's watching so yes I want to see
it have the staff connects you've
cranked the theatrical aspects of this
right and then you've delivered to rump
strikes right and that way with with
precision right so clearly pulled
punches right this is this is just like
the attract mode at the arcade crack
right and I'm going to leap back in
front of them placidly
yes so he I think they're going to let
me under the to hunch that the two
punches destabilize his rump oh you know
what I mean yeah yeah so he bit he falls
forward on its on his knees and he's on
oh jeez I'm sorry I'm sorry
hands are done here I want to help I
want to reach out
up up and then you see you see like you
see his back arch and you see that he
like he starts to sort of vibrate almost
and then you hear him nice okay okay
good yeah he uses up on one hand thumbs
up I like you I'm on about
G cos my car dislocated but it's my
special move
look out potentially in but city has an
she has a maneuver so you are you are
massing up here on this single layer of
this gigantic
draconic money cake that the lizard folk
are operating under the guys over
options horde and ii you can see that
the other people who have been who you'd
previously seen in the line they're sort
of all congregating in this area and it
is at about this time that you see three
lizard folk emerge from the central core
of this establishment but one of them
clearly designated as a higher rank than
the rest is like much more in terms of
jewelry and then the textiles main
evidence thread-count
oh yeah it's just a superior version of
everything his satellites are trying to
execute and failing so they take you in
and they give you a tour of the facility
that you will be helping out with so the
first thing that you see as you enter
the boat proper is you sort of come in
at the ground floor you can see that
there the ceiling here is lower than it
is out near the front of the boat and
leading up to this glass crawl is a sort
of two tiered stage
and you you're familiar with this a
two-tiered stage and at the top it has
there's some kind of artifact there so
that there's something significant on
the stage already you have to be closer
to see what it is but ringed around this
you're going to Triple Door yeah yeah of
course ring around these two stages are
seating there's plenty of individual
tables plenty of seats and but down that
ramp and out here are various gambling
tables all of them ready to roll and you
can you can see you can see that they're
ready to start taking money from people
the moment they get on like the very
entrance is already ready to go your
handlers take you up to the flat part at
the top of that stage and you're welcome
to examine yeah what this is but as you
get you get here you can see what was
giving you the sense of it there is a
sort of faint glow emanating up from a
very exacting diagram that has been
inscribed into the platform itself I
want to take a peek at that you do a
little perception here ah 15 I'm 14 I've
got a book yes it's I mean this is - no
I mean it's like a laser did it wizard
this day doing it on the right yeah this
is definitely some business some wizard
going on wasn't up the asker
people that are with us yeah I think
what's that about yeah - a teleportation
circle VIPs only
Fleming it means if you spend enough in
this casino will teleport you in
somewhere wherever you want it's worth
it for us to do huh
so but from this he I was almost no
speech he's just sort of flex directing
your attention to different things and
it may be that multiple languages are
spoken by this group but it's pretty
profound tree you can see that from this
stage you can look up and there are two
separate layers above as well all and
both of them have view to the stage so
all of this around here the big big
Tadeo
massive um everything around here on the
base tables dining area and then two
separate layers above and you can tell
the finery like either there's clearly
like a gambling caste system at play
here you know what I mean all the high
rollers oh yeah I'm going to right there
literally high rollers here around from
the side two staircases go up and they
allow you access to this but in order to
get access to the very top that's
actually physically guarded by people at
least as large as the lizard man you
impressed out front
that's an established location how many
of levels of High Roller E are we
talking there's a high there's a high
high level of rollory at the very top
and then as a tier down there this sort
of exists it's nicer than the ground
floor okay but it's not may no is not
actively sure physically guarded we have
by guards and weapons like Paul Grande
then yeah exactly that's very well put
it's very well put and then he sort of
guides you to the next area with his
shoulder below the stage itself there is
some access that goes beneath the stage
and this is where you can already see
waiters bringing out the silverware and
platters getting this place ready
you go straight down through there that
gives you access to the kitchen he takes
you from the kitchen through an area
that is clearly where the waitstaff
stays that looks like it's not there's
not very many of them is it clearly
distinct from the rest back behind that
there is a sort of open ish area that
has a very large column in the very
center the rest of it is open that sort
of goes up some consuming structural
behind that you go into basically a a
largely open area that it seems like
many of the crew basically live in
community they live together and you can
also see in the very center what clearly
must be the Volt so they sleep you know
more than a hundred physically around
the Volt Wow how big assault the vault
itself is probably thirty feet on a side
in the center you see more of what you
might call lizard sure literally we
asked about that little sure what's
up with that with your chest don't touch
it I won't what does it do it keeps
people from touching it I think I look
at the fuel-injection I know um in order
to adequately perform our services I
need to I need to have a visual on the
object that we are protecting I need to
or - what - whatever it is you want us
to you to protect I need to I need to
physically see it just that's it the
vault place what's inside it gold and
gems I need to see them Tyrion said
is something so it's a very special
power that she has it actually works
extremely well it's just a specific
druid thing it's just this sounds like
wizard yeah I've enough stuff in
unfortunately I wish I had more of it
myself but that's why we keep her around
tell me exactly what you intend to do I
merely need you to open the vault I need
to look at what's inside it and I need
to muster the amount of energy it's
going to take to protect this within
myself and it is I just need to see
inside it just a moment one second I
will happily roll it works like a charm
I've never seen anything like it
huh he says absolutely not but you're
welcome to try to persuade I will I will
try this I will of course I don't have
any other useful skills useful skills
they should be you can be a queen just
like a sweet little single sweetie yeah
me I'm going to the Vanderburgh no no
and I don't want to try and charm him
because it's going to be trying it just
can't just creates problems does it why
don't ever worked out for me um yeah
I'll see if I guess I mean a 16 it's
pretty good I merely need to take stuff
inventory that's it one one second she
doesn't even need to go in I just need
to look okay he says stand over there
I'm Stangl where you can sort of see in
a crack of the door he goes over to it
and cups his hands by the key cold and
whispers into it and they says I'm going
to regret this I know it it spins a
crank and then opens it up a crack right
there is gold in there do I see anything
outstanding in there there is so much
gold through this crack there's got to
be corners and this thing that you can't
see but it is
it looks like a diorama just like
castles made out of gold do I see any
gem of a mint sighs no you know I you
don't see any particular Jim okay
well I was like okay yep sure whoops yes
oh yeah I know exactly how to protect us
yeah I got it lock and key hmm because
you're clearly like not impressed by
more gold than anyone has ever seen yes
yeah okay you're a thing exactly
so he leaves you he leads you back sort
of up the mechanism behind this communal
area there are some stairs that come up
in the back
you are now behind the lower the gaming
floor opposite side this is where the
rest look the standard quarters are like
not the not the premium not the premium
economy spirit yeah I mean it's it's
basically these are the rooms that sort
of exist people pay in their space don't
wear fiddle playing like where the wheel
is and you can you can see it being
maintained you can see like their rods
and pistons that move underneath that
layer is this intended to be where we're
staying
these are the rooms that are provided
yes I'm saying - yeah sure it's better
run some that's right
no is the vault below us right now I'm
just their vault this yeah yeah okay
other ways to get into this room down
just drill through the floor what's
beneath the vault water are you asking
him yeah rods and pistons that guide the
waterwheel and then the river this one
alternate ways into that room we're
expected to protect a room there's more
than one way into the door a lot of the
security that we're going to require is
going to be on the floor of the vault
the vault is only one source of of
problems and as you see
my brothers can probably handle this and
share down here with us are you
unpacking that no no and in fact as you
emerge up your guide is about to show
you the Suites that go that are behind
the high roller area that's the spike
Suites exactly what candy exactly the
the sort of spikes that come up off the
tail
yeah it links please spikes but as
you're being led out into the common
area you can see you can see cher coming
in here - probably deposit instruments
I'll leave it up to you sir you know I
carry them everywhere that's true
that's you we're in the middle of
getting a tour are you are you working I
don't I don't bother you I don't work
basically unless Varma dies so oh I did
okay good for a while um it's I believe
her name is Brahma Oh what what what
again it's all right how much mother
that's okay
I heard her name mentioned in passing
once uh and I haven't had in mind for
name Fujino well we are about to get a
tour of the High Roller area if you feel
like tagging along on my wood yeah
otherwise I just sleep under a bunch of
Pistons why was that over such a kind of
a good opportunity I mean it sure is not
working anyway because obviously Brahma
is going to play and we don't have our
usual fourth member and you did say you
just went to school for the war loot I
would never put my daughter in line of
fire unless she's super duper wanted to
and then she kick ass sorry I said I
mean I'm only going off of what I
learned last time from Grievous just
don't get me started on drew they met
Rivas don't get me started on drew this
what's not what so everybody nice nice
Oh poison myself - yeah I do now Lawson
thought yeah that's right actually that
guy and I just
okay definitely I'll start tugging it
somewhere Apple okay so we're going to
add I'm going to have my daughter who's
also part of our security detail
she's she's already been vetted okay
great she's got a Jenna exactly um
that's a badly for her my pictures on
and everything yeah yeah why I'm not
painting your lights your go really must
work
this is good I learned about watching
you love it yeah hmm that's right so
you're their lead again from here down
through the main floor gambling area to
see the stage in the distance your lead
of the staircase through here he nods
the guards nod and you're able to go
back through a set of golden doors and
these golden doors open into a set of
staircases that's split in the middle
and go two ways down and you can see
that every every so often every 150 feet
or so there's another door another exit
and then these stairs continue downward
but there it's all well-lit key or
anything like that like everything is
everything is immaculate in this area
all the finest touches you know brass
handles hmm took a Millie I can you Dom
what is what the doors look like the
doors themselves yeah the doors
themselves all have as I said the brass
handle but they have a lock over them
okay and he says that guests are given a
key they call a magic word and so no one
else can access a given room without the
magic word okay each room has its own
magic word each room has its own magic
word okay if a guests were to get locked
out of a magic there they forget their
magic mirrors choose the magic word okay
let's say you've had a little too much
to drink on the floor and you forget
your magic word who we send them to to
like get their magic word reset if if it
ends up being something like that
um send for me what's your name mellow
for mellow for I liked your wink yeah
just email us or we'll handle that
little stuff okay
what's another four I barely know
opening doors I don't know okay and
these presumably are the the spike room
doors that we saw before
yes these are our exclusive okay is
there these the two-tiered areas into
the stage yeah this is right here you've
actually gone behind so those dead set
of golden doors that is of the high road
area and it can very easily see it but
this area with these rooms is actually
back behind closed behind the doors on
each side into them so room so they're
on this the haunches yeah how many how
many arrange how many rooms back here um
each of the spines appears to have two
rooms in it
okay so total of like eight yeah also
lead okay eight rooms and do these all
have occupants for this particular leg
of the journey
ah he's just that's not mine that's not
something I know okay so an atomically
what section of the dragon i or brahma
performing in yeah there's basically
right it's orange Alton okay okay now
that my mouth region itself is where the
stage in the teleportation circle are
okay cool is there anything else yeah
they say so
no yeah there is as you've been led
around at various junctures other
lizard-men
come and take people away there's
something about this process of leading
people around it is only the four of you
left in the original group that had come
through there people are failing some
kind of a test
oh you think interesting okay so just
silently wordlessly they're just being
dragged away until you've been asking
questions and now it is only before
and then metaphors can tell us that a
candy factory is ours now
yes Columbus mill augustus Gloop their
young okay go like Columbus I like
attitude one this should be a thing hey
can we say to the guy like where did
everyone go
there's more than this when we started
what do we need the best no you got it
meeting I ran the other three team just
a like below no one harumph
there is a there is a start like that
you can feel the boats or lurch for a
second oh and then here back here on the
tail you can sort of feel it's just
gentle it's not it isn't jarring anyway
but there's but there the wheels started
to move I got back here so what kind of
security it sounds like we're going to
be on the floor with the performers and
the gambling is that the kind of thing
where you just want us roaming around
making sure nothing bad is happening is
there a particular thing we're supposed
to be guarded no will will direct you
where it's needed
okay many of these situations of course
we can handle ourselves but they're
going to be situations where a different
approach may be required than we're
accustomed to
to be at walkie-talkies or anything to
be able to communicate zones yeah yep
engine is TC he says you want to try to
be you want to try to be in view of me
or one of my other tenants and we'll be
communicating with you that way okay so
are we expected to be like plain clothes
like secret no it's vitally important
that you look just as you look now I'd I
want I want people to understand that
there is a sword on retainer
all right a lot of money moves through
here
great results super vague Hey everything
about this gambling done money the
pursuit of more money the paying money
to lose money on a boat you know what
what Greg as I hate the wreckage the
trying shape yeah any time we mention
the stage or look at the stage it is
very subtle but she like it's like her
muscles tighten a little bit and she
just kind of like was found and it's
like like like as if she's willing
herself not to like turn red at all it's
just very to her but it's very subtle
nobody can definitely and they got like
a really bad stomachache it is best
under normal kind of fatty corn on the
way over here the water officials it's a
classic scowl yes I'm normally a you
smell bit over Rome is a one last
question for you reckon we find Brahma
Luce tonight oh whoa that's not I mean
we're just here to I just wanna I just
want to shake her hand and let her know
I'm excited about the performance yeah
yeah he says he says listen I need you
watching the floor okay
other people on the floor now that here
you're still sort of moving out from the
two high road area he's leading you down
the stairs and as you lead as you're
going down the stairs people are now
coming up the stairs
okay maybe they deposited their their
materials in their rooms um I would like
to a second her question I'm actually
playing a ballute tonight I have no I'm
not give me a good tonight I'm a bronze
understudy when will she be performing
tonight uh she has not yet arrived
oh she's probably gonna use a teleporter
if we are as I suggested previously I'm
not sure if you were here the the
teleportation circle is for our VIP
guests
and someone like Brahma Ludi a student
of Audra courrier ah is it is worth the
materials to teleport somebody but not
her incredibly talented understudy
you wouldn't teleport her understudy no
she's 10 times as good as Brahma okay I
don't know that yet yeah sorry
you burned off I know this maybe you
should rethink your policy once you get
a chance to listen to her once that
Brahma or whoever gets on stage and
makes an ass of herself then you'll be
able to hear the the real thing yeah he
says lady you up you up
how's that now we're going to hear what
she can play great well I'm going to
listen to it yeah and you're gonna be
embarrassed I think so I guarantee you
would you like to make a wager on that
sir this is the right place well I have
license I have a jar Bible
yeah are you guys like no you're gonna
bet on something I do yeah yeah tell me
you weren't moved I was my $2 head room
I had if you have a goal and you said I
would be embarrassed I'll be 200 gold
sad not beerus uh Kermit afar seconds is
for a head not the bacon is making
you're still got money okay okay all
right now vote her where's my daughter
where's your where's my in
your room okay can I go back and get it
or am I just supposed to go okay tell us
yeah Rosie will drop off beat
okay so first what I do I have a couple
can trips I'd like to cast to set the
stage for this performance
I would like to cast minor illusion to
get sort of a stage fog and sort of you
know laser disc going so yeah miss into
the light closer to the stage fog and I
would like to also cast prestidigitation
so that
the room is filled with the smell of
waffle cones okay for the second mode
magic pop out I really like persons like
and I'm gonna I'm going to use vomit
urging to cause any flames or lights in
this room to dim except the ones closest
are just instantly I learned that trick
from your mother oh really well with a
resolute keep soldiers massive arms okay
Robin are working hard to win yeah this
is a classical piece okay it's called
caramelldansen okay good okay good yeah
we know that is the dance of the caramel
but it says it's very similar yeah how
much have we believe it's played on yeah
skulls but other than that I've got a
comparable performance let's see a
performance role oh yeah why don't you
read the sheet which is a performance up
to a heaven yeah you're so fine
well memory a 14 I can't can't burn
conspiration myself huh yeah nothing the
fourteenth normal end is nothing it's
like a nurse ometer G and minor illusion
and pressurization okay and you and
automatically like what's the what's the
criteria for winning here yes need to be
moving you know I'm just not embarrassed
yeah yeah that's it well how do we not
lose money
exactly he says that's why I just
I don't know the context of that work he
says listen we're going to do this again
in the bar I'm going to bring drama and
we're gonna see how it goes okay okay
okay I'm not actually that bra mom very
nervous
okay well don't be nervous make sure the
punk don't worry about it it's in
Bellerophon not fan yeah team glare
front sucks
shimmer works all of them hate them all
they're awesome so cool yeah you know
very charming when you meet her I think
yeah she's great they're the best yeah
okay haunting well okay uh and then okay
so we're we're gonna have just uh just a
regular old moon off that what we're
going to call this hoo-hoo-hoo rest this
I think this interested party should
rough it and I think that's walnut gets
to rest honey yeah I feel like you're
the person I can't know anything about
music
I'm clearly a biased party repeatedly
expressed disinterest in the loot yeah
you don't hate it I hate team
Bellerophon I am definitely the person
that should do this yeah I think you're
the right person
I'm the lizard man I can't say I hate
the other directly those are Hannah's
tickets penniless bet with me oh he's a
clown but she says the bar will decide
okay mash it all right
all right let's do this okay that
personalized exactly bites so thank you
know this this this this boat is you
know by now well underway
no taking to the South it's beginning to
head down and out toward the ocean
proper which is sort of the last stage
of its run until they move around and
then just do the circuit again so you
can see that by now that the tables are
starting to amass some people have sat
down an expectation of entertainment
that drinks are being brought out to the
tables meals are being ordered you
for the most part of people you know
things are things are occurring as you'd
expect but there is something that is
odd that you see these tables are all
dragons nope that's fine I thought it
isn't odd like you're going to like
become mushroom people and no I mean I
know that I'm done passe you say that
you'll be like oh you're in this weird
place everyone inside out and they're
all barfing out of their nose and yeah
yeah everyone's enchanted then you're
like it's just the weird part is no it's
not like that
and they're trying to eat the people
okay what the game of choice here
appears to be Giants and halflings and
you was good at that and you would think
like that's not that's not what you
heard in the doone-gate in yeah that's
considered that's considered more of a
friendly game in favor as the player
over the house oh you know and it
suggests in other games like volts or
pickpocket these are games that have
progressive that's bigger potential for
loss on the part of the player
pickpocket especially is a favorite in
these guilds is it possible that the
second row the grande rollers are doing
vaults and then the venti rollers are
doing three pockets you didn't see you
didn't see a difference or a designation
if you were led through those areas okay
earlier it's it's it's an interesting
piece of information okay Johnson
halfling as well oh yeah you know how to
do it I don't need a can we get our show
last night
criminy never without an expansion of
course allows you we have a high-octane
ride that we need to keep premium fuel
and yeah exactly so so the metaphor
walks through with his sort of tool is
Erdman
new and just sort of like just it's like
like you guys are all still together
necessary spread out oh yeah split the
party keep an eye on a later fashion all
right how long are we here till do we
ever have screws the BIA tried and we
have to adjust the entire crew if
there's a one day cruiser ya know it's
three days immediately they stop at they
sought that docks on the way down okay
okay so what's going on bar but is it
about time yet it's not time it's not
time yet all right little later right
right right
you know this is when before everything
is set here at the beginning is when
people try to test the facility in
various ways I'm going to keep your eyes
open okay
darn you thank you okay
you hear a voice louder than a letter
than a mouth can do and more and more
encompassing it spreads out this is a
premium mouth tell them okay it spreads
out and it seems to come from the walls
if the voice fills the space and then
you know as they begin to speak you can
see that people's eyes start to turn up
to the stage and then the first one the
first voice says introducing arch wizard
numinous primp of the shattered Conclave
and then he emerges from he emerges from
the teleportation circle a little dazed
but then catches his eye
gets his bearings back raises his arms
up he looks like them
he's just draped he looks really do this
was a pile of fabric spacing here Newman
is perfect for right and the voice says
that the 1200 is called and they want
their mystical vestments back
and walnut dyes laughing yeah but he
takes it he takes it in good spirit he
he makes it his way down good
you know fast sort of stuttered steps
down he seems pretty familiar with the
establishment you must be in order to
give the the zip treatment here at the
hoard next is called out barabbas oculus
of the red hive they've been seen
converting cavorting with a great worm
Vulcan Trix is it real or is she just a
trophy worm and then through the through
the portal comes a beholder Oh sort of
bobbing in midair and then just sort of
silently sweeping down the down the
stairs now looking around sort of bowing
as much as it can as much as it can
muster I shock slinking you yeah got a
sink yeah wink out everybody love you
and then the the voice says it's just
coughs for a moment and just explode off
the returned of the six and then from
the portal come two people or two
goblins that you may you may have seen
them before even out front of the drawn
and courtiers
these are his these are his his chosen
different distinct from the ones that
had operated the caravan raids and then
after these two come out and they check
the place out they make sure that
there's no one near the no one near the
teleportation circle they sort of glower
even at the people who are immediately
surrounding the stage then two more
goblins come out these goblins are
similar to the ones that you had seen
out on the the road to Westbridge they
have their ears pinned with rings tied
behind their head and they come out and
they look at their fellows their fellows
nod and then split off the returned
emerges behind them but never everyone
else everyone else has a sort of
practiced grandeur about their
intimidation and he just smiles in a way
that makes you feel like you are food
but it's a different approach different
approach same result right and then he
makes his way down then he as he walks
out they his fellows occupy a sort of
almost like a flocking behavior he as
soon as he walks forward they sort of
lock into some cosmic position around
him that they've assumed in the five of
them go down the stairs and then
immediately find their way up to the
second level and the last says and the
prize student of audre career Brahma Lu
da and then even as she even as she
emerges from the teleportation circle
first just the loot then the hands on
the loot are already playing even in the
moment before she's appeared she passes
through some veil and now she is in the
dragon's hoard and the same the same
mystic property that allowed the voices
to carry is now filling the dragon's
hoard with performance of a profound and
moving nature transfixed
ah transics look very serious looking
like grimacing but it is like so forced
black conflicting feeling it was like
candy
really team Bellerophon really sucks
this is a very confusing barn that gives
her a lot of confusing feelings and then
in her hand she's holding her in her
hand but she has her hand in the air
pocket in the yeah in the document sea
bag as if she's like rifling for
something and then she finds it and it's
the the poem that frog was entering she
has her hands on it that's it she has it
in her hands or in the bag in her hand
but I like just the knowing that she's
like such as like this can you imagine
how worried that that paper is now yeah
it's all like gnarly and and like
fingerprints and dirty he don't bathe so
it's like yeah just mud yeah fine you
know that's like you're you're betraying
it more than you realize
and then so like dinar sees her and then
sees you and just goes oh she's the one
you like the performance is happening oh
it's like a little respect
well that has a little crush no I have a
professional interest it but share just
share for you this is I've studied this
yeah yeah this is for you this is a
different thing
it's less about right now you've heard
this music you're familiar with the
piece you could play it if you
absolutely had to it might not sound
exactly like this
not likely yeah um but a lot of it a big
part of it is the lute itself so yours
has a kind of bayonet on it it's
designed to protect it's designed to
protect you know performers and
travelers on the road it's almost like a
Swiss Army lead in some ways right
it has different ways of storage but you
know that that you can spend much like
with a regular instrument like in the
real world you can spend as much as you
want on a war loot yeah like there's no
other
there's no upper bound for how much you
can spend and she spent a lot like you
just you're trying to take it all in
like you're trying to figure out how
many ways it opens and the string
material is odd and you are surprised
that she can play it without cutting her
own hands off like it is a it is a it is
a work of art it makes art and it's also
a weapon it's one hundred percent of
spooky town um so yes she is she is
playing and you are watching the you
were watching things go down no one
seems to froggy yet we're still in the
first part of this trip agitation seems
to be at a minimum she's gonna headliner
not an opener yeah she says out loud
yeah every time I go past you when we're
doing our rounds around the floor I nod
you and I say something that I'm pretty
sure you can hear but just quiet enough
that you could totally ignore me if you
wanted to things like you should go say
something to her I come back around and
like tell her how you feel look at
happen what what lucky me something we
should know about you like do you need
something okay
like a fly buzzing around here my so
normal any murdered all those people
yeah those it's I forgot it was awesome
yeah no we're looking for so the first
song comes to a close the tables around
this just as just the introduction it's
not even the concert this is just her
well that was just her intro she's just
a pious she was just appearing now
people know what they can expect right
she walks her way down the stairs and
walks right by you
what is she
like question no I have you ever smelled
a strawberry field in summer
it's basically smells like hot Jam
mm-hmm okay
sticky don't make it gross right yes so
my gross it's very sweet
I mean you're honest you're a me you're
you're in her field of vision and she
does not notice you at all that's fine
oh woman doesn't change her face at all
she continues uh looking in the same
direction but if she passes without
looking like she'll just portray it a
little bit and like give her give her
aside I thought she would absolutely not
look crusher exactly she is yelling at
the Atmel for hmm you know tasteful
volume but it is clear that he needs to
offer something up with an immediacy hey
shadow council mayor laborious please
you this is our great don't go anywhere
look at these cool vids and then come
back and see it that's a bit so here on
the dragon's hoard special VIP guests
have just arrived indeed the arch wizard
numinous primp of the shattered Conclave
criminais and easy it but it's necessary
it's under control
yes indeed Barabbas the oculus of the
red hives plus the throw some dice
telekinetically I guess there's also
spewed off the returned of the six which
the party has some affiliation with hmm
at the drawn and quarter he is a goblin
of some renown and with some reservoir
of hatred and anger toward acquisitions
incorporated specifically home and run
and
also just just as a side note of just a
piece of trivia really from Oulu yay of
Team Bellerophon and prize student of
Agra courtier has just used the
teleportation circle she's a headliner
for this event and she is having
finished her some she has secured the
attention of Mela for who is the head of
security on the floor proper and he is
and he is currently being upgraded by
her you can't hear a hundred percent of
what she's saying you'd have to lean in
I want to hear you have to lean in real
good and it's up to you seven it's up to
you so but you can see this - you can
see that this is because you know things
have been pretty cool so far between the
guests and the staff and you know that
the games are moving appropriately gold
is changing hands this is the only
moment really a wrinkle in this fabric
at all can we can't hear what she's
yelling if you have you'd have to get a
little bit closer to break italic
Santa's right right now you wanna count
right now you can just get a sense that
I'm something maybe it should be the
writer yeah maybe the mms or not you
know I mean like I don't know
sure yes mom you're with me and we are
going to approach because we have double
reason one we're very concerned about
the security but also bhrama should be
introduced to her understudy so we come
up and look when your mom forces you to
network yeah yeah yeah I have someone I
want you to meet listen and I come up I
clear my throat mm-hm
yeah brahma Brahmas neck transpose like
an owl like it moves like way too far
over for like what you would think the
skeletal structure can endure and then
the rest of the body turns towards you
and then she notices your loo okay she
seemed mad she saw the loot and then she
looks back at you
he says you yes we've met
hi small world
we're actually running security and this
is my daughter share she is your your
honor study tonight and I were both just
such big fans of your music that I
thought it'd be appropriate to make
introduction she turns to metaphor and
says this is what I'm talking about I
need security to protect me from
security I don't think that we've been
aggressive here we're just this is a is
a professional colleague of yours
imagine my rate per minute
I'm imagine and then imagine how much
you owe me right now I don't
I think that's closer to nothing
actually Noah for is like he's not in
the sight of this just haha maybe he has
some experience with this sir
okay just knowing that they're having
this conversation I'm now doing that
thing where I know something's happening
behind us and like my back to it I'm
looking you and I'm like how's
everything going on the round you're
like way too heartless very scary yeah
I'm I go what no sound I'm like okay I'm
watching
split off okay yes she looks so she
looks to you share and she'd hold your
hands out to me I I would be honored
yeah I won't actually touch it I
actually it took a banjo in it's a yeah
it's a banjo ukulele a war loot the
whirling whirling theater you're behind
why would you do it yourself because
it's all happening behind your deep
inner tam screen yeah yeah this is the
Besson so it just like truss it back in
just like on its own just you know what
I mean
twisted back in looks at at both sides
she said I started with one of those she
turns back over to Mela for and says I
need my own security anybody with these
two your loss lady
and so Ella for millet for walks the two
of them walks over to dinar and says
something like this just going to work
for you and promises what no absolutely
not
we're cool no I don't think so
what is walnuts way right now yeah just
this just gone just stoically looking
straight ahead like and Branagh says
okay Khalil who else do you have
and now as far as like on this shift I
only have one more person
if she's not acceptable and brahma says
we'll cross that bridge when we come to
it
all right he brings her over to you and
she assesses every cell of your body
this isn't because we're role-playing
but I wouldn't feel like it all of that
okay I had did this on purpose what a
walnut house one that reacting well it's
like completely 100% still maintaining
eye contact the whole time
it gets worse she walks around behind
straight ahead yeah straight ahead like
hint like hand on the scimitar as if
that would like as if it's like a worry
stone like just she slaps your hand
selectively I can't believe she's
putting up with this yeah do you want it
first of all not want her to choose her
yeah well not long good yeah down right
now
piranha says as she's getting that I
fold em ha yes promises front and back
yeah every hunt you got she's got her
eyes on 350 of ha yeah I do it's a
television no it's like I just got back
from like Universal Studios look at my
house just exactly like no I did like a
haunch experience it's for D oh you mean
the other thing let's get back to this
all right
look at genius Veronica's building Hey
well I'm just like nods curtly and then
looks at rizzi and like so what silly
like internally screaming and like we
don't have to transfer she can't do that
awakened mine but it's like she's trying
to put on something but like you see
that she just looked at promise you okay
there anything all right
she says I need to freshen up so you led
up the stairs on the right side from the
ground floor up to the mid fork to the
wood from the window to the locked to
the wall to the Wow no it was my good
and thuggish and then up through and the
the guards at the top that protect the
Suites just part like water and the two
of you go through the golden doors and
then she leans down to her door and says
walnut oh why don't you make this brace
it's not real
why can't he realize oh okay it's
alright from here okay stop don't guess
my yarn okay all very sweet is this yeah
the scene can in there if you want I
mean I just I'm going to seek consent
here I mean how do you want this to go
on the children do you want this do you
want this do you want to just do this do
and you can tell me what happens or we
can like email this thing or do you want
to do you want to figure it out right
now no right well if you want to do your
thing
yeah I think I'd like to do my thing
just right yeah real quick I have a
level two spell called detect thoughts
that I would like I would like to see
what's going on in walnuts walnut oh is
it get a nut right up and then I want to
get my men that we read the description
that song yeah yeah it's a 30 foot
radius action to read thoughts of one
creature with it I think in like a great
images over three yes Dan over threes I
think I think we got it can't be like a
worm
apparently yes no wisdom save to probe
um I just concentrate I think okay yeah
all right I'm very busy
yeah that's true so she has to wisdom
save a thirteen plus your wisdom me yeah
yeah so they look a bit that's gonna be
a seat on the twenty over there yes have
you you wouldn't even notice here's a
chance yeah and I don't know no so you
can you can you can you can present you
can you can discover walnuts just really
do talk with my mom yeah exactly exactly
like it's happened before if you're
really if you feel like you couldn't get
introduced or screaming get out my head
like what is happening I prayed I was
like the bloody fun so so sure at what
point are you instantiating this ability
I think what when she when she hears
what the password is her name right I
would really like to know what Larry I
was very feet way way up there
they've already gone up those stairs and
gone back okay I can we in very much as
if you if you want to of course is very
good if you are so I'm in my own tail
yeah yeah yeah I'm like unconsciously
like no I checked I have to pay it off
yeah yeah I'm also worried about you but
only a little bit most am I'm very
interested in how this plays out thirty
thirty feet should be okay for the back
there yeah I think this is actually just
figured because I don't think it's
actually I don't think it's going to be
R rated yes I don't know your character
I don't want to be for your dinner but
this is going to great the Rose because
she wants to know yes sir in the room
yes door closes sure well I guess this
the room is the room is extended we're
just hearing with motivator Nahanni log
yeah yeah yeah so right now you just
hear like in anxiety exactly that okay
whatever but basically I'm going to
describe specifically information for
you guys okay so basically you're
getting it and then you're propelling it
to me because now the best so it's like
if it's tasteful without being trihard
sure like fine woods there's at least
three different three decanters pictures
in sort of a basin of ice you know on
this wooden table tastefully appointed
bed like I say there's a veranda outside
and she has walked straight through the
room and has her hands on the veranda
and is just looking out and we recreate
that one scene from Titanic yeah we
steady walnuts thoughts okay um I was
like part or talked to her your stupid
mouth walnut now all no opens our
mouthing than she is I got your note and
then officious says I think it is idiot
[Laughter]
I know how'd you know I mean of course
you know I play a trick on you and I
want to apologize it wasn't fair what
was the trick I knew you would take the
note and I know where you go I need to
know where you go and then she gets up
it's for you guys it's like you just
start hearing like why was this
incorporating be those a little
look and she stiffened up a little bit
and she's like why like why do you need
to know where I was incorporated goes
because I don't know what I would do if
something happened to you and I couldn't
get there well I thought turn around she
says you went to it town that wasn't on
a map I had a hard time figuring out
where you were for a while that that was
something that that was some unfinished
business that I had and then was just
like.he like the father just say it's
screaming it sounds like out like like
waves like crashing it's a rocket like
doesn't make sense and then she's just
like much of her procreation and she
goes with Romo and she goes well I'm
here now that should be it oh that's the
end of the minute so that we get this is
one more okay somewhere she turns to you
back off of the veranda and she puts her
hand up your back and onto the back of
your neck and holds it a little tight
mm-hmm and she says what's it like not
to be the tough one pornography phase
I can do this for another 40 minutes but
we're going we're going yeah we're not
asking you don't allow to do this cuz
I'm going so the scope just elect cuts
out yeah right before the last part is
how it works you know worse it's like
she's like this pill boom and then she
like fall in the door and then it's just
like a pile of these singers like the
dream is you didn't dream of swing then
I love I've passed under wave destroys
all the glass I think I hate this whole
but know how to animal and so yeah well
I feel like that worked out about as
well as it possibly could um so you are
still doing our job exactly exactly like
the other only one so so you're looking
out over this you're looking out over
this sea of people
you're occasionally walk out to the base
of the steps take a look at the second
tier the second tier in the third tier
have a much stronger their internal
security is there these extra bodies are
really just to manage that influx down
here you know at the layer of people who
are paying these antes right and so as
you're walking back to the lower floor
you feel a tap on your shoulder you feel
sort of like the the tip of a claw you
turn back and it's melih for with
splooge off the returned and two of his
satellite associates Noah for says this
is blue goth representative of six we've
met
good then I'm sure you won't mind making
sure that he has somebody with him at
all times this is a different tasks not
purely a bouncer type situation I want
to make sure you understand
his his servants are not allowed to
gamble he needs like a wingman okay
I can do that he needs a wingman
situation I was like I don't have you're
gonna have to pay for your own chips wow
that's weird that's weird right look if
you want to gamble after we pay you for
this
just wait around on the boat so probably
persuade him try to get some free - yeah
yeah I want to try to persuade oh I'm
gonna be like I'm down to do this but
isn't what I don't know I'm on yeah a
bit all right I got really good
personation -
Wow yeah that's that's my great plan
second he'd like something on the house
exactly he reached it he reaches over
I'm plugging your whale happy on to like
like to the chips like we're a dealer is
actively handing them out and she is
like mid paying out winnings and he just
scoops him up off the table and then
puts him in your hand
nice how many yeah right that many god
oh no that's it he's real eight three I
got eight eight money's there 25 I got
825 money that's right so 800 825 money
probably more math yeah that's Howard so
he's like he's like I just I need you to
keep him company
I got it yes if anything goes down you
need to understand that part of the
reason I chose someone of your bulk is
that
we've had problems coming from him as
well if you know what I mean don't
sometimes these security issues are the
result okay not the target understand
what I'm saying don't you
you start oh yeah okay you guys are
going to get along yeah they spend a lot
of money subscribing Tamar yeah
it could be kind of an okay
thinks he's the best
what's he just what's he think it was
his policy on high five yeah it's just
like you got this right oh yeah I'm all
idiot he lead he leads down screw goth
looks you over and says still
acquisitions incorporated still still
doing that still working with those
for now yeah tell me more till
something better comes along
let's talk yes he leads you up the
stairs not to the highest of the high
rollers but to that second tier that has
visibility down on this down on the
stage and sits down to the table it's
you him and Archibald primp hmm another
another you know high-value client is
this a relation of numinous print yeah
was it numinous ramp yeah
Archibald is the arch wizard Oh arch
wizard Newman is print but ridiculous
name I could come up fair good
yeah exactly so her friends calling yeah
they were showing exactly so he oh oh
one key so he sits down and then his his
evil satellites just sort of fan out
just creating a wall behind the table so
now there's a dealer and the three of
you you are at the far right end of this
table dance blueglass starts to lay down
some chips
all right well do I get in hell minam
yeah what are we playing get Giants it
happens you can okay you see you see the
classic dice okay
laid out there ready to go you have your
halflings ready to go forever on this
one yeah oh yeah I need to d6 is right
don't worry yeah now do you have do you
have rules yeah so rules right here okay
so we go over the world are they in the
channel absolutely little bit heaven
image they have been in the channel
before but it's totally worth coming
back at it
Giants and halflings a more or less
friendly game sometimes used to resolve
disputes inexplicably slightly in favor
of the player the dealer rolls a d-10
the d-10 is a giant in this metaphor and
the number that they roll on that is
called the knee that's the target that
you that the halflings are trying to hit
if the giant rolls a1 players lose the
player then rolls to d6 and they try to
get the knee or higher if they roll 11
or 12 they lose automatically that's the
mall that's the law hey way to go there
grandma and now the odds are based on
where the knee is set between 1 and 10
on a double 1 roll
that's push right that's a snake scares
with a giant and that's that's basically
it now if you roll the knee exactly
you can split your dice and if you
double your bed you can get paid a bunch
of chips like a whole bunch of chips
yeah right right you might give a shot
yeah yeah this is a big big show for the
dealer what's up what's up wall 9 okay
all right I'm still recovering people
playing you know I'm win it I'm excited
for tonight a gamble yeah it's also very
cool I'm going to try me to try to
breathe normally I turn red when people
gamble the sleeves are shown no dice in
the sleeves right
hide them exactly and then oh she tosses
it until one dies oh you know what I
might have to put this down so I want to
play this exactly right with you but all
right oh gee so thinks things are
starting out hot see things are starting
out well I don't begin to by the way
yeah yeah yeah so you got real exactly
ten yeah yeah we guys were snakes yeah
everything else it's a tenner or two boy
it's the snake oh good shot boy
and don't stop like you guys the best
and so the dealer just hisses yeah
behind the behind it behind the table
yes exactly
can I say okay say I got you I got just
Eugene okay that'll take an hour man
miss Lulu got two of laughs and just
slap your back a couple times like
there's bear is it yeah yeah right here
we go let me grab this real quick no
don't peer beyond the veil oh there's a
lot of chips there here so you so your
bet pushes right yeah yes you're eight
eight okay let's up one but good odds
and beat them no item holy that right
now so you have your one do is head
eight three two one three two one yeah
Sam Mac can you keep rolling keep it
going even the eyewriter has the
sickness like that's enough no no no sax
like Harry and I table target have gone
a million casino
no we know about it Leo bet is he's
leaning in on this he knows what he's
doing best player I am what I want I
want to I want to take a moment just to
remind everyone obviously the shadow
council mayor Larry sleeve you think
about last time where Rosie was the one
playing the gambling game and Ryan still
managed to be betting
who's Ryan dinar
still managed to be betting on it are
you are you here what you keep me around
the table oh yeah this is the house
money I don't care what I do a data
right let's not throwing it if I'm
wearing your favorite exactly nice easy
excuse II specifically I have to be just
yeah right now I'm good and then as the
six comes up the dealer says two to one
Oh i junked myself ha now you got to
make the money back yeah yeah there's
blue Gus doing well on these just trying
to keep him happy
Phil Goff is doing well at drinking Oh
and watching dinar let's keep saying the
words blue gospel yeah yeah like I say
Wow so tell abuela that's pretty weird
yeah he says he says yeah that way he's
on the is on the company yeah what I
feel like let's see
he takes right he takes a long ship and
he says like every hanger you've ever
had at once for a second that's all
right
three one keep going I say we hear that
theory that when you teleport that you
actually die and then you're recreated
as a simulacrum so like you're not
really you you're actually someone else
that's weird huh so like when you
teleport out of here the you that's all
I'm talking to will die it'll be a new
one
it's roses eyes yeah I'm good at this
tell man hey you guys aren't even near
him to like hear him talking like this
no no whoo there you go that's agile you
know that one that one big boy yeah
that's what I'm talking about the best
part is that it's engineered so you can
still lose Yeah right just like a
hologram blip it puts the end game here
in which I'm trying to get blue goth
spending right yeah you had a bit but at
any point feel free to discuss things
with split some information at home
yeah right not like oh man our boss yeah
yeah yeah we met before and you didn't
have a lot of good things to say about
oh man why is that have you ever met him
no actually admit his a hologram yeah
you see you work for a man you've never
met and now you're asking me why I don't
like him yeah okay it goes like this
imagine imagine yeah Oh got it ago I got
alright yeah you gotta fit gotta oh boy
so splitting entails yet you have to
roll two more dice I've got a roll one
for each one
uh-huh here's you want it three two
that's yeah you can have your kid a sex
video he'll here's your split dice so
roll the dice for YouTube what else what
yeah I need you go any Khan legendary do
I have to separate them he's out no no
we're about I can I could take all right
well of these ever like crazy odds right
so it's only a three so it's all one way
this is the same all right yeah so I'm
rolling on this one yes I guess I roll
you're rollin here yeah okay all right I
win okay you need more tape n-no no role
for now roll dice for your one okay you
Kenyan and then go back to the to you
I guess Wow 7 years Senate I think I
know I didn't notice fix the player may
split a second time if we wish to become
legendary which I believe you can are
just did yeah what are the people in
luck yeah what happened as everyone
probably around me like patting me on
the back okay I miss my cheek
yeah like I'm the right exactly I'm his
new Goss caboose is up and he just he
just like cheer you don't have a drink
so he just cheers your head no no and
the arch wizard the art the arch wizard
is not impressed with this he sort of
has his diocese doing that thing where
you sort of like like we like this big
square dice adjuster like folding them
up on each other together folding them
back and forth say what's your deal
carpet sample
[Music]
is that racist
hahaha what if it is audience you just
vote on your problem surprise he tries
to communicate as though he doesn't he
hasn't heard you but you can tell that
his very heart yeah as young you know
that you've you've laid a dark egg in
the center of his aorta nice nice nice
nice
so he said and then doctor he says he
says there was a omen had a choice from
the moment I met him I served in to the
best of my ability I was an intern once
I was deputized in his and what
he had the opportunity to reward my
service
he let me bleed out instead you don't
forget it I'm actually a franchising not
anything it's important to sing for this
friend I think he's like yeah well I'm a
part of an organization now that extends
a little bit more concern this will fix
shall we say right yeah you run it no I
don't want to run it I get interesting
jobs I'm paid well and I get to hurt
people mmm can I do a brief thing while
this is happening at otally yeah just be
the lesson those and I'll swing you back
over to you guys okay okay all right I
know it will bring the camera back over
here yeah to the mother and daughter cry
mother and the adventure team Sharon
Rosie yeah well we're not solving crimes
yet but I love crimes what what we are
doing is yeah we have located a bottle
of extremely nice red wine and Franzia
we have the box a box yes Bob's wife are
the GM in the line is the Francey a wine
chip yeah yeah but wine chest and Rosie
managed to get it so we have now dressed
up as service smoke unnecessarily and we
are wheeling a cart together because our
small and requires to halflings to
Brahmas room to deliver fake reserved
can i disguise self be helpful at this
point like exquisite can i oh my god can
I spread disguise self among other like
if we were stacked on top of each other
does that extend my no no no if you
became using like so your two halflings
is that sort of like one like regular
size yeah yeah yeah videos your adult
half like yeah so do I do you stand on
my shoulders we get a robe and then you
disguise self whatever you want to
adjust your head poking out yeah and
then we're sacred service yeah yeah yeah
because others were venal wacky to do
your best
up top yeah this guy self is going to
come into play now obviously is this a
strange torso yes and very long feared
torsos weird people in a relationship
shaped like a dragon
serie or anything be done you can't
judge but we had we should drug growth
with a mantis man last night like a
horse those are not our primary concern
you're in same room so what I described
to me or disguised self my sweet
daughter how do you describe yourself I
don't know what I don't know what the
what would be the most sort of withering
at a maybe a sort of lizard sort of
lizard like appearance so lizard esque
another desk yeah yeah
lazar angelov it adjacent yeah I'm
obsequious lizard lizard Minh all nice
yeah I like that yeah I like that
Johnson a so scaly please yes yes Peak
Oil is Erdman yeah yeah nice nice secret
litter that's good okay stay to dial it
in it's like dialing they obsequious and
then the lizard man and that did the
button that basically how it works right
of the fighters yeah exactly
Oh
we're December now okay I'm at a secret
okay so we're pushing the cart yeah so
you're stressed you're there you see
John downstairs low on the feast all
right there is a knock at the door okay
enough time has passed here Scherzer
put your pants back on they worship room
service
I was it WA you hear snoring shuffle
room it's not yet but it's not expected
okay you see you see another side of
Brahma okay when the knot comes to the
door and she hears their room service
her lute is in her hands immediately um
well why do that she starts to dismantle
it like you know those movies where that
feature snipers and there's always that
elaborate scene where they build enjoy
my taste
yeah no no it's like it's like
sharpening and tuning up and yet exactly
it's like it's like she's just
everything is being tuned she makes sure
that she has the hair pins are in like
she is she is basically like preparing
for war in a complaint her personality
changes like this alright and she's
doing that and then um well not like in
like it don't worry baby I got this but
just like a puts it handlers this is you
know I go you say I go no no following
here and then she dies yes and then she
goes to goes to the door and she has her
hand on the honest and trans like and
then she nudges the the door open a
little bit um and she's like what do you
want yeah you see a hassling oh you see
a lizard man at adjacent lizard
engagement
no seriously the adjacent server in the
serving garb pushing a cart that has a
bottle of wine on box crate
chess a frenzy of wine chest
and as soon as you I see it's you that's
open the door I'm thinking between you
can't see me but I'm like - two - two -
oh yeah
yeah I just because I'm worried about
you I haven't heard anything come on in
there and Brahma is whatever so you hear
from roughly the knees of this
obsequious lizard man everything okay -
I recognized it as a reward owed
instantly instantly and first a second
one looks like to get swab am i in their
existence yes all okay forget here enjoy
the wine yup you can yeah great
she like and meanwhile I'm up top like
management apologizes for this yeah
earlier please enjoy this complimentary
bottle of wine okay grabs it and it's
just like shut the door and unlike you
to tear like 1000 latches even though
there are chemicals of the management
closet this is the minimum word three or
four times
walnut just says the word latch just
latch Jane sambal hahahahaha
very secure very autumn on area like she
saw that walnut different oh so she's
like the opposite of walnut um yeah this
dude or any horns across this world is
the opposite
how did the Exile on the on the diagram
scroll it's the polar opposite yeah it
may be there's a dire I don't okay
how does your help okay sorry just
wanted to make sure that you know there
was no death okay I can go back to your
cool yeah yeah exactly
no it's like that it's fine um so it's
starting to get a little it's starting
to get a little the tenor of this table
is has changed yeah when the camera
swings back to this game the arch wizard
has gotten more and more agitated he's
going to fold the dice together
ever quicker between rounds and slew got
this on a losing streak hmm
like it's been it's been going for a
while he's he's got ample chips but he's
losing them fast it has situation where
it's like you know it's like you win
that one time betting ten ships yeah so
then you think that that's like your
base by the ground floor right and it's
starting to go down and then after the
next round of hands
he says smooth I says I'm rich so I
don't care
you owe me both yes but I keep looking
over to the arch wizard he says I just
want to know how you're doing it I don't
I don't care
I could lose money like this for weeks
but I want to know how you're doing it
and that RN numinous primp is like what
doing what hmm yeah what guys I'm not
call right it's a Dyson anyway permanent
character as a girl I don't I don't care
I just it doesn't it doesn't make me mad
wizard it doesn't make me mad but I want
you to tell me how you're doing it and
then what is Meredith don't say yes is
how much it is not a necessity that I
tell you how I've done this or that
especially since I haven't done anything
okay all right a couple ways it can
happen couple ways it can go there was
another way before you started
talking like that there was another way
and now it's going to go this way and in
a second a fraction of a second a knife
comes out hmm numinous primp slides back
from the table and then falls backward
off of his stool and begins producing
wands and rods of various kinds yeah
out of his substantial rug supply yeah I
try to get between the two of them may I
jump in is a row I try to cool it off I
like vent but when I get it a nice can I
get that perception role for me real
quick perception per second on a cruise
the mushrooms cover yeah sure is so so
you you have shed your disguise your
like upper torso is a lizard I you might
have returned to share them like from
the neck down yeah exactly to do you you
just want to keep one special lizard
part so another hand here I'm just going
to kind of doing it maybe exactly and as
you're coming down the as you're coming
down the stairs from the gold door and
whatever might be occurring behind it
there's a flat that flat place below the
high roller but not all the way down to
the floor you can see that your friend
dinar blitz in friend your associate
your partner hmm let's see
okay dinar Blitzen of janar is it has
just stood up from a table wheres plug
off is also split off has a knife in his
right hand there is a wizard on the
ground who has begun to produce various
you know mystical artifacts in a
dangerous way can I get a perception
role from you sir
and from my darling share as well we
share move 73 that's an 8 - oh god I
can't see anything
dad you're for someone she's got out of
12 August right there oh hell was that
+4 yeah to 12
okay it seems a little weird to you ah
only only two of his people normally sit
at yeah this is only two of his retinue
has
turns to defend their their boss the
other two our star still standing
looking out from the group arms folded
looking out across the area they just
not noticed or have they seen it and
show the amount of attention it has any
idea okay thank you you grant is the
wizard speaking it cells appear to be
spoken no right right now it's just sort
of like a standoff okay
one of them has a knife and everyone has
a rod and a wand okay nice damn okay and
dinar is between them dinar it was at
the far right side of this table so
currently and you'll have an opportunity
to act soon he is behind blue goth I'm
wearing never turn away indeed indeed
you are coming down the stairs
just opposite them coming down from the
from the upper deck and so you are you
can you can be as close as you want to
be very good you just laugh at cousin
said upper deck I did like bard defusing
calming I don't have I do have even on
emotion go anywhere share it can
actually chair is very good at this yeah
there's like I'm a musical comeback I
think so
yeah yeah I tend to suppress strong
emotions and a group of people each
humanoid humanity in a 20-foot radius
there humanoid 15 40 foot diameter
sphere centered on a point that I choose
with enrage free charge they must make a
Christmas saving throw creature can
choose to fail to saving throw it wishes
creature failed to save and throw then I
more active read more stuff on the card
yeah yeah 16 I got yeah I know I know
exactly what it is because that
character is built to ran a
small commotion um I know one um Susa
soothe the savage beast
[Music]
did I do it
that's a super Souter yeah she yeah I
don't know you have you have you have
actually a substation with you attack
these die sets down help that was
miserable no you did what they did they
immediately like it's things stopped
immediately it's like she drops a
soothing blanket over it smells like a
dryer sheet it just Falls a downy that
which are snuggled to the bear
yeah it just lands over it and then it's
exactly another branch state exactly
it's a great brand that I see I use it
some tight aspirant yeah that's inside
we got to use it tight has a great one
to Connie's matter now and audible is
great I do like audiobook it better way
what do I charge you know is also
Squarespace little bit easier I cut good
I got one of these sheets in half and
it's plenty Wow like I use that you
thought I was moving on no I'm still on
it no so what happens is that you can
have such epic um is that you can see
just like the the goblins muscular frame
it just sort of rising and falling with
the breath and it is getting slower and
slower and you see the arch wizard
exactly you see the arch wizard sort of
like getting up standing up stowing his
[Music]
mystical ordinance in you know
mysterious allure pouches maybe he's a
marsupial I don't know and they take
their seats back at the table and they
each buy a drink for the other member
so I'll scoop that off no I want to get
why I'm gonna get another perception
role from each of you each of the three
of you give you three that clues yeah
you are possibly wait whoa that is 21
yeah so you so you you pick up on it now
you pick up on what was strange about it
before the calm emotion the spill it
didn't mean they were not agitated I
mean dish they were alert they look
alert like they're there bouncers it did
not have any effect on them at all they
are continuing to just hold their
positions and then as his defenders get
up and make sure that spook off is okay
they are they go out to occupy their
positions as well what you detect with
your 21 is you see two goblins slip out
from this from this area they have
slipped out stealthily and has made
their way away from this group and has
gone down the stairs
oh not supposed to happen what should we
do you tell me about this oh yeah okay
that's the kind of relationship you have
yeah I can't give ya mommy
don't worry about it goblin goblin I'm
going to I'm going to do it there's a
thing to gesture at you you decide what
you want to do if you want to stick
around with calm sweets with us or if
you want to come with us but we're gonna
trail those goblets downstairs all right
so you're like they're up on a thing and
I get a little ya be today y'all comes
up yeah I don't know I feel like I will
stick with everywhere to get along all
right hard to do yeah yeah and plus if
he is going to be causing trouble now
and I want to get more info out of them
yeah exactly but you're probably feeling
very calm - yeah and I'm up a lot of
money do you want to do you want to do
you want to play another round that for
nothing
yeah it's okay no problem for more quite
exactly don't worry there'll be an
opportunity so
the two of you make your way down
we both hug the shadows yes we've
exactly well obviously yeah yeah and
that's that's precisely what that's
precisely what they've done as well I
mean they're moving around more or less
like the systems seem to have worked
pretty well I mean most people were
looking where they were not and that
continues to be the case there's
something about how they're moving
that makes them incredibly difficult to
see if you're not actively watching for
it they're in techniques that I
recognize or am i impressed
you're definitely impressed but they are
they're doing what you can do another
way okay but but yes yes I mean this is
this is you know a way to do this right
but that's not how they're getting it
done people you know you learned this
through study and meditation and there
are people who have you know there are
shortcuts to this oceans artifacts you
know crossroads pacts that sort of thing
so they are moving down on this main
floor they are moving along the outer
edge of it sort of phasing in and out
almost in place the lower the light gets
the better they are at this and then you
see them going into the crew quarters
yeah back pass hmm Oh sounds like
split-off is here to rob this bulb
that's my father what's wrong yeah okay
yeah I guess they just say to each other
now your sister dies but in the movie
version of this it's like I get always
doing it right she know if that was good
thrusting like just like an empty line
my god use your dial man yeah okay
okay so we just were to keep following
oh if you're cool with that I think I
think so cool about yeah I'm better off
with you around
yeah they feel very calm
basically there they're moving back with
a swiftness alright we are moving with
unhesitatingly behind them right so now
they are going through this main
corridor and they are going to the exit
that goes down into that shared that
communal living area near the vault
right okay but the door closes behind
them and locks oh okay is it one of
those whispering locks you say word into
it I have no idea
yeah you should know there the GL I know
that but I'm saying you know we don't
know from the P I know exactly you can
go and start talking into the lock if
you want okay well we see um the door is
really you you actually as you approach
it you hear the dork sort of click shut
okay um this is the this is the exit
that goes down now from your tour
previously right you know that there's
another way to get down but it was
always you going to the front of the
ship and then showing around the front
way and go through the kitchens
basically this is also the crew living
area where presumably we are living
right well shouldn't we have access to
this area this this goes down to a boot
loader isolating areas okay all right I
guess quick quick I've got the I got the
route here but we got to go we got to
run back to the stage behind to the
kitchen through the service quarters did
you check to see if it was locked like
did you touch it not I didn't maybe but
it sounded locked anything I don't what
oh okay yeah yeah we could just try to
whisper non going into the key we might
yeah I hate my job oh yeah I'd be a more
effective use of our time so down to the
area with the big column and then into
the crew living area is where we are
exactly so you so you peel around you
you're not able just before you were
able to sort of track and trace them
from place to place right this time
you're not able to find them they have
there they're open sort of communal
living area that is around their vault
right but you notice something down here
that you didn't notice previously
when you first came through before the
casino was in operation before the Horde
had begun to move downriver there is a
central column that exists between the
area where the waiters where the
waitstaff wait and the galley and end
the communal living area and from that
central column you don't it's a
basically a featureless surface but you
can see a rectangle in sort of like
carved into the structure facing the
vault and from that from that rectangle
from that sort of like door or portal
shape you see shadow just billowing out
like smoke and all we have time not this
game and I mean shadow council mayor
labor Spanky
it is time for our next break we're
going to go take full advantage of the
facilities we will come back and feast
feast upon your questions don't go
anywhere
you