I meant the enemy the past address the
fastest Levin you wouldn't make the fat
second and that the question play a
flash and reckless to choose of course
the wishes you saw was prudent in any
Sepulcher pulchritude will become the
putrid it's that well said I pursue in
no mountain too steep but dungeon duties
to send expended them marks up to the
top of the peak of beneath this we
become like sharks to and while I swim
in that learning goal like Carl Barks
ruin so send your national talks do it
I'll send them home in a natural box of
the post Tata most of the part included
save your breath for a cleric confessor
this is a lesson that life isn't any
profession let's just speak in my
official advice sign on the dotted line
and this in the twice hello no okay
children hi sorry
hotline bling hotline my name is drink
stop it I am Tycho Brahe has panic
attacks I am also a mini fest Hereward
run CEO of acquisitions incorporated but
today I am Jerry Hogan here to run a
game of Dungeons &amp; Dragons from my
friends specifically not limited to
dinar within Dragonborn narcissist okay
how could we possibly forget after last
week's explosive debut share beef singer
hey share with everybody okay thank you
chuck - yo what's up you were moving
your hands in a rhythmic way and it was
snap adjacent revering the natural world
walnut done grass slowly but surely
transforming my pic clapping my campaign
into a pornographers paradise it was
very sweet very case well knee-deep in
far - yeah exactly I know that's not
true I know it's not true
oh god I'm asking this yeah let's go
here yeah we're going to get to you I
know your thrift route not your
grandma's grandma Rosie pasting
Oh indeed now cathuria Stroud who you
know previously had retreated into a
mist shroud yes now you're actually
you're emerging from a mr. out yet again
guess who's back yeah exactly about back
again
now listen hash good and how skin good
oh I fear you have a cold
no it's like this it's like this but do
you catch up because we've been planned
for months now like four months did you
listen to the podcast even on 2 or 4 X
no it was a nice intro this was nice but
then the word was the wrong word onward
it should have been the affirmative word
on the record well hog refer no done no
it's gonna say no I don't know obviously
that's for maximum you know time
efficiency now did you happen to catch
it live on Twitch
no I was never that easy we killed
you're different
yes again how I get four down oh well
she didn't catch a live on Twitch did
you to you for under the novelization
exactly did you watch it on the video
on-demand either on hyper RPGs channel
or on penny okay I didn't know there
were so many options yes you did now and
then well great ways to consume this
come and Wow and those oh hey youtubes
that's too many places and that's 1/2
minute well at last he would have
watched it you know to far under APIs of
choice I had built all this up as like a
scenario for me to like become
increasingly angry but now I realize
that it's perfect for you not to know
because your character wasn't there
that's the metagame in gray the
mitigating potential is is constrained
substantial impacts your Intel's right
now suppose yeah yeah and then I just
realized that there's another problem
with it which I've been scared of not
knowing all week so well you got here
you know I appreciate yeah no one here
okay I can hook it up leap when last we
saw our heroes they had boarded the
river going
games of chance festival called the
dragon's hoard are rated by
one of the posts the fishing is a post
that you check your mouth it's risk
route I want to get back to where I was
laying know yourself everybody got on
the boat I think so
hey hi how'd you get here I think the
whole time oh my gosh on the boat
everybody's having a good time on the
boats
on the way up rosy bee stinger sees that
her daughter share bee stinger another
Bart is available on this craft for you
know as an understudy in case something
happens to the headline at something did
happen to the headline act Oh something
arrived allegedly allegedly the camera
was not in there a lot of fan sects have
suggested yeah yeah yeah
exactly what this is my power I see that
fanfic and just stamp huh Wow BAM
but as the party boarded the vessel
examined it were taken on a tour you
know in the / you know in the pursuit of
their security tasks the incredibly
clever walnut Don grass got a glimpse
inside the vault and saw that the
treasure that they had heard about was
not even contained therein I thought
that was very very classy for a long
time I couldn't figure out what you were
doing and then I was like I want it you
know I didn't know what you're doing but
I supported you on a break you know and
that now I was playing with you and that
actually looked a better play now but
different members of the party were
given were given different tasks by Mela
for who is basically the head of
security on the Dragons ward share and
Rosie were basically working the room
dinar was assigned directly to spook off
the returned an agent of the six he's
been assigned to be a sort of wingman
type figure but it's almost like a
reverse bodyguard insofar as Lou goth
Creek causes so many problems
it's worth having a guard assigned to
him just to protect the rest of the
vessel from him and then you know what
can be said about Brahma Lu da's private
bodyguard scenario walnut on grass top
of your professional movie Enclave
Pentax anima currently running a
security detail in Brahmas private
quarters background yeah olan olan now
is the reason i can't sanction the other
fanfic it's because you have your own
very elaborate fanfic we'll get to it in
the game okay okay listen I have checked
out no no we're going to make this
happen this is going to happen so we'll
see
Kotaro but you know not not a part of
that previous rundown because you were
not there with your friends you were
elsewhere doing other things the scene
opens Ted doone-gate in the dune gated
under new management
obviously Trevor so holding it down even
though he runs the place he's wearing
the The busboy cap it better works for
him I mean it's possible that werewolf
size garb is difficult order from Catala
right that's less entertainment for you
right I've got business opportunity oh
yeah yeah yeah you could crack that
market wide open
the rebels had gone on for a fair bit
rosy V stinger who as we established
previously is not your grandma's grandma
was able to defeat a ghost
and that ghosts former skeleton inside
of a gelatinous cube full of strange
treasures yes she was able to defeat
them in a game of dice specifically
Giants and halflings
and it's to her credit because she was
able to they extend her
the player role there's a slight benefit
to being the player it could it could be
an issue maybe they think that they
can't lose maybe they have a high
opinion of themselves because they
exclusively play Lich's who are bad at
dice so all right
yeah well discipline this I don't think
it's in general I feel like a powerful
undead Lich could probably do something
to manipulate the chance but they're
afraid to roll by my dice again oh
what's ya know positive positive
situations have gone dinar has made
money betting on other people betting
copious amounts of grubs have been
consumed people are making merry
sweaters and scarves are being
manufactured an alarming rate by the
spider that is hanging that it's hanging
from the chandelier and it is about this
time you see bless and rosy nip off to a
corner for some privacy you decide that
it's time for you to turn in you've
you've you've done what you can in a
social context and now it's time to
return to your quarters tell me what
that looks like for a Chris Brown well
as I recall I had been in my cups that
that evening is thorough yeah it finally
understood that that delicious custom of
alcohol drinking goes right down oh yeah
a lot of the night yeah the buddies
right yeah yeah yeah a friend get pretty
got in common yeah I kept I kept going
over like Oh to smell like that redolent
yeah what think of it think about it
like this what are we talking about what
talking about the clove oils mmm you
know what I mean this sinem yeah you
know what I mean that hard Imam and that
grave wax oh wow woah the end heady sign
me up
yeah please continue so one of the birds
that when I when akka through Stroud
enters his private chambers here at the
doone-gate
and what is that process like for him
and I'm in my mind I just see you sort
of like standing at the edge of the bed
and then you just like fall down and
they sleep there and then get back up
but I bet it's different than that I
think that I typically might my
nighttime and waking rituals involve a
lot of self questioning and guilt
because and the question I asked at the
end of the day is have I are taken too
much of this plane am I getting too
close to these pointless physical
pleasures this this pathetic husk which
we all inhabit one of right like some
idiot
it is so relatable danielís it'll give a
real Chris this is not out of care they
can you roleplay please no you exactly
notification is me I think it's a
customer yeah thank you same my feelin
so neat so but at the time I attempt to
do so I find that I'm actually too drunk
to do it and that makes me angry but I'm
also very sleepy it's the proof so I'm
like no I have to to shake off the
reserve I was very tired of me just go
sleep yes then in his collapse in the
bed ordinarily I would disrobe except
for the cloak my sleeping cloak yeah so
silky yeah but I just have gone to sleep
flowy dress yeah so just just as as
precious sleep is about to whisk you
away the little of living like so much
Calgon yeah you hear I started going to
scrape on the door it sounds like it
starts from about 75% of the way up and
it's almost certainly doing damage to
the wood or paint okay all right but
it's bits rhythmic it's not like it
isn't like a beetle or something it
isn't being chewed by a beetle okay the
pine said no yeah you know a friend of
mine goes and you hear no other beetles
yeah yeah you're likely to the end I
color the guy what we doing well where
were you just back in here
now he's in here with me oh yeah he's
right there just like just over the
shoulder just like it's right in here so
his little face is right here and then
the rest of the tail and barbs yeah our
down preserve along the back just
wrapped around the wrapped around the
shoulder oh yeah
it's chittering I think his little his
tentacle dreams yeah yeah whatever
whatever whatever his senses generate
for him yeah actually plank how tall is
that door no um I moved to get my
clothes on I'm already dressed and I
don't feel well
I don't feel that well why why is this
happening now another another another
frailty yeah exactly and he Richard
coils another grabbed on that reserve it
frankly it just ends yeah
why would anybody do this briefing is
more insistent in the middle of your
existential crisis all right all right
all right I'm uh I go to the door I
don't open it and but I say what what is
it knock it off
some people are trying to die in here
you hear you hear a [ __ ] a chittering
sound I for I know that that type of
chitter very well thank it's a door
beetle is my Ultron normal College know
I open the door yet framed in the door
the head of the creature is above the
doorframe but a chick saw from the bar
leans down and in like this you see but
one of the antennae sort of folds down
and up and enters the room and then from
one of his satchels you can see that the
his raiment is designed to be of maximum
utility to a multi-armed massive bug
person yeah so it's not again not
available from the catalogs just pout
and have strange pouches every replaces
you oh that's good place for a power to
death robot if I had a tiny arm in front
that'd be a great place
how I would be able to read somebody's
got dog now he was ready to go he folds
open a flap rough leather reaches in
grabs a Stoppard vial that has a piece
of paper wrapped around it and sealed on
one side and then he uh he offers it
first to one of his other hands and then
offers it to you with that hand in turn
I took it with this hand and I put it
into this can be accustomed exactly of
it and I chipped off my arthropod friend
what he's done he's already you're
you're trying to you're trying to
establish an authentic communion with
this creature and you know that they're
capable of it but maybe this particular
one isn't with you yeah right now okay
so all right let's son let's take the
note off yeah okay can i you see you got
that well the door slope and you see him
sort of tramping down that another
middle stair in a rushed away no just
like I did yeah I bet I did my thing
okay
I'm shut that door the wax seal has a
highly stylized rendition of a D and an
E so imagine a large D symbol and then
inside there is an e rendered in that
space okay all right
take a sniff that damn eels
I'm not going to opening it let's take a
look at this lick that feel as I had
many times tonight okay hey this is all
that it says know if that is the that is
this on the paper oh that's on the paper
and the symbol and what it says to me
yeah in doing it in a fine hand at the
bottom it says if you're curious drink
it what's the worst that could happen
I didn't know they had like door to door
soda salesman was a curious slogan
I wouldn't buy it a lot of bad things
can I'm jotting it down oh yeah don't
worry don't worry what if what you need
from the de if what you need is the
information let me look at any safe I
know that's why just melt it de across a
table Sarah I think it is no yo okay
dang elephants it's you're doing this
whole time dark elf its darkest oh damn
you know whatever you know bank it's for
a dark elf yeah I'm going to go back
through my copious notes
forget dark elf drink no I know who this
is
just wait nobody said it pretty sure
alright yeah I know it is been acacia
myself cuz I don't say things out loud
yeah yeah as well but yeah it hasn't you
had you had been an affiliate of
acquisitions incorporated as a as an
individual of substantial power at one
time right a nice level as a as a
warlock you know how to do Smee [ __ ]
yeah those times are past obviously a
previous iteration of this life that's
rain one another problem yeah you know
with mortal mortal frailty yet again in
line where the positives what's the
upside yeah I know I use I look at that
keep getting XP so how's the vial filled
is it just the simple just a very simple
very simple quark no that's nothing
special
hair of the dog yeah yeah a little
really gotti
like I've heard about the hair of that
dog maybe it's from that dog young clear
so so he's smoking with oh yeah okay pop
it open give it a you walks as we
chemists do yeah well what it what notes
am I good you can't
it is completely inert as near as you
can tell color
there's no it is jet black okay looks
what I wanted but if it's not sick it's
not sick okay it's ready to port
well not if I do some subject note on
the least well this is I dragons the
entire game is about checking out less
things before you drink them let's see
some drinks Archana
and looking at doors yeah yeah and I
roll the dice like that I mean
the dice are different from yours yes I
mean euphemistically Romi yeah
that literally McKenna that's going to
be a 16 yeah you think what in the way
that in the way that an acid break
things breaks things apart this just
from the dist from the word go that's
just its nature yeah you put something
in there and it would eventually become
a liquid version of its original self
this takes things apart with some kind
of purpose
like I like it reconfigures yeah like a
strategic purpose that's that's a check
in the don't drink column let's see
that's really my only check that I care
to make can i intimidate if you ensue of
that listen up yeah
let's meet GRU he's looking good so I
believe right to Chickasaw generation
cha-cha is I've come to observe them as
a friend
and so it's an half drunk half hungover
state I think maybe he brought me a
little good stuff
Oh miss give you some sample get a
strike creme beverage I'm game
alright at quarks yep yep down is the
whole thing in one shop cuz volume wise
yeah I had much more tonight yeah I
think this as it's a it's a minor amount
it seems it seems fine I mean it no
obviously no aroma that was a that was a
concern
yeah um flavor profile molasses hmm like
a nike molasses
that's funny and yeah I imagine like it
imagine like a hawk molasses so sort of
it this sort of a dank tang inside this
sweet syrup be the maritime way about
writing that would tell
this is the nangka design line oh what a
shame
um I roll with dankus check you mat 20
on there anymore 20 definitely counts
today Alyssa rapidly and I thank you
funny please make this happen where the
shadow council obviously you know mayor
Labor's please you now so we are vapors
what yeah you can put the stopping
background yeah and then eat legate sort
of looks at the top of the bottle nips
at the cork a couple times seems okay
the room is getting larger oh I don't
know if that's a problem it's having
like a lot it's getting a lot larger oh
um and go ahead and rest I guess the
hand that the hand that is holding the
stoppered bottle is no longer able to
hold it because it's gun so well in the
first two skin oh and then the muscles
and sinew and then the bone liquify the
rest of me - absolutely
okay you begin to pour down through the
slats of the floor down into the first
floor pour down through those slats and
then begin to travel at tremendous speed
underground Wow and over land where
underground doesn't work and then you
occasionally have to go even lower than
that
traveling along and through but
retaining this liquid form am i
retaining even in the sewer yeah but
your neck smack your classic senses time
son exactly exam cyst on perceive the
sewer but you're aware that that's where
you are traveling yeah it's incredible
speed okay I'm going to guess I go back
to the future sorry villain Ted kind of
situation where you leave us a note and
200 gold just like kind of happened in
there I said he did it guys
okay about that money classic
bait-and-switch tell me that money
all right so Karissa yeah that's recent
and as it as a culmination of this
scenario you feel like you are being
poured into a cthis drought like imagine
again it was the novelty container is a
metaphor I'm going to get a lot of value
out of to imagine there was a costura
Stroud themed restaurant where you could
get drinks in a crystalline a crystal
crystal drab containers yeah so imagine
that you're being poured like from a
picture into a costura Strout picture
it's just Mrs Butterworth yeah exactly
but but get rid of me yes yeah versus
Butterworth I got there but I did
everyone for whip yeah you were amazing
you're letting me hang and I'll get you
a burger you're you are defeated you are
seated at a table well it's good that
you wore your nice cloak because dad is
sort of that is the sort of garb that
you see around you in this place oh the
same cloak same style Club yeah you are
you put it on and it's nice and the
cloak of stars it's pretty well in this
fine restaurant okay dining experience
this is this is a dining experience a
pop-up you have a view of the water
this is this is this is living this is
this is fine living oh wow and it's
still a chorus draw themed restaurant no
no no isn't it is actually a gift rest
route themed restaurant but here's a
grander like an open for that bottle no
no no there's nothing like that and the
Sun has begun to set so the last few
rays that are sort of creeping over the
edge are a little bit too much and you
can even your distress as noted by one
of the attendants mmm in that fraction
of a moment of discomfort she comes over
and tugs a little curtain
so that it's edge just cuts out that
that part of the Sun come on thank you
that's right angle in those like yeah
that what our weather clientele is into
spot this is this is the the cream of
whatever crop this is could be judging
judging by the the location like v2v the
Sun the water could be water deep how
far that it's south of red larger ways
yeah but not me not an infinite distance
but I don't have any time today a long
ways to no drift no it's not it's not
conscious like that yeah you just have a
sense of the passage okay and the speed
but not the time
how's my angle ver so I think this is a
this is a side effect of it you don't
experience you don't have it okay that's
great good news I pick up that menu I
guess yeah like every time I drink this
is we're going to have you in eternal
cuddle I know yeah oh I can see why
people have you know I'm not against
this beverage and you you reach for the
menu and tip it up and over the menu
your dining companion is also looking at
the menu oh describe this companion but
this is a drow woman and so almost
instantly just purely from a raw
cultural perspective just like you know
you are from a matriarchal society just
the pressure like the disparity in your
relative social position even here in
this place like to be seated by each
other directly across from each other
just love is this is very modern her her
age compared to mine similar okay so I
think I'm in turn 80 nope
give or take 100 yeah who's coming in
seeing that I am shocked to be I think
so like casual about it
oh she laughs but if there's no there's
no edge in it okay there's no edge in it
at all
I bet that relaxes me some and I she
says she's just we're not in men's /
Esmond how how does this happen now
would what I like I'm trying to play up
instead of confused
yes delighted and please stick like this
why why why why am I here why am i she
said before and immediately all the old
structures erected themselves okay yeah
pick up that menu again clear much wrote
any any favorites
that's good here yeah real huh moms
spaghetti yeah big the evidence it sort
of goes down and it's like it's like you
know it's like from this field outside
of this town it's like they have to have
a session for exotic favorites oh yeah
yeah in a little call-out box yeah um
yeah if there's anything remotely drow
yeah yeah it's some kind of wet yeah
know anybody called engravings yeah
exactly I was gonna say mom's sphaghetti
certain sweater side no there's linguini
there's there's a cardigan missus sure
it is a 30 letter word that's about 40%
Z's that you know would just be written
mushroom in common yeah yeah I am and it
wouldn't even be considered like nice
food it really considered a normal food
already somehow through the lens a good
water d-brane binary yeah has become a
whole so yeah I didn't like like that's
nice
for the mushroom at the peasant dish yes
great ratatouille now I don't know yeah
it's over drop stuff now I really held
on to it Wow I guess I'm glad to see an
old favourite on this menu but I don't
have a major 20 she's still she's still
not looking up she says they just picked
them outside of town and diamond plaque
I am so mad she said that knowing that
that is what I would be eating if I had
ordered it
I want that taste of home that's the
section I wanted yeah yeah yeah that's
the only spot right there that notice
joke you're down back equivalent exactly
I thought when I was heroes family
different so if you want I don't think
you know I should google it let's stop
the stream real quick if you want to
denigrate the [ __ ] Olive Garden
I'm not familiar in my game you're
welcome to yeah we're going to come back
from in here yeah we're going back with
but there's there's all kinds of there's
all kinds of delights fish seems like a
good pick a good pick sure we have those
those sightless ones and those round
rivers out yeah no eyes damn yeah yeah
there no eyes are like wait way too many
items like you don't get to choose to
ice now those are the two lobsters like
your eyes just dive all that fish tails
until hi hi here's our ears our
bifurcation eyeball gills yeah so I may
die ah she she she tilts her menu up and
snaps with her left hand I start via the
idea did the attempt the attendant that
had modified the curtain comes over with
all the visual cues of deaf
that are demanded required expected okay
um she gets the salad my choice maybe
not
it gets the things on there she lived
above ground strips yeah yeah yeah yeah
this is it's not necessarily a
curatorial selection but right it'll
work in a pinch
um so what brings me here did you I come
here often
yeah she says did you like the symbol it
was interesting on the know if I'm
familiar with the script and generally I
am try to remember
no wait a long second let me step out a
character for a second this is this a it
was a logo or simple no use a glitter
glitter okay try to remember give it to
any the role to remember yeah I see a
role to remember yeah there you go
Obama symbol no but it doesn't it's a
narrative doesn't like yeah turned on
the other side and say this like a the
six items line on the bottom part of the
glyph I didn't even notice I did not
make this symbol up it's an actual
old-school symbols oh then I then I
don't know it but maybe Catrice does yes
so is it reject well it's going to be a
eighteen or nineteen sorry I guess I
know it yeah you remember it not from
[Applause]
scholarship but I have a hazy image of
seeing it in two places one in the Black
Gate that you saw in the gullet of the
wandering crypt it was one of them and
it's also one of the symbols that was
burned underneath the glass in the that
vaulted cave that it escaped through
okay so this is a real quipped this is a
business this is a novel this is a novel
entry yes
certified crit yeah yes from the from
the Christmas wanders this says a lot of
holes a lot of intrigue for me yeah just
wandering crypt business I think that
that has the that has the unnecessary
poetry that one has to endure a lot of
around almond drawn that was my
experience as well yeah yeah yeah well
we're obviously we're not completely
unfamiliar with your work that's good
because I am a lot of the time how do
you think you came to lose your powers
that is the question I'm trying to ask
but how long would you say after you
began working for acquisitions
incorporated what was the period of time
between you being a powerful warlock and
you going back to warlock school one day
well ray days the airship ride lasted a
while I would peg it at about seven days
to lose so much of what I had accrued
hmm well yeah she's not your right hand
hmm and a plate close on that is called
yeah oh yeah yeah oh really yeah yeah
yeah oh yeah exactly
and adults on I haven't thought about
that working here I'm talking right now
yeah
the tray comes out in this set in front
of you and when the top of it is lifted
you see a chunk of black stone that has
emblazoned on it this symbol that was on
the note
and it's sort of like they seem like a
like a metal like a pie plate yeah but
if it's drops and sort of leaves and has
rolls around like this it is as soon as
the top is removed it begins to sort of
undulate in a circular pattern on that
but on the train I've instinctively
reached for mine just to get after that
hold on exactly and it they want to be
together any day because this is a show
of faith from drawn enterprises
obviously your powers aren't what they
were but we like the we let the growth
track you're on right now
we like the career arc we see and the
fact that matter is that you wouldn't
have to work for us to work for us we
could work together even while you
remain a part owner of acquisitions
incorporated tokens okay I was trying to
find a way to work to let the in there
to let the kiss of Newt help doesn't
work so can either we get in closer some
spooky action at a distance that's for
the physics yes duh she's like I say I'm
not not listening
yeah with every you take a very long
time to go through absolutely everything
we know about you sir drought but we can
cover some of the highlights the
greatest hits right that won't take too
long
so when you encountered but again
wandering crypt there's a bit of
unnecessary poetry there the terminology
that we deploy which we feel is superior
and contains descriptive power is shard
lling now have you noticed when you cast
certain spells that shards are brought
to the surface of the planet have you
seen this oh the when I invoke my
tentacles that entity that you are in a
love-hate relationship with is that
accurate I'm just like it's like uh it's
like Street magic well my my see give me
what you're examining here this one of
the fascinating things that it does is
send pieces of itself to find its next
meal but something odd happened when it
did that here there were a race of
druids that made the difference on our
planet and took this world off the menu
at least for a time when the shard
landed they built a living prison around
the shard and they were confident that
as had happened at other times this
prison would hold but the shard is much
much being a part of a god a good child
of it in a way it had a cleverness about
it
and it transformed that living prison
into a body for itself it grew and grew
and grew
wandering crypt for lack of a better
term so that's we're going to say
burrowing crypt no the only does that
yeah it's a mob I'm telling you this
problems with the turn right we all talk
about it it's not a bad name yeah isn't
terrible yeah it really is something
else but doesn't that that's neither
here nor there you have spent some time
in the Charlaine correct yes
now what stopped you from going further
again out of character Manette sir I'm
going to have to remember what's tapas I
guess so we had we had encountered
Devine indeed later when you came back
inside the crypt itself this would be
good for everybody
yeah it's worth heads up right this
Black Gate okay it's been real circled
by symbols and there are three in the
middle when you interacted with it at
that time you had a single symbol right
but my focus began to that unfolds at
reduce more visible exactly I was going
on to that gate and try to communicate
with it right and I was ripped away by
my teammates because yeah it was a mean
situation couldn't get big meaning they
don't like and the room was filling with
apathy happen yeah so I so in regular
spectacular group yeah yeah they were
freaking I use I use my special power
and the power failed by the mouth god
yeah exactly to harm you and you argue
entitled him he says she says look I I
know that there is I know that your
employer has an interest in this crypt
that is beyond the purely archaeological
he believes certain things
about the contents of this crypt that
there are no proofs of any kind for but
here is how we can work together should
you enter their shard link a second time
you may find yourself passing through
first three doors and then two doors
than two beyond the last of these doors
you will see a silver curtain what we
had drawn enterprises would like you to
do is to kill anything that comes out of
it what from what my letter what it says
well no matter what it claims no matter
what it does and in exchange we can
sever the link that you have to this GOG
you have right now that may not be a
favorite it's not great god we're aware
of it we've had we have had agents in
the past who from one you know one way
or another
ended up in its management structure for
lack of a better term and it was a
negative experience for all parties but
you would believe that we know we know
how to do it and we can do that for you
anything that comes out of that silver
curtain must be destroyed and how did
you come by this knowledge how familiar
are you with this shard link are you
familiar with drawn enterprises only
crew saw really well certainly you know
a minute is Hereward drawn or no up
sadly yes yeah well
he's not the only drunk I shouldn't add
I also heard that he has two sisters
auspicious and pretentious yes and I
would like a character I had seen them
dead oh yeah you and you are a good
listener where you are 100% right sure
in the right time you are 100% right to
ask me this question that is the right
question to ask that back right now back
to kiss risk
I saw them dead we had retrieved their
bodies yeah she says my mistress is very
much alive which mistress mmm keep em to
you sorry I'm nothing like that no maybe
when you say which mistress you hear a
laugh for another table and she looks
over at them and they look at her and
then she says he's good you just need to
notice that there are more and more eyes
on you from different tables hazings
oh geez yeah now in my in catharsis
memory is able to tell because I
personally do not recall which one a
special attention was the one with their
head crushed and thus was disfigured no
they were beyond ready on yeah but they
were both in very very bad shape they
live in a table that the one who was not
identifiable not her that is exactly the
question you should be asking I can't
say as Jerry K Hawkins oh no you know
Danny Matteson he wouldn't answer
yeah well I'm asking I'm asking this
drought woman drew a woman yes show us
Oh a which which mistress yeah which
mistress that's why I want to know says
do ya do we ask and she will be indebted
to you profoundly indebted there's no
there is no telling the heights you
could reach
in an organization that takes such an
active interest in its employees
forgive me but I I don't seek height I
seek knowledge
yes fellows now I don't seek I say seek
knowledge but if height is the way to
attain that knowledge then we'll see
what I can do
where do you go where you want to see
everything I'm surprised that you have
been able to resist this treat for so
long here on the platter I think we're
all very surprised
we had a betting pool you know which way
did you bet you still have it you still
have a chance to make me some money here
in my mind there was a there was a test
occurring and at worst a opportunity for
my focus and this focus to absorb one
another
and I needed more information before I
would allow that to happen
you understand I'm not posed in the
slightest all our calculations have been
very clear on this point
be aware that
my focus is already as absorbed or
pressed is polluted by another schedule
this one and I do this there's somebody
else I come in and I do that in order
you are in the world that you want
winces Walker migration a little bit it
goes like this some reason she didn't
know she says I'm going to be out about
ten gold but you don't have to absorb it
now I have every faith that you will and
when you do you will be a better tool
for our purpose but there's no reason
for you to do it now I will you single
but you don't have to it is tingle
you're going to only ten gold if you
ever come and work for us
but you don't have to if you have ten
gold and you can give it to me now that
would be amazing
I'm looking to hear I'm like feeling the
table a little bit to see if it's like
is this cheap like she's a choices in
the jungle does not a lot so if I nights
in billion if I were to if I were to
come back at a later date for the focus
for the sigil but I have to drink
another vial is that the easiest method
of transit we have ways of of contacting
you
we thought you'd appreciate some novelty
I did oh I did it looks very genuine oh
yes yes just understand that our our
calculation our profile of you indicates
that no matter what you do ultimately
our aims will be achieved
so I bear you no ill will if you don't
do what I want you to do right now okay
so your very nature you will create the
outcomes we want and we thank you for in
advance
I say that's very similar to the
arrangement I have would be this God
that I'm in service of and it's worked
out all like so far but I'm but think
about q4
this is the firm that she uses yes SOI
lumen what's your five-year plan either
become all-seeing or destroyed so like I
said Sam's like I might like I said we
like the arc you're charting here sir
drought philosophically fill up on bread
listen yeah yeah filter fill up on
philosophical Brendon she says I know
you have somewhere to be
I reach into my pocket where the focus
is and I put 10 goals on the table hmm
she scoops it over not putting a falling
stalactite check on that we don't have
rain we have rocks that fall on us and
they're on the dark they are sharp
rain lights but I'm going to go ahead
and pretend and I really have done
rather do stab us but I appreciate the
opportunity and it sounds like you're
going to enjoy the outcome oh we have
watched with some interest yeah get that
coming out or would you just start going
to check yes yeah but then the resident
the rest of it extract the rest of the
meal goes is completely normal okay I
thought that's no be silent no that's
really food comes out always like a
really awkward first date without it
yeah yeah yeah it's just like it's just
a sound of
works squeaking on plate uh no no
attempted conversation are made well
here's the thing I don't know if it's
worse would even try exactly because of
the structure no injury I would really
have heard no and she I didn't she is
she knows what's up and she is perfectly
fine with it um the the after-dinner
drink is the same liquid that was in the
Stoppard vial so after after the meal
dessert that the last drink there at the
end is the same drink that brought you
here she raises her glass yeah
to you your help get to my hell brief it
yeah oh hell yeah she drinks it and
around the room people are lifting
glasses of the same fluid and just
disappearing piece by piece just meld
into a giant Porgy pool
yeah liquid it's just if it's very
evening out of a pool it's it's some
distance oh yeah yes they found her sir
yeah yeah I said that she drinks it and
then she turns into liquid and she goes
away and then reforms like in front of
the ladies room doors it goes a great
way do it um so you with some interest
and novelty you undergo this process
again I gotta get back
just as it as a frame leash yeah good
it's so fun that's true
all right that that scene is over walnut
on grass huh yeah me you you you so do
we want to say that the stand sick I
mean is that is the real thing that
really is just a prelude right oh yeah I
would just say that yeah I mean you know
whatever I should their Milan is a
ladder at the fans yeah yeah whatever
you have to doubt not know just that um
there was you know some like there's
like some
rotation and maybe Brahma recited her
poem in a very like aggressively flirty
way I know um yeah Sarah how do you care
some kind of bonding ceremony or walnut
what walnut would call it so they're
married now
yeah that's it yeah no not rot this is
the Joker the Chris maybe when I brought
a u-haul to deceive yeah that's what
they do that joke anyone watch The L
Word dance yeah similar ya know what
we'll get there we'll get there uh
Brahma is in bed and she is telling you
that she wants to burn the ship down and
make a completely separate life as two
new people because there's no way
there's no way for you to live the lives
that you want with the responsibilities
and with the people that are around you
that seem sad about it
she thinks as a matter of fact she
thinks that this is like a good plan
and she's put it together as you can
tell you can you look in your eyes you
can see the boat on fire but she knows
exactly how she Anna she knows exactly
how she would do it and I know she
showed me the both radically descendants
of Oberon plans she showed me your pitch
dick
um hmm I wanna look good right knee it's
me it's me wall not your friend
concerned sits on the edge of n she's in
like over normal apparel it's like
fixing happen and she's um just saying I
there's still things that I have to do
they're still things that I have to - no
I can't you
I can't just stop right now when are you
going to be ready to stop when I find
out when I find out who it was that
destroyed my groove and when I see them
die by my hand she nods she says I can
help with that and then that can be what
we do I can't it can all I had never
considered this option as a lone wolf
character it how could you help I've
been around the block a couple times
from it I mean that you might not have
liked the results but you know what I
can do when I'm pushed into a corner yes
uh well yeah yes we're talking about the
people dressed as vampires
the vampires okay yeah it's important
for insurance reasons than maybe
vampires right and then Walnut says
really loudly to the rumors of the room
was bugged the vampires that were very
real and not LARPers yes she says thank
you okay she leans up and then she says
turn around like six hit on the other
six hit away on the bed what uh turn she
goes through and then she is just sort
of meticulously by tightening each of
the armor straps like it's a little it's
a little bit too much hmm but she's just
she's just making you ready for a new
life
she said this this would be every
morning all right
and every afternoon have whole night oh
this is good this is what this is what
we need share this is what we need is
the best air babe last things that I
have to - no oh come on shoot out your
pocket yeah I want to go I want to go
with you but I spent the last who knows
how many decades of my life focused on
this one thing and like finding this one
person maybe you maybe you found her
didn't think that there was bring in
that story for more than just me she
nods her head and gets up walks over to
one of the decanters in the ice dish on
the table
drinks directly from the pitcher did
that Francey all right sir fat friend to
you white you only from acquisitions
incorporated and then she starts to put
back on her garb her performance garb
okay just piece by piece by piece and
then every couple of seconds she'd nods
to herself as though she is hearing you
saying no again and then just steal it
look like a like I Akane powder when she
found my life she has to take a little
bit she's just--she's inoculating
herself against - well I see this and I
go that doesn't mean no this hat no
forever just no no not right now is it
now or never I think we have dangerous
jobs I think that now is all we got
[Music]
Hanan you look at my bonds real quick
roll for ya yeah I'm about these roles
well okay okay all right I got it um I
go you think you can help me get my
revenge I know I can does it end with us
killing somebody hopefully I got a
couple notches there's like that that
like doubting voices like this is mmm
everything to perfect is not not my god
oh yeah and then there's the cord yeah
but you coming back and I'm one was this
like very she goes let's do this alright
and she gets out went our know is she's
important get wait a lot of on I think
that she we have to leave our corporate
they're both in acquisitions reverse
this stupid okay yes yes yes she's like
a okay alright James retains all be
maintained babe so that English isn't
interrogation
give or take
Wow we can work it out on the road I
guess Oh Mary don't worry
so yes exactly so she's drunk
yeah so I am coward she's like she
thinks I'm gonna do this boat job what
boat job what a boat Oh play yeah I'm
always gonna go job and that's also name
was three sex acts there's a yeah we're
gonna go job well we just have our guest
do the bow job we're both going to do
our respective dojo yes um well I'm
actually yeah you're here to play it
right yes right with us I'm here to do
security and also after I'm done
protecting it I'm also here to rob it
and I'm thinking that maybe while you're
doing your bow she goes up on you fast
when you say you're also so she is like
she's got she has like the but
everything from the waist up is on sure
but everything's in the waist down is
not on when I was in the process hey
would you say that you're also here to
rob it hmm she pounces on you mm-hmm her
hands are on your shoulders in the front
mmm and then she puts her forehead
against your forehead and she says
omaticaya wolf whoa
she says wolf wolf that's Enid I see so
dinar blitz in hey you were here you are
you were here with your your good friend
blue got fast friends fast friends there
was an issue very recently obviously
with blue Goths and the art wizard
numinous primp that very very nearly
almost came to wands and knives but he
is now back on his he started back on
his grind and numinous primp either he
was not you either he was authentically
unlucky before or numinous parentheses
an anything else going what's going on
here I'm just conveying I said was this
what it was like last week
oh yeah cargo split remember why I
always split the party yeah it is what
it good what is five pieces right even
your attention is split you're like I'm
here but I'm actually anything about
Jack on top of each other inside of a
cop
you missed a great day problems they
brought the frenzy of wine chest we did
check out these episode on YouTube yeah
we're back at our Delaware on iTunes all
right on YouTube all right we're on
middle I will try to her house and
explain the plot I thought all no
Riddler
that's right was viddler know I've got
patreon so euros yeah exactly tell agree
month mean you'll explain the blood only
on title yeah exactly exactly only piece
is part of doing noble little baby uh
continental I from joke but when they
were there as it had gotten to its worst
share and Rosie be singer swept in hmm
yeah and with a quick song she was able
to tamp down what witnesses what we
exactly what was yeah what would have
been like a magical artillery like
powder keg yeah on the middle tier of
this of this largely wooden vessel with
a cool awesome it would have been pretty
sweet so so smug off so there's there's
there was a blue got says so what's your
story what's your deal dragon oh you
know why got tail my god goofy years we
back oh whoa whoa what it was a fake
tail that is an arm you know Rio no no
it's a real tail of dragons oh my oh
it's worse though it's worse he actually
has a very small tail no and anywhere
it's like a prosthetic tail and I gave
my shoes look at my huge guys it's true
he's read your novel but uh that's right
that's right
yeah for tail teen chapter feel sleeves
let's not tale shame exact tail the tail
is an honor and the rest it's a good day
yeah that's the attachment yeah but but
yeah he's getting he's getting sloppy
some of these dice girls are going off
the table yeah I'm like
amen not that it is great to see you
again
by the way I loved when we met it before
uh why are you here just hanging out I
got too much money
yeah what's that like fine
yeah oh sorry tries to take the come
here yeah like this guy
yeah like blondie over here yeah okay
you heard me you miss new Miss proof
yeah yeah yeah good way not cool bro uh
I'd say all right well it's just you
know last time we met on really weird
circumstances I was just here doing a
thing you being here in LA yeah weird
last time we met under weird
circumstances because you were [ __ ]
with my [ __ ] I was me man how I think
you killed 30 goblins that's over the
your goblin that's it really
that's a rough estimate you got we were
they it could be more it could be more
Goblin well who's to say and this you
know work at a world I can say we're
mine Wow and you [ __ ] it up yeah I had
a good thing going they stole an egg
okay now listen what do you know about
that egg the egg mom yelled at me this
is what you need to know you [ __ ] with
me Celeste [ __ ] with you how do you
think they did they just came down they
just came down all the way from Scala
they just rolled down in four carts with
the Royal Guards they just rolled into
exactly the place where it was told on
me
you [ __ ] with me and that's [ __ ] with
you know this is a cycle we can carry on
forever we can just keep doing that
there's another way this yeah look
like I take a lot yes buzz was mom I am
a man all right
he tries to do the cheers on the side of
the face again what is likely here is
just on the side of the face all that
hard dodge it look sell cheer he he
brings he brings it back and sets it
down it's like listen I want to tell you
about the man that I work for all right
yeah I want to hear about you making a
lot of good points about omens so far
you driving him bet so working for omen
it's just it really is just a matter of
time until he decides he's more
important than you maybe you can
understand that maybe that's a joke he
would make but he's the one that wins a
hundred percent of these you the game
the game he plays is not one other
people can win so imagine imagine that
you worked for him dutifully in one of
his larger one of a larger franchised
offices and then imagine that you were
told you had been granted power to
defend that place and then when they
when the enemy rolled through you were
annihilated now what happened with me
that's a choice he'd save one guy you
can save another guy the end of the day
somebody's still getting saved maybe
just maybe you just that's the hug hand
you got don't this is cruelty that's
almond rum
so he he said he powered you up and he
didn't that's the man I work for
so eventually you [ __ ] with somebody who
[ __ ] back and we're putting we're
putting a team together right now
there's six of us there's going to come
a time where you're on the wrong end of
one of these deals and we're going to
have a place for you in that happen
doesn't even matter if you die from it I
died a couple times it's all right
it hurts to die depends on ER yeah it's
a coming back that hurts
hey I join this under certain pretenses
that so far I haven't seen so I'm always
listening this adventuring company been
doing a lot of adventuring so far this
kind of I joined Pinterest so you know
everybody is yeah like the first word
from a buddy oh yeah we're like okay
yeah I want to know a lot of dragonss
you guys we have one dragon yeah okay
what's his name
I mean his name is knowing that I'm not
going to use
oh no BIA we're doing for a dragon I
think it was the aware dragon name I
think I think so too is too it's really
it's really short
I may be nice yeah via so dragon names I
think it's cool man yeah yeah big all
right there you hear a murmur from the
crowds out low you're your bodyguard
sense starts to tingle and then you see
costura strobe emerge on the cynic lab
yeah nomura pissed clue my bathroom on
the teleportation circle just sort of
like a light light like a dog who wants
just like right there just like flats
played out in the middle of the in the
middle of it it's not a performance but
it looks like it is a strange
performance okay I actually thought I
was like boarding the boat and let's
just sort of all enter our rooms like
okay everybody
okay so I've materialized on the ground
yeah okay
I think against that against that the
stage took you part it is a bizarre
situation there is sort of like floor
bulbs lighted floor bulbs you are
looking out like I mean it's like you
were on a performance stage there are
people some people dining around the
Oakside clapping do toyo and I'm not
here okay I materialize I I jump up
surprise and then try to play it up
another restaurant
ah this is good this is what I want I
like to move so behind you behind you
there is a massive stained glass
structure sort of interlocking triangles
like teeth to sort of make up the entire
window structure behind the stage okay
you see a lower floor and there's a
middle floor above that looks down and
there's a high as a high floor up in the
edge okay and I'm on the bottom one you
think it's okay first thing I do is try
to reach out assume um they send me to
the boat which was nice of them yeah hey
I got on the boat hey is anybody there
reaching out I'm probing with my mind
there yeah he's closest to me I'm on
that I'm not on a stage in a mouth I've
never liked it I never like that this
kind of mouth for the mouth with you we
also got the gall oh the draw tab your
wallet goes to voicemail
yes I can't get through here I was
connecting to you a silent moment yes
the place is goodness you're back where
were you sweetie just sleeping it in
sleep it off which everyone is the had
to go for a big big emergency drow stuff
those are the property of the drought
body that you just got to take care of
don't worry about it without going to
note sense no it's it's funny that's
exactly what I figured I was in a hurry
and I had to I wrote that because it's
less ridiculous and where did you go
then you know just uh rustling up some
clients checking in on what are you guys
up to
how did I get how you come to ten how
are you faring it's going really well
really yeah you has a hold on let me
patch in my daughter yes hello this is
my daughter Sharon she's not like home
now oh yeah you've seen some crazy [ __ ]
with Gorman with you dinar
oh I'm just hanging out with slew guys
okay he's awesome okay well that's cool
but we just checked on Brahma and Roman
in there they're doing really well whoa
oh yeah
Rama's on the ship yeah bronzed
ownership she's a warrant for my
wonderful daughters a word ludus as well
and way better oh [ __ ] Rama is so
overrated it's very nice for my mind to
make your minds acquaintance I knew -
every time she's got it but but you're
situated outside of that frame in that
bear wall you can see what looks like
the outline of a door around with
shadows are sort of pouring in and out
of breathe right a turn that's right
that's where you that is where you a
fellow fell on down and d-did right
you're in hot pursuit
okay can I direct fits wrists down here
to make some arcane ass decisions you
can but currently we
he's not known to the guards right they
don't know I was about to ask like so
what I'm now that I'm here at my
security or am I on the other job that's
it's not a surety that's you yeah so
your opposition to the plan was yeah we
were all any screenings but I think well
we are in front of the place that needs
to robbing sure I think that's I think
that's the case is there any can you
like disguise yourself as like a lizard
person or maybe you like wallet
get down here get down to where you are
am I able to tell all of you just when
you described it Tamaki threat okay
gosh where I am on me it could help me
disguise myself
what's the culligan what's the client
Taylor I'm always I'm going to look out
for like am I the only drow in the place
we use the general sort of reptilian
looks
yeah and that works for us yeah but I
think the clientele here is pretty
pretty out there I think this is the
kind of place we Australia now there's a
bigger one yeah yeah a blinking room
right intrigued yeah so I know beholder
calm it can't be intrigue and get on the
case you can be intrigued later okay I
am I do my best to well I'm going to
play against type because I may not like
look weird and see key like I already
think that so I'm going to appear
opulent like um ah I'm kind of a high
roller yeah yeah I can attack secured on
the oculus
yes exactly opulent appear in Sofia and
yeah so I just walk instead of slouching
I straighten up I mean you you did you -
he did materialize on there on stage on
the stage
so he goes so you go back behind the
stage to the kitchen through the service
quarters to the area with the structure
to the crew living area and then there's
a vault know meet up there is that we
cartographer at nice we know aren't we
the only people running security other
than for some lizard man with some
built-in security additional security
okay as I'm receiving directions from
you I walk down as though like are
dealing with
what annotation and I'll run to meet him
in case there's any trouble I can say
he's with me
there we go like as he used s you sort
of like coming through the last part
he's starting to develop an unsettling
level of interest that you are able to
tamp down in addressable in a timely
fashion if you think I'm taking too long
you just you just it's awesome all day
yeah okay so evening exactly so you have
your very own Chris Chris job I mean
it's what everybody wants this Christmas
this Christmas anyway the way the way
that it works
Chris is that you you have a natural
attunement to shadow and so for you it's
not a sophisticated process you you are
just aware of it like you would be any
other phenomena its behavior is known to
you forecast RIS you just notice
something is odd here but you don't know
what it is hmm odd in front of the vault
or exactly sort of vault itself is
actually paired with the living quarters
it's one place they live eat and sleep
around the actual vault what Rosie and
share have found is something else
entirely a secret door here in the guts
of the ship right okay
is there any kind of perceptions that I
can do on it since I'm so familiar with
leaves of shadow refer for right now
that there isn't anything that that
needs doing I mean you literally see
this like a like a physical like a
shadow mist okay sort of pouring out of
these doors and breathing in it like it
to you it's as plain as day okay there
is a secret door
osei-san see okay and there's a smoke
this is billowing around the door hinge
and just share see it but I don't think
that share is attuned to shadow
this is a process that you have I
understand you learned from your
monastery okay so I all I know is that
this shadow is cast into a secret door
and we should totally open that door
okay explore slash examines yes you hear
a throughout that when you were up on
the main floor there was a way of there
was a way of projecting a voice that
could be heard and the music as well
there's a way of projecting the voice
all around and that for those voice
projections are apparently audible even
down here below the ship because you
hear a voice that says in 15 minutes
prepare yourselves for a night of
incredible music from our own Bramall
ooh yay oh my girl oh and so yeah it's
like it's funny like a slapstick
slapstick tear funny trying to give the
clothes on fast hmm like it's not a
hundred percent working and no one wants
to put them on so the whole thing sucks
but you come to you come to some you
know you know dressing tear that is
acceptable for leaving the suite and
make your ways out of the golden doors
shadow council mayor labor spacing this
is our break here we're going to try the
facilities and we will return to
entertain you shortly look away
hello shadow council mayor labor sees
you when last we saw our heroes rosy be
singer cher Basinger and cthe wrists
route had collected themselves around a
mysterious door in the base of the
Dragon sports a river going house of
chance now from from the secret door
force mysterious shadows so we will get
back to that so we will get back to that
part of the crew
in just a moment dinar blitz in is with
splooge oath the returned still got the
returned deep deep in his cups revealing
things that he perhaps should not 100
people to his new confidant in our boats
n walnut dawn grass and Brahma loo da
are mostly professionally dressed and
have now made their way out of the
golden doors at the High Roller section
of the dragon's hoard so howhow are you
protecting Brahma in this context how
are you how are you delivering maximum
value as a bodyguard in this in this
situation tell me how it feels to come
upon this and like say what are my
chances right okay um so walnut is um
anytime they have to pass through any
kind of entryway she gets in front of
Rama so she can enter first okay um and
looks around and then you know just
gives her that like she knows to just
keep going cuz she promised but yes does
the cursory look and then when she's
moving through a space
she is directly behind her hands on the
Scimitar for mother and is keeping her
eyes on her the entire time I love it so
she's sort of leading mmm of course
Romilly yeah exactly so I listen I just
nothing I don't understand about this I
see this Merc I know what's going on so
you you get all the way all the way down
then where are you wait like where are
you during the performance hmm um well
I'm her personal detail so I'm assuming
we like go through some kind of green
room situation
so I'm backstage you know when you're
waiting in the wings they can look out
so just doing round so I can look out
and see if there's anything like I have
eyes on the crowd because I'm but sad
but out of someone lower tier yeah yeah
exactly so you sort of looking up but
you can see the looking at us looking at
the crown I can say
exactly and her back is to the glass
wall itself yeah okay all right I like
what I'm seeing
Brahma okay even even even just
preparing this loop for a performance is
a performance like she's you are there
you were you like it the most but there
is a look a pre-flight check that goes
on for the for the loop and maybe at an
earlier point in her career she would
have she would have been more discreet
about the Arsenal that is present in
this thing but that's not that's not
where she's at at her at her care of
notoriety and performance there is
knowing that this music is being played
on a weapon of mass destruction
is part of the lure sure I get it so
she's been playing she's been playing
for about 10 minutes and splooge off has
gotten increasingly agitated so by the
play by the play no he just literally he
just like I can't I can't [ __ ] pay
attention I can't I can't pay [ __ ]
attention I did this is not why I came
here I think it sounds nice you know it
doesn't it doesn't
it's I'm with you yeah yeah then or just
get out of here that's the worst he
grabs he grabs archibald or he grabs the
arch Wizard Prince dice and just throws
him over his shoulder off the top or
tear off the upper deck and you hear
somebody you hear someone down below
boom boom that was nice yeah game is
nice back ah yeah we don't have to
listen to music there's other parts of
the don't lay it everywhere there's no
place on this [ __ ] ship you can't
hear this music this is your first time
here it's my first time here with her
okay my last [ __ ] time here with her
I know right
and Helia he wants to turn away I don't
have you ever been in this position I
have been in this position I'm not proud
of it there was one time where I got so
drunk this is not a character this is
actually Jared cave or camp that my
fleece was configured such that it had
those sort of like flexible draw strings
for the pockets and I walked by a
pinball table and I one of them got
caught on there oh yeah and there was a
not insignificant period of time where I
thought there was a force field yeah
right that's the situation if I were
here he wants to get off of the stool he
thinks that he's going to turn and do
like a tough thing and he actually falls
back off of the stool yeah
and hits his back and then rolls up
quick and picks up the stool and throws
it over the front down toward and
clatters down toward the bottom of the
stage mm-hmm he starts to sing along do
it does it look like someone threw it at
the stage oh yeah he starts to sing
along with it yeah what is your parody
of he is singing a parodic version
mocking of it yeah you see him reach for
a knife do i yeah yeah yeah no no this
is walnut vision yeah okay you like you
have this whole thing assess of predator
stuff you can see it yes you can see
here you can so you can you can see that
this has come straight over the top you
thoughts and diets come over and you're
like okay and then you saw a [ __ ]
stool come over and then hit the ground
and skitter toward the front of the
steps to go to the stage and now you can
see this same individual who got the
returned reaching like what there's no
hiding it like there's no mystery he's
not he's not even he's not being a rogue
okay I want to say that I I do I see
dinar yeah right next window usually the
nurse unit seen dinars like his
silhouette rise
behind him his gold scales are sort of
catching some of the torchlight Isis
hand as I pre have produced a flame and
I'm holding it and if it looks like you
gonna throw it that will trigger my move
uh I'm gonna try that again
I'm going to try to talk them down I'm
gonna try to persuade them I like this
don't do it man it's be like chill out
cool just normal persuasion cool out
cool out you got them that's Plan B oh
yeah time thing
nd I'm gonna take advantage too okay um
let me see it and I'm gonna say spooky
cool out take a chill pill there's a
room somewhere with this music aim plane
we can go hang out there
now let's Jack Jack that's Jack is your
goods going hey badness on my team okay
Oh actually you know what we talked
about this I'm gonna use my disadvantage
dice as advantage oh yeah no it didn't
help because yes [ __ ]
I'm joking don't come on okay thank you
no I don't do it I'd I've done quite
well are you putting a hand on him uh
I'm just no yeah I know yeah yeah I'm
just as I'm saying this as I get up no
II say that he snorts and it's just like
it's got to be four or five tablespoons
worth of slimiest poop all right snarl
oh that's a no yeah that's what I say
all right well then I'm going to go for
Jerry Connick entailment to try a really
pushing to do what I was talking about
do you have you have a yelled yet they
did it for I I don't will not here Rosie
says she loves it yeah but do you have
versatile yeah person our eyes first of
all on him yeah hmm always
also know we're here sure one yeah
what's in the nation stage left
egg this pays really all the exits eyes
are born out put the load the spaceship
with the rocket fuel
it's a classic of the warrior with her
the different wrestling from of each man
it's great
who got the return you and me got to go
to another room
oh yeah I want to be nice for example
are you doing audible no damn work yeah
I got one more I say oh sorry a name
your first I fit the kitchen
oh yeah all the way he'll never stray he
he pushes it back in to the holster
attaboy
eight walks up comes up behind you he
says well made it one maybe 100 hold it
as he but he has so many but you see
this - you have a ball of fire ready to
go yes my friends you see Brahmas
attention turn up to the upper floor of
the stage of that best second floor like
directly at him and it's I mean you it
didn't require Arkana
to know that this song is materially
changed rope in complexity so it was
loose limbs are sweet and classical like
but very very much like this is for like
a grandparents like this is like the
songs of old but executed with taste and
style this has a lot of percussion
like slapped against the front of the
lead like that everything has just
changed and like you can just see that
the tendons in her arm flexing as she
that she performs this piece yeah I mean
yeah and then live and then get into it
he has so he has gotten this other
dagger and he's put it up and then as
soon as that music starts to play he
just drops it and it falls behind him
and then he starts to walk in sort of a
staccato music word and it's sort of a
stutter steps way toward the edge of the
of the upper tier and he is walking over
to the edge and holding onto the post
and he's like putting his leg up in Troy
like he is trying to he is trying to
throw himself off fling him to safety
good day out yeah well I got a grab him
I'm sure he'll love that to save him so
he doesn't fall and hurt himself go for
it land on someone and hurt them to toss
that toss that's funny I like it do our
bones athletics yeah it's great we were
basically going to do some Rachlin like
this is what you this is what you do bet
I do
I do enjoy good rassled meaning yeah
that's that's real good just basically
sliding the rest of his way over and
just let's go let's go right off of the
edge of the of the set and you are able
to you were able to grab him right
around the middle and sort of didn't
just like flip him back over and another
in something akin to a wrestling
maneuver I was going for a baby crib
that surely it was one hand was when I
you're looking down and then he becomes
an egg yeah uh so you bring back and
didn't just fling him down and he gets
up and is trying to get around you and
try to go around I fling himself off of
the edge she's great well I'm a big
strong tough boy so grapple him up good
let's do it good dad wrong like yeah and
just keep you just keep a hold of them
yeah just keep get them in that full
nelson yeah yeah mission a partial a
partial nelson lady fisherman's suplex
right a portion of them bet the whole
knows because well there's no mana
momentum hold nelson yeah it's an entire
know i love it
it's the milton fan so I'm getting
Mandela's so you so you you start lacing
but he is it's like a cat's cradle type
scenario like there's no escape there is
no escape force plug off the returned
got him I'm strong boy he picked Elin
are kicking up a jumping kicking forward
trying to sweet baby try to calm him
down and cool yes cool help everybody
cool out after after she's after she
seems that he has been restrained the
music evens out a little bit and she
looks down she looks down to you where
you're looking up and she says I look at
her I've been very sick this whole time
but contrary myself a little bit
endoscope and then diffuse low supply
all right now basement team team
basement let's get at it
so you can see much of now you know you
know that there's there's something here
something malevolent oh I'm a so deed so
tell me no no no yeah the call came from
inside the Chris so do you have do you
have this other chunk of of focus you
just have it in a pouch which other
chunk if you have you have the new
brother so oh yeah I've got it just with
you yes okay that's why I wonder in this
check no I don't like the kid I'm not
let them touch okay okay no not yet I
don't want to get in deeper with the
areas and then leave
this one I want to like muddy the waters
it's a classic it's a classic scenario
so so that is exactly where we are
situated here okay before again it looks
completely featureless okay except for
to you you can see that there is some
kind of strange physics in operation
around this door and this this is not a
doing a perception or our can of check
not going to help up here we should just
throw it open try all right yeah I mean
for you to see for you it's easy to
finally say for everyone else okay this
is just something you're telling them
it'd be like you said hey there is a
yeah totally a dragon kind of trap check
anything like that
I got to do me any good here chop check
classic D&amp;D trap oh you gonna be right
these are the traps we don't want that
Nicki Minaj no I love it
thank you I love it yeah that's it all
right trap check I'm jealous a
perception mmm no trap no and in fact
you think that there's pie in there this
is safe let's go around yeah there's a
good door there's a good all right I'm
just going to pretend Archie I'm going
to UM golden sort of elbow my way in
front of my daughter
in no car the same size if yes this this
protector not at all be like I got this
mi your speech and I open I go to open
the door
okay it has no handle of any kind okay
oh one of those one of them password
doors yeah
could be could be you know see as the
keyhole okay it's a store eclis where
people were you would for it yes it
there's a cheesy it's really sitting
it's a door it's featureless but we just
don't have a way to get in yeah that you
can see so far all right I believe you
can i you guys have any cool door
opening spells nothing back the door a
person because I could try to turn it a
maid or okay it depends on which episode
of the show you I know where were you
the first one yeah like describe the
door is there any is there any opening
of any kind in it others it just like a
cracker you really yeah you basically
see what looks like a scene so they look
dirty
come on can I beat it up it feels me
yeah this all looks like it's data stone
stone door okay
I'm not going to kick it yeah I mean all
I got a I mean brute force such as a
warlock Tom Locke has I mean I try to I
can try to whisper to the door are their
house is it that's what I was asking I
was trying to figure out whether or not
I could send the body through a minute
and then the misty stepping aside but
doesn't seem like a good ass snake in
here okay okay alright can I can i peek
through the crack l is it enough to see
inside
you can line up the next year okay I'll
try that good I'm so you get you get
close and try to peer through you're not
sure anyone else could do this even then
it's sort of like it's like when you
look at like it looks like the view
around the edge of a lens yeah where
it's just sort of warped a little bit
but you can see up this close you think
that you hear water but inside this room
it's very dark if I had dark vision
would that help me at all uh darkened in
that there's not much there either like
okay just sort of like a there's do you
hear you hear like water splashing
inside there okay okay I have any reason
to believe that Locati
singing through its eyes would would
show me the door I just try it I don't
think I'm I see nothing well I can point
out the door yeah yeah yeah gasps oh no
but if I'm gonna if I'm gonna teleport I
have to see it with my own eyes oh you
mean mr. stuffy do it right got it I try
it all right I'm gonna switch I'm gonna
switch with a guy you real fast you can
hold the gotti yeah and then switch to
him right and but I put it I hold it
here so that I it's not that different
of a view yeah yeah yeah so I go ahead
and then I spotted some new and oh my
gosh yeah let's take a look for my
feeling yeah you see you see yeah this
pitches do 80 pitches
we're all seeing that no matter where it
is pay attention you say are you with
the other one charlie pictures with a
naughty door symbol okay
you can submit this is from pretty like
old-school like tastefully old-school um
symbols of protection from scrying and
things like that okay
big goals don'ts cry I had that written
down four weeks ago wait again that's
incredible yeah listen that's a premium
experience so he's able to look through
there you can you can sort of see this
water but the floor and there is is
lower than the floor out here okay but
it looks solid yeah you get you feel
like you feel like there is a it's not
dropping or anything like that it's just
like a moat almost so if I if I miss you
step in there yeah
and I should be fine oh my god II would
be out here actually take a little drop
thank you everybody and made follow me
bottom oh damn it alright I might go in
there alright I will go ahead and misty
step through that that keyhole I suppose
and I'm glad he will drop exactly yeah
so about it legate drops and then just
just just on a little bend of his
delicious noodle swaps around angry for
a little while well yeah and then he he
starts sort of like just poking at this
get this crap this would describe this
everybody else is visible he's just like
shrine again okay guys and say okay
laughing against the back of it from the
inside
um you can see you can see like a stone
circle that you can turn from the inside
okay like a look at sub yeah yeah Anna
okay let me go ahead and do that
you're annihilated okay well I was
getting to violation yeah we were still
playing down and like literally just the
two in the denial is
it's actually two pages and one of it is
a table of contents you don't mean like
it sucks it's the other one before work
so I think I've had it so you can't
metagame like your players will excuse
no I I have it it's super long um it
isn't just two pages I promise
um I promise it it may be really good
because you're amazing everybody on my
right now wrote it and even if it was
two pages it would be amazing so you
need your the attention to drink I as an
Android dragon but you'd give it a twist
and then you push it open and then for
you you can see that this shadow mist is
just flowing and like once it's like the
pressure changes on the shadow when the
door opens it just starts to flood in
it's like it's pulling in even more into
this central chamber than before but
when you teleport and Chris yeah Chris
grout by me that was a lot you're
actually about three or four feet below
the surrounding floor it is actually
much lower inside here and low like
there's a moat okay does it go around
the room yeah yeah we can tell us that
it branches out to the left and to the
right and then continues it forward okay
how far into the room am i able to see
now yeah and you the extent of here you
can actually see the entire thing in
your vision I mean it's literally only
like 20 feet this way 20 feet oh okay
okay let's set that back when I look at
ya hmm let's draw a picture 20 feet
display let me beat this way I quickly
jump back into a guy what do they get up
to initial change automatically 'no
dirty adventure let me know you're the
one saying the words right away boy
Scott oh yeah do I feel like like this
is a shadow that is my ally or does this
feel like a rolling kind of shadow yeah
yeah yeah absolutely this is a this is a
this is a manipulation
of the shadows you know this is a deeper
richer truer shadow than you're familiar
with and it's still awfully fun Brad
yeah exactly
Phil it's so silicon philosophical bread
you have light and shadow and then you
have to contend as a matter of personal
improvement with this with your shadow
but it's you typically like a
euphemistic interpretation of this these
shadows have their own nature and
character that seem independent of light
casting they are co-equal it is as
though there was another type of light
hmm and I feel chill with them you don't
you don't you don't hate them you think
they must be related in some way to the
shadows that you have power over okay
but but but as they but as you get
through this threshold and as as you are
sort of like in the wake of these things
pushing in you can hear things in them
but you can hear little voices that
accompany them in sort of in like a it
isn't a cacophony you can pick out
individual things but it's groups of
voices and cheers and laughter and the
rolling of dice and the knee is for the
things like you're hearing like as these
well as these shadows are flying by you
you're hearing all these moments in them
okay hmm that's odd
so I think the thing to do I'd like to
do a little just for fun just do a
little pass about trace on us as a group
and we will then have plus some bonus
itself in case it comes to it and I
think I would like to pick the passage
to the right okay
as everyone entered in yes you rent
yours from everything so stupid mom my
mom's cry oh my it's like when you get
to the crosswalk you know I mean grants
a little hand get a bike I thought this
was a phone plug some time in the room
no no anyway that you have the cross
wall so as you as you come in it's the
both of there are many children zone yes
there's mojo yes club so as you as you
as you enter into this and begin to go
around the right side stone circle in
the door spins the opposite way and
seals with a click and it is at that
time that the water level rises from its
current we're talking about hassling
neck chin level water here oh this is
not high and cold young the bill yeah
I'm not that tall either is not gonna
feel good for me we're up above it all
right no no this is actually a trou I
think that goes around top neurologists
wrong if they're only ugh is a true is
there a raised area that we hope get to
ICS no the entire thing is like a moat
yeah okay the entire path is like a moat
and as soon as the door clicks the water
level in this section begins to rise
precipitously okay okay that kind of
it's the while I do this oh I need them
you take two points of damage
sure as as the water is rising you feel
just like the jagged edge like a like
the edge of a saw alright then it's like
the edge of a saw just like catches like
the the side of your thigh okay and is
that normal for fantasy riverboats that
that's not common okay this is not this
is not on the pamphlet okay it's like
get your thigh underrated
yes and our like that's not more like a
sanity riverboat casinos got it I turtle
Patrick I'd like to I want to use vomit
og just sort of out of desperation to
see if I can throw that door back open
again hmm
from back right here on the corner yeah
no dice no dice is it locked
oh this so the water is now from the
floor to the ceiling so we lit from the
windows on the ball so it is it is from
the very bottom to the very top started
the complete and now you're here yeah so
we know we're sorry here here here right
here can your old famous [ __ ] here do
we have any names yeah
I need to know your Constitution bonuses
actually in goodness gracious
well I want to tell you +1 same
ok we're on the same boat
I went to I get it's true yeah we could
use those boat chokes monster they work
good just into some entire jokes when
you sort those though if the water goes
from the very bottom like I say this
displaces this volume space is
completely full of water so you tell me
where tell me where you're traveling in
this in this space you've come around
our corner to the right there are
current no no no it's just just about
block of water ok
can I bear like that I would like to I
destroyed a block I dig on beneath and
around in my eyes I'm do did you do yeah
so this place is full of shadow
what would the power of Grandma man see
have across a hot pond shadow like this
ooh that's super cool I think the it's
pretty dark in here I think that you
would need some kind of light source
- and you hit me with a light first
always alright let's see what happens
do some very fire for me smile there
anything like it
it pops those dancing lights that's
right Elmo glimmering lights it what's
the shape you want to give them your man
what's your preferred like weird nearly
like manner
close your club man well you know go man
- oh yeah glue man brand gloaming feel
like I'm I despite myself I'm just going
to do some light yeah what does Joey
stuff but I actually invokes my Justin
you know like this figure of comfort
you're panicking yeah it comes out as
little man thanks for having whoops all
right is them in for my gold man that's
okay I make this work story yeah where
do you want to be want to consume more
I'm up high okay Virginia I'm staying
there but if you need them on the ground
to cast that light so shadows go up he
just pee like reclines yeah Emily wanna
I like if not yeah exactly me in my
drowning room this is are you would he
he don't feel like it's a specific
designated drowning area um how many
fake friends Institute's have there's a
lot of different enough that I got for
all the real ones he did so really what
hold on of them so you see that because
because you've had a positive experience
with his going man yeah previously yeah
you've managed puzzles cleverly with my
use of going then yeah he materializes
in his friendly pose and it just it
casts light through a sort of writhing
twisting it looks like a spinal column
that's covered in sharp Barb's where the
ribs would be um and it's topped by a
novel potentially even curious skull
sort of enough ideon snaky skull okay
is this guy I can you try to talk to
yeah so are we like are we
but has been informing yeah I'm track
all drive I'm tracking time yeah alright
so we see this thing yeah I'll say not
friend yet but I do you speak I do we
can't live here
we don't breathe this what is this I
didn't build this machine but I do like
it
can we go back to how it was earlier and
then you can turn it back on when we
leave I don't think so I don't know why
I would around the corner the far corner
you see a goblin sort of float upside
down into view if you look dead quite
amazing how long a fresh one fresh oh
okay and you already drowned he's good
to go out the fresh wine we have like I
like a breathing apparatus we could
steal no no okay sure those one final
breath out of me a little one breast
right so he says sometimes I have to
kill them but I don't like to and
usually I don't have to if I wait
they'll stop moving classic scenario oh
yeah like no no judgement we just we
just don't want to die
is this yeah oh that we like the machine
to reason with nothing to knock the
machine of course you you won't live no
I mean that which brings us this to our
previous point about we would like to
live and if there is there anything that
can be done so we could live I asked how
I guess I'm typing you through because
Veronica yeah III hortie do you hear
what she had to say just a shadow
I want to hear everybody had no equal
voice try stay calm no I say how many of
them do you require
required there's there is a whole
structure full of these more all around
us can you bring them okay absolutely
littles will they die as these did we
resume all do you mean yes a delight how
many can you bring where it's more than
us certainly many more than I was really
really little I would like to see that
just like we all with the voice did calm
the body a woman trying that but I'm
like when we all I have no control over
it maybe one um died they will come down
to it's a difficult place to find we
found it by chance
hmm when's the last time you were able
to feed other than this one and us
potentially why don't I don't need the
body what do you need hate the death oh
now this is interesting
[Applause]
oh my god drown so is it doesn't matter
I but I've cut you out the two of you
and then like I'm just gonna listen to
what this fella Philips leaving a sweet
embrace bone daddy I know I switched
back to bother you that he's gonna get
our death that's what he wants you just
want to meet he doesn't want to meet he
doesn't need to meet it's a cookbook
alright you just you know are we
completely underwater thoroughly
yeah if I speak a word underwater does
it still have a spell casting effect
yeah because it's it's a it's still
audible even if it's quiet okay
I mean if I was going to be on who I was
going to be why I actually am what I
would do is I would truncate the range
but the range is here very close okay
mmm-hmm [ __ ]
yeah I mean let's see it was there any
lemmings
no no good all right what's a shot hey
how did deliver this fellow death
talking about it I know that's your
specialty
Josh Cortina glad his death is a problem
the death of another you don't you don't
know that meetings that would return
Aman I guess is with a worth a question
and Jim bet would you even consume your
own death I say this purely out of
curiosity I consume so many deaths I
might be gourmet you've had a steady
diet yes hmm regular slaw ground dead
yeah the foster care program isn't able
to consume any other way final mmm we're
gonna get some inception out of this I'm
going to need some persuasion yeah yeah
yeah okay
all right so let me address all given a
kill all right well maybe just
permitting it I don't know that he can
do it you know well can I give him guard
against per Asian yeah quick
oh please similarly under are you blind
I'm flying I don't know I can maybe
that's worth a question let me first see
if this succeeds and then we'll inquire
but I'm guessing it huh you can't work
it up ah geez no no see when one does
experience I'll tell you about also
thank you very crushing welcome t as a
d6 to is roll with it yeah that's
exactly that's that's my memory of it
here there's gonna be a hearty hearty
roll so if I'm doing persuasion because
I will take an advantage I got in Seoul
advantage you're doing okay let's try it
let's just try okay think up the best
oh well I'll need out what it could be
six I believe so so I will be I'll take
the five I'm going to add that to my
persuasion of four and then let's let's
hope for high roll on this B six big
money
- okay mmm all right it's a 13 yes
monokote he says okay but if I do it now
imagine how much more delicious I would
be after your death yeah Yair yeah good
point
yeah like well said oh yeah yeah well
Tatum he gave his counters off you know
he says he says he says it is awesome
this way lissa bargaining near the end I
only seek information the machine what
is the machine full of them no I'm your
old yeah yeah oh yeah I know but we're
gonna yeah so like I say it's time the
press so here so here so here you are I
got certain Hartog refer you got shadows
yeah here's here's your cartography
scenario yeah you've come around this
corner you can see that it goes up he is
in the next corner up that and then the
passage continues on to the left past
him okay no no if we're going to be able
to go over there living it means yeah I
suspect he will try to eat us if we go
past him uh it's the natural death he
seems like you're just going to hang out
until we go all right we can we just
keep going past in that Bank oh um it's
an underwater music my hands your okay I
suppose either of you guys are nervous
we still have half of that trace so we
could try to sneak past him you
extinguish your glow man but I don't
have time I don't know I might need him
all right I'll just you I would see you
ago all right Rosina goes first
she's she swims cautiously you able to
up to this thing no movement and then
skirts past them I guess I used to swim
okay you're gonna snap at you okay you
can get past him but he can see you in a
snap okay
and he snaps like a pro impatient he
snaps it like a pro g-man right up laid
on the table first
14 points want me oh yeah yeah no you
see anything on that no this justice
hits okay this hits okay yeah he gets
ahold of your arm and just shakes you
underwater and you're able to pull
yourself away as you round the corner
you can see that much like the door out
front there is another featureless
partition inside here around the central
core and you can see that the shadows
that move in to the front sort of slide
around maybe there they travel through
the water and then they go into another
doorway that you can see can I see that
the thing to know but there is that's
not visible on this side okay but you do
you have you have shadows you have all
that you have all the all the tools at
your disposal
okay let's grab em and see them yeah all
right so describe this to me
grandma Mansi is your capacity as we
describe this want to make sure we're on
the same page right will you go for it
just just just crank it up and go well
okay grandma Mansi allows me to take
control of and manipulate shadows so I'm
going to I'm going to do at least one
thing which is reach out to the shadows
that I can see in front of me and push
them through the cracks in the door and
up toward what I think is the mechanism
by which this door will open
that's very cool on it that's not what I
saw you do have any either that's
awesome does it work yeah totally works
that's amazing okay else we got relief
or a little water exactly okay so water
rushes out it's just it's like a fish
tank yeah breaks in front and in the
three of you are sort of pushed out and
deposited but this thing has no interest
in that and water is a natural place for
it so it's able to keep itself out the
last push of water trending
scooch it out the edge bites onto the
lip of the door and then Rises its way
back down the place that you find in the
center of the half of this power right
jerk yeah the the central column of this
is spatially distinct from what it
should be I mean from from your card you
know from your cartographic you know
scribbling right this should be you know
yay big it's going to be about 40 feet
on a side okay and it's going to be
about 20 feet on a side and that's going
to be the total volume of it that's not
what it is at all okay now in fact when
you as you pass through this is another
another physical space and you can see
okay you can see the shadows sort of
traveling they're still there whispers
these moments of victory and joy that
are travelling down through them and if
you emerge it looks like a ruin almost
like a Greco Rowling type ruin columns
columns are path columns are stood up
full columns are laid down and snapped
in the middle you know there's just just
chunks of marble everywhere and in a
central place beyond these beyond this
sort of like marble forest on the way to
it
you can see that you can see a sort of
Plaza that is ringed by these and the
plaza is sort there's a seam along the
middle of this Plaza where implausible
implausible
this side is has physicality and this
side is made up of shadow interesting
and in the center of this plaza you can
see a decrepit Lizard King
a just heaped with the finery and marks
of his station and he is clutching a
gigantic Jim that is sort of misty gray
and purple and all of the wood no that's
the thing I know okay Michigan and these
it I think that's the thing we have to
rob and these moments these moments of
joy are flowing out some of these
moments of joy are going right into this
Jim that he is clutching he looks he
doesn't look alive but he has gripped
around this gym and this shadow energy
is flowing into it
a portion of it flows up onto the table
that is positioned between him and a
shadowy version of himself and some of
some of this shadow stuff is collecting
itself in the form of ships to his right
and these two appear to be playing a
game down in the core of the dragon's
hoard what games you may appear to be
playing um you don't recognize it okay
so when you you don't recognize shadow
version of him he's playing against this
undead just like he have given how is
this one playing we haven't seen that
most yeah or is it like his his pieces
his pieces his dice raise up and our
role I see it in front of him to his
right so you've clearly come upon
something something of a ritual a social
gathering backgammon club from beyond
space and time situation sometimes I
think D&amp;D stood up and then 2 to 2 the
shadow Kings left is a looks to be a
halfling woman with a red cloak with a
black
and around the edge and this cloak goes
down to about the shoulder and then on
the left side it actually extends far
down like a full cape and you can see it
you can see it's silk sort of spill over
the haft of a sword underneath it
initiative shadow version corporeal she
is a combination of machine she has
shadow it by way of this place shadows
seemed to be very shadows seemed to be
very concrete comparatively here her
face even not even underneath the cloak
you find her face very hard to make out
it's very sort of polymorphic underneath
that that's not true for you and it's
not true for krisstraus oh but you
cannot make out even underneath this
part of the cloak like it's just very
shadowed and to the lizard Kings right
is someone who is speaking sort of in a
low tone to this woman and then he turns
to the lizard king and he says is this
acceptable my leash and immediately is
sort of gripped in space lifted up and
then just flung away you don't even know
where he goes you have no idea where the
[ __ ] he went he just when he was in a
catapult that me [ __ ] was want from
it Wow and this is the scene that you
enter what do we see a nice face okay I
just underneath ya see a woman's chin I
don't know if you guys have ever done on
a riverboat but this is really common
this is how they all are yeah yeah
Brian's already got this figured out
when I was a Louisiana it was the same
exact yeah like tomorrow at Disneyland
yeah exactly
so John wired so too much treasure whoa
so the the woman chuckles at this
a newly airborne intercessor and says
that's five in one day and she says oh
these must be the replacements indeed
friend we see then friends and never
give up getting different stuff um what
what have you
creatures done with the shadow here let
me catch you up there's the voice from
beneath the two lizard Kings are not
speaking in the classic sense whatever
their dialectic is it's connected with
this game and this energy they're waging
back and forth right right she says how
our task is to arrive at a solution for
a social problem and a metaphysical
problem simultaneously thus far we have
been unable to do it this key this only
take a second this King Anna for 700
years has been the ruler of his people
and there is a ritual that they can
undergo to bring him back to life the
ritual has ceased to work now due to the
gracious assistance of my king he has
been given a system by which he can
retain life but he what the Lizard King
would like to know is how is the true
nature of the malady that ails him what
my king needs is an heir to follow him
to the Shadow Realm
thus far your king I assume he is the
king of all your people ah details a lot
of people a lot of them certainly thus
far he has been unwilling to
a steal accede to this wish we asked for
one son
the shadow daughters but the shadow king
wants the Lizard King to be his heir no
just provide him he needs one of his
sons one of his many sons okay so one of
the Dead Lizard King sons a prince
perfectly except it would be a shad okay
okay the problem is that anytime a
person tries to talk sense to him
he flings him into space it's been a
challenge for us I see is that where
that guy went with space we were
wondering well that's what we call okay
they're like a splat sound when you know
nothing servers K rockets and there's no
cartoon and she says it's possible that
you as the six will be able to talk some
kind of sense into him he can learn what
he needs to know we can maintain our
legitimacy in the shadow Court this just
seems very straightforward I'm not sure
exactly what the problem is I think that
I it's possible that if we work together
we can and then immediately behind her
someone rushes through like Liz like
like the lizard by the shadow version of
the lizard Kings the manner putting down
spears trying to stop this person from
coming in but he is just like in a
dazzling martial display just slicing
spears in half he's kicking people and
he penetrates all of the defenses and
comes up behind this woman that you're
talking to and she her body language
visibly slumps and she says this has
happened this happened a couple times
olá
and she turns around and he says I have
I have I have his name on here I have
his name no damn it no no no he says he
says oh I know you have waited for this
day
Rosie bee stinger it is I the dawn
lariat and I have risen you will feel
the crack of my whip and then she's just
like okay okay all right and he's like
he's like yes yes I know you quick and
you're very and then he reaches up to
his cheek which has started to bleed
like so that he says yes you know you
know this day was fourth other cheek
starts to bleed and then he he realizes
that maybe he has done the math on this
incorrectly and then as he starts with
you know his fourth Proclamation that is
profound capacity and reaches for his
sword the hand is gone and then he
reaches with his other hand and it's
gone and he looks at the situation that
he has created for himself and
lizard-men dragged him away
that is all we have time for today on
this episode of tasty teams good to have
you back with risk who obviously an
absolute pleasure share is always shadow
council mayor Lee receives you we are
going to go and use the facilities and
then we're going to come immediately
back and we're going to talk about all
this stuff and more don't go away
well you should
you