JERRY: Hello.
I am Tycho Brahe of Penny Arcade and PAX.
I am also Ominifis Hereward Dran,
CEO of Acquisitions Incorporated.
But today I am Jerry Holkins and I am running a game of Dungeons &amp; Dragons for my friends.
Who I will introduce now!
Over here to my right,
Amy Falcone as Walnut Dankgrass.
JERRY: I've got Ryan Hartman, as Donaar Blit'zen-- RYAN: (clapping)
JERRY: That's... okay.... good!
RYAN: No one? JERRY: Exactly...
KRIS: (soft clapping) &gt;&gt; RYAN: Thank you. JERRY: I got Kate Welch.
JERRY: Not your grandma's grandma.
Rosie Beestinger. Monk of Shadows.
And Kris Straub as K'thriss Drow'b.
A warlock who doesn't 100% know what he's gotten himself into.
RYAN: Impish. JERRY: That's right.
KRIS: Right. Delightful though. JERRY: Indeed, indeed.
JERRY: Hey so, before we get underway, we have our classic interactions from the channel as far as
advantage and disadvantage. Don't forget to put those to work. They have offered them to you.
You may need them to survive. But there are some boons and banes up there also. That's new stuff.
I just wanted to make sure that people know what's up.
Reflux will refresh your breath weapon, Donaar.
RYAN: Oh, nice. KRIS: Mmm!
JERRY: Walnut has got Forest Friends. Now maybe it's not as direct damage oriented as a spray of acid.
AMY: It's fine.
KRIS: A spray of small animals. JERRY: From your thick sacks.
JERRY: But... small friendly animals can help you get dressed and, you know.
KATE: (gasp) &gt;&gt; RYAN: Ooh. AMY: Disney Princess!
KATE: Oh my god! JERRY: Do some-- just rock it Disney-style, obviously.
JERRY: Back In My Day. So obviously Rosie, you have had many lives before this one.
This modern incarnation is but the most recent.
Back In My Day will let us grant your proficiency bonus to any of these old tasks under the assumption that
you've done a little bit of everything over the course of your life.
The Neuveunomicon, K'thriss, will let you consult the book of shadows or your focus, and then you can use it
to gain the effect of Augury, which is a spell that will just say if something is-- It's Weal or Woe.
It's like, is this a good idea or a bad idea?
KRIS: Okay. That's valuable. JERRY: Right?
JERRY: It's like a magic eight ball... RYAN: I was about to say.
JERRY: but devious and mystical. RYAN: Ooh...
KRIS: Just like the magic eight ball itself. JERRY: Indeed, indeed.
JERRY: All right, hey, now.
We are about to get underway with the second episode of the "C" motherfucking Team.
KATE: (whispering) Yes...! RYAN: Titled?
JERRY: Are we ready to go? Yeah. This, episode two, entitled "The Test Market."
RYAN: Nice. I like starting with the title. AMY: Don't act like you got it!
JERRY: Oh yeah. No, no, I think starting with the title--
RYAN: So wait, we should-- what's the...
JERRY: Shut up! RYAN: What's this infer?
KRIS: Let him do it! KATE: Write it down!
RYAN: Write it down...
JERRY: No, it's an acrostic! Can you solve it in time? No, no, no...
KATE:  You can scramble it to say Lord Voldemort!
RYAN: The test blarket? What's a blarket? JERRY: No, this is some Dan Brown shit.
RYAN: Can I...? JERRY: No, it's like this. Donaar, shut it.
JERRY: So when last we left our heroes...
RYAN: (self high five)
JERRY: When last we left our heroes you had mounted four hale, hearty mice.
And you were on your way running towards the guttering point of the Homeward Star directed by
Rosie's lifelong fascination with the stars.
You have yet to see the creature that the mice have called Onyx,
but you know that such a creature caused all the fur along the ridge of their spine to ripple with terror.
That's the main thing that you know about this beast, whatever form it might take.
AMY: Weird. KATE: What could it be?
JERRY: Yeah, it's totally nuts.
KATE: I'm riding my mouse and I'm telling it in a very conversational tone stories about mice
that I've met in my long years, and asking if the mice maybe knows any of those mice.
AMY: Because they're all... JERRY: All mice know each other?
KATE: You know what... maybe, it's possible... KRIS: Wow! &gt;&gt; RYAN/JERRY: Whoa.
KATE: She can talk to mice! AMY: She's older. I get it. It's an older way of thinking.
RYAN: I apologize for my grandma. KRIS: It's not so cool anymore.
AMY: I apologize for my halfling friend.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. KATE: She's too innocent.
JERRY: It's been a problem in the past and we're all a little embarrassed. But it's fine, she'll forget all of it soon.
So, here's the situation. After probably 2 hours ride, the light has begun to dim out in the windows.
You think that day and night don't function correctly.
This was true the first time you experienced it in the first iteration in the Dran &amp; Courtier.
These don't seem to be the traditional day and night cycles at all.
It's some simulation of it.
It's some interpretation of day and night at some whim.
You're not exactly sure how it's measured out.
But as it begins to get dark, the spell has worn off.
You can no longer communicate directly with these mice, but it is definitely time to
make a more traditional camp and get at the long rest.
In this case, before, when we do a short rest-- what that means is that a lot of your individual powers recharge.
You have the ability to spend hit dice and regain hit points.
The long rest can grant you some of those hit dice back.
But it also recharges all of your shit and gives you hit points.
AMY: Okay. KRIS: And the longest rest...
JERRY: Yeah. AMY: We get it K'thriss!
KRIS: Dismissal... From the table.
JERRY: And then obviously the longest journey, you're accompanied by friendly animals.
That's a different situation.
But in order to provide for this rough and ready crew, I'm going to need some more survival from the pro over here.
AMY: Sure, the pro is me for those playing at home. JERRY: You are the professional--
JERRY: in this context, yes. AMY: I'm the professional survivalist.
AMY: Okay. So just a little survival check?
JERRY: Yep, yep. Just a little survival check.
AMY: All right lets see what we got. Big money! JERRY: Give it to me at the full juice.
KRIS: Getting hungry. KATE: Get that juice!
AMY: Argh... ten.
JERRY: Ah, that is not quite enough uh-- KRIS: To survive. &gt;&gt; RYAN: To survive, you die.
JERRY: to feed all of them. You can feed four people or animals with that check.
KATE: Uh oh.
AMY: Well...
JERRY: They gave you advantage dice
JERRY: and you did not use them so... AMY: And I did not use anything!
JERRY: that's not on me. RYAN: Summon Forest Friends, eat them.
(laughter) AMY: Well as a druid I do believe in the circle of life.
JERRY: Exactly! &gt;&gt; KATE: It's true. RYAN: Yeah right? You know? Sunrise, sunset?
KRIS: Summon them in my mouth. AMY: I say... I look to the team and I go...
AMY: Once again realizing that we have never properly introduced ourselves to each other,
AMY: so at this point I say--
JERRY: Hey I'm a druid and..
AMY: I go, hi I'm your druid. I was in charge of getting your meal for you today here's the thing--
AMY: No. Walnut just says, she goes-- JERRY: It's one of these restaurants.
RYAN: Yeah. AMY: I go...
AMY: Due to the sparse surroundings that we're in I was only able to procure enough for our mice friends,
who I think it's only fair to give them the food because they carried us the whole way.
Then I look at Donaar like maybe he has something to say about this.
RYAN: That's fine. No, I'm okay with this. AMY: Okay.
KRIS: It's all right, I'm full up on disappointment. RYAN: Yeah. Yeah.
KRIS: Stuffed. RYAN: I'll just eat my anger.
AMY: I'm worried that they won't be able to carry us... I also have a hemp rope you could eat. 50 feet. so...
KATE: Yeah, I have a bag of sand. KRIS: Yeah, bring it on.
RYAN: I don't have to brush my teeth if I don't eat dinner so that's a good thing.
AMY: So, even though I can't communicate with the mice I obviously bring whatever rations
I was able to find over to them.
JERRY: Yeah, food has historically been a form of communication.
AMY: Mmm, they're big on that. JERRY: Yeah.
AMY: That's all I can do. JERRY: So you feed them up.
JERRY: I would love to see constitution...
JERRY: ability checks from all my people. KRIS: From everybody.
KRIS: All right. KATE: Oh boy.
JERRY: That's a one, Rosie.
KATE: But! I do have lucky, I can re-roll a natural one on any ability check.
JERRY: That's good for you. KATE: Thank goodness.
RYAN: Oh Jesus. KATE: Starting it off strong.
KRIS: Can I burn this advantage over here?
KATE: 11... plus one. So 12. KRIS: Let me throw on that. So I have my garbage roll...
RYAN: Oh I get plus two, all right. KRIS: And I have an equally... no I'm okay on that one.
KRIS: Okay, so I got a 14.
JERRY: All right, that's okay. So you've got...? KATE: 12.
JERRY: 12.
KRIS: Ah I found some jerky, it was right here! Had it the whole time.
AMY: What have you got? RYAN: Eight.
JERRY: Eight... AMY: Seven!
JERRY: Se... All right. The two of you are distracted...
by hunger.
It isn't a serious-- 100% serious thing but you do have disadvantage on rolls.
AMY: Oh, just that... &gt;&gt; RYAN: All rolls. JERRY: Only serious if you want to succeed.
AMY: Oh. RYAN: Yeah. (laughs)
KATE: It's a shame because I do eat human meat, but...
JERRY: Yeah.
KATE: but we don't have any humans. KRIS: No.
KRIS: Not available. AMY: True. Right, I just forgot.
AMY: Me Walnut, that I'm not a human.
If we're gonna conti-- I don't know what your plan is but at some point, I want to say now,
I would like to establish the watch schedule.
JERRY: Absolutely, tell me more. KATE: Learned that lesson.
JERRY: Let's hear about it. AMY: Oh, I will take first watch.
AMY: As atonement for not being able to provide for all of you, my traveling companions.
AMY: Strange though you may be. JERRY: Okay, I like it, who's got second?
KATE: I'll take second.
KRIS: You'll take second? How long do you need to sleep as a halfling?
KATE: Not long. JERRY: Yeah, how long do your people sleep?
KRIS: Right. (british accent) I'm curious, I hope it's not rude... but...
(laughter)
I only need four hours. Like I figure that's four, four, we get through the night on eight.
KRIS: I mean, provided that that's a real night. AMY: We could just stay up all night and party!
KATE: Yeah. I'm usually in bed by seven... AMY: Elf time!
KATE: but I'm up at like four. KRIS: Right.
KRIS: For that early bird special. RYAN: Yeah, the blue plate. &gt;&gt; KATE: Right. Yeah.
AMY: This guy needs his beauty rest, I assume.
RYAN: Yes! Eight hours. Start to finish.
KRIS: And then another four right after. RYAN: Plus I've gotta... yeah.
RYAN: Another 15 start, I need a wind down period too.
RYAN: What does that count as? KRIS: I've got to read for a while...
KATE: It takes me a while to fall asleep. JERRY: It's like your amount of rest equals 27 hours.
RYAN: Well, because I'm gonna get-- JERRY: Per one day cycle.
RYAN: I can't go to bed fussy. I need to cool down. KRIS: Right, settle down.
RYAN: I need the me time.
JERRY: You got the... you have a cold bath, then a hot bath, then a cold bath.
Absolutely. So we'll slot you in...
KRIS: Second, I don't care. JERRY: Third slot.
KRIS: I feel like that gets us in there.
JERRY: Absolutely. KRIS: How long we sleeping?
KRIS: It's a long ass night.
RYAN: I'm like, man, you-- KATE: Rosie's already asleep.
JERRY: I need these. I need these treasures. KATE: She's out.
AMY: You need your trouble dice. JERRY: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
KATE: Oh I don't like trouble. JERRY: Well no, no.
JERRY: You will like it.
You will like it because it will create a dramatic scenario you'll be able to tell your friends about the next day.
AMY: It's true. Nobody makes a movie about the weekend nothing happens.
JERRY: No. KRIS: Weekend at Bernie's.
AMY: You're right.
KRIS: Yeah. That guy was dead the whole time. RYAN: Yeah!
JERRY: That's the exception that proves the rule! KATE: Stupid me.
RYAN: But... he wasn't.
JERRY: Shut up! KRIS: I didn't watch the ending!
RYAN: Oh ho...! AMY: Oh my god! &gt;&gt; KATE: God...
JERRY: There's a stat-- KRIS: He was rotting!
(laughter)
JERRY: There's a statute of limitations on this shit.
Walnut and Rosie... you do what you do. Nothing particularly odd occurs during your watches.
AMY: Oh! RYAN: Wow.
JERRY: Is this-- What's...?
AMY: This is a special handshake that we've already come up with.
JERRY: No. It didn't work guys. KATE: We worked it out in the cab.
KRIS: Clasp!
JERRY: I'm going to apply negative-- for that type of... KATE: No!
JERRY: It's like somehow you manged to leave each other hanging.
JERRY: I don't know. This-- it's never happened before! RYAN: Yeah. &gt;&gt; KRIS: Incompatible.
KRIS: Protocols all wrong.
JERRY: Well listen-- Don't hadoken!
That's even worse! That's a blast of psychic energy.
All right. K'thriss. I would love to see what a perception roll means to you.
KRIS: I'm going to give you that, and I'm going to burn one more of my advantages.
Also I did take two, including this one, so I should have three, not four.
Or not five! Come on guys!
AMY: Can someone please nerf this warlock? Oh I'm sorry. He's on our side?
KRIS: I got to-- No, it's good. AMY: Never mind.
KRIS: So let's see. That's trash. You don't want that one at all. You want this one instead. It's way better.
KRIS: It is way better. JERRY: Is it?
KRIS: It is... 21.
RYAN/KATE: Ooh. JERRY: Jeez.
JERRY: So you hear-- KRIS: No, it's 20.
JERRY: Yeah-- it's-- well-- it's--
RYAN: Oh never mind. AMY: Don't bother.
RYAN: Game over. Kill the stream. Sorry everyone. Bye.
JERRY: Eat it. Swallow it. Eat that dice!
No, no. Don't do that. That's actually a metal dice. God only knows what that would happen.
JERRY: So everyone else... is... RYAN: (whispering) Hey you got four.
JERRY: is in various states of repose.
There's a little trickle of acid leaking out of the corner of Donaar's mouth.
RYAN: All right. JERRY: Directly onto the wood.
JERRY: But the amount of damage, very small.
JERRY: You know what I mean? KRIS: Negligible.
JERRY: It's not like an Aliens situation where it's like multiple decks. It's fine.
But you hear a rhythmic bass rumble...
that carries through the wood of the great floor that you are resting on.
KRIS: Bass rumble. RYAN: Mmm.
KRIS: Is then-- I can't determine a direction. It just seems like beneath?
JERRY: It feels omnipresent.
RYAN: There's a party in the bowels of the ship. Like Titanic.
KRIS: Yeah I'm trying to remember whether or not this bar had a basement.
And maybe that's the case. Maybe they're just cleaning up. Getting ready for the day.
RYAN: Trying to remember the CAD drawings? (laughs) The architectural layout?
JERRY: Yeah. For the heist movie.
KRIS: This is second watch?
JERRY: This is third watch. KRIS: The third watch. Okay.
KRIS: Who's the least likely to be a Cranky Gus if I rouse them?
KATE: Me. JERRY: Probably be a grandma.
KRIS: Okay. KATE: Mm-hmm.
KRIS: (whispering) Hey! I wake you up.
KATE: (whispering) What?
KRIS: (whispering) Do you hear that? In the ground.
KATE: Do I hear it?
JERRY: You feel it. KATE: Okay. I can feel it?
JERRY: Yeah. KATE: I can feel it.
KRIS: (whispering) What do you think it is?
KATE: That's a great question. Thank you for asking.
KRIS: (whispering) I'm sorry. I mean I woke you up to determine the answer to that.
KATE: Well I think we got a miniature situation happening here, so my guess it's either footsteps
or perhaps someone walking around upstairs.
We should maybe wake the others.
KRIS: Where have we made camp? Is it on a central location on the floor?
JERRY: Your guess...
just trying to map--  the scale of the environment,
trying to map it, you think that you are underneath a three-legged stool.
So it's got the long trunks that come down at these sort of extreme angles over here.
And then a round canopy at the top.
KRIS: Okay. Yeah we got to wake everybody up. KATE: Yeah let's wake everybody up.
KATE: I don't trust this. Yeah. KRIS: It's concerning.
KATE: Wake up! KRIS: Get up, gang.
RYAN: Huzzabuh!
AMY: Being woken up on third watch, does anybody take any penalties to stuff that they're getting back?
Don't bring that up to the DM. Who's talking?
(laughter) KRIS: What?
AMY: Sorry! JERRY: You fucked up.
KRIS: It was a ham radio. Interference. JERRY: You fucked up.
KRIS: Did you hear that voice? AMY: Just joking, folks!
JERRY: You guys were already relatively well rested so I'm not going to adjudicate it too much.
But as you are roused from camp, you can see that the mice are wild-eyed.
RYAN: Ask them-- KATE: Could this be Onyx?
AMY: This could be-- RYAN: Ask them what up?
AMY: I am saving the ability to talk to something for when we meet Onyx.
RYAN: (sigh)
KRIS: Hmm. Wise. JERRY: So your first thought, Rosie Beestinger,
is how long-- dead run-- how long would it take to get from where you are now to where the guttering candle
of the Homeward Start points to this door.
KATE: With no mice to help us?
JERRY: (stammers) That would be-- With no mice to help you-- you don't even want to consider that yet.
KATE: Okay, okay. RYAN: Yeah.
KATE: All right. JERRY: You don't want to consider that.
KATE: Okay. JERRY: We're talking about perhaps an hour.
KRIS: They're going to run anyway. We may as well be on their backs.
KATE: That's true. &gt;&gt; KRIS: That's not even a thing. RYAN: How big is this room?
RYAN: How small are these mice?
JERRY: Are they going to run the right way? KATE: Sure.
JERRY: You know what I mean? AMY: Mmm!
JERRY: Are they going to run the right way? So you see against the opposite wall, against the door,
you see a black shadow. Almost like an elephant's truck, drop down and dip...
KATE: Ugh. AMY: Great.
JERRY: on the other side of this canopy.
Swoop down and curl up languorously.
Like an upside-down question mark. Curls up around the edge.
KRIS: (whispering) That's a cat's ass-trunk!
RYAN: Ooh... AMY: (coughing) Sorry, had to cough once.
AMY: (coughing) I've been holding it in!
JERRY: No, no, it's fine. I understand that we're all dying of some disease.
AMY: I'm ready!
JERRY: Some random disease! AMY: It's all the dust being really close to the floor.
JERRY: Yeah, oh exactly! AMY: (coughing) This is in character.
KRIS: Bring it into your performance, yeah.
JERRY: Obviously there are mites! RYAN: Use it!
KRIS: Yeah step on my choker. Dumb cough. KATE: Giant mites! We've been riding them around.
JERRY: It's all material. It's all material.
KATE: If I had to pick an animal to talk to, it would probably be the ass-trunk of that cat.
AMY: Sure. RYAN: Talk to the tail.
KATE: Talk to it. Talk to its butt.
AMY: I would like to-- KRIS: It must possess a rudimentary intelligence.
KRIS: It's part of the spine!
JERRY: All right. KRIS: Surely there's...
RYAN: (laughs)
AMY: Whew... wow! KRIS: No more.
AMY: I would like to try and parlay with this cat who I believe to be my friend Onyx from before.
JERRY: Well here, so how are you going to get at this? Because it may do something as you're trying to do this.
Are you going to approach this as a ritual casting of the spell? Which wouldn't require a slot.
Are you going to cast the spell directly?
JERRY: Things may move too quickly for you to-- AMY: To be able to stop?
RYAN: How much bigger than us is this thing? JERRY: to get at that.
AMY: Oh big. KRIS: Yeah, what's the scale?
JERRY: We'll have an opportunity-- There's a reason why cats fear mice.
Part of it's the scale.
RYAN: Cats fear mice? Or mice fears cats?
JERRY: Listen. It's topsy-turvy. The opposite. RYAN: Oh all right.
JERRY: Don't worry about it. KATE: It's Dungeons &amp; Dragons, dude!
RYAN: I know! I keep being told that. KATE: Cats fear mice in this world.
(laughter) JERRY: It's Cats &amp; Mice! It's Cats &amp; Mice.
The mice begin to paw and scratch agitatedly at the wood. And you see them lower their shoulders...
AMY: Okay. JERRY: like ready to...
JERRY: Ready to try to make a break for it. Ready to try to keep their part of this bargain you struck...
AMY: Okay. JERRY: to get to the door.
JERRY: So they are--these mice are ready to collaborate with the party in trying to get the fuck out of here.
AMY: Okay. I mean then maybe we should just go and if the cat intercepts us then deal with him?
Like let's just-- the mice are going to go without us.
KATE: Can you cast the spell on the go?
KATE: From the back of a running mouse? RYAN: Aren't we supposed to be killing--
RYAN: this cat for the mice? AMY: Yeah I would just have to deal with concentration.
KATE: No, I don't think Walnut's going to let us kill a cat. AMY: We're not killing the cat.
RYAN: What? &gt;&gt; KRIS: I'm undecided. KATE: I don't think Walnut will let us kill a cat.
RYAN: Circle of life! The cat's going to kill the mice otherwise.
You're going to broker peace between cats and mice?
AMY: I can't go back on my word.
JERRY: Would you like to talk about this...
AMY: On the mice. &gt;&gt; KATE: Yeah! JERRY: On the mice. &gt;&gt; KRIS: Mouseback.
RYAN: Once we run away we like-- AMY: I really can't break my oath.
JERRY: Do you want to do a-- RYAN: I think we should kill the cat, everyone!
JERRY: It's like an Aaron Sorkin-type thing. KRIS: Yeah.
JERRY: Where you're just jalking down the corridor. RYAN: Yeah.
KRIS: Breakneck speed.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. But you each get a cool pithy line in there.
So yeah you have got a handful of the fur around this thing's neck.
And once everyone is on, it's like the shot of a gun. It's like the beginning of a race.
AMY: They're off. JERRY: And they are off.
JERRY: Bouncing back and forth over these troughs between the boards and the floor.
You pass underneath a second stool.
AMY: Okay.
JERRY: Cut to the right underneath a chair. This is something they know how to do.
There's a lot of zig-zagging underneath these-- basically wherever they can find canopy,
they are trying to emphasize that.
They reach one of the larger canopies, what you assume is one of the tables nearest the door.
And as you are riding forward, you see what looks like a waterfall. You hear a heavy-- like a loud clank.
AMY: Oh no.
JERRY: And you see what looks like waterfall sheet-- like an amber waterfall-- fall straight over the edge.
And we need to keep these mice out of the way. They are completely panicked with fear.
But everyone else can tell me how they're trying to manage their mouse situation...
in the face of this new threat.
KRIS: Oh man!
KATE: Whew! KRIS: That cat's trying to piss right on us.
KRIS: That amber sheet-- (laughter)
KATE: Is that cat peeing on us? JERRY: That amber sheet. It's thick.
AMY: I don't think it's cat piss. JERRY: It's gelatinized urine!
KRIS: Rips of cat urine!
KRIS: Flooding the entire-- RYAN: Ropes of cat urine?
JERRY: No, no, no. It's-- KRIS: It's entwined!
JERRY: It's thick like a whip!
Like it cracks and-- No, nothing that's--
JERRY: None of that's real. RYAN: Just a pungent, real acrid--
KRIS: Oh yeah. RYAN: Fills the nostrils!
KRIS: I hate it, but... I kind of like it.
JERRY: I respect it! I respect this cat's urethra.
No! It hits the ground and begins to coil-- No it's nothing like that.
JERRY: It's like a spring-- None of these things are true. KRIS: It's like honey.
RYAN: Yeah. KRIS: Uh...
JERRY: Anyway, so K'thriss. Let's start with you. KRIS: Are we currently-- we're in formation--
JERRY: Yeah Exactly. Imagine that there is a greyhound racetrack except it's all small people on mice.
Imagine that configuration.
Just sort of a loose phalanx rushing toward this surprising, heavy curtain of foamy, amber liquid.
KRIS: I-- (laughs)
KATE: I'm going to gently encourage my mouse.
I've been talking to my mouse the entire time because I don't care what any of these people think about me.
And I'm going to tug on my mouse's fur ever so gently--
JERRY: Fur? Ears? KATE: making conversation. Yeah, yeah.
KATE: Just like-- oh there's some liquid coming. Let's dodge around that real quick.
Can I encourage my mouse to steer around it?
KRIS: It wasn't literally the pee-pee though, right? KATE: No, it's not!
AMY: You made that up!
KRIS: It just kept coming and I thought-- KATE: It's beer!
JERRY: No, no, no. So yeah, yeah. In this case we're talking about a wisdom proficiency--
we're talking about a wisdom ability check here.
KATE: Okay. I'm pretty wise. Maybe. JERRY: So let's see it.
KATE: 18. JERRY: Any animal handling there?
KATE: 18. No animal handling. JERRY: Okay.
JERRY: So you are able to--
despite what you have seen elsewhere--
the communion, the rapport you developed with this rodent is profound and lasting.
JERRY: You're going to be writing letters after this. KATE: Absolutely.
JERRY: It's incredible. KATE: We go way back already.
JERRY: Oh yeah--
KATE: We already identified three mice that we both know.
JERRY: And two mice that you both hate!
KATE: Yeah. Hate them. Can't stand them.
JERRY: Exactly. So this curtain-- this sheet is coming around, it's just a quick zig-zag.
It isn't even like the momentum goes forward and around, it's just like a quick left hop, quick right hop,
and then right past the sheet.
JERRY: K'thriss. KRIS: Incredible.
KATE: It's easy!
KRIS: This whole time-- What kind of check is this?
JERRY: This is going to be wisdom. We have the animal handling. But remember-- I want to emphasize this:
This is Dungeons &amp; motherfucking Dragons.
KRIS: Oh I know, yeah. JERRY: Look at this sheet,
KRIS: Well this is why-- JERRY: Think about your spell list...
RYAN: Do something fun. Entertain me. KRIS: Make them like it. &gt;&gt; KATE: Make them laugh.
JERRY: Exactly. KRIS: Well here's the thing--
AMY: Where's the magic, Magic Man? KRIS: and I don't know if it'll inform the roll,
KRIS: but since I know we're getting ready for this cat assault.
And I know your game; you want to speak with it.
I've had my hand on my sigil, my glyph, this whole time ready to pop Dissonant Whispers. Just in case.
And I don't know if that's going to give me the grip I need on this mouse pelt.
KATE: That's true. KRIS: So let's find out.
KRIS: Guess what. I'm not even going to take the advantage.
AMY: Why would you not take the advantage on the important--
JERRY: One hand on the neck. RYAN/KRIS: Yeah.
AMY: Fine. KRIS: Let's find out. Just all the way around.
JERRY: That's a d12! KRIS: That's not it! That was a huge number.
AMY: Sabotaged yourself. KRIS: Physically large.
JERRY: You want to keep it?
KRIS: Yeah, I'm going to need better than that.
KRIS: I have no animal handling-- RYAN: (laughing) You took advantage.
KRIS: And that is a wisdom... (tongue clicks) that's a eight.
JERRY: Oh my god-- KRIS: Yeah.
JERRY: So this-- RYAN: He fucked off.
JERRY: This-- You're riding forward. You're moving over here. You're whispering something to your focus.
Nothing happen. This sheet hits you like a prizefighter.
This heavy liquid just-- it's like... riding through...
KRIS: Like a lake? JERRY: Like a curtain of iron!
JERRY: It's just like (punches palm)
It's like-- Imagine an evil version of a carwash.
A dangerous version.
KRIS: But of beer.
JERRY: Yeah. Exactly.
KATE: Oh no. A dark car wash.
JERRY: Yeah. Take two points of damage.
RYAN: Beer damage.
KRIS: You are inebriated until next round. JERRY: No you are.
KRIS: Uh... okay. JERRY: You are inebriated.
KRIS: All right I did that.
JERRY: You are inebriated and you come off of the mouse and the mouse rolls over here and you're both
on the ground, basically on your backs.
KRIS: Like a motorcycle accident.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. It's like there's two shots.
There's like, before beer curtain. And after beer curtain.
And post-beer curtain, there is no longer a rider and the mount.
KRIS: No. It's two flailing creatures. JERRY: It is just a pile of flesh.
JERRY: Exactly right. Donaar Blit'zen.
How do you contend with this threat?
KRIS: Do better than that.
RYAN: I'm a big, strong, tough man-- boy.
So I'm going to use my strength, and I'm just going to grab him by the haunches up here and be like, turn!
And then turn back. And then turn his little head like a steering wheel.
KATE: Are you riding backwards?
RYAN: Yeah. Aren't you? KATE: (laughing) Okay.
RYAN: I never ridden a mouse before.
RYAN: I never seen any of this stuff. AMY: The French-style.
RYAN: I'm a dragonborn, side-saddle--
JERRY: Yeah I want that dragonborn side-saddle on the mouse!
RYAN: I'm like...
KRIS: The tail doesn't work, you gotta-- RYAN: Yeah.
KRIS: You got to sit there-- KATE: All right so you grab its haunches.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. (laughter)
KATE: (laughing) That's what you said. JERRY: You lean back.
RYAN: I used the wrong word, Kate, apparently.
I don't know what a haunch is. I'm a dragon man. I just saw a mouse before. I live in a secluded city...
You people all look like walking, upright pigs to me!
AMY: It's a very clean city. No mice.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, exactly. Mouse-free!
He doesn't even know what these are. So yeah I am totally okay with--
RYAN: Just overpowering it with strength. Just turning it where I want to go?
JERRY: Yeah exactly. AMY: You roll too high you strangle it.
JERRY: I was going to say, yeah--
(laughter)
KRIS: You just go snap! AMY: You snap its neck!
RYAN: (laughing) And then I just slide to like a halt.
KRIS: He's not running. He's not running.
JERRY: No it's just like a chunk of mouse licorice-- RYAN: My mouse broke.
JERRY: like just twisted into a coil.
RYAN: All right well let's cross this-- JERRY: Yeah I like it.
AMY: Let's see. RYAN: All right.
RYAN: I'm going to use advantage. I'm not going to fall into-- I saw what happened to my buddy over here.
KRIS: Yeah okay. I was trying to play by the rules.
JERRY: I love it. AMY: Thanks folks at home.
AMY: Maybe?
RYAN: Ten...
JERRY: Remember. Advantage. AMY: You get to do it again.
RYAN: Oh yeah advantage. Also I'm doing this strength--
RYAN: so I'm getting a bonus here... RYAN: Yeah plus three right? Yeah.
RYAN: Okay so that would have been 13. AMY: Yeah but get better.
JERRY: So 13 yeah. RYAN: Better than 13...
KRIS: You should do better.
RYAN: Well nope! 13's better than that!
AMY: That was a one.
KATE: That was a one.
RYAN: Or do I get an athletics bonus?
RYAN: Or is this all just strength? JERRY: No I think athletics is okay.
RYAN: Then 15!
KATE: All right. JERRY: 15's all right.
AMY: He gets to add whatever he wants. JERRY: So basically this is just about conditioning...
RYAN: Yeah. JERRY: You trained for this!
JERRY: You trained for this mouse-riding--
RYAN: I'm pommel-horsing this mouse. Hup! Hup! Hup!
(laughter)
KATE: Still backwards. RYAN: And I'm looking at you on the ground like...
JERRY: I like that.
KRIS: Whoa! I flip my glasses up.
RYAN: I flip mine down. JERRY: No, there's more glasses.
KRIS: Yeah. JERRY: So...
JERRY: You're able to adjust around the edge--
This isn't the hop hop.
This is more like steering aircraft carrier type thing.
You catch the edge of the beer curtain but are not--
RYAN: Take a little sip to be a cool guy.
RYAN: It's like (slurp) and I keep going. JERRY: Delicious.
RYAN: I wink. (tongue click) JERRY: No, so you make it through.
JERRY: So through, through, heap of flesh. RYAN: Dead.
JERRY: And what do you got?
AMY: Let me ask you this. JERRY: Yeah.
AMY: Do I-- I only get one action right? I can't do two things here?
JERRY: This is one action, right now. Action packed!
AMY: Blat. Soon as I had a good one.
JERRY: What do you got? Describe your fantasy scenario.
AMY: My fantasy scenario is to-- JERRY: That involves these mice.
AMY: fortify my mouse, and also rescue K'thriss at the same time.
KRIS: Whoa. RYAN: Wow.
JERRY: I'll let you do something about K'thriss once you're through.
AMY: Okay. JERRY: Because he is tumbled out past.
AMY: Let's see if I get through. KRIS: Are we separate--
KRIS: Did I bust through it and then collapse? Because I'm through the curtain, but I'm on my ass.
JERRY: Yes! And so is your poor mouse. KRIS: Okay.
RYAN: So we're under the bar, I take it? Roughly.
KATE: I think I'll go after K'thriss if you go after the mouse.
AMY: I think...
RYAN: You got to get through this curtain first. AMY: Just wait--
AMY: Just wait 'til you see what Walnut's cooking in the kitchen.
KATE: All right. AMY: Maybe nothing. We'll find out!
AMY: So I see this before me. And I see everything that's happening to... my companions?
AMY: Meh I don't know if we're going to use that word yet.
KRIS: The mice you care about and the people who have enslaved them.
AMY: People that I have-- Yeah exactly. The mice I care about. The people that I have to share equity with.
RYAN: We defend the mice. AMY: I look down on my mouse.
AMY: It doesn't seem like there's much time to turn, so I am touching this mouse and I cast Barkskin.
To fortify my mouse so we can barrel right through it.
RYAN: The mouse's armor class is 18.
(laughter)
JERRY: Interesting. Well here, no I like this.
AMY: I think I can do it.
JERRY: I like this.
Yeah. So give me your check and I will adjudicate.
AMY: Okay! We'll see.
AMY: What check? JERRY: You got the animal handlings.
JERRY: You got the wisdom.
AMY: I have wisdom. JERRY: Let's see it.
AMY: My build actually called not for animal handling. Weird for a druid!
RYAN: Yeah weird for someone with Forest Friends. JERRY: Yeah because you're the animal. Right?
AMY: It's because I'm the animal. Thanks, internet.
JERRY: Yeah.
AMY: I hate it.
Why didn't I use advant-- Hmm...
AMY: Oh hey! RYAN: Ooh you got lucky there.
AMY: It's plus wisdom, plus-- 21.
JERRY: But everyone's hungry so you have disadvantage.
KATE: (gasp)
(grumbling)
AMY: But this one's going to be even better!
Big money.
Oh my god! It's a 19! It was! And she said it and it was.
JERRY: It was. And it became so. AMY: 22.
AMY: Or 21. RYAN: 21. You got to use your worse one, right?
AMY: Well whatever! RYAN: Yeah.
AMY: They're both really good. KRIS: So you fall off the mouse.
KRIS: The mouse dies. AMY: The mouse is dead.
JERRY: Exactly. So you...
RYAN: (whispering) Can we eat your mouse? KRIS: (whispering) Yeah.
JERRY: There's no mouse eating.
Wait. Not yet. Obviously that's going to happen.
It's inevitable.
(laughter)
KRIS: It's our prize.
JERRY: So... you got a firm grip. Arms around the neck of the mouse-- Gently!
AMY: Gently.
JERRY: Yeah it's not a thing.
You...
Through your hands you communicate the Barkskin spell and the bark forms over it. Almost like barding.
Lke a horse's barding. Like in plates that fold...
JERRY: from the front to the back. KRIS: You conjure the hull of a ship.
AMY: Wow. RYAN: Nice.
JERRY: And then you just whisper--
What do you whisper into the mouse's ear as you are about to connect with this sheet, or get around it?
KRIS: I got one for you but you're not going to want it. AMY: (whispering) Oh my god--
RYAN: I love you. (laughs) AMY: What do you got?
KRIS: (whispering) Full squeaks ahead!
AMY: (laughs)
No! Because I care about this mouse and I would never say that.
JERRY: Full squeaks ahead. AMY: No, I don't know.
KRIS: That's their word-- Sorry. AMY: I whisper some secret prom-- (laughs)
JERRY: Satan.
AMY: I whisper some secret promise to keep it safe and allow no harm to come to it.
KATE: Nice. AMY: Something cute.
RYAN: Oh this is going to end poorly. I'm excited. KRIS: That's what mine came as.
RYAN: You should name it too because this is only going to end well later.
RYAN: Get it as attacked as possible. KATE: We're not going to eat your mouse.
AMY: No, I say, I told you I would not break my promise.
JERRY: Nice. AMY: And I go-- (kissing sounds)
JERRY: Yeah yeah. I love it.
KRIS: I love you, boat mouse! (engine sound) RYAN: (kissing sounds)
(laughter)
AMY: (laughing) That really got me!
JERRY: All right. AMY: (laughing) That was good.
JERRY: Wuh wuh.
AMY: (chefs kiss sound)
JERRY: So you are riding straight through.
And as you get right to the edge of it, you sort of swing yourself off to the side...
AMY: (gasps)
JERRY: And the beer curtain connects with the top,
and then you go right underneath the mouse,
and then swing yourself up on the other side.
And then you see your two companions still riding away,
but you can see K'thriss, who smells like a brewery...
JERRY: And his soaking ass mouse-- KRIS: Clean now.
RYAN: You finally got that bath.
JERRY: Maybe ten feet to the right.
You can see the two of them getting up and trying to make sense of this situation.
AMY: Great. At which point, I go-- (laughs)
Sorry about this buddy! And I cast Thorn Whip, which...
Don't worry!
(laughter) KRIS: I'm not. I'm just astounded.
AMY: Don't worry. This is my cantrip. RYAN: In a drunken stupor.
AMY: Haven't pulled this one out yet. I create a long, vine-like whip, I mean covered in thorns...
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. Listen!
AMY: Lashes out at your command towards a creature in range. Right. Blah blah blah blah blah.
Anyway, the creature takes (mumbling) piercing damage.
KRIS: (snorts in laughter) AMY: And then the creature--
AMY: is pulled up to ten feet closer to you, which would be on my mouse with me.
AMY: So I'm about to... getcha. KATE: Lasso your ass.
AMY: Get you with my thorns.
KATE: Young seed. AMY: Let's see.
JERRY: This is mystical. KRIS: This is incredible!
JERRY: Yeah, yeah! This is awesome.
AMY: This is the only thing I did not do-- This is the only thing doesn't make sense for my build.
JERRY: For your build? AMY: I thought it was badass.
JERRY: Ah... I see. &gt;&gt; KATE: Nice. AMY: So I took it! (laughs)
KRIS: It is! &gt;&gt; JERRY: It's the utility. RYAN: It's super cool.
JERRY: Well it's like Jim's spell list.
KRIS: But can it land, is the question. AMY: It's like Jim's whole spell list.
JERRY: He's 9th level... RYAN: Yeah all she does is just slashes your face.
JERRY: Yeah he's 9th level and it's all tools. KRIS: Well... I'm glad that it worked.
AMY: Well, we'll see! KRIS: So I'm on the back of the-- (laughs)
AMY: I don't know. JERRY: So how does it work?
AMY: I have to make a melee spell attack against the target.
JERRY: Now remember, you have disadvantage.
So if you want one dice, you should probably use the advantage from the channel.
AMY: I would love to use the advantage from the channel.
RYAN: I would love it if this just whips you in the eye, and miss like--
AMY: Why would you love that?
RYAN: It's fun. AMY: We're on the same team.
RYAN: Because it makes me laugh. AMY: I think last week I called them Walnut's Nuts, so...
AMY: Thanks, Walnut's Nuts. I would like to use my thing.
JERRY: Yeah. Use your thing.
AMY: Okay, I don't know how to do a melee spell attack.
Maybe the people at home also don't know. And also maybe Donaar wants to learn how to do it.
RYAN: Oh yeah. Teach me. I'm new.
AMY: We're all learning here. RYAN: I'm new.
AMY: It's only the second episode.
JERRY: Oh here we go. Let me see your sheet.
KRIS: Well don't metagame this.
RYAN: Apparently this...
AMY: I have a spell sheet... RYAN: The way to play is just to hand paper around?
AMY: Spell attack bonus is plus five?
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. AMY: That sounds good.
KATE: You want to hand me another one? KRIS: You have to say, I'd like to approach the bench.
JERRY: It's the same as the other bonus so you're good. RYAN: I have Bane.
KATE: Ooh let me see that.
AMY: Well that was a two.
JERRY: K. AMY: But I get to go again, right?
JERRY: No, no, no. This advantage just-- All this--
AMY: All it did was just made it that I had a--
JERRY: Daddy's working.
KRIS: Yeah no cross-talk. Christ.
JERRY: Daddy's working. KRIS: Shut up.
AMY: Okay so I rolled a five. So that is truly the number I got. Plus five is a ten.
JERRY: What's your AC?
KRIS: Uh it's a toilet.
KATE: It's 13.
KRIS: I'm just drowning in an unflushed toilet. It's 13.
AMY: (whispering) Son of a--
JERRY: So as you're riding by, this arcing whip of thorns, reaches out, shreds part of his cloak...
KRIS: (groans)
And that spins me as it goes.
JERRY: Like a top.
KRIS: Yeah. (sounds of trailing off)
JERRY: He pirouettes in place briefly, and then is back on the ground.
AMY: Well um...
RYAN: And we all see this and I say, what are you doing? Why are you hitting him?
KRIS: And I go, what a heck of a brew.
(laughter)
That's some powerful stuff.
KATE: I'm going to sigh heavily and cast Minor Illusion.
JERRY: Yeah.
KATE: Somewhere far away from us, I'm going to make the sound and image of a mouse lose its shit.
KATE: To hopefully... JERRY: Just flipping out?
KATE: to buy us some time to rescue K'thriss and K'thrissmas.
AMY: Aw cute. JERRY: You're going to save K'thrissmas?
KATE: Yes. Yeah.
RYAN: How's his mouse?
RYAN: Like is it still on the ground? Is it doing anything? KRIS: I don't know. We're going to find out
AMY: It's inside out. JERRY: We'll get to it. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Okay.
KRIS: The beer pulverized it. That's what happens. All right.
KATE: So hopefully Onyx has been distracted by my Minor Illusion.
JERRY: Yeah let's take a look here.
KRIS: I haven't heard of a cat's presence yet. I mean I assume-- it knocked something over, but...
KATE: The mice are going crazy so I feel like... JERRY: Oh! &gt;&gt; KRIS: Yeah.
JERRY: Okay. That's... KATE: Onyx fell in love with my mouse?
KATE: Is that what that says? JERRY: They... is going to get married.
KATE: That's amazing. Again! AMY: Don't like marriage.
KRIS: It's fully satisfying.
JERRY: It's like that's what you can come to the "C" Team for. Every episode a marriage.
AMY: We're all about love here.
JERRY: Sometimes it's about a bipedal dragon and a liquid door.
RYAN: Yeah. JERRY: Right?
RYAN: Sometimes regret. I should have married that door.
JERRY: This time... KRIS: Yeah. You let it get away.
JERRY: This time--
RYAN: It comes back it's yours. (laughs)
JERRY: So you create this mouse, and basically just on another vector that is running way over.
And it's just squeaking, scrabbling...
JERRY: Like it's delicious.
JERRY: Like this mouse was engineered-- KRIS: (kissing sound) Choice.
JERRY: for maximum flavor and freshness. KRIS: (chef's kiss sound)
KATE: (laughs) AMY: Mmm... Ugh.
JERRY: And then you-- KRIS: Rancher's Reserve.
JERRY: And then this is--
I would say, legitimately... terrifying.
You see this giant, black shape.
I mean like a-- Imagine a person trying to hang a cloak on a hook.
And then just a cape just falls to the ground.
That's how much sound this thing makes.
KATE: Huh.
JERRY: When it comes off of the canopy and lands on what is not a mouse. Like there is no sound.
There is just a shape and light, but there is no sound of any kind.
KATE: Ah.
JERRY: All right. So you have problems. You have serious, serious problems.
RYAN: You still going to try to parlay with this thing?
AMY: Anytime now.
JERRY: So we still have our K'thriss.
KRIS: I'm just going to take it easy. JERRY: Your mouse is shaking off its fur.
JERRY: It's sort of a beer aerosol mist around it.
And then it just looks over at you like, what? What are we doing? What's next?
AMY: Get on the mouse, drow!
KRIS: Yeah I haul myself to my feet, if it's possible.
JERRY: Yeah it's possible. KRIS: Must a check be performed?
KRIS: Is there an inebriation state? I believe you.
JERRY: There is an inebriation state.
KRIS: I trust you. RYAN: Nice.
KRIS: So I take it cutaneously?
RYAN: You went through and you were like, what is that? (gargling sounds)
AMY: (laughs) KRIS: Wah! (gargling sounds)
JERRY: No, no, no.
KRIS: (sounds of drinking and inebriation)
JERRY: I have checks. It's just that thus far you haven't had any negative outcomes from it.
KRIS: Oh okay.
JERRY: The mouse had its own problems there for a turn.
He seems like... He's looking at you like, wow!
JERRY: That was all incredibly real. KATE: That was some good beer.
KRIS: No we're fine. But not for that much longer. So I run over to him to remount him.
JERRY: "Re-mouse?" KRIS: Yeah.
KRIS: Mouse up. JERRY: Grab up on. Yeah exactly.
JERRY: Tug, tug. And now you have begun to run further toward the door.
The black shape-- So you look back over your shoulder.
You see the black shape, same level of sound, just jump up into the air and disappear.
KATE: Okay.
KRIS: Whoa. JERRY: I know. I know.
KRIS: Then I ground again.
KATE: Okay. I need to do another thing.
JERRY: More Dungeons &amp; Dragons? KRIS: Hope it's friendly.
KATE: Yeah well, Donaar, would you like to do anything or can I scoop you?
RYAN: No, it's fine.
KATE: Okay. Well then I shall cast... RYAN: I'm just going to mess around with the door.
KATE: Pass without Trace-- JERRY: We're just steady mousing.
KATE: upon myself and a in radius around me. So stick close, folks.
RYAN: Yep. KATE: We're going to Silent Town.
KRIS: Yeah so the question becomes as you do that... RYAN: Yeah how far apart are we?
KRIS: do I become the only thing outside of that radius? (laughter)
KRIS: And now you zeroed in. AMY: I hope so.
KATE: It's possible. I've done my best.
KRIS: Well okay. Does the magic scale? So there's a range there.
KATE: Is this real feet? KRIS: Yeah. An equivalence?
KRIS: Everything, including the cat, is now invisible?
JERRY: So here is what happens next.
AMY: Oh no. JERRY: He is behind you trying to catch up.
JERRY: As you are running, she whispers a few words, and you feel and see the shadows around you gather
and cling in a gauzy way to the mice and yourselves as you are running through this area.
It is at this time that you see...
a rain of objects...
KRIS: (whispering) No...
JERRY: from the other side of this canopy...
AMY: The cat. Where you inch it closer to the--
JERRY: No. This is exactly it.
I want everyone to appreciate how dangerous and scary a cat would be just doing its normal cat shit.
KRIS: I like the idea like all these objects tumbling, make haste!
And then cut to the cat going...
(laughter)
JERRY: Meow. Meow. KRIS: Just this BS.
KRIS: Cat nonsense. JERRY: No, no, no.
JERRY: You see this rain of objects. It's hard to tell what they are just yet.
But they just cascade off of the edge of this and they are hitting the wood. Some are sticking into the wood.
Some bounce briefly and roll.
But the closer you get to it, it's clearly a chess set.
So this is basically almost a forest-scale chess...
AMY: We are so tiny. KRIS: Bad cat.
RYAN: Yeah wow. These are the smallest mice.
AMY: If we're going to talk to the cat I'm going to be like--
AMY: (squeaks greeting) KATE: Let's challenge the cat to a chess game.
RYAN: I like it. They weren't playing chess before. Weren't they playing some weird game?
KATE: No they were playing some weird game.
JERRY: She didn't throw the board down, so it would be hard to...
KRIS: Yeah. &gt;&gt; KATE: Oh. JERRY: Know what I mean?
JERRY: So those things are kicking. And then the board's staying there and all the things are flying off.
We've all seen it.
(laughter)
KRIS: Classic cat move. RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: But navigating this-- I mean, again this is more like a forest. This not like a dressage thing.
Like this is-- You are entering a context that requires a different approach.
At least for the duration of the pieces.
AMY: Okay.
KATE: And the cat still cannot see or hear us.
JERRY: Right now. That's right. KATE: Currently.
AMY: So who's at the front of the pack?
JERRY: I think that you are at the front of the pack. AMY: Great answer.
AMY: So can I make some check to slow my mouse's roll a little bit?
JERRY: Mouse slow? Absolutely you can slow the mouse roll. Sure.
AMY: How would I do that? Can I do a survival thing? KRIS: It's a racial trait.
JERRY: We're still talking about that wisdom stuff.
But remember, disadvantage. You're welcome to use a dice to make the boo-boo go away.
AMY: Is this what I want to do?
JERRY: I think so. AMY: I'd really like to avoid conflict with the cat.
JERRY: No, no. Listen. This is Dungeons &amp; Dragons.
RYAN: It's inevitable. JERRY: I can pick up whatever you put down.
JERRY: I'm just saying one dice is better than two bad dice.
AMY: Then we all escape. And we did a great job. And also I did something cool to make it happen.
JERRY: Yeah and I'm the winner.
RYAN: Wow. Theater of the mind.
AMY: I'd like to use one of my-- JERRY: Yeah. I won Dungeons &amp; Dragons.
AMY: Oh all right. Well.
AMY: Bye. KRIS: New Game Plus.
KRIS: Keep going. AMY: I'd like to use one of my special nuts.
AMY: One of my special dice so I get one good roll here.
JERRY: Exactly. That wis. Throw the bonus in.
KATE: I think you're taking my dice away.
AMY: Okay and then the bonus... JERRY: Now add the bonus.
AMY: is... three, so 15.
JERRY: Perfect.
KATE: Jerry. I think you're deducting my dice instead of Walnut's. I just saw my number go down.
JERRY: Boop. KATE: Thanks.
AMY: No, I think it's fine. KATE: No, I think I'm going to address this really quick.
KRIS: That's good. You're a team player. People appreciate that.
KATE: I would happily donate one of my dice to Amy.
RYAN: Yeah but that's not in the rules.
AMY: Well now I got nothing! JERRY: Yeah exactly. You ate them all up.
RYAN: (hisses) Stickler. Believe me I want to. AMY: It's because I was getting peer-pressured!
JERRY: You're the worst. Long story short, you're the worst.
So you are able to tuck back, pat, calm this thing down, along its barky plates.
AMY: Oh right.
JERRY: And the closer you get to the set you can see that it's actually a dragonborn chess set.
AMY: (shudders)
JERRY: Like some part of your mind registers that this shape is all dragonborn warriors, clerics...
You know what I mean?
JERRY: Like that's the theme, right? RYAN: Handsome.
KRIS: It's a great set.
AMY: Great. RYAN: Yeah.
RYAN: That's a good set. That's a strong, powerful set.
KRIS: I have one at home. RYAN: Admirable.
RYAN: Something to aspire towards.
JERRY: Quality set. KRIS: I stop to admire.
RYAN: Yeah. AMY: Nope! I don't stop!
KATE: I stop to admire as well.
AMY: Ugh.
JERRY: So you pull...
AMY: I slow the mouse. KATE: This one looks like you!
RYAN: (laughs) I hug it. JERRY: Exactly.
AMY: You cross-talkers.
I'm trying to rescue you.
JERRY: You got a good situation going here.
AMY: Yes.
JERRY: Behind a rook you can see that there are a couple dragonborn on top of it.
Sort of looking out over the nonexistent battlefield.
AMY: Yes.
JERRY: Yep. Rosie.
KATE: I'm admiring a chess piece until Walnut tells us what the plan is.
RYAN: So we're all running towards these because they're all scattered on the floor.
JERRY: They're all scattered on the floor.
RYAN: Roughly how many? Do we have an idea? Are we able to tell? Are in front of us.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, yeah. I mean like I say, some hit, some bounce, some rolled away.
In your field of vision right here you can probably see 30, 35 pieces of varying sizes.
Imagine a forest scenario. There's tall pieces, there's waist-high cover, ala Gears of War.
RYAN: Gotcha. Some are on its side. Yeah. KATE: Are we able to do--
KATE: like an Endor forest speeder bike thing with our mice? And just--
KRIS: (Star Wars speeder bike sound)
KATE: Like that. RYAN: What are they made of?
JERRY: You can try-- They're heavy. Like a pewter-type. RYAN: All right.
RYAN: I'm new to this game, so I don't know how, like say acid, works.
Could I theoretically blast a blast of acid and just clear a line?
RYAN: Could I just go over my mouse and bleh. KATE: This is how this game works.
RYAN: But I don't know the rules of acid.
KATE: Ask him what the rules of acid are. RYAN: Are those the rules of acid? Can I do that?
RYAN: Can I shoot an acid blast ahead of us to clear a path?
JERRY: Yeah my position, generally speaking, with stuff like that, is that as long as it is sufficiently rad...
RYAN: Okay. It'd be pretty badass.
KATE: Acid barf is so rad.
JERRY: It's kind of balling.
But you can see your companion, Walnut Dankgrass, is clearly trying to establish a different tone.
It's up to you. Like I say, you can't get in trouble with me.
RYAN: Fill me in on your plan then.
AMY: Oh I look back and obviously we're trying to be quiet.
And I go like this.
And then I go this.
And then I go...
JERRY: There's some special-- (laughs) AMY: And then I go...
KATE: Right. AMY: And then I go...
AMY: And then I go...
KRIS: And I'm like, what the hell is any of that?
Curve ball.
KRIS: All right. Got it. KATE: I get it. She wants us to admire this chess piece.
RYAN: Oh yeah. It is a nice chess piece.
KRIS: Order today.
(laughter)
AMY: Well all right I'll try to whisper. I don't know what the rules of Pass without Trace are.
KATE: I think you can just talk.
AMY: Can you talk in there? KATE: Yeah.
AMY: Well I wouldn't know that. KATE: Let me read it to you.
JERRY: Yeah this is good information. AMY: Sure good information but I wouldn't know that.
KATE: A veil of shadows and silence radiates from you, masking you and your companions from detection.
For the duration, each creature you choose within 30 feet of you, including you,
has a plus ten bonus to dex (stealth) checks and can't be tracked except by magical means.
A creature that receives this bonus leaves behind no tracks or other traces of its passage.
AMY: I take it back. That's actually also one of my spells so Walnut would know about this.
She looks back and goes, I was saying...
We're going to go this way.
I'm going to take the lead.
We're going to go.
Then all you,
follow me.
AMY: Obviously. KATE: Acid barf?
RYAN: Yeah. AMY: Sure.
RYAN: Can I-- &gt;&gt; KATE: (laughs) AMY: What? You got something?
RYAN: Now I don't want to do it.
(laughter)
KRIS: Is there like a time dilation? Has this been 20 minutes of this?
JERRY: No, here this is all very, very quick. This is happening very fast.
You guys are-- you are catching up to the rest of the group.
KRIS: Right.
JERRY: But you did not have the benefit...
Kris: (whispering) Oh no.
JERRY: of this mystical shroud.
So you are seeing the same thing they see, but you have a very different connotation. Right?
And as you approach this forest of game pieces.
That same...
It's like a manta ray. Imagine swimming beneath a manta ray.
You see that black shape fall opposite the chess pieces.
And you see it just reach out, just completely casually, reach out and grab a piece and just fling it.
But it's like a catapult!
I mean it's like what's happening with this paw is, at your scale, beyond terrifying.
KRIS: Yeah. JERRY: These are heavy pewter pieces.
JERRY: I mean you seen a set like this.
JERRY: It's just gone. KRIS: We've all played with them.
JERRY: Just... through the air.
KATE: At what point-- how close does he have to get before Pass without Trace affects him as well?
JERRY: You mean for him? KATE: Yeah.
JERRY: He can move into the thing but I think that Pass without Trace...
KATE: It's 30... KRIS: We need some equivalence.
KATE: This says range so 30 yards I think. KRIS: Figure out what the range is.
JERRY: Exactly.
Yep. So as he enters.
I was trying to figure out if it would happen, if he had to be there at the beginning. But no, it's a veil.
KRIS: Okay.
JERRY: So as you approach the edge of it and get within, you can feel...
And obviously for you it's like a spa.
KRIS: It's like I'm in the Halls of Medicine.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. Exactly. KRIS: It's like a relief.
JERRY: (laughing) It's like a...
mentholated shadow.
KRIS: The darkness. It soothes. JERRY: Exactly.
JERRY: It enters the sinus and you feel better immediately.
KRIS: Ah immediate relief. For only 12 hours.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. At least!
So you move in and as soon as you-- because you can hear the scrabble of the mouse. It's slight but it's there.
And then it just disappears the closer you get in.
KRIS: I see, I see. Okay. I am still going to pop...
Dissonant-- no I'm not going to do that.
(laughter)
AMY: I can't stop you. JERRY: Hold on I pop... Cat Murderer.
KRIS: I was going to say Detonate Feline.
Animal. Which works in a-- all right.
It's a detonation check. I don't know if that's on there.
JERRY: Oh! He fails!
KRIS: There's no multiplier.
JERRY: His head goes one way.
KRIS: I'm going to do Dancing Lights behind me.
KATE: Ooh what's that? KRIS: Just to uh...
KATE: What's Dancing Lights? AMY: Oh. It's a laser pointer.
KRIS: It's just a flashy show. It's just a little racial trait I have.
JERRY: Is it like Laser Zeppelin?
KRIS: Yes. It's fancy. Yeah it's the logo in that, you know, constantly withdrawing shape.
JERRY: So right behind you?
KRIS: (sigh) Well I'm assuming the cat is back there.
KRIS: Right? We've come through-- JERRY: No the cat has dropped in front of this forest.
KRIS: Okay so... forest in front of us.
KRIS: We have not yet-- JERRY: You are right at the edge.
JERRY: Ready to move right through this thing. And it's over here clearing a piece.
AMY: Through the forest. KRIS: Right so the question is...
RYAN: Yeah it's doing our work for us.
KRIS: So the question becomes am I able to cast this such that it will distract the cat but not the mice?
I don't want it to disturb the mice. I want to get the cat's attention elsewhere. Off of us.
That's why I was thinking if it was behind us I would cast it immediately after so,
because I know it's heading this direction. And then it's going to be distracted.
KATE: What's your range?
JERRY: Go ahead and cast it, but tell me where you're going to put it.
KRIS: 120 feet. It's a long ass way. &gt;&gt; KATE: 120 feet. JERRY: By you or behind you.
KRIS: I can do wherever I want. RYAN: Yeah.
AMY: You can still put it behind us
AMY: and the cat would see right through us. KRIS: I put it directly inside the cat's eyeballs.
RYAN: 120 feet relative to you? Of your feet? KRIS: I'll put it on to the cat's retinas.
AMY: Yeah that's less one inch. KATE: Okay but seriously. Maybe?
AMY: Maybe do it. Put it behind us.
KATE: Try put it-- I mean on the retinas of the cat.
KRIS: I'm going to ask you a question, and it is a serious one. Do I have line of sight to the cat's retinas?
AMY: (laughs) JERRY: Yeah you can see the... You can see its--
KRIS: I am very small. JERRY: Yeah you can see its iris.
KRIS: And it's flashing in the dark, I assume. AMY: K'thriss and the mouse with the laser pointer.
JERRY: Yeah it's just emeralds.
KRIS: All right. JERRY: Evil emeralds.
KRIS: I am going to take my advantage on this one.
KATE: This is very good.
KRIS: You like lasers? I don't know if I need an advantage for that.
JERRY: Is Dancing Lights a...
KATE: I don't think you need to roll. JERRY: Yeah you don't need to roll.
KRIS: Do I not? Is it? Oh no it's-- KATE: You just do it.
KRIS: Yeah I don't need advantage. KATE: It's a great roll though.
KRIS: No, it's a great roll.
RYAN: Save that one for later. JERRY: Bank it.
JERRY: Yeah. No, no. Here's the situation with Dancing Lights.
Like this is something drow children do.
Like this is not-- (laughing) You know what I mean? This is not crazy pants stuff.
KATE: Yeah, dummy. RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: This is normal stuff.
JERRY: You would do it to entertain yourself. KRIS: Kris doesn't know that.
KRIS: K'thriss is well aware.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. You do this to entertain yourself.
So you-- so right in front of it?
KRIS: Yeah. JERRY: Okay.
JERRY: You see the-- you make this cloud of fairies or you know, at this range it just looks like a mesh.
KRIS: I think it's literally-- JERRY: Of mathematical lights.
KRIS: Yeah I seem to remember that it is... either it's Dancing Lights or Faerie Fire...
KRIS: No, it's Dancing Lights as a cantrip.
But it's like four spheres?
KRIS: Anyway I can center those right up-- JERRY: Yeah exactly.
KRIS: onto those eyes. JERRY: So its eyes cross for a second,
and it blinks a couple times and then just walks forward and moves through the Dancing Lights.
KRIS: Into the other two.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. (laughter)
JERRY: Dun, dun, dun! KRIS: Good luck.
RYAN: Just keep blasting it at him.
JERRY: And then it gets low and is just raking its eyes across this mesh of pieces.
And just in the back of its throat it says,
(hoarsely) "Far Mice!"
KRIS: That's what they all say. RYAN: Mm-hmm.
KRIS: Yeah. RYAN: That's your buddy right there.
KATE: Real nice guy. RYAN: Yeah.
AMY: Hoh! (laughs)
RYAN: He doesn't know we're here yet! Maybe we should wait 'til he sees us before we...
AMY: That's the other thing. I'm really... I'm truly keeping this until the cat gets closer and gets a bead on us.
KATE: Great, great. I think that's good.
AMY: Maybe we should try and move through--
KATE: So Onyx is now moving across the chess piece forest?
JERRY: Just right now just sniffing-- like it's just using all of its profound senses.
Senses designed to catch and eat things your size.
And it is just playing it across.
RYAN: He ain't magic though.
KATE: I got Pass without Trace for an hour, so...
AMY: We should go around...
KATE: Unless it just starts to bite at random spots I don't think it's going to find us.
AMY: That's a dog move.
RYAN: Give Felix here a wide berth. You know what I mean?
KRIS: Yeah. Cat... name.
AMY: I think we should try and make our way through?
JERRY: Yeah you approach this anyway you want.
KATE: Yeah let's take as direct route as we can because these mice are not getting any happier.
AMY: I agree. Let's go right through.
KATE: Let's go through!
RYAN: Between his legs? KATE: Yeah.
RYAN: (laughs) All right. KATE: AT-AT style.
AMY: Let's do this. Lots of Star Wars.
KRIS: Ah you could have used Thorn Whip.
JERRY: All right that's plus ten on dex checks?
KATE: Yep.
RYAN: Oh! I got bad dex.
AMY: No, but we get the plus ten from-- KATE: We get the plus ten from me.
KRIS: Everybody gets it. RYAN: Oh. Yeah.
JERRY: Plus ten-- KATE: We all rolling dex?
JERRY: Plus ten, but remember! Hold on, hold on, hold on.
AMY: What? KRIS: (gasp)
JERRY: You have disadvantage because you didn't get anybody food.
JERRY: Now you can use your checks-- RYAN: Yeah. Well just us two.
JERRY: You can use your checks if you want.
KATE: You guys have disadvantage. I'm good. JERRY: Yeah, yeah.
KRIS: I'm going to eat-- KATE: Beer counts as food.
KATE: That's what Pat Rothfuss just text. KRIS: So full. It's like a Guinness.
RYAN: I said, spit in my mouth! (laughs)
JERRY: Did Pat Rothfuss
KATE: He texted me. He says beer does count as food.
KRIS: Don't-- Why is he in here? AMY: It's liquid bread.
KRIS: Why lie about it? It's a good idea.
AMY: (laughing) It is a good idea.
RYAN: Tell him to go find some beeswax and mind it.
JERRY: Patrick Rothfuss!
AMY: Please, I'm glad he's whispering in your ear.
KATE: Rosie's fine with it. RYAN: No, no, it's great.
AMY: She's bedfellows with Viari.
JERRY: I'm going to get him. Let's go ahead and see it.
KATE: Okay. Everybody gets a dex-- Oh boy. That's a-- I'm going to reroll that one because I got lucky.
JERRY: Yeah. Your lucky trait is paying you big time. KATE: I'm a lucky bitch. Ooh. 14. Yikes.
KATE: Oh but I get an extra five because of my dex bonus.
KRIS: Everybody likes me. KATE: 19.
JERRY: Okay.
KRIS: All right. I'm going to take my advantage. One of these.
KRIS: Because I don't want to miss again. KATE: Do it. You don't want to get this--
KRIS: Those are hard pewter pieces. KATE: bullshit happening.
KRIS: That's... well I mean, that's not great. Whatever. 14. Screw it. Don't want that.
KATE: Ooh. KRIS: Even better than that. It's infinity.
KRIS: So... Yeah. JERRY: Amazing.
RYAN: You transcend space and time.
JERRY: I like it. All right. KRIS: It's 25.
RYAN: Uh...
RYAN: Huh? AMY: So you roll a dice and then you get plus ten.
RYAN: Plus ten, yeah.
AMY: And then nothing else because you don't have--
RYAN: But we have to do it twice because we both have disadvantage.
KATE: Yeah. AMY: Right.
RYAN: And we got to take the bad one.
JERRY: But you can buy your way out of it if you want to.
KRIS: Yeah and then you only have one. AMY: Stop pressuring me.
RYAN: You've already essentially failed, right? AMY: I only have one.
RYAN: Have you? Or...
JERRY: No, no. She's okay. KATE: No. I'm fantastic.
RYAN: All right then I'll use it then.
AMY: Yeah you got three. Go for it.
AMY: You have lots of friends.
RYAN: I'mma use it. JERRY: Hit it.
AMY: (gasp) RYAN: That's a 27.
JERRY: That's increda.
RYAN: I leap into the cat's mind.
(laughter)
JERRY: You make your home in its brainpan.
AMY: This actually might be fine because if I get revealed then I'll just...
AMY: sweet my way out of the cat. RYAN: This is what you always wanted.
JERRY: Are you using your dice?
AMY: No! And I got 12! RYAN: Holy shit!
JERRY: Okay. KRIS: Wow.
RYAN: I forgot about the plus ten.
KATE: Could be worse. JERRY: So as you're picking you're way through...
AMY: Yes.
JERRY: Everyone has moved through the back.
JERRY: Except for Walnut Dankgrass.
So you noticed something strange about this cat as you're sort of-- as you are...
JERRY: Aside from the size, obviously. AMY: Sure.
JERRY: As you're moving beneath it--
This is not out of the ordinary. It does happen, it's rare.
The cat has six toes.
AMY: Ah yes. KATE: (gasp) Polydactyl.
JERRY: Right? RYAN: (whispering) I don't know what that is.
JERRY: Six toes.
RYAN: Oh. KATE: It means multiple dactyls.
AMY: Means it's-- RYAN: Oh wow.
JERRY: And so as you are coming around the edge,
AMY: Oh no. JERRY: navigating this edge.
JERRY: Your cloak catches on the back claw.
KRIS: Oh no. KATE: Classic.
KRIS: The one that doesn't do anything. Just there. RYAN: You got caught by the pterodactyl.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. The vestigial-- AMY: Well actually...
KRIS: Blegh. AMY: Walnut doesn't wear a cloak.
KATE: (gasp) AMY: But, yes.
RYAN: Then your hair. AMY: Some article of clothing.
RYAN: Your hair-- AMY: Walnut has short hair also.
RYAN: Some hair though. AMY: Yes.
KRIS: Then you escape.
(laughter)
JERRY: So the three of you; so you, K'thriss, and Donaar have moved past and you have gotten caught...
KRIS: (whispering) Oh no.
JERRY: by the back hook of this extra vestigial claw.
KRIS: The yucky one. RYAN: The pterodactyl.
AMY: Okay can I--
JERRY: It rears up. You know how when cats get surprised it jump up in the air? It takes flight.
AMY: Am I on the back foot or the front foot? JERRY: Back foot.
AMY: Okay. I want to let go of my mouse and try and climb the cat?
KRIS: Wow. JERRY: Climb the cat?
KRIS: Who are you? AMY: I want to whisper in this thing's ear!
RYAN: Oh man. JERRY: All right. Okay.
AMY: What's the worst thing that happens? I die and you get a funnier person here.
KRIS: I was going to say--
(laughter)
RYAN: Well we would get-- franchise-wise... this is a good question.
KATE: Let's say 33.3% each. I go, bye! RYAN: That's 33.3. I say, good luck!
RYAN: I believe in you! KRIS: I say, and that whip hurt! As I dart past.
(laughter)
JERRY: Dissonant Whispers. KRIS: Yep.
JERRY: Yeah you can climb. You can do whatever you want and I'll roll with it.
AMY: Well, would I-- I don't know but maybe Walnut would know...
JERRY: Yeah. AMY: I mean...
JERRY: She probably does if it's about beasts.
AMY: If I'm touching the cat I can probably speak with it, right?
JERRY: Yeah.
AMY: Okay then maybe I don't need to climb it. But I want to grab on to it.
JERRY: Yeah. AMY: I'm on.
AMY: And at this point, I want to use Speak with Animals to try and communicate with this cat.
KATE: I been waiting. This is the money shot right here. RYAN: (claps) This is all we wanted.
KRIS: This is Hollywood Mouse. JERRY: This is the D&amp;D equivalent.
KATE: Whew. RYAN: And the cat goes, fuck you.
(laughter)
KATE: Fuckity fuck meow! RYAN: Meow. Meow, fuck you, meow.
JERRY: So you have an audience with this cat.
AMY: So I say-- JERRY: So you're going to hang on to its back leg?
AMY: Yeah I just want to hold on to it.
AMY: I say--
JERRY: It's just like-- It'll fling you off. Try to imagine trying to hold on to a dragon's leg.
AMY: Oh I thought I was clawed on to it.
JERRY: Oh no, you just-- AMY: I just nudged it.
JERRY: Yeah it got hooked and dragged out. AMY: Well I'm exposed. Fine then I'm here.
AMY: I'm at the mercy of this cat. And I would like to say to this cat,
Friend, who brought me not one, but two mice in friendship not long ago.
I'm here. May I speak with you?
We'll see!
JERRY: So it...
KRIS: Tell it, look at the bounty I have brought you!
(laughter)
KRIS: Two you bring...
RYAN: You should say--
JERRY: No, no. You have brought me two...
And I have given four.
(laughter)
KRIS: Right. Two upon two.
AMY: That's a different type of druid than that. RYAN: I also hate Mondays and love lasagna.
JERRY: Yeah exactly.
KRIS: Yeah. RYAN: Cat joke.
JERRY: It gets down...
It hears the voice and you can tell that the claw, like the swipe is ready.
And then it puts the claw, like the paw's right by you.
And you can hear the claws enter the sheath.
And it says,
"This is how you repay me?"
"In league with these mice?"
AMY: I say...
JERRY: "Were you a mouse when I knew you before?"
AMY: I have nev-- JERRY: "Have you always been a mouse?"
JERRY: "What is the extent of your trickery?"
AMY: I say, friend, you know me.
I have not been a mouse long. And it is not by choice.
However...
you have been going to the food place and it seems you always find in your mouth their queen.
And so...
KRIS: (exhale) KATE: (whispering) Oh shit! Calling it out.
AMY: And so in exchange for my help
these mice have promised to take us to a place where we can become un-mice.
KRIS: It's okay. Cats understand that.
KRIS: They know what that means.
RYAN: We could have fed the mice to him and gotten his help.
AMY: Different type of druid!
This is how Wally rolls.
RYAN: I know. KATE: (whispering) Wally!
RYAN: I should have tried to persuade you. KRIS: (whispering) Wally?
KATE: (whispering) It's so cute!
AMY: So I have-- we got--
JERRY: What case are you trying to make to this mouse?
AMY: To this cat.
JERRY: Yeah to this cat. Thus far I would say that this argumentation does not compel.
AMY: I'm trying to say, it killed...
Listen you have killed not once, not twice, but many, many times their queen.
You kind of owe them one.
KRIS: Ooh. RYAN: Err.
AMY: I'm asking... KRIS: I don't know if that's going to play.
AMY: I'm asking for a personal favor. JERRY: "I owe... a mouse?"
RYAN: Yep.
AMY: Well not one. JERRY: "You are a mouse."
AMY: I'm not-- You know-- JERRY: "What do I owe you?"
AMY: You owe me nothing.
JERRY: It puts its paw on your chest.
AMY: Sure.
JERRY: And just pushes you down directly on to the ground.
AMY: Great. At which point I use Animal Friendship.
This spell lets you convince a beast that you mean it no harm.
KRIS: I don't think it was worried about that.
RYAN: I don't think it was worried that you meant it harm in the first place.
AMY: (sigh) KRIS: Okay I'm sorry. Keep reading.
RYAN: Sorry yeah.
AMY: This is my thing. KATE: Be a friend. Be a friend.
AMY: If I'm going to mess it up, let me dig my own grave, please.
AMY: All right, so-- JERRY: I use my gravedigger.
AMY: I use my gravedigger-- JERRY: Talent.
AMY: Actually that's not-- All right fine.
JERRY: Auto-gravedigging.
AMY: Whatever I take it back. This is the one time you're going to let me take it back.
Instead I use Enhance Ability to give myself advantage on charisma checks.
KATE: Ooh.
JERRY: Interesting... AMY: At which point I would like to now...
KATE: Speak with a very charismatic mouse. AMY: persuade the cat.
AMY: And I would like to play to what I assume is probably a very vain existence, because let's be honest.
KATE: Here we go. Here we go! AMY: And I say,
AMY: I say, friend.
Beautiful, beautiful friend.
I know it is through your lands that we pass. This is your territory. I'm at the mercy of you.
JERRY: "Yes." AMY: I am only asking--
JERRY: "Yes."
AMY: That you, in all of your greatness...
JERRY: "Glory."
AMY: Glory. Of course.
JERRY: "Felinity." AMY: Great glory.
AMY: Felinity.
JERRY: "Cathood."
AMY: Cathood.
KATE: Liquidity.
JERRY: No. AMY: Liquidity. Equity? I don't know.
KRIS: Moisture. RYAN: Liquid.
AMY: Fuzziness. RYAN: ROI?
JERRY: 2.1?
AMY: Merely that you let us pass this day, and no other days, into the lands beyond.
As we have found ourselves turned into the form you see now and wish to return to normal.
That is the extent of my grovelling.
JERRY: Let me see it. So right now you are at disadvantage, like I said.
AMY: Sure.
JERRY: You can buy yourself to one dice.
AMY: I'm going to use the advantage.
JERRY: I recommend that you do.
Now...
AMY: But I get-- JERRY: Let's see it.
AMY: So I get advantage...
RYAN: Well that just makes you back to even. KATE: Can you use Forest Friends?
AMY: I don't think Forest Friends is going to help me here.
I'm not going to bring out a bunch of things for this cat to--
RYAN: Ooh that would be a good idea.
JERRY: That's one way to do it. KRIS: Meats from the forest!
KATE: You call Forest Friends and all the mice comes for the cat.
KATE: (whispering) What if? AMY: (laughing) What kind of druid do you think I am?
JERRY: Potentially a druid that's aware, at some level, of the natural order.
AMY: I know. I also--
JERRY: So it's like this... KRIS: I love this, Amy. I legitimately love this.
RYAN: This is great.
JERRY: There is the weight of this paw on you.
AMY: Yes. JERRY: Let's see the dice.
AMY: Okay. So I use one of my special advantages from the crowd.
And also I have advantage on charisma checks. I'm assuming this is going to be a charisma check?
JERRY: Yeah exactly. AMY: So I would actually have advantage.
JERRY: You boughten your way completely out of it now.
AMY: I just want to make sure and no one's going to be--
Oh! Don't worry. Plus nothing.
RYAN: Oh hey. Persuasion.
AMY: Big money. RYAN: Nice.
AMY: That's 18, right?
KATE: Yeah. AMY: I just want to see if I can do better.
AMY: She can't. It was an 18. KATE: Nice.
JERRY: The weight comes up a bit.
AMY: K.
JERRY: And Onyx says,
"I have known you in two worlds. Maybe more. I may meet you in a third."
"When this happens, I will expect payment."
AMY: I will take that deal.
Absolutely. You have my word.
JERRY: The paw comes up.
Paw down here.
Looks around a little bit. Says,
"You may go but your mice are forfeit."
RYAN: Well he can't see us still, right? He can only see her?
JERRY: Well the mice that you allied with, certainly.
RYAN: Oh okay.
AMY: We... we need our mice to be able to leave.
They're not our mice. They're just the mice.
KRIS: Can we parlay this into a ride on the cat's back?
RYAN: Yeah. KRIS: Perhaps?
KRIS: We can cover more ground. AMY: How about this.
JERRY: Cat ride? AMY: How about this.
AMY: I agree. KRIS: Upgrade.
AMY: The mice are forfeit.
However you being such a great hunter,
it would be no sport for you take them when they're right under your feet.
You, who enjoys the hunt so much.
If you will take us the rest of the way, you can be free to hunt these mice to your heart content.
AMY: I will roll again for that. You want me to? JERRY: Let's do it. Let's see it.
AMY: Got nothing left. RYAN: Yeah so you have disadvantage.
AMY: So I'm at true dis-- Nope. I'm just at blank.
Please!
20!
RYAN: Hey! KATE: Oh!
AMY: That's never happened ever!
KATE: (grunting) Yes!
AMY: That's so good! For me. I'm a bad roller. (laughs)
JERRY: So you guys are ahead of this. You can see this conversation.
I mean your hand is on your greatsword. You're ready to kill cats.
RYAN: I'm bringing those acid up. Like, oh boy. Bleh. Bleh. Bleh. Bleh.
KRIS: I dial 9-1 on my sigil.
KATE: I hear this conversation and I start to say my goodbyes to my mouse.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. KATE: Well it's been so nice.
JERRY: Good pets. Good pets for everybody. We're going to pet two mice. Let's do two mice at once.
KATE: Two mice. Two mice.
JERRY: So you are-- it's like a contact juggling thing, like a David Bowie thing.
Like you just have your chunk, your geometric shape--
KRIS: Yeah. I may not even be aware that I did it.
JERRY: Yeah you don't even know. You're just watching this happen. You're ready.
You see she's pushed into the ground.
You see it lessen.
You see it come back like this.
And then you see the two of them walking toward the door.
And then you see it get down on its haunches, and you feel that same rumble.
As soon as its belly touches the wood.
KRIS: The purr.
JERRY: You feel that rumble again in the wood.
RYAN: Cats purr?
KRIS: That's a great twist. That's good short story writing.
JERRY: I'm a professional. I ain't fuck around.
AMY: If you bring up a purr in act 20 you got to--
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. KRIS/RYAN: Chekhov's purr.
RYAN: Damn it. You got there first.
JERRY: No. That was the purr that was on the mantle.
RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: The mantle purr.
Anyway, that's the situation. You can get right on that haunch.
RYAN: Yeah. I go for the haunches. JERRY: If you will.
RYAN: Dibs. Haunch dib.
JERRY: The mice do not understand what's happening right now.
AMY: So I still have some time left, to what I'm assuming that didn't take--
JERRY: About ten minutes?
AMY: Now I don't know this, but Walnut would know this, so I'm going to ask you.
JERRY: Yeah.
AMY: If I speak to the mice, will the cat be able to understand it?
JERRY: Mm-mmm. Mice don't speak cat, and vice versa.
AMY: Great, so I look at the mice,
RYAN: That's why they fight so much. AMY: and I say--
JERRY: Yeah exactly, at the end of the day-- RYAN: Communication.
RYAN: You know, this is just an allegory...
JERRY: Isn't that the issue? They're at loggerheads. It's about language.
AMY: So I just want to look down at them as we're climbing up, and I say,
I bought your freedom for now. Do not go back to your old home. That is the food place.
I bought you this chance to find a new home. And a new queen.
And then I start quoting Watership Down to them because--
JERRY: You start talking about flayrah...
AMY: And then I say, you know he will eat you but first he has to catch you.
And then I say maybe like fly you fools, or something. Just turn them away.
RYAN: And they say, didn't we hire you to kill this thing?
As they run away, this is not what we thought this to be.
KRIS: Okay I guess we'll move. All right.
JERRY: You see their eyes glisten like jewels in the dim light and they break off in three different directions.
AMY: Bye.
KATE: Goodbye. They did call that one, by the way.
KATE: They were like Far Mice usually fuck us over. JERRY: Far Mice are full of fucking shit!
KATE: Yeah we kind of did it. RYAN: Happened again.
KATE: Sorry. KRIS: At the end of the day they're mice.
RYAN: Yeah. I say, I don't care. You're a dumb mouse.
And I'm a dragon man.
KRIS: Thanks for the ride.
AMY: My life's more important than yours. RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: That's what's going on.
KRIS: I put my cigarette out on its forehead.
(laughter)
RYAN: I kick it as I get off with my spurs. Ugh. On to a bigger animal. Whatever.
AMY: I've been thinking about this problem all week.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. RYAN: I know.
AMY: Talked it over with my mother, my grandmother...
JERRY: Yeah. What did they suggest? RYAN: Us?
AMY: Try and convince the cat it was the mice's new queen. Which...
RYAN: Ah that would have been funny too.
AMY: I don't think that's a level for K'thriss to have those spells yet.
KRIS: What the heck. I don't think that's ever in my purview.
KATE: Could Rosie have done that? Sorry we're metagaming.
RYAN: Yeah we're going to--
AMY: I just want you guys to know there's been a lot of stress in my life.
JERRY: But fully three generations of Falcones had to be engaged on this problem.
The cat is languorously moves the rest of the way.
It's a easy, smooth ride. It's like the shocks are there.
It lowers you down.
And this door is not open but you can easily go underneath it.
And you can see that telltale, black, cool dark underneath the lip of the door.
As you're scooting yourself underneath the door to move out, you can see just the cat's mouth.
And it says, "Remember."
AMY: Mmm okay.
AMY: On my way out... JERRY: Yeah I kill the cat.
AMY: I got to do something real quick.
JERRY: Cat Exploder. AMY: It's a cantrip so it doesn't matter.
AMY: On my way out, to give the mice a fighting chance,
because I did promise I would give them a fighting chance, I use Druidcraft,
which allows me to mimic the sound of a small animal.
And so very near the cat, but not too near, I want to mimic the sound of a mouse.
And that's my parting gift to the mice, so I feel as though I kept my word.
JERRY: You see the cat's mouth curl up into a smile.
And it wheels away from where you have visibility in it.
KATE: Whatever helps you sleep at night.
KATE: (laughs) RYAN: Yeah really this was all morality play.
AMY: You know what. When you guys have a moral conundrum, I'll be sure to make fun of you too.
KRIS: It's like a fable. KATE: I know.
KRIS: It's like a fable we just watched happen.
RYAN: I legit live pragmatic dragon terms.
JERRY: I was-- I don't know. I had a super good time.
JERRY: In any case, the classic thing you have experienced it multiple times now.
That pressure shift each time you enter a new version of this construct.
KRIS: This time the Homeward Light is on the ceiling!
Or we're on the top floor! Oh!
JERRY: It's all gelatin!
No, no, no.
As you pass through underneath...
you enter the upper half-circle where the doors and rooms are.
And you look down into the place proper.
You can still see the chandelier has its classic configuration.
It doesn't really change at all.
Like that seems to be the North Star of this construct. You always know where it's going to be.
And you see three people...
around this table...
just seated at the bar.
Plates of food in front of them.
And as you enter laying down, of course, as you get back up and look over the edge,
the three of them raise their glasses and say, "Hey!"
PLAYERS: (unenthusiastically) Hey...
KRIS: I have my hand on my sigil. RYAN: Dusting myself.
RYAN: Hey, hey. KATE: Hey...
RYAN: Mouse fur on me. KRIS: Can I kill these guys now?
KATE: What do these people look like?
JERRY: They look like...
RYAN: Does Kris recognize them?
JERRY: Professional adventurers from the looks of it.
RYAN/KATE: Okay.
JERRY: Obviously different skill sets, different traditions than your party. But no less valid.
You know, these are choices that people make.
One person-- obviously K'thriss is a warlock.
His approach to the mystic arts involves a pact with an entity of some kind.
It's a power transfer type of arrangement.
This is clearly someone who engages with magic in a more studious, studied way.
There is someone who is dressed in platemail seated at the table.
And there is also someone in light, loose-fitting leather armor with their hood pulled back.
KATE: I'm going to point to them and go, Far Mice?
JERRY: The um...
KRIS/KATE/RYAN: Yeah...?
JERRY: They look back and forth and laugh.
KATE: Yeah... RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: Right? KATE: Us too.
RYAN: I put my hand on my sword. Because I don't--
I've had enough of this fucking place.
(laughter)
If I don't trust a door, I sure as shit don't trust three randos at a table.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. It's like where's the fucking basement floor here? Right?
One thing that you do notice that is strange.
Immediately. I mean, aside from the fact that you've been stuck for literally three days now.
Multiple rests, you have lived inside this construct.
There is something unique here and you don't think it's a part of the original set of this place.
Many of the chairs and one of the tables from the common room environment
have been pushed up against the door to barricade it.
KATE: That's not great.
I immediately go into helpless old lady mode.
JERRY: Oh nice. KATE: Which is great.
JERRY: It's not true.
KATE: No. No, no, no, but they don't know that though.
JERRY: We've seen it. I know where the DPS comes from.
KATE: I'm going to lean heavily on my quarterstaff and make my way over to the table and ask the studious one
how they managed to find themselves in this particular version of this construct.
JERRY: "Well... tell me if this sounds familiar."
"You entered into a contract with Acquisitions Incorporated..."
"You went where they told you to go and there was no one there."
"And then you left that place."
"But you didn't really leave it and you went to another version of it."
"And then you went to another version of it."
"And then you went to another version of it except you were small."
"Is that the same?"
JERRY: And the... KRIS: That's relatable.
JERRY: The fellow... KATE: Universal experience.
JERRY: She, this is the wizard, she is like,
"Yeah. We've been around the block a couple times on this."
And the knight just sort of like grunts
and you can see him just like shoveling the last couple bites of food from the plate into his mouth.
KATE: You guys are pretty hungry right?
RYAN: Yeah. KATE: Does that food look good to you?
RYAN: Oh yeah. That mouse was looking good to me.
KATE: Yeah.
JERRY: No, no. The one with the hood draped back...
Slight frame, but you know that that's not an indication.
You're way past making that type of judgement.
Just cracked like a whip. It's just a different musculature end to end.
She gestures over to the bar and says,
"I want to show you a trick, grab a plate."
KATE: Okay. RYAN: I'll say,
RYAN: I've gotten this far in this house by trusting strangers,
RYAN: so me first. KRIS: And objects.
RYAN: Yeah. And then the plate bites me.
(laughter)
KRIS: I put my hand near the plate's mouth. KATE: And you're immediately in love.
RYAN: Yeah. JERRY: No no. Exactly.
JERRY: It's just like you just have it, you just hold it close. So close.
KATE: I thought it would never happen to me again. RYAN: Yeah.
KRIS: A chance to make it right.
JERRY: Well no, I mean, you can see it, this is the point
at which it becomes like a Behind the Music black and white flashback.
It's like, this is where it all went wrong for Donaar Blit'zen.
His heart was broken by a door. He moved on to cutlery.
RYAN: I was fed up with this place when we were in the first room talking to the bartender.
I'm like beyond fed up with it now.
KRIS: I'm rich, I don't need to work. RYAN: Yeah.
KRIS: I don't want any of this. RYAN: Yeah.
KATE: So you've grabbed a magical plate.
RYAN: I'm really hungry. I don't want to do any of this at all but I'm like blinded by hunger.
KRIS: I'm going to take a plate too because I was interested in that glass that I held.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. So you grab the plate.
RYAN: Yeah, and then I say, all right.
JERRY: He's like "Set it down. Just set it down on any table. Any table! Just set it down on a table!"
As soon as you set it down...
Imagine like when you've flipped a coin and it hits a table and sort of spins, like this...
You set it down, it flips, it jumps over, and sort of rolls like a coin and by the time it's done it's full of food.
RYAN: What kind of food?
JERRY: It's a mixture, this particular one looks to be a stew. Almost like a shepherd's pie type thing.
Like a stew on mashed potatoes
KRIS: Oh nice. KATE: I'm getting hungry for real.
RYAN: Yum. (smacks lips) Ooh yum, yum, yum.
I say, ooh, yum, yum, yum, yum.
(laughter) KRIS: Roll for it.
RYAN: I just go (eating sounds)
Oh I fail. I miss, hit my eye.
KRIS: You say, yup, yup.
KRIS: And they don't know what that means. KATE: That's nothing.
JERRY: Give me a constitu... Nah, I'm just...
AMY: I was like, come on. RYAN: Actually, yeah I should like--
JERRY: No, no, no. There's-- RYAN: No, I know.
RYAN: I've learned my lesson with the door.
I sniff it, I examine it, incredulously. I say, wuh?
JERRY: You place your dragonborn snout right over the top and just draw it in.
There isn't anything wrong with it that you can tell. You think that this might be food.
You don't know why it comes-- you don't know why the plate flipped and did all this shit.
But you think that this is food.
RYAN: All right.
AMY: I mean, I would have added more rosemary but yeah there's nothing wrong with it.
RYAN: I'll-- JERRY: It's like 3.2 on Yelp.
RYAN: I go, huddle up! Huddle up!
And then we all gather around the plate.
Then I go, I'm gonna eat this first. I will take this bullet.
RYAN: Because I'm immune to diseases. KRIS: Okay. Right.
RYAN: And I'm really, really hungry, guys.
(whispering) And I don't trust these three.
KATE: Yeah. RYAN: I don't trust these three.
KATE: You guys can eat. RYAN: (shouting) I don't trust these three!
And then I go, om! (laughter)
JERRY: They laugh. RYAN: And then I go, om!
RYAN: (eating noises) Oh it's really good.
RYAN: Do I think it's good? And I'm like-- (eating noises) JERRY: Oh, no, no.
JERRY: This is absolutely-- this is 100% food. Do you finish the plate?
RYAN: Hell yeah! And now I'm no longer disadvantaged.
JERRY: As soon as-- (laughter)
JERRY: As soon as you scrape up the last bite... KATE: Uh oh.
JERRY: And put it into your craw zone.
It jumps, flips, and refills
RYAN: Nice!
KATE: My natural-- RYAN: I eat the second plate.
(laughter) RYAN: And then I go, (eating noises)
KATE: And then what?
JERRY: Yeah. RYAN: And then the third one.
RYAN: We've got an hour left! JERRY: Yeah but how many are you going to eat?
KRIS: You glutton!
KATE: Rosie... KRIS: That's the circle of hell we're in. Enjoy.
KATE: I want my companions to eat.
Because clearly this joker is having no problem with it.
But I have a natural suspicion from 120 years on this, this great--
JERRY: Yeah, particularly where food from strangers is involved.
KATE: Yeah, not super trusting.
So I'm going to continue to engage them in polite conversation and try to figure out
why we are both here.
Do they still have their letters? Can I ask them to see their letters from Acquisitions Inc?
JERRY: Oh. AMY: But didn't they dissolve?
KATE/RYAN/JERRY: The nuts did. KRIS: The acorns did.
KATE: Yeah. But if they've got-- Can we compare letters? See if they're identical?
JERRY: Oh! Yeah, yeah, yeah. They all come out.
JERRY: They just slap them down. KATE: Right.
JERRY: 25, 25, 25. &gt;&gt; KATE: Uh oh. KRIS: The letters immediately fill with food!
KATE: Excuse me! Excuse me! Excuse me! RYAN: Hey, where's your fourth guy?
KATE: Yes, so these numbers don't add up! What happened to...
AMY: Where's your fourth? KATE: What happened to number four if I may ask?
JERRY: "Let me tell you."
KATE: Please. RYAN: (eating noises) Hmm?
KRIS: (sound of spitting food out) KATE: You're eating him.
RYAN: No...! KATE: That's him!
JERRY: "So..."
"What was your experience with Onyx?"
KATE: Oh! &gt;&gt; AMY: Great. JERRY: "Positive?"
KATE: Yeah, Walnut had a very good time. AMY: "Paw-sitive."
RYAN: Yeah. KATE: Very-- I think it was a productive... interaction.
AMY: I think that's fair. RYAN: We're indentured to him now. How about you?
KRIS: You know, I don't like cats but I liked Onyx.
KATE: Yeah. JERRY: "Yep."
KATE: Onyx had a bend for death that we appreciated.
RYAN: Yeah, I liked it more than the mice. KATE: How about you?
RYAN: (muttering) Stupid mice. JERRY: The warrior...
JERRY: scrapes the last bit of the plate done.
It fills with food, he lifts up the plate and he just throws it behind the bar.
KATE: Well that's disgusting
JERRY: And he says, "The cat..." RYAN: We can do that?
JERRY: "was the frying pan. Are you familiar with the metaphor?"
"The cat was the frying pan."
"So, we came in to the top..."
"deck of the inn."
"Of this inn. Of this version of the inn."
"Which I don't even think is an inn!"
RYAN: I hear you. Yeah. KATE: You two would get along great.
JERRY: Right? RYAN: And I throw my plate in solidarity!
RYAN: Fuck this place. JERRY: Air high five.
RYAN: This guy's awesome. KRIS: That's cool.
RYAN: Hey I could be your last 25!
JERRY: He said-- (laughter)
"We came in and there was a dire wolf.
KATE: Hmm.
JERRY: "We slew the beast."
RYAN: Nice. JERRY: "And it became a werewolf."
JERRY: "And we slew that beast."
"And then it became a wolfwere."
The wizard laughs at this.
KATE: It's funny. JERRY: "Then it was a wereshark."
KATE: Nice! RYAN: Ah cool.
JERRY: "And it went on like this for what must have been a ten-day. I don't know how long we fought."
"Different..."
"assholes..."
"But when we defeated the last one,"
"and I don't even remember what it was,"
"our friend lay dead."
"But the inn changed."
"There are fresh beds whenever you open a door."
"There are-- there's hot food. Good food."
"Every time you get a plate."
"And I said,"
"If I left here..."
"I would be trying to earn money..."
"so that..."
"I could have fresh beds and food."
"And that's when it occurred to me that I didn't have to do it."
"I think maybe being a lackey for Acquisitions Incorporated isn't in my business plan."
KATE: How long have you been here?
JERRY: You want to do an intuition check? KATE: Sure.
KATE: I don't have it... What is the actual skill for intuition? I don't have that listed.
RYAN: Has anyone else eaten? AMY: Oh I'm eating.
KATE: Perception?
RYAN: If this goes south for some reason I don't want to be the only one in the boat.
KRIS: Oh I have a little more insight than that.
RYAN: Oh the food congeals in your stomach and turns into a monster that rips out your chest.
JERRY: Ten? &gt;&gt; KATE: Yeah. KRIS: Am I within hearing range of that?
JERRY: You want to get some? KRIS: Yeah. Let me take my advantage.
KRIS: I'm going to need the advantage for that one...
Ah... That will be a...
What is that 12?
KATE: Mm-hmm. &gt;&gt; JERRY: Okay. KRIS: Yeah.
JERRY: He says, "I don't know."
"And I don't care."
KATE: Okay.
RYAN: How many nights have you slept? Ballpark.
KATE: We're going to enjoy a brief meal.
And then we'll join you perhaps for some chess.
After this. In your beautiful inn.
JERRY: "Mm-hmm." KATE: Okay.
KATE: Good talk. JERRY: "All right."
KATE: I think this inn requires blood sacrifice.
JERRY: Okay.
AMY: That was a big jump--
AMY: Walnut just drops her spoon. RYAN: Yeah, wow. Jeez.
JERRY: So she-- K'thriss and Rosie. He's in feast mode.
K'thriss and Rosie are engaging with this group.
I would like to get a perception check from you...
AMY: I bet you would. JERRY: Walnut.
AMY: I bet you would. RYAN: You're eating too, right?
JERRY: Yeah, you ate the food. Everybody's okay now.
RYAN: Can we sleep?
KATE: Oh my god. RYAN: 20! Wow look at you.
AMY: 20. That's a 25. Sucka!
KATE: These rolls, my god. KRIS: What's going on over there?
JERRY: You hear...
So, while this is happening...
I mean, it's noisy. There's clanking of plates and then...
It's like a pie pan falling, like whenever these plates refill with food there's a ruckus.
AMY: Mm-hmm. JERRY: Right?
JERRY: The reason you can hear this is because it is very rhythmic.
AMY: Oh no. Are we being like soothed to stay?
JERRY: You hear like...
(knocking on table - three rhythmic taps)
AMY: Is it... JERRY: It's from upstairs.
AMY: Ah. Okay... RYAN: Ugh.
KRIS: Ugh. AMY: I would...
KRIS: Let's go. Right away. Up there. AMY: I would like to go investigate this noise.
AMY: I mean it sounds like someone may be knocking.
KATE: The door's also barricaded downstairs which is interesting...
RYAN: Yeah. AMY: That's true.
AMY: But is this coming from upstairs? JERRY: It is.
RYAN: Are they... What's that about with the barricade?
KATE: Just gonna ask them straight up?
RYAN: Yeah. Why is it like that? Did you guys do that?
JERRY: "We don't know what could come through on that side."
"We know where people come in."
"But we don't actually understand how any of this works."
"It's not an inn, I don't think."
RYAN: Hmm. Where have you been sleeping?
JERRY: "Fresh beds upstairs." RYAN: Hmm.
RYAN: (whispering) Upstairs' where the knocking is. AMY: We should.... see what's--
KATE: Let's go get Donaar to open a door.
RYAN: (sigh) AMY: When the inn's a knockin'....
RYAN: Yeah. AMY: Rockin'...?
AMY: Don't come a....
AMY: Night folks. KRIS: All right. Roll again.
KRIS: Let's have a advantage. RYAN: You took a look at the wrong camera. That one...
AMY: That's my left. I like looking at the wrong camera.
JERRY: No, no. No, that's what it is. It's just ah...
(laughter)
AMY: Bye! JERRY: Exactly.
KRIS: I'm repulsed. JERRY: But that's the thing.
JERRY: So as you are starting to move toward the stairs,
you can see the rogue just sort of like cast an eye over...
over the shoulder just like...
AMY: Ah. RYAN: I say, hey man. Just going to check out the beds.
AMY: I say, what big guy said.
JERRY: Yeah. RYAN: Chill.
JERRY: It's like-- he's like, "Our rooms are the first three."
"Any room past that is fine."
AMY: Absolutely. KRIS: Sure.
AMY: I make my way up, and I want to...
Can I listen at the first door?
KATE: Should we come up so we don't split the party?
AMY: Oh! I mean... KATE: Yeah.
KATE: I'm going to lean heavily
KATE: on my quarterstaff and take the stairs. RYAN: Team Food, we are rolling together.
KATE: So slowly. RYAN: Team yum yums.
KRIS: Yeah, I'm already on my way up there because these-- like this is un-life to me.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah.
KRIS: The idea of people who have denied themselves the beyond.
KRIS: This is satisfactory... is just wretched. AMY: The chance for death.
RYAN: These guys volunteered for prison, essentially. KRIS: I have nothing...
KRIS: I have nothing in common with these people. RYAN: A bed and a meal. That's jail.
AMY: Yeah, they've taken themselves outside of the cycle of life.
JERRY: So as you-- as your-- So you guys are all going to go upstairs?
KATE: Yeah all together. RYAN: We just said we were going to take a little nappy.
JERRY: Yeah, exactly. KRIS: Let's all go up.
JERRY: As soon as your foot hits the first stair...
AMY: Of course. RYAN: It bites you.
JERRY: I would like to get a wisdom saves from...
KRIS: What? AMY: Saves?
JERRY: Rosie, Donaar, and K'thriss
AMY: Oh. &gt;&gt; KRIS: Okay. KATE: Oh my, okay.
AMY: Oh no. KRIS: Wis...
AMY: I'm sorry my little chickadees.
RYAN: So I get a plus two on my saving throw for wisdom? &gt;&gt; AMY: Yes. KRIS: How many do I got left on this bad boy?
KATE: I'm going to use an advantage.
AMY: Yeah, yeah, you got it. KATE: You want to knock me down one, Jerry.
KRIS: Knock me down as well. RYAN: 19!
KATE: Oh yeah, it's not good.
JERRY: 19 is very good.
RYAN: I'm smart as shit. KRIS: Ugh. &gt;&gt; KATE: 18?
KRIS: So it's gonna be a... JERRY: God that's really good too.
KRIS: (lip smacking) (singing) Ba ba ba bah. What is it wisdom?
JERRY: Wisdom. KRIS: It's gonna be a 12 for me.
JERRY: Ugh. RYAN: I start quoting A Brief History of Time.
KRIS: Hmm wise.
JERRY: All right. RYAN: E equals MC Stairs.
RYAN: (fake laughter)
JERRY: Monster. You're the devil.
AMY: I get out my bow and I just shoot myself.
JERRY: (laughing) Exactly.
It's got to be context appropriate.
I want all the suicide in this game to be legit.
KRIS: Okay, how do I get bitten?
JERRY: Not yet. KATE: Door bites me.
KRIS: What bites me?
JERRY: Not yet. You hear a whisper.
Almost like a person who is reading a book
and just sort of like mouthing along with the words.
You hear a whisper from the wizard.
KATE: (whispering) Oh no.
JERRY: You really don't think much of it. There's no reason that they would harm you.
Like you can't think of any reason. In fact, you feel...
your attitude toward them, generally, is positive.
You can't imagine a scenario in which they would do you harm so you don't...
pay a lot of attention to that. It's fine.
KRIS: It's not positive, but it's ambivalent.
JERRY: No, it's positive. You feel good. KRIS: Really?
KRIS: Feel good inside? Something's wrong. JERRY: You feel good.
JERRY: You would help them move. Let me put it like that.
AMY: K'thriss and the brain. JERRY: You would help this wizard move.
RYAN: Ah great. KRIS: Do they know I feel this way?
AMY: Without payment. KRIS: Do you guys know?
JERRY: No.
KRIS: Oh my god. KATE: Does my... Do I feel the same with my 18?
JERRY: No. No, no. You're just following Walnut upstairs in this version of the Inn.
You are behind Walnut.
JERRY: You're heading on your way up. RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: About halfway up the stairs...
RYAN: Mm-hmm.
JERRY: Walnut, I need a wisdom save from you.
AMY: I bet you do... I bet you do.
AMY: Mmm. Hang on. That's plus five. 12. RYAN: You need some books. Book learning.
JERRY: That's a shit show. RYAN: Yeah.
KATE: Yikes. AMY: Well they can't all be 20's.
KRIS: Hey mine was a 12. JERRY: Exactly.
KRIS:  I thought it was okay. I like these guys.
RYAN: (laughs) We should stay here. KRIS: Yeah.
JERRY: Yeah, it is at this point-- So you're right behind Walnut as you're walking up the stairs.
JERRY: You're like not touching the railing. RYAN: Oh no.
JERRY: You're like tippy toe on the thing.
It's like in your mind you're sort of psyching yourself up to reach for that door.
You have like door-- You have PTSD but the D is for door.
RYAN: I will not touch the door. Yeah. We made that joke last time. I'll make it every time.
JERRY: No, no. Every game it's going to come back.
RYAN: Post Traumatic Stress "Dis-door-der."
JERRY: Until it's fucking appreciated. KATE: Yep.
JERRY: So... Here's the situation, so from behind...
from behind Walnut...
you can see...
like growing up from the neck
you see this shimmering...
razor sharp crown form from the base of her neck.
All the way up and around until it's like a gleaming diadem.
That must hurt to wear in some way.
KRIS: That crown... RYAN: I say,
JERRY: Walnut... RYAN: I don't think that was there...
JERRY: You turn around...
JERRY: And Donaar is right in front of you...
and you attack him.
RYAN: Ugh, great. JERRY: With your scimitar.
AMY: Awesome. Cool, okay. Let's see. RYAN: (wheezing noises)
KRIS: Dang it, I know what this is. AMY: That's plus five... Nine.
RYAN: Yay.
JERRY: What's your armor class?
RYAN: 18. JERRY: Okay, so it's half.
JERRY: So she turns around. You don't see Walnut in there at all.
And she-- the scimitar comes of the sheath in the same motion that it catches you in the chest.
But even on the stairs you don't move at all.
JERRY: You don't move an inch. RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: It just like connects and nothing happens. RYAN: Big tough boy.
JERRY: It just stops. All right we need initiative, folks. RYAN: And I'm like...
RYAN: I mean I'm proud for a minute.
AMY: You're gonna fight your nut.
RYAN: I'm like, hey I just met you. KATE: 12.
RYAN: (sigh) One. AMY: 20!
KRIS: Let me give you something.
RYAN: I go last. JERRY: 20?
KRIS: What is going on? That's three of them! AMY: That's my third 20 of the game!
AMY: Mwah! &gt;&gt; KATE: Amazing. JERRY: Dude you're heatin' it up! It's like...
AMY: Blessed! KATE: Don't be excited. You're trying to kill us now.
AMY: Well... RYAN: Yeah.
AMY: We never introduced ourselves. I'm going to kill-- RYAN: I know, I'm gonna join these guys.
AMY: you without even knowing your name. RYAN: I'm not joking anymore.
KRIS: I have a 19. RYAN: They haven't attacked me. You have.
KRIS: 19. JERRY: Jeez.
JERRY: All right. KATE: I think they've identified you as their fourth share.
JERRY: Yeah
AMY: Well I'd get the share, that's really all that... KATE: That's true.
KATE: Don't have an emotional connection to us at all.
RYAN: At least we ate... JERRY: Ugh god.
KATE: At least you ate. Rosie-- AMY: If you're going to murder your friends
AMY: you should do it on a full stomach.
JERRY: All right... AMY: "Friends?" &gt;&gt; RYAN: Ugh. Friends.
JERRY: Here's the situation, Walnut.
AMY: Yeah. JERRY: So you can, you can move where you want to,
JERRY: but I determine the attacks. AMY: Totally fine.
JERRY: So I would like you to try to strike him again with your "sci-mi-tar."
AMY: Okay. RYAN: Go away!
AMY: That is a 23 to hit.
RYAN: Yeah well, I have an 18. KRIS: Stop with these 20s.
AMY: So then... JERRY: Okay. Let's get that damage going.
AMY: Okay, so it's a 1d6 plus three slashing so it's a five.
RYAN: So I take 5?
JERRY: Yeah, the first time, it just bounces off and you're like, okay. That's nice.
That's cool. That's therapeutic
And this this next one catches--
This next one actually catches under a plate and digs in a bit.
KRIS: It's a team-building exercise.
RYAN: Yeah really. JERRY: Yeah, exactly
RYAN: Is this a weird D&amp;D version of a trust fall?
JERRY: K'thriss Drow'b!
KRIS: What yeah, what's my-- RYAN: I say, dude!
KRIS: What's my state? Describe to me again. I'm now witnessing...
What's the lineup, who's in front of me? I'm witnessing this--
JERRY: Yeah, exactly. So you are at the back. KRIS: Yeah.
JERRY: Then Rosie, then Donaar Blit'zen, and then Walnut at the top of the stairs.
KRIS: Who spun around.
JERRY: Who has spun around and is now attacking Donaar.
KRIS: Momma mia... It's not great.
KATE: You're drunk. KRIS: I don't like the feeling.
KRIS: Am I still drunk? Is that still happening?
Ah I drank when I got here.
(laughter)
KRIS: It wore off so I...
Yeah what's going on behind us? What are these three clowns doing?
JERRY: Right now they are just watching the events.
Like they're watching it like you would, like a normal person would watch television.
KATE: (whispering) They're feeding us to this inn.
KRIS: Where does the combat and roleplay intersect? Because I want to speak to these creeps.
JERRY: You can. You can do whatever you want. KATE: At the corner of Dungeon and Dragon.
RYAN: Yeah, thanks for the help!
JERRY: (laughing) Yeah, at the corner of Dungeon and Dragon?
JERRY: That's the new name of the show! No we're taking a-- No more "C" Team!
KRIS: Get rid of the rest of it. Yes. JERRY: Hi!
RYAN: Can you magically bind her so I stop being attacked? How about that?
KRIS: I might not have any of that. JERRY: You can do whatever you like.
RYAN: I want to spit acid in Walnut's face.
JERRY: If you want to say a quick phrase or something like that, like--
RYAN: You're too close. You're way too close. JERRY: Again, if something is sufficiently...
JERRY: If something is rad then I'm okay with it.
KATE: Do a rad thing. &gt;&gt; AMY: It's the rad rule. KRIS: Oh boy.
KRIA: No, I've got nothing rad yet. KATE: Be a rad roach. &gt;&gt; AMY: Rad roach!
KRIS: You gotta give me-- (laughing) You gotta give me more time than that!
KRIS: No, I attack you too. RYAN: Oh great.
(laughter)
JERRY: I annihilate Donaar. KRIS: To show fealty to our new king.
AMY: Tag-teaming this dragonborn. RYAN: I call for the cat.
KATE: It's her diadem. RYAN: Onyx help.
KATE: I think that's the secret.
KRIS: I will... I'm going to... I'm going to... KATE: (in a high pitched voice) Attack the diadem!
KRIS: Oh boy. Hold on a second, RYAN: The what? &gt;&gt; KATE: Diadem.
KRIS: I'm going to-- I want to cast hex on you. AMY: Fight me, drow.
KRIS: Because I want to-- I want to drop your...
RYAN: Knock the crown off her head, yo.
AMY: I like my crown.
KRIS: Hang on, hang on, you all.
Uh... Hex!
KATE: I like your-- You're like, I like it! You got bougie real fast.
KRIS: Right, so the way Hex works is... RYAN: Raindrop.
AMY: Tell me. KRIS: You take extra damage when I attack you.
KRIS: But nobody else. AMY: Hmm oh so it's like your Hunter's Mark?
KRIS: Right. JERRY: Yeah, but spooky.
AMY: But spookier. KRIS: But scarier.
KRIS: But you also take a disadvantage to an ability check that I choose.
AMY: Take a guess which one you think would be good.
KRIS: What is your dex? Use that?
But the thing is, is that that doesn't define this stuff...
I want to make it easier-- I want to make it more difficult for you to cause harm.
AMY: Okay, what are you doing? KRIS: I don't think I can pull you out.
AMY: What do you think that might be?
RYAN: Just take the thing off her head!
KRIS: That's not... AMY: This is his way.
RYAN: All right. Okay. AMY: That's your way.
KRIS: That's my way. You knock it off! You're right next to her.
RYAN: Oh I'm gonna. AMY: You're a giant. You're a giant man.
RYAN: I got a big, wide acid spray. Might hit the crown, might not.
That's what we'll all find out in--
RYAN: in a few short turns. AMY: My beautiful girl.
KRIS: What does she need-- Does she sa... What does she need to save out of this? Or can she?
JERRY: She needs... KRIS: I'm assuming.
JERRY: Yeah this is probably--
JERRY: This sort of thing is usually a wisdom save. KRIS: A wisdom, okay.
KRIS: I want to...
You're all... are you Charisma?
KRIS: You are, aren't you? I can see it. KATE: You can't ask her.
KATE: You can't ask her. NO. KRIS: I can't ask her?
KRIS: I can go online right now... AMY: Slash, slash, slash.
KATE: Let's look at the Twitch feed...
AMY: Let's look at the Twitch chat. RYAN: I'm bleeding. Like, little faster!
RYAN: Slice, slice. KRIS: Okay, I'm going to do--
RYAN: Kris is over here consulting his books. Hmm. KRIS: I'm going to take away your dex.
KRIS: I'm going to give you a detriment to these dexes.
KATE: Dexes. Good one, yeah.
KRIS: That's my idea.
I'm going to do-- let me do another advantage.
Wait let me make sure I got to actually cast it.
KRIS: Oh it's a bonus action. JERRY: Yeah, yeah.
KRIS: Yeah, okay here we go.
KRIS: (silly thinking noises)
Nope. Don't want that. We don't like that.
KRIS: That's better, I like that a lot better. KATE: Ooh yeah.
AMY: What you got? KRIS: That's an 18.
AMY: Okay. KRIS: You can tell me if that hit or not.
KRIS: Did I Hex you? AMY: Yeah, oh yeah.
KRIS: Did you feel that Hex? JERRY: Okay.
AMY: Ugh. I'm vexed by your Hex.
RYAN: You done been Hexed. KATE: Nice.
JERRY: Okay so basically she takes more damage from you.
And her dex is in the bone zone?
KRIS: Yeah JERRY: Okay
KRIS: You take disadvantage on dex. JERRY: All right, now that was your bonus action
JERRY: what are you going to do with your regular action?
KRIS: Now I'm going to Dissonant Whisper the shit out of you-- No I'm not going to do that.
RYAN: Wait you can move. You didn't move.
KRIS: No I didn't move yet.
RYAN: No, you didn't move. AMY: That's fine.
RYAN: Move away from me. (laughs) AMY: No.
KRIS: (sigh) This is really difficult.
KATE: You can do it. JERRY: Yeah, so what are you gonna do?
JERRY: I mean you have this situation down here.
You have this situation up here on the stairs.
It's a double situation, situation.
KATE: (clapping)
KRIS: Oh my god, I don't want to open that door! RYAN: It's called the fisherman's gambit.
AMY: It's the razor's edge.
JERRY: This is the fucking razor's edge. RYAN: Yeah.
KRIS: This is the danger zone. RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: Or the highway to it.
KATE: Dungeon this dragon, son.
AMY: How long can he stall? KRIS: What would K'thriss do? WWKD?
KRIS: Besides hold the game up.
RYAN: Three weeks later... Yeah. (laughs) AMY: We're all dead.
KRIS: Umm...
RYAN: I go get another plate of food. I get a plate of food while I wait.
JERRY: Well here let me see, we have...
KRIS: Let me speak to these guys, it's all I can do. JERRY: We have this barricade...
JERRY: We have this here. KATE: Talk-- You want to talk to--
JERRY: We have that. KRIS: I want to talk to them.
KATE: to the dude bros? Okay. JERRY: Yeah, go ahead.
KRIS: Is this your doing?
JERRY: "Which?"
KRIS: The crown! And the attack!
JERRY: The wizard giggles.
RYAN: Guys, not cool. KRIS: Vampyr!
JERRY: But here's the terrible part, is that...
you giggle a little bit too.
RYAN: (whispering) Oh god... KATE: (whispering) Oh no you like it?
KRIS: Well I know what it is. JERRY: Well you understand why they would do it.
KRIS: Oh yeah. JERRY: Right?
KRIS: I can tell. JERRY: Yeah.
JERRY: It makes perfect sense.
And it is a little funny.
RYAN: It is a little funny. KATE: I fail to find humor.
KRIS: Has that been my action? RYAN: I'm stabbed and I'm like, this is kind of funny.
JERRY: If you have another thing you'd want to say...
Since you didn't use your action proper, if you want to have some other juice, go for it.
KRIS: All right, let me give it a shot. I'm going to do a--
I'm going to in a jestful way-- Vicious Mockery.
JERRY: To who?
KRIS: To the wizard.
JERRY: You cannot. KRIS: I cannot?
JERRY: You can't. You wouldn't.
KRIS: Not even in a joshing sort of a "you-so-and-so?"
JERRY:  No, but these other people, maybe.
KRIS: Oh okay. RYAN: Hit that rogue.
KRIS: Now that I'm aware of that...
Yeah, let me pop the leather wearer.
RYAN: Or open that door. Someone's knocking. They're probably here to help.
We've had a lot of success with doors.
KRIS: I'm going to... RYAN: I'll open the door!
KRIS: I'm going to hang back on that one.
JERRY: Go for it. KRIS: Yeah, let's do Vicious Mockery.
KRIS: Ooh! That's going to be a 22. KATE: What's Vicious Mockery do?
KRIS: Wait a minute.
KATE: To what? Can you just cast it? It's just a cantrip right?
KRIS: I think I can just say it.
JERRY: No, no, no, Vicious Mockery you don't have to roll to attack.
KRIS: That's right. They have to save against it. KATE: Right.
JERRY: Mm-hmm.
KATE: You just want to roll those dice. KRIS: I have these cards here that I haven't used.
KRIS: (whispering) Because I didn't-- JERRY: I do save against it.
KATE: Uh oh. KRIS: Okay, damn.
KATE: All right. KRIS: All right. Then I just relax.
AMY: Vicious Mockery I always just think of as like Cyberbullying, the spell.
JERRY: Yeah. KRIS: I wrote you a really bad review.
AMY: I leave bad comments on your video. Yes. JERRY: It's the magical version.
JERRY: All right.
KATE: Is it Rosie's turn?
JERRY: It is almost Rosie's turn.
AMY: Nope. KATE: (groans)
AMY: It looks like you've got a little vampyr face before Rosie.
RYAN: I got this knife in me. KATE: Oh vampyr?
RYAN: And I'm just... AMY: It's a good looking scimitar.
JERRY: So the three of them stand up from the table.
And say...
the rogue says,
"We have a really good thing going here."
"And we don't know what happens if someone leaves."
"So you can't leave."
AMY/KATE: Hmm.
JERRY: "You can make your peace with it..."
"or we can figure you out."
"Just like we figured out the other groups that came through here."
KATE: I crack my knuckles... menacingly. (knuckles cracking)
KRIS: There's so many. KATE: So many knuckles.
JERRY: New knuckles come out.
AMY: Just everything cracks. JERRY: So they're waiting. They are not attacking yet.
JERRY: Now it's Rosie Beestinger's turn. KATE: Rosie Beestinger...
KATE: I cast Silence on that wizard!
JERRY: Ooh. KATE: Shut up!
KRIS: (whispering) Oh yeah. AMY: You kids quiet down!
(laughter)
KATE: Do you know what time it is? It's late! AMY: You're making a racket.
JERRY: Awesome. Okay.
So the middle of the middle of the--
there's no more creaking of chairs, tables--
the middle goes out and you can see their mouths furiously moving.
As soon as you notice-- as soon as they notice the silence they move immediately into a very sophisticated
set of gestures that are not, I mean it's like...
It's robust. It's not-- it isn't like, hey let's do this.
They are communicating ideas with it.
Um, next up we have Donaar.
RYAN: Ah...
AMY: (grunts) RYAN: Hmm well, I got to...
AMY: (grunts) (laughs)
RYAN: All right we've got a couple things going on, I'm getting stabbed.
JERRY: Repeatedly. RYAN: By crazy-pants.
RYAN: There's a knocking upstairs.
Invariably will be helpful.
JERRY: Yeah. RYAN: And then three...
KATE: Very quiet.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, yeah RYAN: Yeah, very quiet.
RYAN: Umm... JERRY: Yeah.
JERRY: It's your choice. It's your choice. RYAN: And you got the crown on your head.
JERRY: Welcome to Dungeons &amp; Dragons. RYAN: And it's like... yeah...
KATE: Get that crown. RYAN: I want to get her off me.
RYAN: I'm going to... KATE: Yeah, smack that crown around.
KATE: Can you barf acid on her crown?
RYAN: I--I was-- JERRY: Just on the crown? No.
JERRY: It's not. It isn't that-- It's not like a lathe. RYAN: It's not precision.
JERRY: (laughing) It isn't just like... right here.  KATE: I cast Acid Lathe!
JERRY: Yeah.
KATE: You can do it! AMY: Just put me out of my misery at that point.
KATE: You can do it! RYAN: I kind of want to throw Amy at them.
AMY: Walnut. RYAN: Or Walnut. I want to throw her at them.
RYAN: To disrupt their little dance. KATE (whispering) Can you do it? Please?
JERRY: Yeah, you can. KATE: (whispering) Yes!
KRIS: Oh yeah
KATE: Yeah, do it! RYAN: So...
KRIS: And she's gonna suffer on that dex...
KRIS: so she's going to land hard. AMY: I have so many HP!
AMY: It's fine! I don't want you to see. Go ahead.
RYAN: You shouldn't have done that! AMY: You said you were going to do it.
RYAN: I can't like, make a swipe at the crown first, can I?
RYAN: That's two actions, right? JERRY: No no, just give me... you can just give me--
JERRY: If you want to throw her or get her out of here...
RYAN: Well, I do, but...
KATE: Like a bowling ball.
RYAN: Onto the table, onto the table to-- KATE: Knock down those pins!
RYAN: just disrupt their little dance. JERRY: Yeah, it's...
JERRY: it's shimmering and lightly translucent.
RYAN: Okay. So this will-- JERRY: Like it's-- you know what I mean, like you're not--
RYAN: And this will knock-- JERRY: It seems like some magic bullshit.
RYAN/KRIS: Yeah. RYAN: Which I hate. I fucking hate this place!
JERRY: Yeah. RYAN: All right.
KATE: She's bendy and you have mending so you can heal her.
KRIS: I'll fix her, whatever, it's great. RYAN: So what do I got to-- what do I just roll strength?
JERRY: Yeah, I was gonna say, this is going to be a strength...
KRIS: It's going to be a caber toss. RYAN: Athletics?
JERRY: Yeah, this is-- Yeah I would say druid throwing is a sport where you're from.
RYAN: So when I'm doing this, I have a strength bonus and an athletic bonus,
I don't do them-- I take the bigger one right?
JERRY: You get-- it's a combo pack.
RYAN: Oh, so it's eight? Plus eight? JERRY: Yeah.
JERRY: No, no this is-- You are good at this. This is... RYAN: Cool.
RYAN: I got two advantages.
RYAN: How bad do I want to whip Amy over there? KATE: You do. You want it real bad.
AMY: Walnut. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Yeah, Walnut. KATE: You want it real bad.
RYAN: How bad to I want to whip Walnut over there? KATE: Yeah, real bad.
RYAN: I'm going to chuck Pinecone across this room. KRIS: Put your back into it. &gt;&gt; KATE: Yes, yeah.
JERRY: You want to try it?
RYAN: 19. JERRY: 19.
RYAN: Oh wait plus eight.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. KATE: I think you chuck her. You chuck that nut!
JERRY: She's a little cagey. She's come at you once already, twice already.
And then, she goes in for another like overhand chop,
and you just catch her underneath the arm.
Just one motion. Just like whoop!
Like that, just one smooth motion.
Scimitars up in the air.
Right over the railing, down on the edge.
That's four points of damage for you.
RYAN: (whispering) Sorry.
AMY: (angry noise) Frothing. RYAN: I took five!
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. Right on the table.
So food, stew...
It's very Game of Thrones, I could go into it for ten minutes.
JERRY: Just every-- AMY: It's pornographic--
KRIS: But you eat some of it as you land and you get that four right back.
JERRY: And you regain health. KRIS: Immediately.
JERRY: Absolutely. RYAN: Gravy.
JERRY: So you've tossed her down and then this...
(tapping on table)
JERRY: The pounding is less rhythmic. AMY: Nice.
JERRY: It is now more insistent. KRIS: Hee hee. That's why I'm giggling.
KATE: You love it. Love that pounding. (laughs) KRIS: Yeah. Mm-hmm.
RYAN: Oh man. You're going to be a problem too.
Uh... All right.
JERRY: It's like this is some other bullshit you have to deal with.
JERRY: This is Donaar in a nutshell. RYAN: Goddamn it yeah.
RYAN: I know, it really is. Like, I hate the shit out of this place. I did from the word go!
KRIS: It's all we've done. RYAN: And it's only getting worse!
RYAN: And now there's more of you than ever.
All of you non-dragons; therefore, not as great.
JERRY: Less good. &gt;&gt; KRIS: It's a problem. RYAN: Variations of just...
RYAN: hairy, pink little monsters.
All right. Wait and I get a move now too, right? JERRY: Mm-hmm, yeah.
JERRY: So you-- RYAN: Where are you in relation to me?
JERRY: Right behind you. Yeah. KATE: I'm at the base of the stairs.
RYAN: Okay, we're all at the base of the stairs right? KRIS: Behind you, yeah. We haven't gone up yet, yeah.
KATE: Except Walnut. KRIS: We may want to dart up there.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. So there's-- AMY: Dead friend.
JERRY: Whomp whomp upstairs.
JERRY: This crew down here. RYAN: Hmm.
JERRY: She's also down here on the table.
AMY: Hmm. RYAN: Right.
RYAN: Should I go up the stairs? I'll go up the stairs. I'm going to go up to the top of the stairs.
I'm not gonna mess with any doors or anything. I'm just going to go to the top of the stairs.
And I'm gonna say, you guys just want to be in prison?
Is that it? You just are happier in prison?
I say this as I run.
This is stupid, you guys are dumb.
JERRY: It's weird. KRIS: I've seen the cage! &gt;&gt; RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: It's weird but that sound is coming from the second door, and it appears to be the door itself.
RYAN: Oh good.
JERRY: Pounding-- The door itself is undulating...
JERRY: Sensually.... No. KRIS: Ooh.
RYAN: (laughs) Nice.
KRIS: It beckons. AMY: Yeah!
JERRY: That's not what's happening. KRIS: An ancient art.
(laughter)
KATE: Is there a Mr. Door?
(laughter) RYAN: So... yeah.
AMY: What's a pretty young door like you doing in an inn like this?
JERRY: Yeah doing in an inn like this.
JERRY: We are back up at the top with Walnut.
So Walnut, now that you are down here by the table,
AMY: Yeah.
JERRY: you can no longer attack Donaar Blit'zen.
AMY: Sure. RYAN: Phew!
AMY: I'm not in control of my own faculties anyway. JERRY: But Kris...
JERRY: But K'thriss Drow'b is near enough for you to get a good swipe at.
So why don't you give him a swipe with the scimitar. AMY: Sure.
KRIS: Go ahead. Give it a shot!
AMY: That is a 14.
JERRY: That's, that should be good. KRIS: Yeah.
AMY: Oh no that's a six! RYAN: I was gonna say...
RYAN: It's a six but don't you get a Dex penalty?
AMY: But it's not... RYAN: Does that effect this?
JERRY: No, no, no. AMY: No, it's just plus five.
RYAN: Oh plus 5 on your scimitar. AMY: So, that's actually only a...
AMY: that number.... 11.
JERRY: Oh! No, that's insufficient.
KRIS: I catch the scimitar blade in my teeth. JERRY: Yeah. (growls)
AMY: What would that be if I did a one maybe.
JERRY: No exactly, just like-- you're looking at her,
JERRY: just a quick move to the left. RYAN: I'm glad you're rolling poorly.
RYAN: What if these were twenties? JERRY: Is all it took. Right? It's all it took.
JERRY: The twenties are coming in at the right spot.
JERRY: I need you to give me a wisdom save please. AMY: Sure.
RYAN: And she has a movement too, right?
AMY: I do, you haven't been giving me those movements.
Oh! Wow! Seven! (sigh)
AMY: Eight. JERRY: Your mind is still clouded but you can move.
AMY: Cool. I... I guess somehow find the strength within me to move as far away from K'thriss as possible.
KRIS: Go behind these guys.
RYAN: Run over to the door and start moving-- AMY: Where are the other people?
JERRY: So they are... AMY: Just lay them out like...
JERRY: They're basically right behind you.
So whatever this crown is, and you can sort of see it out the edge of your peripheral vision,
whatever it is it's making you attack people but it doesn't control where you move.
AMY: Okay.
JERRY: So right now you are sort of interposed between K'thriss and this other party.
And now you have the ability to move.
AMY: Well I want to move towards the other party.
Absolutely. 100%.
JERRY: So you just turn around--
JERRY: and prepare yourself for the next-- AMY: Oh yeah, just like...
AMY: like I'm hollow but there's like a tear.
JERRY: Yeah, there's just the one black tear. AMY: Yeah
KRIS: Question. JERRY: Just coming down. Yeah.
KRIS: Okay, it's not an attack but as your movement
can you walk past them and hold your sword out at an angle...
and just sort of clothesline them. It's not an attack!
KATE: It's not technically an attack. AMY: It's like stealth keying a car.
(laughter) JERRY: You can decapitate three of them.
AMY: Can I key the party? KATE: Yeah. &gt;&gt; JERRY: Exactly.
JERRY: K'thriss Drow'b.
So basically, you're just going to turn around and get ready for the next round.
AMY: Yeah.
JERRY: Okay. AMY: Are they closer or farther away?
AMY: Are they close to like the entrance to the basement at all?
JERRY: No, no. They are-- so imagine they're sort of in the center of this common room--
AMY: Gotcha, gotcha, gotcha. Okay I'll go to them. JERRY: And then they are, you know,
JERRY: it's all about maybe 15 feet from this door barricade.
AMY: Gotcha, gotcha. JERRY: K'thriss Drow'b.
KRIS: (whispering) Oh no, monstrous.
I am... I... Am I able to attack this wizard?
KRIS: This giggler. JERRY: You wouldn't.
KRIS: Oh I wouldn't because I'm feeling pretty good about them.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah yeah. But there are other people here.
KRIS: (laughs) RYAN: Amy. I mean Walnut.
KRIS: Oh yeah! That's a good idea. No... RYAN: Yeah.
RYAN: She took a swing at you.
KRIS: I go back to that-- I go back to the rogue.
JERRY: Mm-hmm. KRIS: And this time I'm going to do Dissonant Whispers.
AMY: Finally. RYAN: Yeah.
KRIS: Dissonant Vespers (Amy whispering indistinctly)
RYAN: Fan favorite. KRIS: Again! Another one I don't have the card for.
KRIS: So let me pop it in there,
because it too, is not a...
KRIS: if I remember correctly... JERRY: Mm-hmm.
KRIS: Yeah, you have to save wisdom against it.
So the question is do you?
JERRY: All right. Uh...
Ugh.
Nope, that's the filth zone.
KRIS: All right! JERRY: What happens next?
KRIS: You have got to take 3d6 psychic.
JERRY/KATE: Ugh. AMY: Get them.
KRIS: And enjoy that.
So that's gonna be... nine... Woo! That's 14!
KATE/AMY: Schnitzels. KRIS: Enjoy 14-- 14 psychic damage!
JERRY: Good Lord!
KRIS: And you have to take your reaction to get away from me.
Because I made you feel very bad.
JERRY: Oh okay. AMY: Go think about what you did.
JERRY: Yeah, it... KRIS: It...
JERRY: Yeah I was going to say it...
runs at like-- like scramble--
JERRY: All of its dexterity is in play here going over-- KRIS: (making scared sound effects)
JERRY: Yeah, like a spider. Just over tables and chairs, and then it just slides over the back edge of the bar.
KRIS: Right.
KRIS: Like a Western. JERRY: Mm-hmm.
KATE: You're calling it an "it," where prevously it was a "she." Is it now an "it?"
JERRY: I messed up. KATE: Hmm...
JERRY: "She". I was like hmm... KATE: Okay. Okay, okay, okay!
KATE: Just checking. I was like, are we fighting--
KATE: some kind of spider-monster now? JERRY: No. Is it a changeling? No, no, no.
KATE: It's Dungeons &amp; Dragons, motherfucker.
JERRY: No, no. I was like... shit... Shit. KATE: Yeah. Okay.
JERRY: Yeah, anyway. Next up is this crew.
From behind the bar...
you see a hand crossbow come up.
And he is going to take a shot at you--
JERRY: K'thriss Drow'b. RYAN: The fourth guy.
RYAN: The fourth guy. RYAN: Nice.
JERRY: That is 14....  yes. Mm-hmm. KRIS: Yeah, you got me.
AMY: Got him. JERRY: Two points.
KRIS: Okay.
KATE: Wait there's a fourth guy now?
JERRY: No, no, there's the person behind the bar.
RYAN: There was the hand behind the bar.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's the person...
JERRY: it's the rogue. &gt;&gt; KATE: The rogue who just-- RYAN: Oh! The rogue who ran away.
KRIS: I thought it was like a secret ambush.
RYAN: I thought it was a secret ambush too!
RYAN: It's a good story, it was clever. KATE: She's like John McClane-ing it over the bar.
JERRY: Now you're paranoid. RYAN: I am paranoid! Yeah.
RYAN: Because I'm in a magic house that keeps attacking me!
KRIS: I love how lame it is that we didn't even check behind here. He's like, he was just right there!
He's like five feet away. Now he's shooting at you.
JERRY: He was just reading the whole time. KRIS: Okay, so two points of damage for me. All right.
JERRY: Exactly. KRIS: Sure. Right in the...Take it on the arm.
JERRY: The wizard... is going to...
scoot around the back edge of the tables and chairs,
and take up a position behind the barricaded door.
And you hear the sharp whisper of Magic Missiles
JERRY: erupt from her hand. KRIS: (whispering) Magic Missile. Magic Missile.
KRIS: (whispering) Magic Missile.
JERRY: That's seven points for you, Donaar.
KATE: I still do have Silence going.
JERRY: Yeah.
JERRY: She was able to move far enough out of the-- KATE: Outside my range?
JERRY: out of the edge. Exactly.
RYAN: I just take it.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. And the knight... AMY: Uh oh.
JERRY: the knight can do all of his work in a completely silent room.
KATE: That's true.
JERRY: He basically moves up past you. Just scoots you to the side. Just like--
AMY: Rude. JERRY: Well yeah like you would move a chair.
JERRY: Just pushes you off to the side.
And tries to bring his greatsword down on Rosie Beestinger with a one.
It doesn't happen at all. Would you like to interpret this one for us, Rosie?
KATE: Yes, absolutely. Rosie sees-- sorry. (claps)
I see the knight coming.
I plant my quarterstaff down and I wait because I think he's probably an idiot and I'm right.
JERRY: Yeah, it turns out.
KATE: I don't move at all. The sword comes down slowly and doesn't come close. And I say...
I thought so.
RYAN: Punk.
KRIS: It sweeps around and just goes back in the sheath.
(laughter)
JERRY: No, it's just one thing. All right. KRIS: (sheathing sound)
JERRY: No. And then he goes home.
(laughter) KRIS: Just like, puts his hat on.
JERRY: No, tips it. KRIS: Yeah.
JERRY: Rosie Beestinger, it is auspicious that it is your time to go.
KATE: Okay. So we've got a wizard casting Magic Missiles at Donaar...
We have a rogue shooting a crossbow at you and a knight on me with a greatsword.
JERRY: Mm-hmm.
KATE: Oh boy, oh boy. Okay. JERRY: Lots of approaches.
JERRY: Got the barricade. All kinds of stuff. KATE: Okay.
RYAN: Forest Friends. Oh you can't do that. KATE: So certainly what I'm going to do is...
KATE: go after this knight. JERRY: Ooh this is going to be a good fight.
KATE: Yeah it's gonna be a good fight. I'm also-- so I'm gonna do a regular attack,
I'm also going to spend a ki point and use a power called patient defense.
Which means I dodge as a bonus action and attacks against me have disadvantage.
JERRY: Oh this is going to be sweet. This is like that David and Goliath fight.
JERRY: That classic technique. KATE: Yeah. Yeah, classic! Classic.
KATE: It's gonna be more like Shadow and Colossus. I'm gonna climb all over this bitch.
KATE: All right. Soo... oof. JERRY: You're gonna climb up on his back ridge.
KATE: I'm gonna climb over nothing.
RYAN: You trip. KATE: Yeah, I got a ten to attack.
KATE: That's not good. That's not good. JERRY: Okay.
JERRY: So you make a quick swipe with the quarterstaff,
and then as he's pulling the sword back up from his previous failed maneuver,
it just clangs against the side.
Donaar.
RYAN: All right, I can-- JERRY: You have a good sense of the scene?
RYAN: Yeah and I've got a vantage point on everyone. I can see everyone, right?
JERRY: Yeah. RYAN: All right.
RYAN: They're all within range of me? Correct? JERRY: Mm-hmm.
RYAN: All right. I'm going to cast Bane.
JERRY: Bane? RYAN: So three creatures of my choice that I can--
JERRY: My choice! I choose!
AMY: My bane. My choice. RYAN: All right, yeah...
RYAN: They must make charisma saving throws.
JERRY: Okay.
RYAN: So all three of these...
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. And then what happens? AMY: All three--
AMY: of these people at the table with me right now. RYAN: I don't know. Let's see if they made them or not.
RYAN: And then I'll tell you.
KRIS: And if they don't, now what?
JERRY: Uh huh...
Ugh.
KRIS: (whispering) I was going to say, why don't you--
JERRY: Wizard's good. KRIS: (whispering) get that door open.
JERRY: Knight is an F fest and rogue is an F fest. RYAN: (whispering) No.
RYAN: Damn it. KRIS: (whispering) Get that door. Get that door.
JERRY: So two of them RYAN: All right, so...
RYAN: Those two who failed, whenever they make an attack or a saving throw before the spell ends
they have to roll a d4 and subtract that from their roll.
JERRY: Oh smooth! KATE: Very nice, very nice.
JERRY: Yeah so negative d4 plus disadvantage is a pretty good mess for them to be in.
AMY: That's what they get for being mediocre layabouts. RYAN: So they shouldn't be able to hit anyone anymore now, right?
Theoretically, they're just going be useless.
KRIS/RYAN: (silly "bleh" noises)
JERRY: Yeah yeah...it'll be like pool noodles
JERRY: (pool noodle whipping noises) RYAN: Yeah.
RYAN: Yeah.
KRIS: And you relax! RYAN: Yeah, I relax. Fight's essentially over now...
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, just check it out. Walnut! AMY: Is it?
KATE: Thanks for carrying us, Donaar.
JERRY: Take it away. So Walnut, he has pushed you to the side.
You are...
You sort of wheel around.
It's this first, mindless part, like you have the ability to move but there is this mindless part of you
that longs to destroy your friends.
AMY: Okay.
KATE: (whispering) That's so-- JERRY: Uh...
JERRY: Specifically in this case, Donaar.
AMY: Mmm... okay. Can I... I guess then I--
JERRY: Well actually, no, no, I was wrong. K'thriss. KRIS: Mmm.
AMY: I was going to say Donaar is really far away. RYAN: I was going to say, I'm really far away.
AMY: I really hate this dragon. RYAN: I'm like, hi, from across the room.
AMY: I'm like, you! (grunt) JERRY: I don't like you.
AMY: Okay, I guess then... I mean...
JERRY: Yeah, make your attack roll. AMY: (sigh)
KRIS: Yeah. JERRY: And deal damage to your friend Kris.
KRIS: Go ahead, that's how this works.
AMY: That is a 15.
KRIS: Yeah. RYAN: Plus five on that scimitar.
KRIS: Yeah. &gt;&gt; RYAN: Good yield. JERRY: Yeah, yeah.
AMY: Yeah, it's good. JERRY: It's pro-tier.
JERRY: All right. How much damage does your friend K'thriss take?
AMY: He takes... eight! JERRY: Oh! (sucks in breath)
KRIS: Whoa. That's not good for me.
KATE: Not looking good. KRIS: That's not good for me.
JERRY: All right now, lets get a wisdom save over there, Walnut.
KRIS: Yeah, I'm past bloodied now.
KATE: Think of all the wisest things you've ever heard.
AMY: Yeah, I look at my druidic focus... please!
KATE: (sigh) KRIS: Oh!
AMY: Nope! It's an 11.
KRIS: Ugh. JERRY: All right. Next up we've got...
JERRY: Oh here, so where do you want to move now?
AMY: Away! RYAN: As far away as possible.
AMY: I want to move towards the barricade?
JERRY: Sure. KATE: Toward that wizard.
JERRY: Yeah, over in the wiz...in the W zone.
AMY: Yeah, I want to go to the W Zone. JERRY: You want to put up a W?
RYAN: The dubs. JERRY: Okay.
RYAN: Dub trub.
JERRY: Yeah, just the look of contempt from this wizard is profound.
K'thriss Drow'b.
KRIS: Whew. All right. Not a lot I can do. I mean my big stuff's gone.
JERRY: You got potent cantrips.
KRIS: Well, no. The cantrips are good.
I'm trying to get that door open.
JERRY: All right. I like. RYAN: Knock that thing off her head.
KRIS: Huh? It doesn't--I don't think it works that way.
AMY: It's translucent. KRIS: Yeah she's got to save out of it.
JERRY: So door upstairs. KRIS: Yeah.
RYAN: Try. JERRY: And...
KRIS: (laughs) AMY: With an arrow.
RYAN: Shoot her in the head.
JERRY: Okay so you get the door open, yeah. KRIS: Shoot her how?
JERRY: When you say get the door open, you mean the door upstairs and not the--
KRIS: Not the barricaded one. I want to go to the knocking door.
KATE: Just pull that-- RYAN: Oh up there with me?
KRIS: Yeah. Let me run up there. And on my way up I'm like,
What? Why did she open the door?
Am I able to get there with my move?
JERRY: Yeah. KRIS: Okay.
KRIS: I'm going to make that door open if I'm standing next to it. What am I looking at here? Describe it.
KRIS: It's just being knocked at from the other side. JERRY: Yeah exactly.
KRIS: All right. I try the handle. RYAN: You could try like say--
RYAN: Hey, who's in there? And then just say, nope.
JERRY: I would like to get a strength check from you.
KRIS: That's the wrong check for me.
KRIS: But I will-- I can do-- I'll do one. RYAN: (chortle) You'll be like-- (feeble exertion sounds)
RYAN: Scolding me and then-- (sounds of exertion)
KRIS: I'm going to blow this door wide open! (feeble sound of exertion)
(laughter)
JERRY: Here. Now don't forget you have some help here.
KATE: Yeah! &gt;&gt; AMY: You have a lot. KRIS: Okay. Oh yeah I-- okay.
JERRY: You have cultists. KRIS: I'm going to do that one.
KRIS: Well yeah, I like that. Cultists. That's nice.
JERRY: They help you out. KATE: (laughing) That's nice.
JERRY: That's nice. Nice cultists.
KRIS: Uh...
AMY: Try again? KATE: Not too bad?
KRIS: Ooh that's not a bad one. KATE: That's not bad.
KRIS: Let's see what else I can do. KATE: Roll again.
KRIS: That's not a good one. Okay so it's going to be a 17.
JERRY: Oh yeah. that's plenty.
KRIS: All right. (grunt) KATE: Nice. &gt;&gt; AMY: Might!
KATE: Yeah. Lifting.
JERRY: It's clearly stuck.
RYAN: You're so impressed. JERRY: There's something designed to keep it closed.
JERRY: But you are able to break it out. And what you see inside...
They're knocked back by the opening door,
you can see someone bound and gagged in the darkness of this room.
AMY: Hmm. Number four?
KRIS: Yeah.
Am I able to run over there and get that gag off of him?
JERRY: Yeah but you already did your... KRIS: Okay.
KRIS: My move.
JERRY: Your move yeah. You can act if you want to.
KATE: Can you Eldritch Blast it off?
KRIS: (laughs) I'm perplexed and just kill him?
RYAN: Can you use tendrils to go over there and just be like-- (snip sounds)
Kris: I don't have any of those to use at the moment.
RYAN: Oh yeah. KATE: (laughing) Scissor tendrils?
RYAN: Yeah. It's a spell, right?
KRIS: Can I Mend that off of him?
JERRY: Can you un-Mend?
KRIS: I can return him to the state of him *not* having the tied-- on his mouth.
KRIS: I Mend-- No, okay. KATE: That's pretty rad.
(laughter) JERRY: You're trying.
KRIS: No that's-- Can I do Guidance on them to allow them to bite it off of himself?
JERRY: No, no, no. But you can probably remove it.
KRIS: Let's do that.
(laughter)
KRIS: Sounds good. Yeah I take it off of him.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. KRIS: Pull it down.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. You pull it down and it's just, "Thank the gods. Thank the gods."
It's just like writhing on the back trying to get his hand out of the bindings that they're in.
He's basically-- he's like a grub.
Basically. He can speak now but he's just like flopping around.
Next turn you should be able to get him ready to go.
KRIS: Okay.
JERRY: That's K'thriss.
JERRY: Here we come with our interlocutors here. KRIS: (claps)
AMY: (laughs) KRIS: It wasn't much.
AMY: You took a gag off of a guy. JERRY: Yeah, yeah.
AMY: It's not... KRIS: An important gag.
AMY: (laughs) JERRY: No, this was a vital gag.
JERRY: You don't understand. KRIS: It's a beautiful gag too.
KRIS: It's one incredibly-- AMY: You're going to love your gag.
JERRY: The hand crossbow fires a bolt at you, Donaar.
You hear the twang, you feel it's one point of damage.
JERRY: It's an inconvenience. RYAN: This guy hit an 18?
RYAN: All right. JERRY: It's an inconvenience at best.
RYAN: Getting low.
RYAN/AMY: (singing) Get low, get low...
KRIS: I'm at nine by the way, so...
RYAN: Is that a lot? Huh?
KATE: I feel fine. AMY: I'm feeling great.
RYAN: Oh great. Yeah.
JERRY: As you are approaching the barricade and the wizard that has made a home there,
AMY: Shit wizard.
JERRY: She makes a sign with her right hand and then
holds her hands together and a curtain of flame lances out at you.
RYAN: Oh. AMY: Great!
AMY: Just what I love. JERRY: Take three points of damage.
JERRY: And you can feel just in the heat of that blast--
AMY: (shuddering) Ah. JERRY: you can feel the crown sort of disintegrate.
KATE: (gasps) Tight. RYAN: Hmm.
AMY: (sucks air through teeth) Get ready to suck on this!
(laughter)
RYAN: It's bear-ing time. AMY: (growls)
JERRY: No, this is the drop.
AMY: Yeah. JERRY: This is the drop.
AMY: (record scratch sound)
JERRY: We are back to the fight of the ages between this knight.
JERRY: Do you have a 13 armor class? KATE: I certainly do. I have 15.
JERRY: Mm-kay.
AMY: Ain't nothing to Rosie. JERRY: Then you did very well.
JERRY: You didn't even need the disadvantage. It was just a real shit show.
KATE: Nice. JERRY: All right. Next up...
JERRY: we have Rosie. KATE: Okay.
KATE: So my patient defense... JERRY: Mm-hmm.
KATE: is... is that ongoing?
I spent a ki point. I'm not sure if it's an ongoing effect.
JERRY: That my understanding is that it is, but let me check.
KATE: Okay. All right. You check for it. I'm going to keep going.
JERRY: Yeah go ahead and figure out your next part.
KATE: All right. So I'm going to do a cool whirly attack.
JERRY: A cool whirly attack? KATE: Yeah. He's not going to see it coming.
KATE: I'm going to use an advantage die too.
KRIS: Yeah.
KATE: Which-- okay that was an 18. KRIS: Ooh yes.
KATE: And... seven.
Okay. So 18 plus five is 23.
JERRY: Mm-kay.
KRIS: Cool whirl. KATE: I did a cool whirl.
AMY: Very cool.
AMY: Wow! KATE: Starring Brad Pitt.
KRIS: Whoa!
KRIS: Yeah I know that's where it was referenced. KATE: You like that?
KRIS: But I was going-- I hung back. KATE: Yeah, and you're like that's...
KRIS: Nobody knows that. KATE: Too old. Nope.
KATE: It's a me. RYAN: What do I...
JERRY: I like it. We'll keep it. RYAN: If I want to use my...
JERRY: All right. What's the damage on this?
KATE: It is a six. And I will use... RYAN: my acid breath? Do I just do? Do I have to roll anything?
KATE: my martial arts to take an unarmed strike in as well.
Which is an 18.
JERRY: Yowza. KATE: Does that hit?
JERRY: Yeah that's good. KATE: Okay.
KATE: And then seven. KRIS: Nice.
KATE: Seven with one punch.
KATE: Elbow punch right to the groin. JERRY: Yeah you go in and it's just very close.
JERRY: It's the right height. It's the right height. KATE: Yeah. Perfect height.
JERRY: You know what's going on in there.
JERRY: You seen it before. KATE: It's no good.
JERRY: And it's right here. It's one of these.
AMY: Just laid waste to his groin.
JERRY: Yeah he's just stumbling back, sort of catches himself on a stool.
And pushes himself back up toward the fray.
Donaar Blit'zen.
JERRY: Lots of opportunities for you here. RYAN: Yeah...
KRIS: Feast or battle. JERRY: Puzzle solving...
AMY: (whispering) Jump off the balcony. RYAN: Puzzle solving?
JERRY: Yeah. The beasts here. These enemies. You have all kinds of cool stuff you can do.
KRIS: Do something. RYAN: I'm just going to--
RYAN: I'm going to spit acid at someone. KATE: Yes!
RYAN: I want to spit acid at that stupid wizard. KATE: Yes!
RYAN: Right in his dumb face. KRIS: Please do.
RYAN: I don't know how to though, so I pass.
(laughter)
JERRY: So you'll need to get closer because this is a...
RYAN: It says five by 30. Am I more than 30 feet away? Where's he?
JERRY: Yeah no I'm just saying like... Walnut is close.
RYAN: Oh!
Oh to the-- well yeah...
JERRY: You have plenty of leeway to get over there.
AMY: Just don't roll a one.
RYAN: No, they didn't even hit me yet. Oh, you're fine though. Okay.
RYAN: All right. Okay. KATE: You have advantage die.
AMY: You do. You have friends in the audience. Who knew?
RYAN: Oh I'm going to get in there.
KATE: Okay. Dragon Boys?
RYAN: But do I hit my-- my Dragon Clan?
I don't know. I'll come up with a better name than Dragon Boys (laughs)
(laughter) JERRY: The DBs.
KRIS: Dragon-wise. RYAN: My Scalies.
AMY: That's what they're called in the furry community.
(laughter) JERRY: No it's true! I'm going to look it up.
JERRY: I'm sure there's already enthusiasts. AMY: I didn't have to look it up.
RYAN: All right. KATE: I knew that as well, Amy.
RYAN: Good. AMY: Whee.
RYAN: All right, so then scuttle over there. JERRY: Yeah.
RYAN: Get close enough. Make sure Amy's not in the way.
JERRY: Yeah just push-- &gt;&gt; AMY: (silently mouths) Walnut! RYAN: And then I hit them with acid.
JERRY: Just like a hand on the face. No. We're here.
KATE: (laughs) RYAN: Yeah. I go, excuse me!
KRIS: Nyah! RYAN: Thanks for the swing earlier!
RYAN: We'll table this for later.
And then I go, blegh!
(laughter) RYAN: Like a...
RYAN: (hisses) AMY: Like Jurassic Park?
AMY/RYAN/KATE: (hisses) JERRY: No... Frills, you did not know about, emerge.
The sides of Donaar's cheeks open like a...
AMY: I throw up.
(laughter)
RYAN: Me too. JERRY: I rolled to vomit.
KRIS: I love the reasonable, hold on a second-- (vomiting sounds)
(laughter) KRIS: A surge.
RYAN: Everyone just calm down! (violent vomiting sounds)
(violent vomiting sounds)
Tears crying. Just like the vomit-- (crying and vomiting sounds)
KATE: Oh... fuck.
(laughter)
JERRY: Next. KATE: Aw jeez.
RYAN: All right so... Do I have to roll for this?
Or maybe I didn't write it all down. It just says 2d6 damage.
KRIS: Why you got to roll to vomit?
RYAN: Do I got to roll to hit? Or something?
KRIS: You roll to not vomit, most of the time.
JERRY: I'm going to ask my friend, Eric Benson.
RYAN: If I'm doing my... ERIC: Say what?
RYAN: acid breath.
ERIC: Yeah? RYAN: Do I just roll just a normal attack?
RYAN Do I get--? Okay. No bonus on it, right. ERIC: He makes a save.
RYAN: Does it go towards-- Okay. JERRY: What's the save?
ERIC: The target makes a con save.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. Gotcha.
RYAN: DC 12. AMY: We're all learning.
JERRY: Ugh. No. That does not happen.
KATE: Yes! RYAN: All right...
KATE: Describe it to me!
JERRY: Yeah, yeah, yeah. Ooh! RYAN: Eight.
KRIS: Aww. &gt;&gt; KATE: Nice. AMY: Paint the picture.
RYAN: Nice. KRIS: Paint the target.
KATE: I want to hear every detail. AMY: Theater of the mind.
JERRY: Eight. RYAN: You want me to describe it more in detail?
KRIS: Chunks. AMY: Transport me.
RYAN: All right so then after it's all done,
I'm sitting there just like (gasping and gulping sounds) dry heaving afterwards.
And you're all clapping because it was so impressive.
It was the most disgusting thing you've ever seen and I'm just like,
(dry heaving sounds) I did it, guys!
KRIS: Your head's down and you're like, ugh!
RYAN: Amy's holding my hair.
RYAN: (coughs) I'm just like, I get my toothbrush. (groan)
That was really gross. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry you had to see that.
JERRY: It starts out as a spray and then just becomes a jet.
AMY: It's like a fire hose. JERRY: A green, translucent jet...
JERRY: that comes into contact with the wizard.
RYAN: Mister wizard.
JERRY: Yeah, with mister wizard.
KRIS: Where on the wizard? The mouth area.
JERRY: The entire wizard.
RYAN: (laughing) I just vomit into his mouth.
JERRY: Eight points. The wizard-- Even just from that, the wizard is not looking awesome.
Is not looking a hundred percent.
AMY: Who would? KATE: Yeah. She's looked better.
JERRY: But the corollary aspect of this is that about half of this barricade
is just being winnowed under this liquid doom.
RYAN: Let's open the door and kick them through it.
KRIS: Yeah. JERRY: Yeah they don't want to go.
RYAN: Yeah.
RYAN: Now it's becoming like a torture situ-- now's it's like when they're victims-- Last House on the Left thing.
Where we're just like-- (wordless sound of aggression)
We'll rise up!
KRIS: No what we're going to do is we're going to capture these guys
and then put them half-in half-out of that door.
RYAN: Over and over. KRIS: And just pull.
RYAN: Yeah. KRIS: See what happens.
JERRY: Here so, Walnut Dankgrass...
AMY: Yes. JERRY: Your crown is gone.
JERRY: You have 100% control of all your deal.
AMY: Finally. (clears throat) So I'm right in front of this wizard.
JERRY: Oh yeah. You are present. AMY: And there's the barricade.
JERRY: A "bear-icade."
AMY: A "bear-icade."
KRIS: (air horn sounds) RYAN: (gasp) Are those all the animals you can do?
RYAN: That's awesome. AMY: Very cool.
JERRY: We need the-- Laura QQ, we definitely need to get a soundboard.
KATE: Only air horns.
JERRY: Think about that for next game.
AMY: All the buttons are air horns.
JERRY: I know you guys are taking notes. Definitely sound horn.
AMY: Well anyway, this situation looks dire.
I use wild shape.
JERRY: How wild are we talking about?
KRIS: (snarls) KATE: Hold on! Hold on!
KATE: Start over. This situation what?
AMY: (clears throat) Walnut looks up and goes,
This situation looks dire.
And then I use wild shape and transform into a dire wolf.
And again, it's one of those Teen Wolf things where it's the shot of the hand...
AMY: And then it just starts cracking. RYAN: And I go, I don't get it!
JERRY: I didn't see that movie.
AMY: It's all media with werewolves.
RYAN: Oh. KRIS: What's happening to her?
AMY: And then I turn into an awesome dire wolf,
and then I look right at this wizard and I want to just like...
JERRY: Feast? AMY: Feast...
AMY: but also use my movement action to just like... KRIS: eat Donaar's barf.
AMY: try and bust it up into the barricade.
Like maybe if I were to break it, that would be cool. But if not, that's fine too.
JERRY: So...
AMY: I just want to chomp that face.
JERRY: At root, are you biting?
AMY: Bite. JERRY: K.
KATE: Do a bite.
AMY: (humming) RYAN: Yeah do a bite.
JERRY: Do a bite. KRIS: Do a bite through him!
JERRY: Roll your bite dice.
MY: Where are my bite dice? RYAN: American Werewolf...
KRIS: Hit him. &gt;&gt; JERRY: I'm just fucking with you. AMY: Oh my secret...
AMY: Same dice. RYAN: You want my special dice?
JERRY: Reach into your jowls and get the bite dice.
AMY: (kissing sound) Mielikki.
KRIS/RYAN: Aww... AMY: Seven.
RYAN: You bite your tongue. JERRY: So it's a wizard...
JERRY: But what's the attack plus?
AMY: Seven... It's a plus five.
AMY: So it was a two. Plus a five. RYAN: She rolled a two.
JERRY: Oh!
AMY: So it's a seven.
KRIS: That's not good. JERRY: Oh I thought it was maybe a seven on the dice, Amy!
JERRY: Ugh!
JERRY: (sounds of consternation)
JERRY: All right. Gross! KATE: She's a dog so she's distracted by the vomit.
AMY: Let me ask you a question through.
RYAN: Laps up the vomit too. AMY: Let me ask you a question...
JERRY: Yeah.
AMY: Is it too late to Summon Furry Friends?
(laughter)
JERRY: No. KATE: Oh snap!
JERRY: No. &gt;&gt; KRIS: It's never too late. AMY: It's not too late?
AMY: What kind of animals can I summon? Whatever I want?
JERRY: Well you tell me what kind of animals you want to summon and I'll tell you--
AMY: Spiders! RYAN: Skunks. Aww.
KRIS: No. I summon a dire wolf that does what I tried to do.
JERRY: Yeah. I summon a second dire wolf.
AMY: I don't know. Something rude.
JERRY: Forest Friends. AMY: Squirrels are friends.
KATE: Nasty ass squirrels. RYAN: Armadillos that come rolling in.
KATE: Yeah. Nasty boys.
AMY: Squirrels. But like angry squirrels. You know when they're pissed off and they're all chattering.
KATE: And they're all skinny-- like kind of mangy. KRIS: You know like mange.
KATE: Yeah, yeah. You can see their-- Gross. Yeah. KRIS: Maybe diseased. Yeah, diseased squirrel.
JERRY: No. Dire squirrels.
KATE: Dire squirrels! AMY: Dire squirrels.
JERRY: Well there's no dire squirrels.
AMY: Mmm. KATE: (sighs)
JERRY: But sort of squeezing out-- RYAN: Sugar gliders.
JERRY: you know how-- KATE: (gasps)
JERRY: Oh, that would be the best. Yay!
JERRY: No, no. Here's how it works... KRIS: (groans in pain)
JERRY: From beyond you see like a...
AMY: Thank you.
JERRY: you see-- Absolutely.
You see one of the floor boards pop up a little bit.
JERRY: And 12 squirrels...! KATE: Yes!
JERRY: Start squeezing their way out of this like, one and a half inch...
Think just this chain of squirrels are going over there and they're just nipping and biting at the hem of the robe.
KATE: Nasty. AMY: Yeah.
JERRY: She looks like she is wearing a robe made of squirrels at this point.
AMY: Don't wear fur, but I love that.
JERRY: Living fur. Listen this is a collaboration.
KRIS: Still alive. &gt;&gt; AMY: That's true. It's fine. JERRY: See what I mean?
JERRY: K'thriss Drow'b.
JERRY: We're playing Dungeons &amp; Dragons. RYAN: So when I attack again I murder all the squirrels over her.
KRIS: All right I'm in the room with this... RYAN: Are you going to be mad at me?
KRIS: Describe to me this person I just ungagged.
JERRY: This person...
Mostly simple dress.
No armor of any kind.
JERRY: They've clearly been defanged, basically. Right? KRIS: Okay. Yeah.
AMY: Thank you.
JERRY: But they are ready. They're still just muttering to themselves.
Thanking any god that they think might hear them.
And continuing to writhe like a grub.
KRIS: All right, let me undo that knot in the back.
KRIS: I just cut it. JERRY: Yeah.
KRIS: I got a sickle. AMY: That's a lot of drugs.
RYAN: Yeah we're only fighting three.
JERRY: You just get the sickle out. RYAN: You cool with fighting four now?
AMY: Got him!
KRIS: This is an incredible stratagem. RYAN: He reaches up and strangles you.
KRIS: He's like, aha! And then they just punches me in the mouth.
No, I-- So I freed him.
RYAN: Even now? He's been in captivity for a while. He's all crazy.
RYAN: He's just lashing out at whatever's in front of him. AMY: He's got Stockholm Syndrome.
KRIS: Yeah. I'm in trouble.
JERRY: So you... RYAN: I can fight a naked guy.
JERRY: You slash this back part with the sickle. KRIS: I slash his bonds.
KRIS: I say, do you have any heals?
(laughter)
JERRY: Heals?
KRIS: I'm sorry. I don't feel good.
JERRY: Yeah. Tell me about it.
RYAN: I freed you. I'm very vulnerable.
JERRY: He's tied up. He's down. He's worse.
KRIS: I got a confession. I don't feel good, friend.
All right. Let's go.
RYAN: This guy was all tied up, you cut him free and then rolled over on your back,
and just show your belly and be like, please be nice to me!
JERRY: Oh me! I'm the one with the problem.
JERRY: Yeah, so you-- KATE: You had it tough.
JERRY: So you're like, "Yeah are you like a--" KRIS: Let me sit there for a second.
JERRY: "a doctor or something? A cleric? What do you got? What's your deal?"
No. He's just like as soon as he realizes that you're not going to be any more help,
he just like sit up, reaches down, fixes his feet.
KRIS: Yeah.
JERRY: There's like a rough stool sort of in this place.
You think that might have been what was holding the door shut.
He smashes it against the wall and just comes out with this ragged piece of wood.
KRIS: Whoa.
JERRY: And then runs out of the room and heads downstairs.
KATE: Did you say, whoa?
KRIS: Whoa.
RYAN: "Dude-icle".
(laughter)
KRIS: Wha...
KRIS: You know what, I just want to know what class wields a chair leg.
Like I said. Is that like a finesse weapon?
RYAN: So you're like, so just for the record, not a cleric? KATE: Is that a finesse weapon?
RYAN: It's just like doo-doo-doo.
KRIS: So food, or...?
JERRY: So halfway down the stairs-- KRIS: You had to eat.
JERRY: So you're-- he just runs out.
You look out. Halfway down the stairs he sort of kicks over the railing.
And then foot-by-foot on the back of chairs and tables,
jumps up and just brings this down on the knight's head.
KRIS: Oh. Like a club. RYAN: Hey.
AMY: Mmm.
JERRY: It goes right past the head and just connects with the pauldron.
It's like a pleasing sort of xylophone sound.
KRIS: Yeah. It's okay. He's tired. He's sore from the...
JERRY: Exactly. KRIS: Yeah.
JERRY: The... AMY: Chafed.
JERRY: The wizard is trying desperately to cast a spell.
It's not the type of magic you're familiar with.
But you can tell that she has started and failed three or four times.
In the space there's always another squirrel.
There's always one additional squirrel.
JERRY: That has to be... Yeah exactly. KRIS: (sputters)
RYAN: Squirrel cloud.
JERRY: That has to be managed. Yes Cloud of-- Cone of Squirrels!
JERRY: It's Cone of Squirrels. AMY: Ah!
JERRY: 3rd-level.
She is not able to do much this turn.
AMY: Aha! JERRY: The knight...
JERRY: This cled-- You saw this stick clang down.
You recognize this technique.
JERRY: You have seen this. KATE: I see.
JERRY: You learned it a long time ago. But you have seen it before.
KATE: Okay.
JERRY: The knight is trying to take a swing at you. What's your AC?
KATE: 15. JERRY: No. He doesn't.
JERRY: So he's continuing to just bring this thing down on both sides of you without actually finding--
KATE: It's like I'm not even moving. I'm not trying. JERRY: Yeah exact-- No. You're just staying.
JERRY: It's just always wrong. It's just whatever way he wants to do it--
KATE: Anytime he comes down I go, wrong. Wrong!
JERRY: Also-- also-- also incorrect. KATE: Bad.
KRIS: You just sort of swat at him for his form. Straighten up.
KATE: (laughs) Back tight.
JERRY: Exactly. KATE: Glutes engaged.
JERRY: This... the rogue...
slips over the bar and then you see her drop the hand crossbow this way, and then a knife comes out.
And there's something going on between these two.
Kris: Oh between the rogue and the-- JERRY: Between the person that you freed.
JERRY: Yeah. She catches him. Real good.
KRIS: (whispering) Dang it. Darn.
RYAN: You didn't throw her a-- Bane? Even with the Bane?
KRIS: Even with Bane.
JERRY: It was a really, really high roll.
AMY: It's the highest of rolls. RYAN: Hmm.
JERRY: So just in the middle of these attacks,
she's just taking this opportunity to just sort of rake along the flank with the dagger.
Rosie Beestinger.
KATE: I'm going to continue my assault on this terrible knight. Just the worst knight.
JERRY: This has been the worst knight.
KATE: This has been the worst knight.
AMY: Hmm. RYAN: Hard day's knight.
KRIS: He's not great.
KRIS: (hums) KATE: Nope. That's not good.
JERRY: Rosie, you have advantage. Would you like to use it?
KATE: Yeah I'm going to use my advantage. Thank you!
KATE: Yeah, I'm going to do that. JERRY: Don't forget the cool channel people.
KATE: Oof. KRIS: (groans)
JERRY: That is not how you should use advantage.
KATE: No. I rolled a two, and then I rolled a three.
JERRY: The funny thing about Rosie is that it's better if she rolls a one.
RYAN: Yeah so you're trending up. The next one will be...
KATE: Could be a four. RYAN: is a couple more of those.
KRIS: Could be a Fibonacci. JERRY: All right. Donaar.
KRIS: You could make it leaps and bounds.
JERRY: Exactly.
RYAN: Uh...
JERRY: Over there by this-- AMY: Still barfy?
JERRY: Yeah still running out. RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: The tip-- dribbles of it from the nostril.
KRIS: Oh yuck. RYAN: Imma finish what I started.
RYAN: Bring out the big boy.
Oh yeah. I can't recharge it.
JERRY: Is there a name for this sword?
RYAN: No, just the toothbrush.
And I pull out the toothbrush.
KRIS: No, the sword is called Toothbrush. RYAN: Yeah.
(laughter)
AMY: Dental hygiene is very important! JERRY: Ragnir's Toothbrush!
RYAN: Yeah. JERRY: Right?
RYAN: And I just go... JERRY: Bristles.
RYAN: Right at him.
JERRY: Let's see it. RYAN: No pomp or circumstance. Just whoop!
JERRY: Over the top. RYAN/KRIS: Yeah.
JERRY: What do you got?
AMY: Hmm... Mmm! The plus? KRIS: Oh cleave this guy.
RYAN: Yeah um... JERRY: Plus five.
AMY: 14. &gt;&gt; KRIS: Give him a chop! RYAN: Yeah so 14.
JERRY: Yeah. Absolutely. Let's see the damage.
AMY: Chop chop. All of it. RYAN: 2d6 plus 3.
KATE: (gasp)
RYAN: Seven.
Uh...
I will...
RYAN: divine smite as well. JERRY: Yeah?
RYAN: Deal any damage with melee, add radiant damage in the form of 2d8.
KRIS: (whispers) Yes... JERRY: Whoa! God. &gt;&gt; AMY: Oh yeah.
AMY: Good night. KRIS: Unload. Yes.
JERRY: It's  la mode? KRIS: Right.
JERRY: Is that what you said? KRIS: Yeah.
RYAN: Where are my eights...
AMY: That's what I said, it was much funnier. JERRY: We have to maintain--
JERRY: " la mode" as a piece of terminology.
RYAN: That's a 12... JERRY: Here you go. There's your eight.
KRIS: Wasn't mine. (laughs)
RYAN: This one always looks like the other one.
JERRY: It's always hiding.
AMY: You got it.
RYAN: Three...
three, so six more.
JERRY: Okay, so here's-- KRIS: Where was that hiding?
JERRY: So here's what you see, Dire Wolf Walnut.
Dire Walnut.
AMY: Ruh! (laughing)
JERRY: Just squirrels everywhere. Then...
AMY: Neat. JERRY: the sword...
JERRY: comes over...
just like catches right on its side,
and it's like you see the wizard sort of slump but like,
"I made it. I did it."
AMY: And then? JERRY: "I'm going to have another turn,"
JERRY: "I'm going to use my best spells,"
"and I'm going to get out of this situation."
AMY: Oh god!
KATE: Get home to see my family.
JERRY: And then a sound like a hammer on an anvil just pounds through the entire place.
Like furniture shifts slightly as just a piston of force just smashes the wizard into the wood floor.
KRIS: Oh!
KATE: And all the squirrels? AMY: And the feast begins!
JERRY: The squirrels are annihilated! RYAN: The squirrels go-- (soft explosion sound)
RYAN: Like everywhere. JERRY: No, no.
JERRY: No, it's like confetti! AMY: Rendered into a fine mist.
RYAN: I say, sorry about your squirrels!
KRIS: No you go, oh they got away! RYAN: I know you're really attached to those mice.
KRIS: They-- they escaped. RYAN: (laughing) I hope you weren't as attached to the squirrels.
JERRY: Exactly. KRIS: That's... how that works.
KATE: Walnut's already eating them. Is that what happened?
AMY: (pants) I'm just like drinking the blood from the air.
JERRY: (growling/gargling noises)
JERRY: Yeah. AMY: Ah!
JERRY: That's Donaar. Uh... Walnut.
The Dire Walnut.
JERRY: What's the situation? AMY: Who's left?
JERRY: We have a knight who is fighting a new challenger.
AMY: Right. KATE: Rosie's not doing anything to him.
AMY: Can I get to that knight?
AMY: I can get to that knight. JERRY: Oh yeah. Easily.
AMY: Oh cool. Then I want to bite the knight.
JERRY: (singing) Knight biter...
AMY: (laughing) Knight biter. (singing) Knight biter!
JERRY: It's a shadowy flight into the dangerous world...
AMY: Oh. 14. JERRY: of a dire wolf...
JERRY: that does not exist. AMY: 14.
JERRY: Now would you like to use your advantage dice? It's fine.
AMY: What? (shouting) Oh my goodness!
AMY: I didn't know I had one. JERRY: Them nuts.
RYAN: You got one back. JERRY: Them nuts. They got you.
AMY: I would love to!
Oh you guys. Wink.
Or do I? Yay! 20.
KRIS: It's like your...fourth?
AMY: No, no. It was a cumulative 20. KRIS: Okay.
JERRY: So remember-- AMY: I mean yes.
JERRY: So... in the periphery of your awareness.
AMY: Yes.
JERRY: You're pulling in so much new information as this form.
AMY: (sniffs)
JERRY: You know that the sword has just been whiffing each time.
You know that it is not connecting with Rosie Beestinger.
You turn and your awareness is filled with this prey.
And you just leap and pounce.
AMY: I sure do!
I sure do.
For an amount, probably.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. I would roll an amount.
KATE: Yeah. Big amount. KRIS: Where's that bite?
AMY: Yeah just get his-- RYAN: Go for the haunch.
AMY: Just get his haunches in my mouth. (slurp sound)
So that is a ten.
JERRY: Savory! Oh man.
JERRY: Yeah it's-- AMY: (lip smacking sound)
RYAN: That haunch meat. Best cut.
AMY: Oh good. JERRY: It's bad. You find...
AMY: I feel that glorious blood dripping into my mouth. JERRY: No. It's hot!
JERRY: It is hot! AMY: It's sweet.
KRIS: It's like a Brazilian steakhouse.
JERRY: You catch the back of his knee.
And you know, just thousands of years of natural wisdom, like this is the place.
This is how we find prey.
AMY: This is how we do it.
JERRY: This is how we do it.
JERRY: We can all hear it, right? AMY/KATE/JERRY: Yeah.
RYAN: Oh. Are we out of time? JERRY: Yeah. It's bad.
JERRY: It's all good. It's all good.
Next up we have K'thriss.
KRIS: All right. Um...
RYAN: (whispering) Like the clock is--
JERRY: Deal with these problems, K'thriss. AMY: (whispering) Yeah we're allowed to keep going.
KRIS: We got this clown-- KATE: Fix it.
KRIS: Uh... (voice rattling sound)
Who's looking-- Okay you're on the knight.
AMY: Mmm.
KRIS: Where's this rogue? AMY: Bark.
JERRY: The rogue is right by the knight,
because the rogue is fighting the new challenger who came down the stairs.
AMY: Your pal.
KRIS: All right I'm going to...
JERRY: From the top deck?
KRIS: Yeah from the top deck because-- well...
Yeah I can do Vicious Mockery on them. 60 feet?
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. KRIS: All right let's give it a shot.
JERRY: Plenty of room. KRIS: Yeah.
KRIS: Saving throw. I tell that rogue, I say,
We're all going through that door.
We are all leaving this bar.
JERRY: Every one of us. KRIS: Everyone is going to leave here.
KRIS: And not get to come back.
JERRY: This roll did not succeed. What happens to my rogue?
KRIS: He relaxes.
(laughter)
KRIS: She has a great night.
Let's see, hold on, on a fail...
Uh... buh-buh-buh-buh-bup.
But that's if they fail a saving throw.
KRIS: I think-- JERRY: It did.
KRIS: I think-- Oh they did fail. Okay. KATE: Yeah. They did. She gets--
KRIS: 1d4 damage and you get a disadvantage on the next attack.
So you're going to take... a three.
Three sweet damages.
AMY: (laughs) Three sweet damage. JERRY: Mm-hmm.
KRIS: Three tender little damages, yeah. JERRY: Love it. Mm-hmm.
JERRY: Yeah. Tender vittles?
KRIS: I'm going to try to remember that disadvantage.
JERRY: All right. The knight has a...
giant dog.
A giant, evil dog literally drinking its life blood.
AMY: (slurping sounds) Bark, bark, bark, bark, bark. JERRY: Out of its calf.
RYAN: Aooga.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. You think that-- Oh that's...
KRIS: (faint truck horn sound)
JERRY: I put the one-- I put the Acquisitions Incorporated logo on the one. That's the joke.
That does not-- So probably because of this giant dog anchor.
AMY: Mm-hmm.
JERRY: He tries to bring his sword over toward this new threat and is not able to.
AMY: Of course not! Because I am so fearsome.
KRIS: This knight hasn't done shit! &gt;&gt; RYAN: Yeah. JERRY: We are rapidly approaching gazelle leg...
JERRY: type situation. &gt;&gt; KRIS: (laughs) AMY: Ooh yeah! I've seen Planet Earth.
JERRY: It's not what we want.
AMY: Hmm. JERRY: Right?
AMY: It's what I want. JERRY: The...
JERRY: You can see that the new challenger actually rushes toward the door.
Does not engage in combat.
KRIS: Yeah. The barricade. JERRY: Rushes toward the door.
JERRY: The... rogue-- AMY: That's good. Don't engage.
JERRY: The rogue is trying to swipe...
Oh!
AMY: All our money? JERRY: Ah!
JERRY: The disadvantage. KRIS: Disadvantage.
JERRY: The rogue is trying to swipe at them as they pass,
but he's literally like walking-- like one of his feet just goes right on the knight's head. It's very nimble.
JERRY: You know about it. KATE: Very impressed.
JERRY: Right over. And then he is just pulling these half-formed chunks of furniture out of the way.
Throwing them behind him.
That's his turn.
AMY: And what a turn.
JERRY: Yeah exactly. RYAN: (laughs)
JERRY: The rogue is going to try to put... she's going to try and put a dagger in you...
What is your armor class in your wolven form?
AMY: Ah... My AC.
A number!
14.
JERRY: No, that's too high.
Nothing happens.
Like you just bare your teeth.
Comes over to you, bare your teeth, the dagger just glints right off of one of your canines.
AMY: Ding.
Next up we have Rosie Beestinger.
KATE: I'm going to make this attack work this time. I'm going to use another advantage!
We're going to do this. I'm attacking the...
rogue, actually.
JERRY: Nice. KRIS: Okay yeah.
KATE: I'm going to switch focus because I just used-- JERRY: Going to switch your flow?
AMY: The knight's useless.
KATE: Yeah the knight's-- I'm just pecking-- JERRY: There's nothing there.
KRIS: He's fine. AMY: He's there for comedic effect at this point.
KATE: He's not awesome. Right. JERRY: The knight is food.
JERRY: You rolling your advantage? KATE: Yeah.
KATE: That's a 12.
JERRY: No, that's not going to do it. That's not going to do it.
AMY: She means well. JERRY: Yeah, yeah. She's doing her best.
KRIS: It's a battle of minds. KATE: It's been a long day.
KRIS: This knight and this monk are just looking at each other! JERRY: Donaar. We have a rogue,
JERRY: we have a knight who is in a really bad spot.
KATE: Oh wait!
But I can-- even though I missed my attack, I forgot to do this last time-- I can still take an unarmed...
JERRY: Do it. KATE: I'm going to do that.
RYAN: Hostage? Oh. KATE: All right. Stay in front of it.
(laughter)
KATE: A meat shield. JERRY: "We're getting out of here!"
KATE: Yeah. Ugh still a 12.
JERRY: Yep. Next up. KATE: Hate that die.
JERRY: Donaar Blit'zen.
RYAN: Um...
RYAN: So I'm still over by the door with...
RYAN: what little rubble that's left there? JERRY: Yeah it's all close--
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. It is very close to being cleared.
RYAN: Just clear that out while I'm over there. KRIS: Pop that--
KRIS: That-- yeah. RYAN: Clear it all over.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. With your strength, this is not a complex thing.
The fact of the matter is that a lot of the cellulose-- a lot of it has been eaten away.
RYAN: Yeah. JERRY: It's just light to the touch.
JERRY: You just sweep it aside.
RYAN: Then I open the door.
(laughter) JERRY: Yep. You open the door. You recognize it exactly.
KRIS: What are we looking at? RYAN: I like this.
RYAN: What am I looking at here?
(laughter) AMY: (singing) And I see...
KRIS: Much of that darkness, right?
RYAN: Yeah. Is the darkness like normal?
JERRY: Yeah you know exactly what it is. RYAN: All right.
RYAN: And then I go... who's closer to me? AMY: Bye.
RYAN: Yeah I know. I'm just like, see you guys. AMY: That is Donaar.
KRIS: Good luck! A hundred percent for me. RYAN: You guys got this. Yeah.
RYAN: And I pull it shut behind me. Uh...
JERRY: (laughs) Yeah.
KRIS: I vomit on it. It won't open. JERRY: Bye! (vomit sounds)
RYAN: Who's closest to me? The knight or the...
Are either within range for me to yoink at?
JERRY: With your massive sword? RYAN: Yeah.
JERRY: You could probably take a quick swipe at the knight if you wanted to.
The rogue is just beyond.
RYAN: Hmm I'm going to go-- KRIS: Knight-swiper.
RYAN: I'm going to throw the rogue through the door.
KRIS: I know I want to punch--
RYAN: I want to throw one of them into the next room.
JERRY: Just wait your turn. I mean, you can do what you want.
RYAN: Well I mean if I-- JERRY: You just can't do it now.
RYAN: Okay.
JERRY: Walnut.
AMY: I bite... JERRY: Dire Walnut.
AMY: I bite even harder!
JERRY: Yeah. Let's see it.
JERRY: Oh hold on. AMY: I'm going to bite him in a new place.
JERRY: You bite even harder, but I'm going to say at this point...
KRIS/RYAN/KATE: Oh... JERRY: the bloodlust...
JERRY: has just made you mad with hunger.
AMY: Oh no.
JERRY: I'm going to throw a disadvantage that my people got me.
AMY: All right well we'll see. Maybe I'll do two really good rolls.
Well that's an eight and that's not good. Don't worry about it.
Oh and the other one was an 18.
AMY: Yeah eight plus five so 13. JERRY: Ugh. So you're just like...
JERRY: blood soaked jowls. Just snapping at him while he's trying desperately to get away.
K'thriss Drow'b.
AMY: Yip. Yip yip yip.
Not that kind of bark.
KRIS: Let's see what I got here...
I'm trying to figure out whether or not I need to come downstairs.
(laughter) Or I'm just like, this is pretty good.
JERRY: In your robe?
KRIS: I peek from the balcony. KATE: You're sitting there like, I don't want any part in that.
JERRY: Yeah, yeah. We're talking about a dangerously damaged knight,
and a rogue that has seen better days.
KRIS: Let's just try a good old Eldritch Blast on this yucky knight.
JERRY: Yeah. Let's see it. KRIS: He's a sour man.
KRIS: I don't like him.
I'm going to punish him.
AMY: You're going to ruin my food.
KRIS: Ooh yeah. That's going to be a 17.
God, it's going to be actually it's going to be a 23.
So never mind that. Yes.
KATE: Yes. KRIS: You got a plus five.
JERRY: Yep, yep. What? 17? Yeah that's great.
AMY: Do the damage. KATE: 23, I think.
KRIS: (singing) JERRY: Oh yeah. That's very good.
KRIS: Ooh yes! KATE: Ooh yeah!
KRIS: That's going to be a-- that's ten damage to him.
JERRY: Yeah. It's just... black-- like beyond black arcs, just perforate in three places.
One at the beginning. And then two more quick ones.
His back arches and that's it for him.
This rogue doesn't know what the situation is here.
The situation for the rogue has become untenable.
KRIS: Okay.
KRIS: Yeah that's not doing great. KATE: Mm-mmm.
KRIS: It's falling apart. RYAN: Time to parley.
JERRY: Yeah. RYAN: Sure you want to keep fighting, buddy?
JERRY: Yeah the hands are going to go up. AMY: And yet you forget to protect the mice.
RYAN: I'll leave him here. JERRY: Like this. &gt;&gt; KRIS: Oh okay.
KRIS: Bite him -- No. (laughs)
JERRY: It's just like, "Go. You want to go so bad, go. That's fine."
RYAN: All right.
We're not here to fight.
Got an open door.
RYAN: Huddle up. AMY: But I'm lusty with blood.
RYAN: Oh yeah.
Well we'll have to kill Amy.
KRIS: Well I was going to say, I think our wolf is still hungry.
RYAN: Yeah. (laughs) AMY: (howls)
(laughter) JERRY: Yeah. Yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah.
This malevolent-like, head low turn toward the--
Rogue backing up.
JERRY: At this point now that you have opened the door-- AMY: Bark, bark.
JERRY: the other...
the new challenger from upstairs...
RYAN: Oh the naked guy. JERRY: he's watching this and...
he realizes he has no interest in any person here.
Or anything that's happening.
And just like backs straight up through the portal.
KRIS: Yeah.
AMY: (laughing) Bye! RYAN: Yeah.
KRIS: He doesn't even give me one of these for freedom? JERRY: So what do you got? No, no. Zero.
KRIS: All right. JERRY: Zero.
JERRY: As soon as you untied him you were like, what can you do for me? Right?
KRIS: So this rogue's looking ragged? JERRY: Just backing up away from this giant dog.
KRIS: Through the portal, friend.
AMY: Ooh. &gt;&gt; KATE: Dang. RYAN: Yeah. Coming with us.
AMY: (exhales) &gt;&gt; KRIS: Time to go. KATE: Ice cold.
JERRY: I'm... I'm fine here. RYAN: Bound his hands.
KRIS: Mmm. I think... RYAN: No. You're not fine here.
KRIS: It's not healthy.
It was a lesson that you failed to learn.
JERRY: (laughs) AMY: Oh my god you're doing him a mercy.
JERRY: Ho ho!. KRIS: It's time to go through the portal.
AMY: (laughing) This is an intervention.
JERRY: Let's get a persuade.
KRIS: That's not how I was going to do it, but okay. (laughs)
Let's try.
KRIS: But I should-- I'm very good at it. So let's... JERRY: Persuasion, yeah.
KRIS: Do I got any to burn? I'm going to burn!
Number one on here.
Unnecessary!
JERRY: What was it? A 20?
KRIS: It's a 20 plus three.
KATE: Dang.
JERRY: It seems as though the top half of this person and the bottom half
are separate creatures with their own wills.
You can see that the legs are moving and the face is somewhat surprised by the fact.
So you want to pop through first?
RYAN: Uh... JERRY: How are you going to get him getting through?
RYAN: Should I just-- Is he walking over towards me?
JERRY: Well he's walking toward the door at your direct command.
RYAN/KRIS: Yeah.
RYAN: Is he like walking backwards?
RYAN: Does he see me? KRIS: I don't know.
RYAN: Or is he like, oh dude! JERRY: Just like this.
RYAN: Yeah. All right.
KRIS: I don't care if he gets out.
RYAN: Uh...
KRIS: I want him to have a miserable life.
RYAN: Yeah. I'm going to grab him by the scruff of the neck just to make sure.
I'll be like, no, you're coming with me. And then go through.
JERRY: Okay-- RYAN: Scruff of the haunches.
AMY: (laughs) The butt?
KRIS: He's all haunch, this one. RYAN: I'm all... You and me, we're going through.
JERRY: When you push him through...
you hear a...
The sound is not the same.
RYAN: Hmm.
JERRY: There's a shriek. Do you walk through yourself?
RYAN: Oh wait, no. I stop.
(laughter)
And I say...
Well he was scared of the portal.
Then I remember all my terror of doors and I say, who's next? (laughs)
RYAN: I hold the door open. As the gentleman that I am. JERRY: Go right ahead. Absolutely.
KATE: I'm going to loot the knight.
KATE: I want to see what the knight's got. JERRY: Oh ho ho.
AMY: Oh looting bodies. The other half of this game.
JERRY: Yeah I was going to say, loot. RYAN: Oh...
AMY: Huh. &gt;&gt; KATE: Yeah. KRIS: Wow.
RYAN: Should we open all the rooms too? KATE: Rosie's nothing if not practical.
KRIS: We just say here for hours. Yeah it's not bad here!
RYAN: Yeah you see-- AMY: There are good beds!
RYAN: Yeah.
KATE: Look, just food everywhere. What?
JERRY: You find a small, gold pouch.
KATE: K. RYAN: Aww.
JERRY: That has a chess piece and six gold pieces.
KATE: Okay. Chest piece?
JERRY: Chess piece. KRIS: Chess piece.
KATE: Chess piece. AMY: And you say, checkmate, motherfucker.
JERRY: A rook. &gt;&gt; KATE: A rook? RYAN: Well I wanted to-- yeah.
RYAN: And I say, that's a good idea.
KATE: But we squished the wizard. So...
AMY: We liquified it. RYAN: We, well...
RYAN: We, as a-- or in another way, I. JERRY: The things that the wizard has--
JERRY: had probably seen better days.
AMY: I want to go through the portal.
RYAN: I dig through the dead squirrels.
KRIS: So we failed the test. AMY: I want to dog through the portal.
JERRY: So you dog through the portal.
You pass through. You see...
Have you passed through as well or are you waiting?
RYAN: Oh I'm going to wait like we do. Knock when you're through.
KRIS: Yeah, I'm going through. RYAN: Could be a portal of annihilation.
AMY: I go through and-- (howls) JERRY: So you go through? &gt;&gt; KATE: Sure.
JERRY: You go through. You go through. You have led this person through.
You can see an idyllic sort of forest road.
AMY: (inhales) Finally. JERRY: That travels through...
RYAN: (laughs)
AMY: Finally. Goodbye.
JERRY: It's one of those forest paths-- RYAN: Just walk away from everybody.
JERRY: where the trees have sort of joined over the top.
KRIS: In holy matrimony. JERRY: You can smell the wind.
AMY: (smells the air) (sighs).
JERRY: One thing... AMY: Oh.
JERRY: One thing that is odd-- that you find odd is that your prisoner is not with you on this side.
And neither is K'thriss Drow'b.
JERRY: (claps hands) That's all we got for today.
RYAN: Yay. &gt;&gt; AMY: No! KATE: Oh my god.
JERRY: We will come back-- RYAN: Portal of annihilation.
JERRY: We will come back and play some more Dungeons &amp; Dragons with the "C" Team next week!
KRIS: Oh! RYAN: Next week. Next week.
AMY: With a new fourth player-- Oh sorry.
KRIS: Bye! It's been fun. RYAN: Who will be the new player?
AMY: Maybe it'll be you-- (laughs) No.
(laughter) KRIS: You just got to switch.
RYAN: Maybe it'll be you!
(laughter)
KRIS: Camera one? Camera two?
RYAN: Yeah. Camera? You? You? KATE: You? You?
JERRY: Exactly.
KRIS: Well done. Well done. JERRY: But yeah, yeah. Thanks for watching everybody.