if this goes according to plan you as
the listener will already hear that
sounds of an inn in furious operation
the sounds from the kitchen maybe this
would be a good time this is an editor's
note maybe a clanging sound of some kind
something in there like a cappuccino
machine that is the C it's in the
drawing corner ok now you can do it now
you simply explore the space alright is
there a kitchen explore this space no I
mean in a conversational context I'm
gonna go to the kitchen Strix goes to
the kitchen you can do whatever you want
the kitchen she's really scared of the
lady with the mace the Mesa is very
large handle of the mace indeed the
entire grip is perhaps the size of Strix
Jesus okay
are we maybe in a festive mood is it a
festive time of year it is what I have
well Chris Perkins can tell you why
there might be a festive atmosphere
inside the inn I thought he had a very
good suggestion earlier it's cthe
ristmas coming mm-hmm oh that's right
exactly
well I would tell you that it has
something to do with Catherine's
and so I'm gonna pass the microphone to
Keturah sand he's gonna tell you what it
means to him it doesn't mean anything to
me it means that people try to describe
to me why we have rituals it was a
deeply personal experience and we have
co-opted it
Christmas is an event at least in the
pseudo Canon we have generated it's been
something that you could risk true in
your solitude over hundreds of years
have observed personally yes it is a
time of celebrating no holiday the
absence of and what has happened as a
just as a as a doomed practice is that
now others have begun to celebrate it
also and they have added ever more
elaborate rules to what was a personal
private observation
these aren't traditions they didn't
exist before everybody's just adding
stuff onto the top what was a boy comes
skipping by we share our hugs and kisses
and we pronounces it making up
traditions every verse she's adding on
which he observed yes every time strict
leaves the kitchen and she's doing that
just turns right around yeah Rosie comes
up to Chris at some point and will say
like you're right I shouldn't have told
anyone
hey they just missed the point and they
like to celebrate and I feel like that's
what they really wanted to do which is
fine but this was my time to celebrate
not doing that thank you voice from
somewhere as he's saying this like
paltin like like just drunkenly stumbles
to Catherine's like a man I want you to
know this holiday that you've chosen to
share with everybody it's a wonderful
thing I love all the traditions it's
very it's very nice and well thought out
this is definitely definitely a great
established holiday and then he just
like slams and hits hits the floor comes
over with
and she goes can I please get that in
writing I really need to send that to
head office if this is going well
I need omen to know it's really
important oh man knows this is going
well and I take his hand his drunken
[Laughter]
wakes up and just like slaps the paper
out of your hand during those
shenanigans as a means of getting the
ready for the celebration imagine people
were decorating around the the end and
the like oh yeah there's there's plenty
of opportunities right for festive
laurels maybe death is no good at that I
imagine evylyn has probably already
taken the brunt of most of that so do
you like putting stuff up and she like
secretly behind him take it down and fix
it yeah what kind of stuff are you
putting up like what is a charisma
decoration when are they everywhere
that's like tons of manger really sure
there's probably like brightly scraps of
cloth not necessarily like cleanly cut
to be decorative but just shreds that
were available and was kind of putting
that garbage yeah but bright colored
garbage and and yes not knowing where to
even like really put things or what even
works and just kind of gives up he's
decided that his contribution would be
to ration out the supplies and divvy it
up and be like okay you guys can handle
these he'll like he brought stuff to
evylyn who took it right away and then
he like grabs like another small wooden
like almost Apple crate of additional
scraps of cloth and maybe some shards of
glass that could probably light the
traditional glass shard probably stuff
that Strix already had yeah it's know
it's stuff that a snail might leave a
trail of mucus yes these are they're
simply treasures that emerge and strix
his wake as he travels naturally yeah
maybe like the shedded skin of a spider
or something
yeah he'll take a small creative that
and bring it over the bar and just be
like here you go buddy meter shavings
yeah
got a label on it there's spider
shavings for Christmas do not hope until
Christmas there's an empty jar that on
the outside it says I wish this was
filled with eyeballs Rosie that like
strokes has been leaving these notes
around aggressively for months
like just whenever she comes to visit
she's leaving these freaking notes
around and Rosie's rosie has started
checking on her jar of eyeballs like
every hour county yes sure she knows
exactly how many eyeballs are in there
and she will know if one is missing
brings a crate over to Donna and just
like all right be really careful with
the glass
someone might still be sharp that's
that's tough but fair just stand there
and hold this box for me I want to walk
over to Chris note for the listeners so
we're recording this way in the past I'm
gonna make us some assumptions between
now and when this was released on some
things that happen sure okay go over to
Chris and I say you know I never got to
thank you for those like when we met
that we had to fight that God and you
know it was my fault like I did some
things wrong and they took it out on you
and I never got to thank you but thank
you for dying for my sins
glad you're back that's not I mean this
seems like the right time to celebrate
that's one interpretation but I think
I'm just a person with some knowledge to
share and that's then that's all
basically that's what a messiah would
say yes Thank You Rosie also as she
heard this and she's like you know I
wanted to apologize that it took us
three days to resurrect you we could
have gotten we could have gotten to that
a lot fast was it must be in that cave
yes very evylyn pops up and she's like
but let's remember that the true meaning
of Christmas is lifting the light of the
morning Lord shining upon us even in the
hour of our darkest need strikes opens
the door to the Kaiser says I thought it
was presents Alton Gus Sakura's he's
like I appreciate the concept of you but
like I don't think anyone can prove you
exist
Oh doubting paltin look at my scars
these holes here here also here get so
into that if paltin said this ticket
risk that no one can prove that he
exists like because chris's eyes would
all 25,000 of them would just like
suddenly turn inward like can they yeah
he would have to come get comfortable
with that idea cuz I mean you can't
prove any of this is real but since I
can't and it seems to hang together
let's just do we can with this space
partway through like his talking palms
already like walked off it may not
matter to cuz wrists I suspect it'll
continue let's try to just proof in one
column or the other it's like okay could
mean don't exist
you just wanted away I wasn't here if he
gets a charisma scar does that prove he
exists Wow I don't know that's like
empirical it's you know the plural of
anecdote is not data are they burning or
do they smell good should I like guess
you should roll I don't know I guess
I'll roll okay you just rolling I'll
tell you if something terrible happens
they are what's the role it's an i pod
casting proficient survival she makes
pie yeah these are survival pies like a
Clif Bar absolutely yeah yeah this role
of a nine-plus your bonus means that you
can make an edible pie okay it's it's
not toxic okay good there's no spores of
any kind of growing on there unless it's
a spore pie so it smells good
oh yeah okay it's it's something that
someone would want to eat on purpose
okay
yeah so I bring out the first pie and I
put a bunch of little candy eyes in it
so just covered in little tiny red candy
eyes and I put it down and we like
everyone is the Christmas Popeye I guess
I don't know when she brings it out 19
I'm sure if anyone notices with Diaz
right away like lake is super eager for
it but doesn't want to be the first
person to touch the pie it takes the
first piece so he just is always looking
over his shoulder be like is anyone else
do it yeah is it okay for me to do it
yet is anyone Christmas pie we have to
sing the Christmas carol palton did you
finish writing it yet yes all right it's
for your Christmas national anthem even
places both hands on her heart I feel
like Holton takes out his mandolin he's
just like wait shit I had something hold
on wait no I have it on my is like wait
no wait no phones aren't a thing okay
you like plays a chord is like thanks
[Laughter]
dude even though you may or may not
exist how many eyes they have so we make
the pie as easy have and Strix already
has a piece ready for do you thank God
she already knew she was like here and
then she just sets it down the table
it's all cut perfectly with a perfect
piece for everyone it's like the only
neat thing she can do is this baking
mm-hmm nice yeah that's and it's very
good Dennard takes the whole pie gets
the first size now I just take a slice
out of these are personal pies
to share these are our pies this is not
calories the spirit the true meaning of
Christmas would be make everyone a pie
big boy
everyone here is causing my brand
you had an invented a god yeah that's my
issue with these these forces oh we made
a god does that mean it gets more
powerful the more we talk about it it
shouldn't work that way but I know that
it does for some yeah they're intruding
on your IP you could like take action on
that man legal action yeah help you with
that I pitched this so I get 10% that's
true you can have 90% for all I care
Wow that's you can have 90% that's it
leads it 10 more than what I said
um upset at this I stock up to my room
to study and Ike I'd come right back
down
my room is empty all of these
decorations this was just stuff that I
own hearing that deaath looked at the
one of their crate that he's about to
bring over to Rosie and then looks over
at evil and it's like where did you get
this yeah
Christmas has made out of keturah stuff
you said you found this in the closet I
think it was a closet at one point I'm
gonna be honest I only put a little bit
of his hair in the pie it's good you
broke all of his staff Esther sculptures
to make the glass like that you don't go
too heavy on ya know it's just like a
garnish on top
it's an art cause I took a thrist just
says you're you seem upset buddy but
remember after we fought the God and in
our places his left hand which has this
awesome future techno glove
remember when we fought the Technomancer
this awesome gauntlet afterwards it
shoots lasers yeah it does like laser
td8
oh I'll show you Oh
he ate that was a great battle why are
you so quick I remember you
asphyxiated Tiamat with it neck in turn
you just went we've had great adventures
together I understand why you're so
upset
these people are barmy so I'm gonna go
back to the kitchen where things make
sense yeah where things make sense even
goes and sits on the floor cross-legged
next to wherever Rosie is it's like
Rosie I bet you've seen a lot of
Christmases this is um the second one
and it is wildly different from the
first one I bet you have so many
Christmas stories oh of course I would
love to does it have a good mood to it
and a hero yep the tradition of
everything I hold dear of Christmas yes
gather round I am gathered and I will
cook okay okay so the story of the first
Christmas hmm by Chris wrist robe all
hail once there was nothing at all and
then there were other things but the
nothing still mattered more to me Chris
wrist robe and I longed for it and then
my friends ruined all of it and and now
I am so surrounded by people and it is
nothing like what I had hoped for in my
very old age well that's my favorite
cause Laurie loved Rome during this
story I'd imagined again with a crate of
Chris's stuff she brought over to Walnut
at this point but they both have the
same face listing this story I've just
we're both late listen listening India's
just like this is bullshit honest we
agree I'm glad we could finally agree on
something it's true
I don't celebrate holidays outside of my
order and certainly not this yeah I mean
I don't really care either but
miss evil and happy Trix gets to make
pies Paulding gets to drink and it's
acceptable you around this time of year
but I guess distractions have their
place I think Rosie would try to just
walk past here and throw a wrench into
things sure be like hey walnut do you
think omen got his invitation ticket
versus well I sent him several so I'm
sure he's due to arrive any minute now
and she's like you've noticed that
actually she's been looking at the
window like every time it would be rude
if he didn't know I'm sure he's busy
he's got so much stuff that he's doing
yeah if I had to guess he probably
already decided that you're not
important enough the kitchens like snap
for the for the podcast listeners my
mouth is a gate that's nice yeah it was
nice they're laminated yeah I'm sure it
was nice I'm sure felt good but I have
to ask like when he wrote to you is it
because he needed something from you or
was he just trying to talk to you he did
need something very important writing me
always because he needs something hmm
well I'm here to provide as a you know
employee of acquisitions incorporated I
don't know if you remember well-done
grass documents a ring - yeah I remember
I just read I hope at some point that
you can see value within yourself that
isn't in service to another
we're done guys I've seen Paulson's
cutting the pie real deep the table
splits into the laminate
you broke my pie pan that's my staff now
you have now you have to I do mend it
I'm man thank you you don't get to
contextualise miracles i fix things I'll
turn my in the pie pan back into my
staff and be like yay see why is that
not a miracle I was impressed because
you didn't do it I go in the kitchen I'm
gonna go in the kitchen wait no but
that's my kitchen I follow it's actually
not your kitchen this might work so you
follow tricks you want you want to
escape the the revelry engine that's
currently yeah I in operation in the
great room yeah and I say that this is
people just want to celebrate they don't
need a holiday to do it they should just
do it if they want to they don't need an
excuse here within the space of an hour
they have invented a figure to celebrate
and that's the entire thesis there to be
honest I just celebrate waking up every
day cuz you could just die any day you
can also celebrate you're in here paltin
I mean no the conversation here was a
lot more interesting so I inserted
myself what up that's hype Alton hey
hello I agree I agree you don't need a
reason to celebrate you just the the
reason to celebrate one celebrate which
is you know or is like drowning sadness
man whatever you need I believe in you
we all do and that's the meaning of
Christmas
[Laughter]
i drowned your sadness when you could
drown in sadness I've just experienced
it and just deepen it and think about it
I'll maybe write a paper paltin like
puts his head in his hands he's just
like oh this is this is why he's the
meaning of Kirk's just like starting she
like turned her staff back into a pipe
and just starts making another pike
she's just like I don't know I can't
deal with this but she's like if there
is maybe have you ever met a power
before power yeah like a god I've met
beings that say that they're gods but
I'm not met they're not really gods cuz
anyone can become a god it's just like
you know you roll over one day and
you're like I just want to become a god
that'd be great and then you just you
know find a way to do it maybe eat
another God or something and then you
begin my god right but then if that's
but then we don't know why we don't know
why any of this exists if everybody just
ascends what was the first instance who
is there exists so then I can feel
things like sadness and feel things like
Christmas Rosie enters the kitchen she
doesn't say anything but she opens the
oven where she has tentacle shaped rolls
filled with Jim where those come from
yeah that's they've just finished baking
they look they look amazing they have
little suckers on them that are
intimately crafted she offers you the
first one you can break it open red Jam
will pour out of it I say this is a
delicious outrage there you it's just
exactly the reaction I'm she was hoping
for
and she trucks the rest of them is she
gives a strict sort of a 1/2 dark but
half curious look because the pie
situation was really rough but the pies
are not delicious and she knows that
there's a lot of non organic ingredients
that are going into these five but I
can't help loving that flavor you know
so she's you don't she's learning she's
she hates it but she's learning the
Reese's he's like perfect little
pastries and they're just so like lovely
and good looking that like you've never
seen her like bristle
[Laughter]
back arch will offer one districts right
she takes it so like it's on fire
there's no hair in it there could be
there could be in the kitchen and the
kitchen is not larger than this size
this is a small country in the kitchen
is designed for one perhaps one elf and
one halfling to function perfectly above
everyone with their flying boots making
a song about the Christmas because well
they're all in there I want to hop back
to the death walnut yeah yeah that
finally I think finally the rest of this
situation has moved away there may be an
opportunity for something approximating
an authentic conversation yeah from your
previous con indie it's kind of see that
and actually like almost regrets a
little bit and looks back at wallet and
he says I'm sorry I did I did not mean
to say that as mean to like cut or
belittle you because I've seen we've
done things before like I've seen the
way that you fight you're so powerful
it's incredible and I've heard the
stories I've heard from others about the
people that you care about and what
you've been through and that's that's
important so I just I just think you
need to know that you are important just
by yourself and people value for you if
you wish to serve Omen that's great that
makes you happy
sure but I just well I I think you
should know that you don't need that or
him to have value there was a time in my
life where I did not have purpose and
acquisitions Inc was that for me and I
can't
lightly forget that and only made that
possible and I'm in his debt
yeah asshole levels of documents are
there this is the future oh yeah sorry I
mean yeah well I'm ranked five now but
so she looks at him and now just like a
little taken aback that she revealed
anything of herself to him um and she
goes truly why why do you hate Holman so
much oh dear I can't speak for a limit
because eight billion things rush to his
head at once he doesn't know which one
to start with and he'll just say because
I grew up in Waterdeep i wasn't born
there but it is where I grew up it
wasn't super Pleasant and through those
times I got to learn about all kinds of
different people and it's because of
that I know exactly the kind of person
that Holman drawn is and I know the kind
of person that he pretends to be and
what everyone sees he's the kind of guy
who what through whatever means as long
as he gets what he wants that's okay
whatever it means destroying property or
taking whatever he wants or stealing
from others or using other people's
lives the kind of guy who would purchase
a child for labor because it was
cost-efficient Podcast Jerry is
literally grinning like a maniac rubbing
his hands oh I am actually doing it
doesn't really know what to do with that
information and she goes must be some
mistake well or there's a good chance
we're both right let me go get you one
of them tentacle thingies
yeah yeah sure sounds good and yeah
it'll go off and get like a treat two
brave girls now it's like a sort of
peace offering but it's a means to sort
of like kind of smooth out Rosie made a
special one for a walnut that it looks
like it is made of gravel and just
flavored nuts yeah like a lot of nuts to
let herb during races yeah
comes back is like I just found a patch
of grass well that goes oh sure I have
something for you and she pulls out what
looks like a three-day-old good berry
that's like half smashed and she's like
this is for you oh my god right right
three yes Trixie's d I've come into the
kitchen to take a pastry that's not hurt
ventilated look at your rosy and then
it's a little typical things and like
back into hip and then back at her PI
and she just is like standing there
shake Alton's gonna walk out and he's
actually gonna approach Walnut be like
hey can I can't talk to you for a second
sure
alright cool I just there's just
something I want wait hold on and he
like you see him just kind of like turn
90 just looking directly at camera is
like is this pre or post waffles Inc I
can't remember oh it's gonna be post
it's post all right cool he's like these
time skips are so damn confusing okay I
know that you and me are definitely the
stubborn character archetype that's
stubborn saying it and I don't
ya know it's just a certain point when
enough people say you gotta like start
doubting yourself and wonder is that
really me by anyway um I know that you
and me we've butted heads in the few
interactions we've had but I get it and
I I respect your perseverance it's it's
something I see him myself it's very
admirable and it was especially
admirable when you came to and gave me
the ring when I asked for it last time
you just like just like finger guns away
some need our help to destroy the
multiverse
yeah this well in hand apparently it's
true rosie has this tray she's bringing
out these plates filled with these
tentacle pastries she comes to you
paltin and she offers the plate but
before you can grab it she pulls it away
she says I noticed you're not wearing my
sweater that I gave you
whoa I mean if there's one day a year
but I would I would hope you'd want to
wear it it would be today well I'm glad
I can wearing the sweater that I've made
for him which is especially shocking
sweater back in back in the Waffle House
there is a sweater in a drawer and
waffles nest Strix is stuffed with
leaves that has been turned into a toy
boy yeah so pan over there and it's just
got bite marks and drool blood on it oh
this is like sweater last kiss this is
mm-hmm is this this is my first kiss
miss I'm learning all the ritual wait I
know I got shoot I think this is so
embarrassing um God okay hmm he was
really blasted last year we need to do
our name-dropper this year oh yeah
that's true we do of course the dame
draw the Christmas baby yeah
as is tradition I'm assuming yeah and I
have luckily baked all of these
potential pastries with the name inside
so mad about this that is a game she's
just standing outside the kitchen just
holding like her pie and it's just like
really sad look he and she's like it's
like the roof of the pie is just she
just sets it down and then you just see
her crawl under a table the top of the
pie the crust is now in contact with the
filling this is not a drill oh no she
was too anxious and upset to make a good
pie after seeing the beautiful pastries
Rosie made disturbing but now her but
now Rosie's pastries also have some kind
of aargh in the exactly I think that
Rosie would look at the pie and look at
strix and
look at the NAR I feel like I'm gonna
tell me twice I would eat the entire
thing as a well making it unbroken
iconic herbage disposal what does that
process look like cuz he's got it he's
got a massive body and a huge cross yeah
it's like a little hostess treat yes
exactly right yes like a ho ho it would
be that and then starting the chew on
the pie tin
that's my staff it's great no great job
scraping no you did good compliments
gonna give you it's great giant heavy
cauldron just keeps getting better now
it's like a hat yeah greatest day of my
life
thank you you're doing catharsis work
I've retired under the table where you
were trying to go yeah and I'm just
meditating
I'm just muttering I think you two have
both gotten your pastries with your
names in them okay but here's the weird
thing
when while not bit into her pastry there
were three slips of paper and they all
had dinars name them they all start
eating our pastries every single pastry
has at least one slip of paper and all
of them say today I got exactly who I
want
[Laughter]
not what I put into these oh wait I come
up and I be like the tradition that's
being established as we perform it yes
the tradition is now that we do a name
exchange and dinar is also the recipient
of each person's gift yes one for your
Secret Santa and one for dinar and so
shall it be a little bit more powerful
but it said hubris maybe that's all it
is maybe it's just hubris and that's the
meaning of Christmas I think it is I
think it is you guys are having so many
breakthroughs and you're ignoring them
even is going around hanging the
traditional fissile mow which you know
as you know when you stand below it yes
you're supposed to give a warm hug to
ever you're standing under it with she
hangs one above strict specifically says
give a warm hug so this is like this
ship engine a device that creates and
exports fully formed ships but it's not
like she's not doing it like oh here
we'll put one here and one here she's
literally like holy in Java she's like
grid creating the room looks like you
almost can't not stand under it because
you can't move without hugging someone
so Diaz it's starting to like edge
between moving through like you swear
it's like him practicing uncanny dodges
like lasers more or less going through
Mission Impossible is like I know evil
ins game just hugging strix really tight
and looking meaningfully at DIA it's
like you don't want to hug someone who's
just totally limp mm-hmm so she just has
like her arms the side in her head like
this just like getting squeezed like
it's just evil it's really strong so you
squeeze like really
she's just like oh just like play dead
maybe she'll go away and then once like
does evil ever stop
not until Strix makes their probably
okay she turns into rats even looks
downcast but then she she has like ten
more of these thistle most sprigs and
she just like smiles and starts going
about the room doing that secretly to
try to make more and more hugs faces I
imagine at the same time everyone forgot
about decorating so DF took it upon
himself so it's done very poorly
[Laughter]
glass-like just kind of grabbing a
handful of stuff and just tossing it out
like this toothbrushes like it is
garbage for sure but also like a lot of
books like really not colorful ones
either but they're being they're being
displayed about like ancient like
thousand-year-old books
stuffed with forbidden knowledge just
strewn about a great hunt a great room
or wrapped up in paper with a tag that
says dinar yeah just like nailing them
to the whole room takes like a very
strong occult best of it all it's
getting really weird I'm like the Tetra
nomicon - it's like these these like
sketches of like these bloody handprints
a Turner staff and she has a green ink
quill pen that does magic ink everywhere
entry signs yeah and she just starts
like drawing symbols on the wall and
she's like I love this this is my
aesthetic and like weird thing humans
will never get in here now writing like
an infernal and this one says but I like
Christmas and infernal do you like that
what level of documents are you I don't
know I just speak to the devil words oh
all right well that's good too as well
that's talking from behind she gets like
me majorly squeezed hula from England
she's like your
they feel that on my skin and shake
she weasels our way out as a weasel does
she scampers away and she's just like
like all like all tense like a very
little anxious weasel do you come do you
emerge from the bottom of the hug or the
top like how do you how do you like that
she just drops like a little brick yeah
so it is about this time that prophetess
drawn the proprietor of the drawn and
Cordia returns in the front door with
baskets of produce and items that are
required for the running of a known
occult in and as she as she pops in she
says I want this to look like to look
something like the drawn and courrier
again in an hour and she turns on her
heel and walks away